"Leopard Kid, Wudang Clan"
Move aside, kid!
"Nian Ruiqing, Shaolin disciple"
"Tiger Kid, Wudang Clan"
"Li Jinlun, Shaolin disciple"
"Fan Tiancong, Wudang Clan"
"Monk Sande, Shaolin disciple"
"Zou Feng, Wudang Clan"
"Hong Xiguan, Shaolin disciple"
"Priest White Brows, Wudang Clan"
Hong Xiguan, run!
Go find our master Zhishan.
Run!
"Hu Weigan, Shaolin disciple"
"Gao Jinzhong,
the best student of White Brows"
"Xiang Yuan Wine Shop"
Watch it!
Stop!
Move over!
It's already mid-day,
why aren't you working?
What are you doing?
What do you know except eating?
Boss, I woke up almost at midnight
to make tofu,
and I didn't get a break.
That's the point of hiring you;
Working non-stop.
I quit. You can do it.
Jin.
Please.
Move over, the tofu.
Jin... l...
Guess I could at least wipe off the sweat.
Boss Huang, I don't think he's idling,
agree?
Careful, Boss Huang.
If you can't hold it,
then it will be a disaster.
Jin, come help!
Coming...
Yes, boss?
Boss Huang, don't blame Jin
that he's not working.
I'm here to buy some tofu.
Yang Dabao, you want me to fire you?
You took quite a while to buy tofu!
I've got a restaurant to run here.
Yes, boss. Well, I'm back now.
Set the tables.
Excuse me, boss.
I need to bring these to the kitchen.
Hurry up!
This way please.
What would you like to eat?
Two bowls of beef noodles.
Right away.
Welcome. What would you like?
Steamed beef, steamed egg
and some wine. Hurry!
Please have a seat.
Welcome.
A dish of chicken.
Okay
Hey! I'm in a rush here! Hurry up!
Yes... can't you hear?
Bring the dishes to them first.
Got it.
Coming. Hurry!
Sorry, sir.
I was careless.
The nose.
Get up. Sorry.
Boss, there's a fly on this chicken leg,
should I throw it away?
Throw it away?
Get rid of the fly, and give it to them.
Hey, what's wrong with this?
Don't worry. There's a fly here,
the boss told me to get rid of it.
Don't worry, eat up.
How can I eat it?
Our food is very clean here.
Don't listen to him.
Gentlemen.
Be sure to lock the shop up.
Clean up everything.
Soak the beans for tomorrow.
Wake up early to grind the beans.
What now?
Are you trying to wreck the shop?
When you're done, start to boil the juice.
When you've boiled the juice,
make some tofu and dried tofu.
And you can deep-fry some,
don't try to slack off.
If I find out,
I'll deduct it from your pay.
If you break anything,
that's coming off your pay too.
And if you open the shop late,
I'll deduct your pay.
Yes.
It's strange! Why do I trip everyday?
Yang Dabao.
What are you doing up there?
Let me see what your
Black Tiger Clan's
martial arts style is all about
What do you know?
This is the fairy's bowl.
I think it's more like a beggar's bowl.
Alright. If you can snatch
this beggar's bowl,
you're in for a yummy treat.
Wear it.
I've got it!
Yummy food!
Very well.
Do you believe that
with this pair of chopsticks
I can stop you from eating?
You don't have a chance to eat anything.
When I was learning martial arts
from my dad,
that's what he did.
For over half a year, I ate plain rice.
The main feature of the martial arts
of my family,
the Black Tiger Clan is that,
we can pick up anything handy beside us,
and use it as a weapon.
While we're eating...
Ain't very nice to eat plain rice
for over six months.
Definitely not.
But when my dad couldn't stop me...
Do you get it?
Swallow first, then chew later.
For the Black Tiger Clan's martial arts,
we can pick up anything handy beside us,
and use it as a weapon.
That's really something.
Don't be modest.
The Mantis Style you're learning
is very difficult too.
I've never heard about your master.
I don't know who he is.
How can that be?
I met my master three years ago.
I was still in my hometown then
Kid, c'mon address me as "grandpa"
and I'll let you go.
Bastard!
Come on, kid!
Spare us, "grandpa"!
Master.
Try this.
My master left after two years.
I didn't even know his name.
That's a true master.
Both of us have skills,
I don't know how long
we must wait
to become something in this field
that we can do something great!
I'd risk my life for that day!
Great!
We both want to be heroes,
we just don't know
when that will happen.
I can't wait.
It will happen one of these days.
Alright! A fight!
Get even!
I'm going to faint.
And you said you want to be a hero,
you can't let go of this wine.
It's not me, it's my boss.
I still need ajob before I become a hero.
Right?
Go to sleep.
You need to get up to work
in the middle of the night.
"Qingyun Temple"
Hong Xiguan.
"Master Zhishan, Shaolin Monastery"
Brother Hong.
"Fang Shiyu, Shaolin disciple"
"Fang Meiyu"
"Fang Xiaoyu"
Help him up.
"Master Xinglong, Lama Clan"
Don't move him, help him to sit up.
Master Zhishan.
Xiguan, you have
serious internal injuries.
This is Master Xinglong of Lama Clan.
He's a healer, don't move.
Master, the West Meditation Temple
has been torn apart
by White Brows Priest,
Gao Jinzhong and the others.
Brother Sande, Tong Qianjin, Nian Ruiqing,
Li Jinlun, Hu Weigan... they're all dead.
Being emotional is
the cause of internal injuries.
Inhale.
I understand.
They will come to
Qingyun Temple eventually.
You're badly injured,
it will take some time to heal.
My student Zhou Cheng
runs a martial arts school.
You can look for him,
and he can take care of you.
If White Brows and Gao Jinzhong come here,
I've to put up a fight with them.
You can't help in your state.
You should leave soon.
Han Qi works as an acrobat
with a theatre troupe.
You can contact him.
Our Tibetan Lama Clan
don't want to get involved
in the fight between the Court
and Shaolin, goodbye.
Wait. I'll give you a prescription.
Yes.
Shiyu, pack some clothes
and money for Xiguan.
Yes.
I'll stay here temporarily
with Shiyu, Meiyu and Xiaoyu.
After we've gathered
the rest of the students,
we'll contact Han Qi and yourself.
Yes, master.
I could walk some distance with you.
I'll tell you how to get to Zhou Cheng.
"Zhou Cheng Martial Arts School"
"Lama Clan"
These are different from the usual setup.
Ours is based on
the Big Dipper constellation.
Forty nine in total,
all different in height.
You all know that.
Yes.
Practise hard
from what I have taught you.
Yes.
Good! Continue practising!
After a certain time, it won't feel
any different up there
from what it's on the ground
Where's Zhu Cai?
Master.
Wait.
You're late.
Do you take your lesson seriously?
It's very busy at the dye factory today.
I rushed here as soon as I could leave.
Then you should head back.
You can never learn the way you are.
I'm ashamed that
you're my student.
Look! He tries to hit me.
Hey! The master sent you
back to the dye factory.
What are you doing here still?
I'll leave after I've practised.
Practise on the Big Dipper poles?
Very well. Come on!
It's easy to get injured there.
I dare not hurt you.
Do you honestly think you can?
Go up!
Look how he listens to me!
Zhu Cai, what on earth are you doing?
How could you be so severe
on your classmate?
Master, he...
You think you've mastered it, don't you?
Fine, challenge me.
I dare not to, master.
Jin, I'm off.
Stand still, Zhu Cai.
Listen up! Beat him up!
I'll pay a tael of silver
for every punch and kick!
Hey! Why didn't you fight back?
You must try your best
even if there's no hope to win.
Come on! You'll get paid.
One punch, you owe me a tael.
Five punches,
six taels of silver all together.
Can you afford it?
One hundred and thirty four taels. Pay up.
One hundred and fifty.
One hundred and seventy eight.
One hundred and ninety,
one hundred and ninety eight.
One hundred and ninety nine.
Two hundred!
Run.
Thanks, they're all my classmates
at the kung fu school
Please stop.
What kind of a master is he?
A rich person won't necessarily
learn well.
I think you're better than
the rest of them.
I've learnt martial arts
on the Big Dipper Poles.
Big Dipper Poles? Where?
Let's have some fun.
I lost my balance.
My turn!
Very well! You rule on the poles.
But I'm better at the restaurant.
And I'm the best in the tofu shop.
"Qingyun Temple."
Han Qi?
I sent Hong Xiguan to contact you!
What are you doing here?
Master Zhishan,
it's very dangerous out there.
I'm here to inform you.
I know, just head back.
Hong Xiguan is injured,
you must hurry and find him.
We're staying here temporarily.
After the rest of the members are here,
I'll contact you, go!
Leave at the back door.
Alright.
I worry about Brother Hong's injuries.
Old monk, is there a Master Zhishan here?
Good thing that you weren't rude.
This is Master Zhishan.
I didn't expect he'd be so easy to find.
You were looking for me?
To kill you.
Old one too tough; guess I will
see to the younger ones.
Zhishan is the head of
those Shaolin members.
His best student is Fang Shiyu.
Tackle Fang Shiyu first;
then we'll both kill Zhishan.
Fang Shiyu's mother Miao Cuihua
soaked him in herbal medicine
when he was young.
It's hard to hurt him with swords
except his crotch.
Try to make him kick,
then I'll take care of it.
For Zhishan,
his weakest parts are his eyes 1and crotch.
Attack his eyes,
so that he'll try to protect them.
Then I'll attack his crotch.
Sure
Go!
Zhishan's dead.
Hong Xiguan is the
only Shaolin member left.
He's not a threat, I injured him well.
Gao Jinzhong, you take the four of them,
and try to locate Hong Xiguan.
Kill him once you've found him.
Yes.
Brother Hong.
Brother Wang, you're here alone?
I got parted from others
after we left Shaolin Temple.
I'm still trying to look for
Master Zhishan & the rest.
Many of them died in
West Meditation Temple.
Zhishan and Brother Fang
are still in Qingyun Temple.
I came from there.
Where do you plan to go now?
Are you hurt?
Yes, the master sent me to contact Han Qi.
But when I left Qingyun Temple,
and bid goodbye to Master Xinglong
Gao Jinzhong and his gang
caught up with me.
I'm not sure whether they'll find me here.
Then you had better leave.
If they get here,
I'll deal with them.
At least we're here together,
we'll think of something.
I'm heading off.
Try to find Han Qi.
Yes. Please be careful with your wounds.
I know. You be careful too. I'm off.
Hong Xiguan.
You two!
Come on!
Another round!
Power of a finger.
Get down here.
You're Hong Xiguan?
Yes.
Your master Xinglong sent me here
to meet Master Zhou.
I hope that you could treat me.
We're both in the martial arts world,
you're badly injured
and have met my master.
Yet my school is just a small place;
It has no room for such
a big hero like yourself.
Master Zhou, say no more.
I understand. Goodbye.
Hero Hong.
What are you doing?
Sorry, sir.
Get up!
Yang Dabao, what's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
Look at these stools!
They're all in good condition, look!
Good condition?
I don't have any problem with it.
Look! All in one piece.
They just don't know how to sit properly.
Welcome!
Please have a seat.
So, how should I sit?
Sir, you're kidding. You can sit
whatever way you want.
Hurry! Sorry. Take a stool
and put it over there.
Coming.
You...
Beat it.
Black Tiger Clan?
I'm looking for a person named Han Qi,
he works as an acrobat
in the theatre troupe.
Have you heard of him?
Han Qi! I've watched him perform.
His red boat will arrive in a few days.
You seem to be injured.
Sorry, it's none of my business.
I'll deduct from your pay
if you slack off,
break anything or open late.
Damn! I must find a monk for a ceremony.
Hey, pal! You knocked off my stuff.
What's the matter?
Can't you walk properly?
I think you're drunk.
Such trouble!
Who are you?
Chen Ajin.
Yang Dabao, come on in.
You want me to do yourjob? Never.
It's different from my martial arts style.
Look.
Who is he? What's he doing here?
You know him?
No. I saw him in the restaurant earlier.
Who is he?
Not too sure myself.
I found this piece of paper on him.
Read it.
Light up!
I can't read anything in the dark.
What does it say?
You are an illiterate too?
I think he must be an important person.
The boss is back.
This prescription was written by
my master's
master, Xinglong.
He's badly injured.
The injured person is inside.
He's Hong Xiguan.
What?
He's Hong Xiguan
The one who's wanted by the Court?
I never expected that we'd have a chance
to meet such a hero.
Looks like he's in a pretty bad state.
I'll get the medicine.
The old master's prescription would work.
Don't let anyone find out though.
I wouldn't mind
sacrificing for Hong Xiguan.
I'd rather be beheaded
than to make tofu my whole life.
"Yan Shou Herbal shop"
How much is it?
Three taels forty five cents each.
Times two, that comes to...
What? It's so expensive.
This isn't an ordinary prescription.
It costs two taels eighty cents for
just the bear's bladder
and rhino's horn powder.
What are you doing?
Keep it for me,
I don't have enough cash, I'll be back.
I only have one tael, what about you?
Don't you have some money
for your future wedding?
Only two taels, I saved up for two years.
Take it out... for saving a life.
What?
Saving a life is more important.
Come on.
Still not enough.
I think you have some money.
Hurry up! Take it out!
Come on!
You slept well after you took
the medicine last night.
Are you feeling better?
I'm a complete stranger to you,
yet you three...
You're very welcome, Master Hong.
Although we are nobody,
but we know that you're a hero.
That's why we'd like to help.
You're indeed the real heroes.
Come on.
This is good medicine,
I guess you'd need to continue.
Yes, at least ten times.
What about the money for the medicine?
Why don't you answer?
I even used up the savings for my wedding.
You're the one with all the ideas,
think of a plan!
Alright, let us think!
Steal!
You're early today, Mei.
Jin, two pieces of tofu.
They're really fresh today.
Yes, looks like it.
Give me two pieces, Jin.
Thanks.
Let's go.
Zhu Cai, what's the matter with you?
Nothing.
What can the poor do to get cash quick?
Yes, there's one thing.
It's called...
Pawn things.
The bill please.
Twelve cents.
Did you enjoy the meal?
It's alright, let's go.
Think I'm too full.
Good day.
Take it. Thanks.
Tofu? It's fresh today!
The biggest piece, here you go.
Mrs. Wang, it's been a while.
Want some tofu?
Very fresh today.
Please come back again.
Jin, what are you doing?
Nothing, it tickles.
Tofu...
A customer!
Fresh tofu!
The best quality!
Here you go! Come back again! Thanks!
Who would have thought?
A dumb wit like you would steal from me!
Count it! You've stolen so much from me!
I'm running a business here.
I've been treating you well.
You bastard!
You must pay ten times
of what you've stolen from me.
Do you understand?
"Pawn"
Chen Ajin, how much do you have?
I've got...
You're looking for Jin?
Do you know that he stole from me?
And I caught him!
You don't look like a decent person too.
What are you here for?
I...
What are you doing here?
I'm here to buy tofu.
Buy tofu? How much?
All of it.
We've a big spender today!
I'll deal with you later.
Come on.
It won't be easy for you
to carry with all that tofu,
I'll get my staff to help.
Make the delivery and come back soon.
I'll deduct from your pay
if you try to slack off.
It's you!
Do you know how expensive the vase is?
What did you buy all that tofu for?
You told me so. You didn't get any money.
I pawned everything,
and now I've all this tofu.
What on earth are you two doing?
Go get the medicine, hand me the tofu.
Yang Dabao, where are you off to?
What are you doing?
Boss, we've got big business.
We have guests who like tofu.
Guests? Where?
If they are,
bring these to the kitchen first.
I'll take care of them.
Please sit down.
What's on the menu?
Oh, tofu.
How about some beef first?
The beef, we kept it from last month.
It's gone bad! Tofu is fresh.
But we can't just eat tofu.
Tofu is our specialty.
We've fried, deep-fried, steamed,
stewed, diced, chilled,
with vegetables, with minced pork,
in a soup... you name it, we have it.
All of the above!
Coming right up...
At this time...
No one would carry weapons so openly,
must be some kind of officers.
Thanks.
Boss.
Master Zeng.
What did he buy just now?
The best, he's been here a few times.
I think someone is badly injured.
Internal injuries.
Can you remember the prescription?
Master Zhou,
this is my friend Official Gao.
He's on the Court's order
to catch Hong Xiguan.
Please assist him anyway you can.
Certainly.
We're trying to look for Hong Xiguan.
According to my master White Brows,
Hong's injuries
can only be healed by the Lama Clan.
I wonder if Hong Xiguan came to you
for help.
To be frank, he did.
I'm a law-abiding citizen.
A traitor like him came for help,
I kicked him out right away.
If Master Zhou captured him on the spot,
you would have
helped the court a big deal.
I think master Zhou didn't dare
to kill him.
Hong Xiguan has a reputation.
There's one prescription
to treat internal injuries.
Bear's bladder powder,
rhino's horn powder...
Yes, that's our special prescription.
Zhu Cai bought this prescription
many times.
Could it be...
Right. He's cleaning the room
when Hong Xiguan came here.
Who's Zhu Cai?
Don't worry, I can take care of him.
He drops by everyday.
Cheers! We've found the traitor!
Let the "Qi" energy
travel through your body.
You three excel in different areas.
But no one has taught you about the Qi.
That's why you might find it difficult
for some complicated martial arts styles.
With your foundation,
it's easy for you to learn.
Let me teach you
Shaolin's own use of "Qi".
Gather "Qi" at diaphragm.
We're treating a VIP guest &
we don't have enough chefs
It's a compliment that
we're using your chef.
How can I run a restaurant without a chef?
Do you have any idea who my guest is?
Who cares whether or not
you can do business!
Get the chef!
Wait...
We're just a small restaurant,
our chef isn't that good.
Yes, the dishes are only good for pigs.
Well said.
For your VIP guest,
our chef is only useful
if you're serving a pig.
What are you on about?
Stop!
Boss, we must.
They've got the chef;
without him, we've no business.
Beat him!
Come on!
Run!
I can walk myself out.
One, two, three.
You broke everything!
I'll deduct from your pay
What are you doing?
One, two, three.
I'm Han Qi.
I've seen you act.
Brother Hong Xiguan is looking for you.
I'm looking for him too.
Come pick me up tonight,
we'll go meet him.
Sure.
Master.
Zhu Cai, the medicine you bought,
who's that for?
Speak up! Who's that for?
For myself, it hurts here.
Must be from the practising.
It's for myself.
Hurts here?
Yes.
Interesting that you can
foresee your own injuries.
Speak up! Who's that for?
For myself.
Where else does it hurt?
Here... no... nowhere.
What's the medicine for?
Only Hong Xiguan would need
a prescription like that.
Zhu Cai, if you show Official Gao
to Hong Xiguan,
that's a merit.
Speak up! Where is Hong Xiguan?
He sneaks around in the tofu shop,
I think Hong Xiguan could be there.
No! He's not!
Alright! You did us a favour.
Who are you?
Let me go! I'm the boss.
Chen Ajin, run!
Freeze.
Where's Hong Xiguan? Speak up.
At your grandma's.
You! You can't do that
This is more likely.
Set a fire! And we can save them.
They're below. We're setting a fire.
Run!
Don't panic! Run! Go!
Over there! Go!
Go!
Where to?
The dye factory is right here,
let's hide inside.
No, when they arrive,
they would know that we're hiding there.
We should hide in
Zhou Cheng's martial arts school.
Good idea!
Here you are!
Congratulations on catching Hong Xiguan,
what an achievement!
Well, I'm here.
But no one caught me.
You stay here. It's better for you.
What a meal!
Let's not ruin it.
That's right.
Zhu Cai works in the dye factory,
he must be hiding in there.
They're in the school, the master...
Careful. After you!
Me?
Go!
They're gone.
Hey! Come on in! No one's here.
I'll take a look first, follow me.
How come he's suddenly acting so brave?
They're gone, of course he would.
It's clear.
Next door is the dye factory,
wonder if they're there.
No lights. Guess they must have fled.
Official Gao, I'm being brave,
I deserve a credit.
Sure, you do.
They're over there at the wall.
They're in the dark.
Unfamiliarity with the settings
is to our disadvantage.
Zeng Shiguang is an example.
Go to the magistrate's office
and get some manpower.
Block all the exits.
Yes.
We indeed need the manpower.
But it's late in the night,
I'd rather not alert them.
And besides,
we haven't contacted the magistrate,
I worry that we can't get any help
until daybreak.
All we can do is bluff for now,
we'll get the men in the morning.
Why don't they attack?
There's no light.
They wouldn't dare to attack in the dark.
The archers on the left,
shoot when you spot anyone.
Soldiers with axes on the right,
chop if you see anyone
We'll keep disturbing them over the night.
That way, they can't sleep
and dare not escape.
We'll launch a proper attack tomorrow.
I think it's just a bluff,
but we need to be prepared.
The power of the palm is
different between yin & yang.
After controlling your "Qi" right,
you can master it.
Ah Jin, you try.
You're not focused enough... once again.
That's better.
Not bad.
Listen up, traitors!
You've been surrounded.
This is where you'll die.
Ah Jin, no!
I brought Zhou Cheng's feast here.
Let's have a good meal!
That's right. If someone comes close,
we can hear.
I'll move all the weapons here.
I think we should hide them first.
Come on.
Let's not congratulate ourselves
for escaping earlier;
It's only because
Gao Jinzhong's gang underestimated us
Those five are very skilled,
and they're backed by the court.
You had nothing to do with it,
I appreciate that you helped me
with my medicine.
I wouldn't blame you
for wanting to leave now.
I'm their target.
Hong Xiguan, you despise us.
If I meant anything like that,
please let me be struck by thunder.
I was wrong, please forgive me.
Come on, sit.
I'm honoured to have friends like you.
This is certainly
something to celebrate for.
It's a long night.
Let's drink and talk about martial arts.
Come!
Brother Hong, please teach us.
Earlier on, Priest White Brows
learnt from Wudang Clan;
Gao Jinzhong remains his best student.
I hear they're hoping to build up
a White Brows Clan.
We must watch out for Gao Jinzhong first,
especially his braid.
Know your enemy!
Zou Feng's sword strikes fast and sneaky.
He has a shield to protect himself.
Watch out for his sword
breaking through the shield,
that's his trick.
Fan Tiancong is a man with
massive strength.
I think he's the one hitting the wall now.
Each strike is deadly,
we must think of a way to deal with him.
So boring! Let's check them!
Sure.
You cover for me.
Go!
They are the Tiger Kid and Leopard Kid.
Tiger Kid has a deadly kick.
Leopard Kid kills with the copper ring.
Don't think that they're just kids,
they're very vicious. You must be careful.
The soldiers are gathering,
they'll be here soon.
Wait. Come on.
Come on.
Have a drink.
What style is this?
The Black Tiger Clan's style.
Zhu Cai...
Dabao...
Brother Hong, the soldiers are here!
Leave with Han Qi, I'll stay behind.
No!
I'm injured anyway.
Leave now! Or you won't make it!
We'll stay behind and block them.
Jin's badly injured too.
If we all die,
who's going to complete the mission?
Run!
Shoot!
Dabao, we lived life to the fullest.
Fun, isn't it?