In the early stage of Mingguo£Â
the political status was messy
The Nationalist Government
was incapable of controlling the situation
that made the powerful countries
from outside try to bully and oppress her
While warlords from
inside monopolized different areas
A lot of bandits were bullying around
There were also endless spying activities
That's what happened
Below the Ngau Tau Shan
The warlord Warlord Lin had monopolized an area
He hates the Japanese invasion most
and uses all his efforts
to fight against the Japanese
The Japanese treat him as an eyesore
The Tiger Den down the hill
has some local tyrants who take over an area
Tiger Hong£Â Leopard Hong
and Phoenix Hong. They are siblings
They do all kinds of bad things
And they tie with Japanese
They hold the candle to the devil
and bully the common people
They are well-known traitors
However more than
15 kilometers outside Tiger Den
There is a Lucky Star Town
which is just like a fairy land
The common people live happily in here
Until that day..
Have we been to this town£À
No
Why£À
The old man said this town is weird
Maybe he suffered before
He told us not to bother
those people In Lucky Star Town
This moth-eaten
Is too old that he doesn't have the guts
How can we not kill him£À
Let's go down Thereafter
we have finished our breakfast
Rob the money£Â the food and the women!
Good!
Don't miss out as you walk past
Come£Â take a look..
Hello
Little Trumpet..
Little Trumpet£Â where is my cream£À
How about my perfume£À        Two bottles, ok
Awesome!
4 bottles
4 bottles ,ok
Me first
Little Trumpet£Â a bottle of perfume
Little Trumpet£Â I want a bottle
You want one as well£Â ok
Roasted pork buns on it sway
Yours..
The roasted pork bun is ready.
It's just steamed
Smells good£ÀWant to try£À
Mademoiselle Hong£À
Mademoiselle Hong
Little Trumpet£À
This perfume is for you
It's made In France
Great. Thank you
I hope my sister didn't notice
Don't worry
Little Trumpet!
Sister..
Let me help you. Pull..
It will be out soon
Can your mouth take up stuff of that size£À
Yes
Shall we try this£À            What£À
Little Trumpet£Â
you are luring my sister again£Â aren't you£À
Nonsense
I'm speaking nonsense£À
I can tell you were just..
Sister£Â stop it
You£Â beware not to lose your self to this fellow
And money£Â too
Little Trumpet
Oh my god..
You bastard
If you come here
to lure Mademoiselle Hong again
I will shock you to death
by my life-taking annoying sound
Go!         Little Trumpet..
Little Trumpet..
Dammit!
You have one bottle left
Many sons£À
Many sons..
There is still one bottle left
May be you could sell it
to me for half the price
That's not milk powder
Why do you need it£À
It's none of your business
20% off
Half price!
Give it back to me..
Nice move
It's nothing
Give me the perfume
50% off
20% off
You're Insane!
Don't go!
You use the iron baby for the perfume£À
I have the bronze cymbal
Lower the price a bit£Â please
Don't even think about it!
Would you lower it£À
No way!
50% off£À
40% off
30% off!
Cheaper
It's hard-earned money!
Beat you!
20% off
30% off
40% off
You said so£Â 40% off
Give me the money now
Tomorrow
That's impossible
The day after to morrow then
Tomorrow is the latest
You said it
Thank you
Abracadabra
Bless the Lucky Star Town
to have peaceful weather
Men and animals are safe and well!
Let's welcome Centenarian
Who shakes the bamboo for tune stick
For the people In the town
Come on
Great£Â it's the best stick
The Lucky Star Town
will have peaceful weather this year
Men and animals are safe and well!
Animals are not safe and well but humans are
If you serve me well
Everyone will be safe and well
You gang of society scum
Gangster£Â scum£Â bum
Raping£Â robbing
and sexually assaulting grannies
and robbing the children's breakfast money
We people from Lucky Star town
are not afraid of you!
You guys agree£Â right£À
It seems that they don't
Warrior!
I know I'm wrong
My wife got pregnant
and is going to deliver soon
I am going to grab some women
What do you want£À
I won't sell myself to you
Even if you get my body
you can't get my soul
I want to have your soul!
You Taoist priest
Got the guts to fight against me
Do you have very good kung fu£À
Actually my kung fu is not good
But it's good enough to fight with you
You dare to beat me£À
I'm not gonna beat you.
But you don't beat me£Â too
It's the Merry Forest that
has a lot of beauties
I gotta see how beautiful they are. Let's go!
Go!
The material is quite fine
Beauty
Hi£Â beauty
What are you yelling£À
We haven't even opened the door yet
We are the bandits!
Don't scare my beauties away!
Look
The colour looks nice too
Great
Hello
It'll be finished very soon
Who kicked me£À
Boss£Â your face has some shoeprints
Just check their shoes
Smart
Raise your foot!
Do they lookalike£À
Yes
Stop beating..
What's up£À
You haven't even heard of my move£Â
Miss Manuelle's Kick Beneath the Dress
and you dare to be a gangster£À
Kill them for me!
Kill!
You dare to beat my boss£À
Help!
Let us get out of here!
Sorry£Â I've missed two stitches
Little Tailor
I give you 7 days to finish
and deliver the clothes
Or I won't give you any money
So scary£Â robbery£Â I'm so scared..
Oh my god£Â robbery
I'm gonna die this time
Robbery
How many of you£À
Robbery£À Robbery£À
I'm so scared
Any one that doesn't want to die£À
Yes£Â everyone
Raise your hand if you don't want to die
You dare to make trouble In Mc Shop£Â are you£À
You have a lot of choices
But you chose to be a robber£À
Bea robber!
This gang of bandits really knows nothing
You don't even know that
We are the seven retired Kung Fu masters
Same old rule
Psychiatric Hospital
I've called a carriage
All of them are experts with good kung fu
They know the Toad move
18 Palm Moves Against Dragon
and Skeleton Claw
Go and get the Skeleton Yin Yang
Sword Move to beat them!
See you
Don't you need to work£À
Why don't you go and work£À
Time to work
Why aren't you working£À
What's up£À
Are you free tonight£À
What if I'm free£À
I want to ask you out to admire the moon
Are you Insane£À Tonight is the first of
a lunar month£Â how can we admire the moon£À
Admire your butt In this case
You dare!
We are really going to admire the moon.
And we have moon cake£Â too
Even the Ching Ming Festival had
already passed. How can we have moon cake£À
We have lots of leftovers from  last year
Maybe next time
She didn't use the sonic boom kung fu
Against you. That means you have a chance
You noticed that too
I'm sorry..
Handsome..
Where are you going£À
We are going to Tiger Den
But it's getting dark
Why don't we stay In the our shop for a night
and leave the next day
No thanks. We are In a rush
Look£Â that carriage is very nice
She is the little princess of Warlord Lin
Don't you know£À
Is she hereto buy food again£À
You don't know
she is the dream girl of Little Tailor
Really£À
There is a pretty There
Are you foreigners£À
We are going to Tiger Den for business
Tiger Den is dangerous. You have to be careful
Thanks for your reminder
My name is Cheryl Lin. What is your name£À
My name is..
My name is Tony Luo
Tony Luo
See you some other time
Miss..
There are a lot of bad guys here.
We gotta be careful
Yes£Â miss
But£Â they don't look like bad guys
Little Tailor£Â your dream girl is here
I really want to make clothes for her
Checkout how expensive
The cloth she uses on her dress
Will she let you make it£À
Better...not
Right£Â baby£À
Don't cry. Time to go back and have some milk
When you are willing to pay the effort£Â
There is hope
Sister
Hello
This one is nice. This one is fresh
This one£Â then
You could take few more...
Okay£Â I'll take them all
The sky is so blue
So beautiful
And sunny
The sunshine is so warm          Great..
Don't bask In the sun£Â
you'll be tanned£Â Little Trumpet
That lake is so beautiful
So beautiful
Is it really very beautiful£À
Very beautiful
What's so beautiful£À
You are beautiful
What are you looking at£À
Bitch!
What happen to you£À
It hurts. I'm crippled
give him 20 big dollars
Miss£Â you don't have to give that much
Quick
Just do what I told you to
Thank you. You are so nice
This dress is so pretty
Brother Four's tailor In Fashion
Go and ask her for an address
I'll go to her place to try it
when I need make some clothes next time
Yes!
Miss...           Beauty..
What's up£À
A man£À
Hey£Â you are disguising as a woman
Are you harboring evil intentions to our miss£À
I don't have any bad Intentions..
Beat him!
No£Â help..
Help..
What happen to you£À
He..
You were the beauty£À
I just wanted to attract you. I am a tailor
I want to make you a dress
You don't need to pay me
I couldn't do this
Why do you want to make me a dress£À
You are the best model I have even seen
You overpraised me
Lucky Star Town
Auntie Seven         Hello
Auntie Beach         Hello
It seems that everyone is very happy
Everyone has nothing to worry about
Little Tailor
Of course£Â because all of us are...
Hello
Happy with what we have got
Lucky Star welcomes you to visit
Visit us and laugh to one's content
Madonna still has no one to love
No one after so she focuses on cooking
Manysons is holding a little boy
Very supportive. So cute
Little Trumpet
and Mademoiselle Hong are falling In love
Madonna is going to break them up
Chanting Bing is teaching the grannies
Tai Chi Punch. He is awesome
Miss Manuelle had ogled towards here
Though making soya sauce£Â
We are happy from our heart
I look to the left and look to the right
Look upwards and downards
All the lucky stars
In the Lucky Star Town are so simple
I sing and sing
I swing and swing
The lucky stars in the Lucky Star Town are cute
The seven Kung Fu Masters
Here Comes..
Lucky Star Town..
Xing 's wife£Â has father come back yet£À
Miss is back
General's schedule is delayed for one day
He can only be back tomorrow
That's bad news
Yet£Â In a way it is good news
That means I have one more day
to prepare something delicious for father
Ok
According to the information
Tiger Den had already formed
an alliance with the Japanese
And transformed it into a covert
Intelligence camp for Japanese spies
Information reveals that the lady spy Kurosawa
Kiyoko will be arriving in these two days
Then we should get the name list
as soon as possible then
Otherwise There will be trouble
We go in There to investigate just after dusk
No way
Why don't we wait
For Tony Luo and do it together
Tony Luo..
He needs two more days to arrive
I'm afraid we can't wait
We just need to be careful
Let's go
Welcome Miss Kurosawa
Please forgive us
for not picking you up soon..
My main purpose of coming here this time
Is to take care of Warlord Lin
That fatso is hard to take care
He has a rough temper
and his kung fu is very good
I've tried many attempts
but I have never found a chance
If he could be bought£Â buy him
If he can't£Â kill him
It seems that someone is looking for you
As expected£Â
it is really the Japanese intelligence camp
I found it
The confidential list of Japanese spies
The senior had been looking fo rthis
Janice£Â you keep it safe
Spy came£Â go and get him
Let's see where you can escape
You go first
Be careful!
Go quickly!
Leopard Hong£À
Are you afraid now£À
Let's go
Good
We should take care
Of the important things first
Go quickly!
He was hurt by my dart and poison palm
He shouldn't be able to escape too far
Go after him!
Miss£Â what are you thinking about£À
I am thinking what I should cook for dad
when he is back to morrow
General loves you so much
He would love whatever you cook for him
Dad is so poor since mom had died
No woman takes care of him
Therefore I have to take care of dad for mom
What are you doing£À
What is the sound outside£À
Shall I go and check it out
Tiger Hong£Â are you Insane£À
You dare come to General Lin's home
and make trouble£À
We are the best citizens
Someone had stolen
Our stuff and hid it In There
So tell me£Â what should we do£À
Bullshit!
Why would we have a thief In here£À
Then let us In to take a look
You dare!
General Lin's family is Inside£Â
How dare you barge In
Why are all of you at my home£À
Go away£Â all of you
General Lin
Mr. Ishihara has given you an offer
He is still waiting for your reply
Really£À
His offer is enough
for me to spend for two lives
So we...will become a family soon
Don't move!
Let me tell you
For all these years In my life
I have had the courage to do anything I want
But I dare not be a traitor
Leave!
What happened£À
Tony Luo..
Tony Luo£Â are you ok£À
Don't come In!
This is dad!
Not even you£Â dad
I am bathing
So why are you screaming£À
I slipped over just now
Be careful
Ok
What was Tiger Hong's reason for coming£À
He said a thief had stolen his property
so he came here
Bullshit
Go and check around
In case someone really broke In
Yes
Go
Come on£Â slowly. Lay down first
You woke
I have a dart on my back
and you put me down like this..
How could I not be awaken£À
I'm sorry
How should I help you then£À
Pick the dart out for me
Stop the bleeding
Sterilize and warp it
Ok
Give me some anti-inflammatory
Have you finished bathing£À
I've finished
Then I am coming In
Dad. What happened£À
Nothing
I was just worried that some bad guys came In
Dad
How would someone dare
To do anything offensive to us£À
You should take rest earlier
That's true
You've grown
Yes£Â I've grown
No£Â I mean your legs have grown
You don't come back often£Â
So you can't even recognize me
Go out...I'm not gonna chat with you
Wait£Â no
Your upper body reacts.
Why doesn't your leg show reaction£À
It does. But the reaction is a bits low
Ok
Take some good rest
Scream In case of anything
Ok
Honey£Â Cheryl has really grown up
There must be a man In her bed
What should I do£À
Since you left me
I didn't have the time to accompany her
But shall I reveal her behaviours now£À
Or shall I let go£À
If I really drag the guy out from her bed
she'll hate me for life
What£À
Let her be£À
That means I should pretend that I saw nothing£À
Yes. I should let Cheryl be happier
Wife£Â you are right
I will listen to you
Wait a moment. I am going to get some medicine
What should I do£À
Cut..
Cut it..
Oh£Â cut it
Needs to sterilize..
Sterilize..
Sterilize£À
Are you feeling better£À
A bit better
But you can't stay here
If my dad finds out£Â we're in trouble
General
Go and keep an eye on miss
Yes
Taoist£Â Taoist..
Taoist
Take a seat first
Why did you bring this person£À
They said everyone In town comes to find you when
It concerns births£Â deaths£Â aging and illnesses
Please save him
Let me take a look
Taoist£Â please save him
Right£Â the live and dead could come and see me
But he is right between them. Why are you here£À
So who should I look for£À
Just hand him over to us would do
Hand him to you£À
Hand ove rto us. What are you worried about£À
As long as he is a man£Â we can cure him
What happened£À
What's up£À
He is dying. Please save him
Who is he£À
Don't worry about it first
However if he dies
I won't talk to you forever
He is hurt so badly.
Only Madonna could cure him
Can she£À
She has a super reviving pill
which could cure all diseases including
Internal Injury£Â kidney disease£Â pimples
constipation£Â disorder£Â syphilis£Â athlete foot
As long as he isn't dead£Â it could be cured
So let's go now
That's not that easy
That pill is her wedding gift
She may not even
give it to her dad if he was dying
I can buy it from her
If I was Injured like this..
How much would you pay£À
100 big dollars
How about him£À
Any cost
You can't buy it with money
What should we do then£À
There is only one person who could help you
Who£À
It's so dangerous here
and you're still bringing this with you£À
It's a long story
When I having lunch..
Get down
Got it
Grab on tighter
The one on her chest is the reviving pill
Lower
A bit more
The rope ends here
No more..
Big Trumpet£Â comedown..
Big Trumpet..
Comedown..
Smart
Go down and get it. Hurry
Go down quickly
Go down immediately. Listen to me
I said go down and get it£Â asshole
Or I'll beat you!
Spider..
Expert of all clans
and you're afraid of a spider£À
Don't fool around. Go get it quickly
This way. Stop fooling around
I can't feed you for nothing!
Spider..
And you claim you are the expert of all clans.
Yet you are afraid of a spider£À
Harder£Â buddy!
Why am I so popular£À
Because we are too cool
You bastard!
What are you doing here£À Trying to kill me£À
I..
I love you!
I should have noticed
No wonder you come for
Mademoiselle Hong all the time
While you keep your eyes on me
Yes
Right. I feel strange£Â too
I am much more beautiful than Mademoiselle Hong
There is no reason for you
To go after her rather than me
I thought you were insane
That's the actual reason
Yes£Â I know it's my fault
I know I'm wrong
I can't confront you anymore
I am leaving now
No way
Both you and I will be very sad if that is so
So what should we do£À
How about from no won..
We have an affair
During daytime£Â you go dating
with Mademoiselle Hong
At night..
Good idea£À
Are you happy£À
Happy
Are you excited£À
Excited
Such an impartible opponent
Just a kiss!
Sister£Â how come it is so noisy£À
What£À
Little Trumpet£À
Why are you here£À
You are such an unlucky guy!
After my sister..
Don't beat him£Â don't beat him..
Sister
Go to hell!
Sister..
You've beaten Little Trumpet to death
Give me back my Little Trumpet
I don't want to live any more
From no won£Â
I won't allow you two to meet at night
He has to come to my place at night
I mean if he comes to my place
I will beat him to death!
I've got it
Sweetheart!
Hey...are you ok£À
Ok£ÀYou may try your self
Hey£Â how about the pill£À
It's already very fortunate
that I'm still alive£Â buddy
That means the lounge lizard would die£À
Sweetheart!
Hey£Â hey..
What's the matter with him£À
What's up£À His circulation
was disconnected because of the shock
He would definitely die. Look at him
No worries. I have a surviving pill
It can revive him
Bring it back and take it
No way. He needs to take it now
He should be fine after taking it
I'm fine now
That soon£À
Let's go play soccer
Great         Soccer£À
Good night
Soccer at this time of the night£À
He...how come he is still sick£À
Ok£Â don't worry and go home
I will return a living man to you tomorrow
Thank you£Â then
Actually the reviving
pill can only keep him alive
If we want to save him
We need to transfer our energy
to push the poison out from him
Ok£Â we should finish it off
Let the five of us do it together
Transfer the energy to him
and push the poison out
OK        Come on
Why all of you go behind him£À
We all small potato
You are the best among us£Â
Of course you do it first
Alright! Fine!
It's already 1 hour and he still not up£À
Maybe I am not feeling quite well these days£Â
Cannot concentrate at all
How about finding someone to replace me£À
Chanting Bing and Little Trumpet£Â
Come and replace me
You are a trouble maker
I already really hurt!      That's for you
It's already two hours£Â
did you guys do your best£À
I should use my left hand
I am right handed
Let me do it
How about me£À
You come here then     Alright
Let me do it
You bastard
What's going on£À
Concentrate!
Mannie£Â actually I like you a lot
But I am a very shy person
I don't know how to confess my love to you
I am old and I don't have much money
I could only treat you nicely from my heart
I don't mind that
you are the lady boss of a brothel
I hope you also don't mind that I am old
After you finish reading this letter
If you don't like it just throw it away
If you like it£Â you may show me some signs
Always love you£Â Chanting Bing
Do they know that
I am writing a letter to Miss Manuelle£À
Chanting Bing£Â I have something to tell you
Acting strangely
Why are you crying£À
I noticed how Cheryl looked at Tony Luo
I know I don't have any hope
When you like a girl
Do you want her to be happy
Or do you want yourself to be happy£À
Her
You've saved the life of that handsome
Cheryl must be very happy
Really£À
But what about me£À
Stop crying£Â would you£À
Cry...you make me wanna cry£Â too
I need to face Mademoiselle Hong and Madonna
I don't know what to do
I wanna ask the world what love is
Miss
You haven't returned home for the whole night.
Where were you£À
We all are so worried
Where is dad£À
He is meeting a guest in the study room
Dad
How come you didn't...          This is£À
She is my daughter. She's called Cheryl
You are as pretty as your mother
And this is£À
I am the daughter of Nie Town mayor
There are a lot of bandits There
I specially come here
To ask your dad to assist us
You go to the kitchen first
I will come and cook with you later
Ok
You have a good relationship with your daughter
Little Trumpet said£Â
Cheryl will be happy if I save that guy
If Cheryl is happy£Â I am happy
But why am I so sad now£À
Losing someone whom I love is so painful
Do you think you are the only one suffering£À
You are the only one that lost your love£À
What do you know£À Have you ever been In love£À
I've lost my love so many times
I can tell
When I was young
There were endless beauties who were so Into me
They also gave me a nickname£Â Handsome Tsoi
How can they tell such a lie£À
Then I retired from the Jianghu and came here
I found the love of my life
Who£À
Tell me
It is..
My Mannie
Miss Manuelle£À
But I am poor
I'm not good enough for her
Have you confessed your love to her£À
I'm so afraid that
She will turn me down once again
No courage at all
How about you£À
Why don't you go to tell Cheryl
That you love her£À
I'm so afraid that
she'll turn me down on the site
Both of us had lost our love
Losing someone's love is so painful
You better kill me
You kill me first and I'll then kill you
If I've killed you£Â how could you kill me
Let's think of away to die together
Good. Let's go to your home for a meeting
Good
Tony Luo..
Handsome
It's dark already
We have nice wine and nice cuisine£Â
We also have pretties to visit your room
Are you coming up£À
No thanks. But I want to get some Information
Did four men walk pass here3 days ago
Saying that they are going to Tiger Den£À
We don't know
But we can ask for you
Mannie...There is a man down There
asking aboutthe4 men
who were going to Tiger Den 3 days ago
Could they be his friend£À
Be careful
If they are people from Tiger Den
They would pretend that they are his friend
But he is so handsome.
He doesn't look like a bad guy
Have you had enough
that men keep taking advantage of you£À
Where does this handsome come from£À
I just want to lookfor4friends of mine
I haven't seen 4 friends
But we have4 pretties here
I would suggest you to stay here
and get the Information
Maybe you'll get some Information
Don't worry.
I will seek for the Information myself
Let's go
I'll use this one. This one it is.
To pierce through your lung
I'll use this one to pierce
through your bladder
I'll use this one to cut your aorta
I'll use this one to cut your Intestines
We'll die for sure
Yes£Â we must be able to die
Able to die
Step back
Even the ants will manage to survive
Why are the two of you committing suicide£À
It's none of your business
Did we say that we are committing suicide£À
No
That's it
But your bodies are equipped with..
Can we just play£À
Sharp weapons..
Have you ever had Western£À
Are you from the rural areas£À
Have you tried steak before£À
Move!
Are you here to help out again£À
Yes
But you need to pay me
What is this kid doing here£À
He was peeping when we were in the shower
Don't misunderstand me£Â seniors
I am just looking for my friends
Who are missing
If I made you mad
Please accept my apology
Young guy
Lucky Star Town won't be bullied
Yet they don't bully others
Just go
See you later
Manysons£Â why did you let him go£À
I haven't fought enough yet
Did he really peep when you were showing£À
Yes!
I am asking why the two of you
were having a shower together
We save water
Save water£À
Disgusting
Miss Manuelle...you've misunderstood..
Miss Manuelle!
Why can't we die£À
Xing's wife.
How come dad hasn't come down for meal£À
Just wait for some awhile
He is chatting with Miss Nie upstairs
That much food that I've made
Do I have to eat by myself£À
I can't drink anymore
That soon£À
General£Â you are good at drinking
What is this£À
Shall we dance
I don't know how to dance
Let me teach you. Give me your hand
You..
This is the poison Injection
That anesthetizes your nerves
The effects will be apparent very soon
It's useless even you've picked it out
You'll listen to me very soon
General!
Team Leader Zhu£Â you want to revolt£À
You are right
Team Leader Zhu is on my side long time ago
Dad!
Push the cabinet away
Dad
Go quickly!
Give way!
Xing's wife. Go after her!
Yes£Â Miss Kurosawa Kiyoko
Those people In the Lucky Star Town
are all KungFu experts
How come all of them take things lightly£À
As they have good kungfu
How come they are willing
To stay In a small town like this
Are they lackeys of the Japanese£À
Be careful!
Let me go...       Don't move!
Miss
Miss..
Are you ok£À
Thank you
What is your name£À
My name is Tony Luo
Your name is Tony Luo£À
I know Tony Luo
Have you met them£À
He was hurt. I've sent him
to Luck Star Town to be healed
Lucky Star Town£À
You would know if we go
to Lucky Star Town and check it out
Ok
Honey..
You said you were going to date me
I couldn't find you all over the town
Honey..
Shit£Â I can't continue on like this
Mademoiselle Hong
We've already closed
You..
It's me
Turn around
Little Tailor£Â my cousin is here to visit me
Go!
Why are you dressed like this£À
Your sister has been looking for me£Â
Saying we..
I don't care. I have to tell my sister
I have to marry you
What is it£ÀWhy it so hard£À
A bowl
Sister
What do we do£À
Hide here          This way
Quick
Hide In the jar
Don't throw away your shoes
I'm so angry
That bastard..
Sister
Why are you still up at this time of the night£À
What are you doing£À
I...am playing hide and seek
With who£À
Little Trumpet
Little Trumpet£À
Is he here£À
No           Where is he£À
Little Trumpet!
Sister...I'm not sure where he is
Has he gone out already£À
Don't worry about him
Why£À
Why don't you let me die when I want to£À
Little Trumpet£Â you may come out
You may come out£Â Little Trumpet
Mademoiselle Hong£À
What's up£À
As I treat you as sister
I have a secret to tell you
You have to keep this secret for me
I am good at keeping secrets
Chanting Bing peeped when you were showering
and Miss Manuelle stole your abalone
Little Tailor said your figure is poor
when he made your clothes
Did I tell you all this£À
You are really good at keeping secrets
That£Â of course
Actually£Â although I am so grown up
but I haven't..
been kissed
I want you to teach me
Now£À
Buddy!
I have never thought of trying it with you
So what do you really want£À
To tell the truth£Â
I am In love with Little Trumpet
Good night
Hey£Â give me back my money!
So what is it£À
I don't want Little Trumpet to know that
I don't have this kind of experience
Teach me
Obviously you don't read books
The Dream of the Red Chamber had Taught
The best thing it described is...what is it£À
Don't move if it's immoral£Â don't look
if it's immoral£Â don't say if it's immoral
I don't get it
Move your lips here. Let mete ach you
Wow£Â you are taking advantage then
You'll take my first kiss. No way
Sodo you have paper£ÀWe can put a piece
of paper In between so it doesn't count
Do you have paper£À
Yes
Don't move if it's immoral means
when he wants to kiss you
You pout and stop moving
Don't look if it's immoral means..
You close your eyes and enjoy the process
Then£Â don't say when it's immoral..
doesn't mean not to speak.
It means you speak while you pout
The happiest moment is to write with him
Not with your hand but by your tongue
You write to him and he writes to you
Like that£À
You can write like that. Are you human£À
I love you so much
Mademoiselle Hong
Mademoiselle Hong..
To be a bad guy£À
Mademoiselle Hong£Â I'm hungry
Auntie£Â what are you doing here£À
It's me£Â Little Trumpet
Little Trumpet£À
Keep quiet!
Look at this
I want to be a bad guy She is dead
Something big is happening!
What£À
And
I removed her first piece of clothing In here
Go!
And then            and
She has no clothes left on any more
She has nothing left on!
She has put her clothes back on
So..
And then..
Mademoiselle Hong..
Is everything ok£À If so£Â get up
It's fine. Let's go home
Let's go home
What had happened£À
I'll organize a wedding banquet
For you two tomorrow
Grown up men and women should get married
You just need to complete the registration
Sister£Â why are you acting so strangely£À
Nothing. She had promised our marriage
Really£À
We should be happy as she promised our marriage
Why are you so Intense
I'm very excited
You two..
Little Tailor..
This alley..
I..
Good bye
Poor guy that can't get a girl
Wait
Glad that I could stop
But I couldn't
Me neither
Sister£Â are you ok£À
My butt hurts!
Are you ok£À
Sister!
Why don't you let me die£À
You shouldn't die like this
Yes£Â you are such an idiot
Little Tailor£Â why are you hanging There£À
To grow taller
Don't you think I've become taller
You bastard
Why are you back after
you have peeped us showering£À
Senior£Â no more joke£Â please
I am Tony Luo
I just want to look for my lost friends
I mean no harm. You can rest as sure of that
He is a good guy. He just saved me
Who dares to harm you£À
Japan Ninjas
and people from Tiger Den
They had grabbed my dad
Where am I£À
You are beside me
Tony Luo£À
Am I dreaming£À
You've hugged the wrong person
She is here
What did I do wrong£À
Tony
Howard Luo and them£Â
they...sacrificed themselves
However£Â we've looted a list of Japanese spies
The Tiger Den became traitors
Even Warlord Lin is In the Japanese's hand
How do you know£À
The Japanese Ninjas were after Cheryl
And wanted to kill her just now
Fortunately she ran Into me
But why did she cry and leave the moment
She saw us£À
She likes you
She likes me£À
She thought you were a man
Miss Cheryl
I actually thought she is a man
Am I as stupid as a pig£À
Do you want to hear the truth£À
Not now
Actually you are the smartest girl
I've ever met
It doesn't matter if I am a man or a woman
You should worry about your dad's safety first
You are right
Dad was grabbed by that evil woman
We gotta save him
It hurts...my shoulder..
It really hurts...Help
Are you feeling better£À
Gently
All seniors       It really hurts
You all have good kungfu
If we could work together
We need not be afraid of them
It's not that we don't want to help you
The problem is that everyone
of us had our own sorrow history
We want to have a peaceful life now
Therefore we retire In Lucky Star Town
If we help you
It will become restless
Lucky Star Town will no longer be a fairyland
Yes£Â just go
Miss Kurosawa
What happens Inside the military camp
General hasn't come out for few days
They have started to suspect us down There.
I can't hold any longer
Help me and General arrange a wedding
Wedding£À
My soul transfer magic
had already controlled his behavior
However this guy has a strong will
I can't make him surrender
Just wait and see what I would do
But
We haven't found his daughter£Â Cheryl Lin£Â yet
What if she..
She is In Lucky Star Town
You guys£Â we're really sorry
In order to keep
our Lucky Star Town safe and well
We really can't be Involved in this
I hope you understand
No problem
I know everyone treats me nicely
I can't force you£Â right
Cheryl
You father will have a wedding party
with Nie WuShuang this afternoon
We should go first
Everyone£Â see you later
See you later
No!
I can't stand by and watch
I have to go with you
If you go£Â it means that we are all Involved
You can't be that selfish
You can't
Am I that useless£À
Do you want to hear the truth£À
Not too true
In my heart£Â you are really a good guy
You don't have to leave
They are£À
18 Silver Evils of Black Storm Fenced Hamlet
Who are they£À
They are the most expensive killing machines
They had a special offer recently
To celebrate their20th anniversary
They can kill the whole family
If you hire them to kill one of them
If you payfor3£Â
They can kill all the people In the village
By Instance they have a special offer this week£Â
So they are especially harsh on killing
Everyone be careful
Little Tailor..
Go!
We rush out together
I'll block them here
You bring Cheryl with you
As well as the spy list
No way..
We have to go together
I am not your fianc¨¦  now£¬ I am your senior
This is an order!
Go!
Come with me
So great
Who are they£À
The 18 Horny Evils of Black Storm Fence Hamlet
No£Â 18 Silver Evils
They are the broadsword team
that had killed more than 200 people
18 Silver Evils
How can we beat them£À
Don't be silly
Do you know if you go out like that
you'll embroil those Innocent common people
Let me go out
We've thought it through
Jianghu is actually not the place around£Â
it's Inside our heart
So we cannot retire
Hey! Come back!
It's so tough that we can't beat through
They are too sneaky. Let me use the needle
I hate people who are taller than me
Invincible£À
They need to breathe after all
Although the 18 Silver Evils are Invincible
they may not be
able to bear the sonic boom move
Start the drum!
Chanting Bing£Â you..
Eat this apple
and you'll act like your dad
Listen to what I say
Chanting Bing
What are you doing£À
Why are you here for me£À
Why is it£À
I am the real Chanting Bing
I got to beat you!
Abracadabra        Abracadabra
Most Exalted Lord Lao
Give me your life!
Give me your life
Which one is real£Â which one is fake£À
Even I can't tell
Ok£Â don't worry
I can
Whoever knows how to sing
theÁ¡The Fore stand The FieldÁ±
That one is real
Let's sing together
How I like to wander In the forest and plain
My dear friend£Â what are you thinking£À
Why don't you sing£À
We don't know this song at all
Our theme song is Á¡Kiss GoodbyeÁ±
She knows how to become Invisible
You bitch!
Why do you mimicking me£À
Outrageous
You are such a bitch!       Beat you
Two sisters..
I know which one is real
The real one had kissed me.
I remember the taste
Let me do it
Let me do it£Â too
Write something
He was poisoned by me. He'll die once he smiles
Many sons.
Why did you block this palm move for me
Because..
Actually I like you a lot£Â Madonna
Don't smile!
This palm move is so cruel.
You'll die if you smile
Men have to seek for happiness
I would rather die if I'm unhappy
Don't smile
I have something that have to tell you
Don't say too much
I have several hundreds of gold..
Fish for you
Then say it
Don't say it too loud for others to hear
But your voice is so soft that I can't hear
I've put it In..
Manysons
Don't die
The gold blocks£Â£Â
I don't want them anymore
No£Â don't die..
Manysons..
Tiger Den
Today is our big day
Act happier
Smile
The speech I Taught you last night
say it to me
After...we are married..
We will go to Europe for honeymoon
Things in the troop..
will all be taken care by Team Leader Zhu
He will take full control over you
Nice
Miss Kurosawa. Everything is ready
Let's start then
Ok
The wedding of General Lin and Nie Wu Shuang
Will now begin
General Lin
Are you willing to marry
Nie Wu Shuang as your wife
For better for worse£Â for richer for poorer£Â
In sickness and in health
to love and to cherish£Â
till death do you apart£À
I..
I am General Lin's daughter
Let me in
I...I..
I..
am...willing..
Forge ahead!
General Lin
Do you have anything to say to your juniors£À
After we are married
We will go to Europe for honeymoon together
The things of the troop
will be handed over to..
to..
Come catch them!
I hate people pointing their guns on me
Freeze...all of you!
You bitch£Â don't lure our Chinese men!
You've been doing it for so long yet
you could just push a little out of it
Take it slow
It will hurt...if you rush
Yes
Don't be so disgraceful. Go
You tom boy£Â I have to kill you
Hi£Â uncle
Dad£Â are you ok£À
I'm fine
He
They are my friends
They are here to save us
Not fooling with you
You are here at just about the right time
This one is too tough. You take care of it
Dad!
It's my fault
Would you let me go£À
You idiot
If I can't fix you. I'll go and eat shit
Are you ok£À
It's your turn..
Go
And you're still beating...
If you keep on beating
I'll hang you high
Great
Thanks
Young Man
I think your hatred towards him is stronger
So I'll hand this bastard over to you
Dad£Â you are so awesome
Tony Luo£Â it's him that had killed Howard Luo
Where do you still want to go£À
That way
Be careful!
She has been here all the time
and hasn't left at all
We don't use our eyes to look,but our hearts
Why are you so desperate£À
I have to be cool In front of girls
You all force her to come out
Not yet done£À
You are dead
Dad
Cheryl
Little Tailor£Â are you ok£À
Miss Cheryl
I have been wanting to tell you something
Say it..
I am 1.6 meter stall
I trust you
And I..
Like you so much
I like you£Â too
And£Â one last thing
Actually..
I got it
How can you be so naughty
We are leaving Miss Cheryl
I hope your dad could join us someday
And fight against the Japanese together
My dad had said that we will always befriends
We seven kungfu masters areal so the same
If There is something that we can do£Â
We will always be There
That would be great
See you later
Little Tailor
I really can't stand it
Little Tailor£Â where are you going£À