-= Caption Riper:Stone =-
-= Caption Collate:Stone =-
This is a copy of
Wang Xizhi's Orchid Pavilion Preface
by Zhu Zhishan ofMing Dynasty
Onthe back
is apainting by Wen Zhengming
The "Orchid Pavilion" Preface reads
Inthe 9thyearofEmperor Yong He
Duringthe beginning oflate spring
We had a gathering atthe Orchid Pavilion
We, the literati
old andyoung gathered around
Amidstthe loftymountains
and exuberantwoods
and bamboos,
the clearwinding stream is flowing by
delivering us ourdrinks
There was no music
but everyone drank joyfully
recited poems and
engaged in lively conversations
In 353 A.D.
The 9thyearofEmperor Yung He's regime
Wang Xizhi and a company
offorty one scholars gathered at
the Orchid Pavilion
atKueichi of Chekiang Province
where he wrote aboutthe gathering,
on silk paper
with abrush made out ofmouse whiskers
This unprecedented masterpiece became
the famous Orchid Pavilion Preface
Wangwas dubbedthe sage of calligraphy
Andthis famous masterpiece
with 28 columns and 324 characters
With each characterdiffering in style
Forexample;
the character'chih' is written
intwentythree different styles
Wang's original scriptwas amazing
Afterhe sobered up
He made overone hundred copies
Yetnone quite as excellent
as his firstattempt
He treasured his original copy
and passed downto his descendents
Whenthe scroll reached
the 7th generation
his descendents Zhi Yong and Hui Xin
Theylefthome to become monks
andtheirmonasterywas called
Yong Xin Monastery
Zhi Yong, also a great calligrapher
He wrote 800 copies
ofthe thousandwords essay and
distributedto all monasteries
ofEast Chekiang province
These are now scattered
all overthe world
lttook great effortforZhi Yong
to complete his works,
he used 8 large baskets ofbrushtops!
AfterZhi Yong's death
His pupil, anothermonk Pien Tsai,
also alearned scholar,
inheritedthe original copy
Pien Tsaitook up
Zhi Yong's love inthe arts
He guardedthe scroll more carefully
than his late master
Emperor Tang Taizong
was in apractice of...
copyingthe writing style
ofthe Wang calligraphers
He triedto acquire allthe works
by Wang Xizhi
To his regret, he couldn'tacquire...
the preface of Orchid Pavilion scroll
He heardthatPien Tsai has it
So he invited Pien Tsaito the palace
Pien Tsai deniedthathe hadthe scroll
Thenthe emperorsentFang Xuanling
to visitPien Tsai's monastery
with silk materials forclothes
gold, silver, and manymore treasures
Pien Tsai insistedthat
he has searchedthe...
whole monastery
and his late master's library
Yethe had seen no such scroll
Fang Xuanling came up with aplan
Xiao Yi's the key person inthis plan
Xiao Yi is aman oftalents andtactics
He toldthe emperorthat
Pien Tsai being alearned man
He won't give into a government official
Instead, he should dress up as a commoner
such as abusiness manfrom Shantung
andtake with him afew copies
ofthe works ofthe Wangs
The emperorgave his approval
Xiao Yi sets out on his mission
He reaches the Yong Xin monastery
and hence the popularlegend
The story of
Xiao gettingthe Orchid Pavilion Preface
has been amuch-toldtale
alegend sort of
Who is he?
Haven't seen him before,
don'tthink he's alocal
Looks like a scholar
Invite him infora cup oftea
Yes
Please have a seat
I've heard aboutyourfame
It's myhonorto have metyou
I'm reallyflattered
You have a certain accent
I'mfromthe north
I came from Shantongforbusiness
You don'tlook like abusinessmanthough
I'm actually a scholar
Yetl haven'tachieved much intenyears
That's whyl hadto try something else
No wonder
Please
Magic herbs grow onfamous mountains
Jiangnan is a good place to growtea
No wonder
What?
The wateris the keyin makingtea
Yangzi River's Nanling
has the second bestwater
Wuxi's Huishan Monastery's wateris third
The waterof
Suzhou's Huqiu Monastery's fourth
The fifth is the Bodhisattva Temple
in Danyang province
Daming Temple in Yangzhou is sixth
Wusong riveris seven,
Huaishui is eighth
Youforgotthe firstpick
Needless to say
Waterofthis monasteryis the best
You are too kind
The tealeaves, the water
andthenthe fire are all important
Also good companyis essential
True friends are hardto find
No doubt
That's true
This is special
No needto talk seriously
to an acquaintance
Only confide in atrue friend
Andwhenyou're withthe wrong company
It's betterto keep yourmouth shut
lfthe metaphysicalwayis notfollowed
then itbecomes atool
The harp is the
scholars' musical instrument
Ajarofwine freshly opened
Fornewfriends fromfarandwide
Throughthe clouds appears the dusk
Thentake a stroll inthe moonlight
We getto enjoythe delightful night
And drinkto ourhearts' content
Strangers from remote corners
become instantly close
Needn'tfeel apart
though it's ourfirstmeeting
Good
Yan Liben has also painted
the same picture
This painting is extraordinary
The old style with anewtwist
Depictingtheirknowledge throughthe pen
and expressing beautywiththe brush
Wang Xianzhi could
write a characterin one stroke
Lu Tanwei couldfinish apainting in one stroke
That single stroke is extraordinary
fromthe startto the end
Wang Xianzhiwas abetterpainterthan...
his fatherWang Xizhi
Wang Xianzhi's paintings
outranked his father's
Theywere both bettercalligraphers
than painters
The calligraphy ofthe Wangs
are world renowned
Certainly
The strokes ofWang Xizhi's calligraphy
are described
as beingforceful like
giants unseating mountains
a dot, like the peak, ahorizontal stroke
like athousand mile long
stretch of clouds
Some strokes are like the thunderstorms
The vertical stroke
like the dried up vine
to the unprecedentedforce ofhis strokes
Yet so enduringlybeautiful
EmperorLiang compared...
aleaping dragon and a sleepingtiger
Unprecedented
Indeed
Wang Xianzhi, also known as Zijing
took up calligraphy atage 7
Wang Xizhi predicted
Xianzhi's fame correctly
whenthe boyrefused his help
Looks like you knowtheirworks well
Notreally, onlythe general background
Butl have tried
to learntheircalligraphy
I've gotafew oftheirworks with me
The emperorloves the Wangs' calligraphy
lthoughthe's boughtalltheirworks
Not entirely
I've got copies of Zhuanghan scroll,
Fengju scroll
and most of all, Orchid Pavilion Preface
Orchid Pavilion Preface?
The one written inthe
9thyearof Yong He?
The one aboutthe gathering
at Shanyin's Orchid Pavilion?
9thyearof Yong He's reign
Wait, are you sayingthat
you've gotthatwithyou?
Of course
It's in myluggage inthe inn
lforgotto bring itwith me
ltmightnotbe the genuine scroll
I don'tthink it'd be necessaryto look
MasterPien Tsai
Look atthem andyou'll know
Maybe it's notnecessary
This is genuine
Of course, and so are the rest
These are all genuine
Maybe notforthe Orchid Pavilion Preface
lwouldn't showitto anyone else
Butl must showitto you
I'll getitrightaway
Wait
Hold on
I've also gota genuine piece to showyou
Calligraphy orpainting?
Calligraphy, 9thyearof Yong He
The one ofthe Orchid Pavilion
Orchid Pavilion?
Orchid Pavilion
Orchid Pavilion Preface?
Exactly
The one written inthe
9thyearof Yong He
aboutthe gathering
atthe Orchid Pavilion
Exactlythat
Butl've gotthe original piece
So yours mustbe an imitation
It's afake, lfear
Let's take alookfirst, shallwe?
It's an imitation, that's forsure
How canyou be so sure?
Look atthe colorofthe ink
Backthen, calligraphers would prepare...
sufficientinkforthe day
Theythrew outthe left-over
The inkstone was large and deep
Thick ink was used always
Evenforthe cursive style in calligraphy
Thick ink was used
evenforthe fine strokes
Look atthis color... so you see
That's the genuine scroll
Why?
Wang Xizhiwrote
the Orchid Pavilion preface
outdoors, notathis home
The preface was justa draft
The strokes were bold andfree
This stroke looks like
along stretch of clouds
Andthis one... seems like thunder
Andthis vertical stroke
like the dried vine
So this could be the genuine
No doubtaboutit
Mylate mastercherished it
He passed it onto me before he died
So itmustbe the genuine one
Inthat case, I mustmake copies ofit
More than welcome
Let's make three copies everymorning
We can worktogether
Excellent
Please
Master
The vegetarian meal is ready
lfyou could go to perform a ceremony
Almostforgotaboutthat
I leftmybag inthe study,
please unlockthe door
Sure
Master
Mayl ask...
I'm Xiao Yifromthe lmperial court
I'd like to meetthe viceroy
Please have a seat
The viceroyhas lefttown
What can I do foryou?
Please send someone to Yong Xin Monastery
And ask masterPien Tsaito the post
I've gotan important documentforhim
Is itaboutthe Orchid Pavilion Preface?
The Emperorwants to summon him?
No
Justtell himthat
a government official asks forhim
Tell him I've known himfora while
I'm a goodfriend ofhis
Agoodfriend? I doubtit
Since I've become
amonk ofthis monastery
I've neversocializedwith anyone
inthe court
Maybe you'll knowwhenyou see him
Is thatpossible?
Please come with me
Alright, lwill
Please
Sorryto have troubledyou
You're sentfromthe lmperial court?
Yes
I've been orderedto bring back
the original scroll
of Orchid Pavilion Preface,
please forgive me
I've gotitwith me,
nowl mustbidyou goodbye
Inthe12thyearof Zhenguan's reign
Xiao Yitookthe Orchid Pavilion Preface
from Pien Tsai
The emperorwas overjoyed
Yuanlingwas rewardedforhis plan
with 1000 pieces ofbrocades
and apromotion
The Emperorwas furious with Pien Tsai,
but...
he decidedto spare him because ofhis old age
The emperoreven sent over
fine gifts andfoods
Pien Tsaiwas terrified;
he couldn't eatanything
except congee
The emperorfell sick
duringthe 23rdyearof Zhenguan
On his deathbed, he toldthe prince:
I have afavorto ask
I've always loved
the Wangs' calligraphy, especially
Orchid Pavilion Preface.
Burythatwith me
Andthat's how the scroll
was buried inthe imperialtomb
The story doesn't end here
The tomb was looted
two years afterthe burial
Indeed amisfortune!
Also quite unfortunate forthe emperor
Here's more to the story
The Orchid Pavilion Preface
was destroyed?
Yes, burntto ashes
No, it's not destroyed
Then, you knew all alongthat...
Xiao Yiwas sentbythe imperial court!
I didn'tknowthat; all I knewwas...
The calligraphy copies he had,
belongedto the court
No wonder!
They've gotthe fake scroll
Then why didyoufall sick?
Who said I'm sick?
Thenforwhat?
I didn'twantthemto hassle me
Xiao Yi cheated me
forthe Orchid Pavilion
Nonsense
Pien Tsai cheated Xiao Yi
would be more likely
This is Wang Shizhen,
aMing dynasty scholar
He's waitingfor TangJingchuan
It's saidthatWang's father,
Wang Xuwas murdered
forhe refusedto sell
the famous painting...
by Zhang Zheduanto Yan Shifan
Afteran investigation
Wang Shizhen is certainthat
TangJingchuan is the mastermind
ofthe crime
But Tang has no ideathat
Wang is aware ofthe truth
He still acts as a close friendto Wang
Shizhen
Anynewnovels youwould recommend?
Which genre?
Adult
Erotic
I understand
There's one, butit's difficultto get
We'llthink of something
Nothing is impossible
The price is not of concern
What's the title ofthe book?
"The Plum inthe Golden Vase"
Goodtitle
The storyis better
It's unique
One ofit's kind
"The Plum inthe Golden Vase", on sale!
Wait
Hey
Couldyou showme the book?
Sure
What's allthis about?
Ximen Qing's family
takingthe 'healthy allyear'walk
Whatare youtalking about?
You're notfrom around here, are you?
Onthe 15th day ofthe firstmonth
It's a customforfamilies
to come outto take a walk
So that one'd be healthy
forthe rest ofthe year
This is called
the 'healthy allyear'walk
Walkto ward off all diseases
Walkto ward off all diseases...
Man lives long
Prayto ourHeaven
Getrid ofthe Starof Calamities
Getrid ofthe StarofMisfortune
Ghosts and monsters are all driven away
Happiness andJoy prevailthe yearround
The everturning horse lantern
The everturning horse lantern...
Man lives long
Firecrackers, firecrackers of all kinds
Scare away
whatevercalamities there maybe
And also all kinds ofmisfortune
The bonfire shoots high into the sky
Happiness andJoy prevailthe yearround
Here they come
Come look...
Look
This is Ximen Qing's wife Wu Yueniang
So that's her!
This is secondwife LiJiao-er
Who is this?
Thirdwife Meng Yu-lou
No.4 Sun Xueo
She's the leastfavored
PanJinlian is no.5
PanJinlian
Look ather
Atotal slut
Li Pingerh is no. 6
She was the wife of
Ximen's friend HuaZixu
And Ximen Qing has taken her
underhis arms
Who's this?
She's got smallerfeetthan PanJinlian
Who's that?
Lthought Ximen Qing has six wives
This is LaiWang's wife,
herreal name is SongJinlian
she was marriedtoJiang Cong
She married LaiWang afterJiang died
She's changed hername to Huilian
What's wrongwiththe shoes, Huilian?
So annoying
She's wearingJinlian's shoes
She borrowed apairof shoes from me
I didn'tknow
she wears them as overshoes
Ridiculous
Master
Huilian
Please invite them inside...
to have some snacks
Betternot; it's the newyear
It's unluckyto go inside a coffin shop
Mrs. Hua? Come on in
Mrs. Hua
Whatare youtalking about?
She's the sixth ladyLi Pingerh
Wasn't she HuaZixu's wife?
She boughthis coffinfrom me...
when he died
Am lwrong?
You're right,
but she's nowmarriedto the master
Ximen Qing likes widows
Wu Dalang's coffin...
was also purchasedfrom here
Then Ximen Qing married PanJinlian
afew days after
PanJinlian is his fifth wife
Look who's here
So Huilian's dad is a coffin store owner
His name is Song Ren, a despicable man
He checks outpeople's sizes
Whatfor?
To measure up the size oftheircoffin
Come by anytime
lthink he's checkingyou out, Jinlian
Please change the subject,
it's afestive occasion
Come here...
What?
Let go
Notin public
Ridiculous
It's late, ladyJinlian
You've still not slept?
Whywere youfooling around...
with LaiWang's wife?
Am I a criminal now?
Lfltellyourwife
you'll be in alot oftrouble.
Stand still!
You're such aladies man
Master
Buy some flowers foryourhair
Look atyou
I didn'tknowitwas you, master
It's alright
Stand up please
What's yourname?
Huilian
Huilian?
LaiWang's newwife
I heard
you have smallerfeetthan PanJinlian
Is that so?
Lwish lwere as lucky
Well
LaiWang's lucky
He's blessed
LaiWang
Whatis it?
The master's askingforyou
Couldyou give him afewmore days?
Is this ajoke?
He could have atleastpaidthe interest
Tell him he betterpayup soon
Yes sir
LaiWang, here's 500taels of silver
Go to Hangzhou
and buy some embroidered clothes
forMr. Cai's birthday presentand
Buy some new clothes foryourfamily
Yes, sir
Hangzhou is farfrom here
Willtake you around 6 months
forthe trip
Be careful onthe road
Yes, lwill
Fine
Hangzhou?
Rightaway, help me pack
The masteraskedyouto go?
Yes, hurry
LaiWang
Why are you goingto Hangzhou?
When wouldyou return?
Around 6 months
Whenyou're onthe road
Don'tforgetme
lwon'tforgetyou
Getme some powderand
embroiderykits fromthere
Yeah sure
Master
Getup
The masterasked me to bringyouthis
Materialforyourdress
Whatifhis wife finds out?
He will explainto her, don'tworry
The masterwill give you anything
ifyou please him
And his wife is
goingto the Qiao family gathering
He wants to see you
It's not convenienthere
You know ourneighbor
Dad has itall arranged
Tonight
Go to the Cangchunwu Room
atthe back garden
Butit's coldthere
As long as you have a warm heart
You do have smallerfeetthanJinlian
Why do you keep comparingthe two ofus?
What?
Nothing, I heardthatladyJinlian...
was the wife ofthe dwarfWu Dalang
Come on, thatwas like eons back
Whatare you doing?
Burning marks
How's that?
Howwas I comparedto ladyJinlian?
She's no matchforyou
Xueo
Letme tellyou
I sawHuilian withthe master
You should have seen her
Shameless
She's laughing atyou
Aboutwhat?
She saidyou seduced herhusband
Unbelievable
You're so cheap
Stupid ass
Don'tpretendyou're drunk
You've gotaproblem since you're back
Whatare youtryingto say?
Damn, who wants to argue!
Shutup
Where didthe material come from?
Whatmaterial?
Don'ttryto fool me, bitch
What?
You've listenedto thatwhore
Damnyou
Get out
You
Fine!
No wonderlwas sentto Hangzhou
Bastard
You've gotno evidence
Justbecause you're drunk
You have no rightto make a scene here
This is the evidence
Bullshit
Justbecause
I'm marriedto apoorman like you
I can still have rich relatives
Youthink I'm an orphan?
I'm notallowedto have arelative?
This is from my aunt
Bullshit
Damnyou
Someone sawyou
fooling aroundwiththatpig
Willyou confess now?
I hate you
you horrible man
Who's the gossiper?
Youwill die aterrible death
You stillwon'tadmitit?
Look atthese
Damn
Help
Shutup
I'm goingto kill him
I'm wronged
Master, ljustwantto informyou
So thatyou knowwhat's going on
Dangers inthe dark are hardto dodge
You betterbe careful, master
Ask LaiWangto see me this afternoon
Yes
Master, LaiWang's been here fora while
Tell himto getup
Yes
LaiWang, getup
That didn't count
So, I beatyou
You should be ashamed
LaiWang, here's 300taels of silver
Go and starta wine store
infront ofyourhouse
Just give me some interest...
everymonth.
Yes
Tryingto buyme off?
Keep them in a safe place
You betterwatchyourmouth
And it's his good intention
I don'tunderstand
Butl knowthat
you're fooling aroundwith Sun Xueo
What, have you seen us?
Don't do the crime
ifyou can't do the time
You're justas bad as others
You only see others'faults butnotyours
lwasJiang Cong's wife
Andyouflirtedwith me
Cheap cow
Huilian...
Whatis it?
LaiWang, you bettergetup
Yourwife is withthatman
They are inthe back garden
How couldyou sleep?
Catchthe thief
I'm LaiWang
I'm LaiWang. I'm no thief
Take him away
I'm wronged
Kneel down
lwoke up, mywife wasn'tinthe room
lwentto lookforherinthe garden
Why do youthink I'm athief
I'mtruly disappointed
Since you returnedfrom Hangzhou
I knewyou had atoughtrip
ltriedto help you outwith some money
I don'tunderstand
Why do youwantto kill me?
No, sir.
Itwasn'tmyknife
It's notmine either
Take back mymoneyfrom his room
Please, master
Why couldn'the just sleep
Why did he come lookingforme?
Got drunk and
couldn'tkeep yourmouth shut
You've offended many
You should have kept quiet
Look whatyou've gotyourselfinto
Nowyou're the thief
That's enough
Just getthe money
Whathappenedto the money?
The mastertriedto help me out
lwould neverdare to do such athing
Take alook
Master, a gentleman would neverdo that
It's obviously aframe-up
He came forme. Whytreathim as athief?
I kept oursix packages of silver
Butl didn'ttouchthem.
I don'tknowwhathappened
Please lwantjustice
No matterwhathe's done wrong
Justbeathim up
How am I goingto live afterthis?
This is none ofyourbusiness
He's been plottingthis
and he triedto kill me
I've gotallthe evidence
lfwe don't go to the police,
what's next?
Look, you sweatlike apig
Hurry, help to pick yoursister-in-lawup
Yuxiu, take herto herroom
Yes
Letme tellyou clearly
No one will bullyherfrom now on
Lai Hsing
Getmyletter
Take LaiWangto the criminal court
Yes
Please don't
Master, showhim some mercyformy sake
Please lethim go
Come on
Don'tyou knowhis temper?
He's angry atthis moment
ltwill pass
We can punish him here
There's no needto go to the court
What do you know, woman?
He triedto kill me, you're on his side?
Take him away
I'm wronged
I'm wronged... master
Please, help me
Don't cry, he won'tbe hanged
The masteris bewitched
In ourfamily
There's afox spirit
who's stirring up trouble
Don't cry
Theywon'tkill him
Speak
Please have mercy on me
Ximen Qing asked me to go to Hangzhou
Then he raped mywife Huilian
It's the truth
Please look clearlyinto this matter
You ungratefulfellow
Yourmastertreatedyouwell
He helpedyoufinancially
Not onlythatyou don'tappreciate
Youtriedto kill him
If allthe men are like you
Who willwe depend on?
Men
Yes, sir
Beathim up
Hurry, someone
See ifyou're stillwearing my shoes
Unlucky cow
Whatfor?
What's wrong?
His daughterHuilian, of course
Ximen Qing?
This is life
I don'tbelieve it
Soonerorlater
Justice will prevail
That's right
Bean curd? Overthere, help yourself
Let's pullthe plug
Little brats
Kids
Push harder
Harder
Addthe water, quick
Thanks
No problem
Careful
Hurry
Oldwoman
What're you doing?
What do you mean?
Youwere flirting
With whom?
Unbelievable!
Where's the cow?
Old Huang...
It's useless to yell here
Then whatare you doing
You...
Go to hell
Come on, Laoerh
Whatis it?
Hurryhome, lwantto talkto you
Hurry, look
Look, goodthings come in pairs
That's Zhou Laoji's cow
We betterreturn it
Whatis yourproblem?
We should return it
You're unbelievable
Astray cat ordog is a good sign
Astray pig is good luck
Astray cow? That'll bring afortune
Have youforgotten
Rememberourchickenflew ontheirroof
earlier? Andtheykilled and ate it
Forgood luck
Whatare youthinking?
Tonight, when it's dark
Let's sendthe cows to mymom place
And ask myuncle to sellthem
Then we can make some money
Thatwon'tbe right
Whynot?
It's allyourfault
Why didyou help them withthe cart?
There's no needforyouto help
The way you looked athis wife
Youwantto replace the cow?
Whatare youtalking about?
Lwantedto help
That's none ofyourbusiness
Well, youwere there too
So I'm notyourkind
I'm an outsider
Letme tellyou
Since I marriedyou
I haven'thad a good day
I've helpedyouwithyourtofu business
And I've eaten nothing buttofu
Andyou're checking out someone's wife
Backthen, myfamily
Enough...
What, so have we offendedyou, is it?
Backthen
Me and my sister
were the famous Qiao sisters
Youwere ugly
We were gorgeous
Look atyourself
No one was interested
No one lovedyou
Watch it
Letme tellyou
It's all because of
the matchmakeryou sent
She's good
She tricked me by saying
allthe rightthings
She tricked me...
into marryingyou.
You're so ungrateful
You don't deserve me
Neitherdo you
You have also arotten heart
You're atigress...
You're atiger...
What's withyoutwo?
Come on, prosperity comes with peace
Prosperity? We lost ourcows
Come on, let's look
I've looked everywhere
I've gotan idea
Go to the Little Fairy and ask
We're sure to geta good advice
Really?
He's good,
when my daughter-in-lawwas pregnant
He said she's goingto have a son
And she did
Right, Little Fairyitis then;
where's he?
EastMain Street
Rightinfront of
the Tiandetang Herb Store
Right
Tian de-tang
The Little Fairy, overthere
Is this the herbal store?
Yes, youwant some medication?
Atthe back...
Since this guy gothere...
Ourbusiness is in shambles
Gettingworse everyday
So unlucky
We should get some bullies
to kick him out
His godfatheris the police chief
Maybe we'lltry something else
What?
He's calledthe Little Fairy, right?
So supposedlyhe's the prophet
Ask him howmuch we'll make today
lfhe's bluffing and said 2 dollars
Then we'll have a sale
We'll saywe only earned 1 dollar
Then we can kick him out
forincorrectpredictions
Good idea
Let's go
Pick one
What do youwantto know?
Catch something
Catch what?
Something?
Well, not exactly qualifies as aman
An adulterer?
How do you know?
The characteryou picked has 3 parts
2 husbands, then a sun
Awoman can onlyhave one husband
She has one husband
The otherone is the adulterer
Can I catch him?
Lthinkthe possibilityis slim
It's more likely you'll lose...
than win inthis matter
Accordingto the characteryou picked
lthinkthe chances aren't good
Youwon't getanythingfrom it
Trustme
Youwon'twin
Damn
Oh, nowit's gotworse
Withthat stamping
You're goingto fall down
I doubtthat
youwould catchthe adulterer
Andyou're goingto trip over
Picking a characterortelling afortune?
Would like fortune foretold
Ohthe boss ofthe herbal store!
Excuse me
Little Fairy
We're neighbors,
lwantto know something...
Pick one
What do youwantto know?
Howmuch business I'll do today?
I'll move outifyou're right
We'll sellyouthe store
lfyou're wrong
thenyou move out ofhere
So youwon't give us more trouble
I see
Alright
lwon'tbe called The Little Fairy
ifl'm wrong
lthink you'll make 2 dollars today
Not one centmore orless
lfl'm wrong, lwon'tbe afortune teller
Two dollars
lfyou're right, I'll move out
5 cents formy service
Here's a dollar
Thank you
Is this the herbal store?
The Little Fairyis overthere
Thank you
What? Two dollars?
Zangqingguo?
Zangqingguo
Out of stock
Go to anotherherbal store
Yes, you go there
Tiandetang is gettingworse
They don't even have thatherb
Two dollars
What do youwantto know?
I lost something, will lfind it?
It should be around
Look underthe bed
Thenthe drawers, you'llfind it
The drawers?
The drawers, underthe bed!
I losta cow, mister
Acow?
Letme see
It's still around, don'tworry
Butyou've gotto take some herbs
Herbs?
I have to take herbs?
It's destined
Sure, anythingto findthe cow
Give me aprescription
No needforit, go into Tiandetang
And askfor2 dollars worth ofherbs
Thenyou'llfindyourcow
Remember, pay exactlytwo dollars
Sure, two dollars
Little Fairy
Two dollars
What do youwant?
Herbs, of course
Prescription?
Don'thave one
Anythingworthtwo dollars
Exactlytwo dollars
Today, we have...
abig sale
That's right
50% off
No, I can'tpay you a dollar
lwant exactly 2 dollars worth
Butwe have the sale
The sale?
Then I'll buy somethingworth 4 dollars
Butl'll give you 2forit
Sorry,
can't do thatwithoutaprescription
Tell me the name ofthe herb
It doesn'tmatter, the Little Fairy says
I'lltake anythingyou picked
Justlistento God's will
Sure, two dollars then
lfyou die, go lookforthe Little Fairy
Don'tblame us
Nonsense! Just give me the herbs
No, thatmuch?
What?
He'll die of diarrhea
Whatnow?
Lthoughtyou have a sale
Bettertake this in portions,
otherwise...
In portions?
If someone has my cow
Youwantto eatthe beef?
Whatever
Croton (laxative)
Who cares whatitis
Hurryup and...
Justboil itall
Ten doses will be more like it
Oryou'll purge to death
Just do as ltoldyou
Youwomentalktoo much
Hurry
Sure, fine
Whatis it?
Wait, it's still early
We should returnthe cows
What?
You're such a coward
You have to be tougher
Poison...
Are youtryingto poison me?
Have apiece of sweet
I can'tmix the herbs with otherthings
Fine, letme have it
What's wrong?
What's withyou?
Beans... Bean paper
Beans
Toiletpaper!
Hurry!
What's the matter?
C'mon quick!
What's the point ofthe pants? Hurry
Little Fairyis playing ajoke on me
Hurry...
Hurryup
Showme howyou move
You bastard, showme howyou move
lfyou have the guts
Move!
See ifyou could pull outmy cow
You bastard
Go on
Showme howyou move
Oh, that's him
What did he say?
He said, 'showme howyou move'
It's allyourfault
ltoldyouto sendthe cows back
Nowyou move them
You bastard, showme howyou move
Go ahead, I'llwaituntil morning
Showme howyou move
See ifyou could pull outmy cow
Go on
Looks like he has found out
What shouldwe do?
Any suggestions?
Ltoldyouto returnthem
Send both back?
I don'tthink so
Say, how aboutwe feast onthe small one
And send backthe big one?
Go on...
Laoji, the cow's back
The cow
Stop sighing
Happynow? Let's sleep
The Little Fairyis good
Where's the calf?
As long as the big one's here
Letme tellyou, you're still alive
you owe itto me
Whatare youtalking about?
The laxative you bought
lfl'd have boiledthem all...
You'd be dead
Howmuch didyou put?
Half
Half ofit?
Ltoldyouto boilthem all
No wonderthe calfisn'tback
Nota good match
I'llfix youwhen I come back
Just go
Have you eaten?
I'm stillwaitingforhim
Son of a gun!
What?
Myhusband
He betterdie outside
Mr. Zheng is away again?
Yes
He's gone to Baoding
He said he'll be gone foramonth
Whatkind ofmarried life is this!
He neverstays formore than 3 days
I've even gotto
fetch my own waterforabath
Poorgirl, Zhao
You help Mrs. Zhengwiththe water
Sure, letme fill inforMr. Zheng
Mrs. Zhao
Listento yourhusband
Don'tmake Mrs. Zhao jealous
He onlyknows howto brag
His name is Zhao Dezhu
Butyou can'ttrusthim
That's true
Myhusband's calledZheng Fucheng
He's quite useless
Come, letme help you
Don'tletme catchyoutwo inthe act
Zhao...
Don'tforgetto come back
I know
lfyou're like lasttime
Andyou didn't showup, I'll killyou
I know
Zhao...
I bettergo
Bitch
Be careful, I'm notblind
Whatare youtalking about?
What?
I know everything
Don'ttryto fool me
Youwomen are all so jealous
You betterbe careful
Listen
lfyoutry anythingtonight
Who is it?
It's me, open up
Zhao...
Oh no!
Who is it?
Mrs. Zhao, is myhusband here?
Whywould he be here?
Open up and letme check
Openthe door
Getin, hurry
Open up
Coming
It's strange!
Myhusband isn'there?
Are you kidding?
It's the middle ofthe night
Myhusband isn'there
Whywould he be here?
Then where is he?
Stand still
What do youwant?
What do lwant, huh!
Where didyou hide myhusband?
You've gotno evidence
Sure, I'll give youthe evidence
Why're you here to searchforhim?
You bitch!
Beatyouto death
You... you didn't go to Baoding?
To Baoding!
I didn'ttrustyou
How could I go away?
Why are you hiding here?
Looking stunned
You ask him
Whatis he doing?
Yourhusband
Okay c'mon, get out
Let's talkthis overathome
lwon'tletyou offthe hook
Whatare you doing here?
Inthe middle ofthe night?
Mr. Zheng is back
I came here justfora chat, you see
Shame onyou
You should be ashamed!
You lied about goingto Baoding
Whatare you doing slipping back here?
Calling me shameless;
You're stealing herhusband
You useless...
You...
Fine
Let's make peace
To hellwith peace
Shame onyou
Yourwife's sleepingwith someone else
Yourhusband seduced mywife
Shame onyou
Why are you blaming others
foryourimpotence?
Me?
How do you know?
LastDecember
Youtook me to ahotel
You did nothing all night
Justkept on heaving sighs!
I mean, itwas so frustrating
You bastard
You seduced mywife,
I'm goingto killyou
Little Fairy