[ Animal Panting ]
[ Man ]
YEAH, THIS IS A STORY
OF FAMOUS DOGS.
FOR THE DOG THAT CHASES
ITS TAIL WILL BE DIZZY.
DOG!
HI, MARCUS.
HEY, YOU.
YO, I LEFT SOMETHING ON YOUR
DESK FOR YOU.
OH, I GOT IT.
YO, MAN!
YO, MARCUS, MAN, WHEN
ARE WE GONNA HANG OUT?
WE GONNA HANG OUT SOON.
SLOW DOWN WITH THAT THING, BONY.
GOOD MORNING, LADIES.
[ Both ]
HI, MARCUS.
SO I'M THERE, RIGHT?
I'M LIKE THIS.
YO, I'M TRYIN' TO WORK.
* [ Humming ]
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
YO, WHAT'S UP?
I'LL SEE Y'ALL AT LUNCH.
PEACE.
OKAY.
GOOD MORNING.
HEY, STRANGER.
NICE TO SEE YOU HERE.
GOOD MORNING.
GOOD MORNING, CUTENESS.
HI, MARCUS.
HEY, HEY, HEY,
HOW'RE YOU DOIN'?
WHAT'S UP? HEY, MORNIN'.
MORNIN'. GOOD MORNIN'.
GOOD MORNING.
MORNING.
HEY, YOU.
HELLO.
GOOD MORNING, NOREEN.
GOOD MORNING, MARCUS.
HEY, DO ME A FAVOR AND SEND
A SINGLE LONG-STEMMED ROSE
TO CARRIE, TRACY,
MIRANDA, CASSANDRA, ALEGRA,
SHIRREL AND MAI-LAI.
WITH THE USUAL CARD?
YEAH.
"THINKING ONLY OF YOU."
RIGHT.
OH, YOU HAVE A MEETING WITH
LADY ELOISE TOMORROW AT 9:00.
COOL.
NELSON'S WAITING FOR YOU.
UH-HUH.
AND ANITA CALLED.
I KNEW I FORGOT SOMETHING.
WILL YOU GET HER ON THE PHONE?
SURE.
NELSON.
HELLO, MARCUS.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SHOW YOU THIS.
I'VE RECUT THE KISSABLE SPOT.
OH, YOU RECUT IT.
BUT IS IT SEXY?
IS IT SEXY? HA-HA-HA!
IT IS SEX-SATIONAL.
[ Nelson Chuckles ]
* KISS, KISS, KISS
KISS ME ONCE, KISS ME TWICE *
* OH, YEAH, OOH-LA-LA
* KISS ME
- [ Chuckling ]
- * OH, SO NICE, BABY
- OOOH!
- * OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH
KISS ME, KISSABLE *
* YEAH, YEAH, YEAH
KISS, KISS, KISS *
* KISS ME ONCE, KISS ME TWICE
OH, YEAH, OOH-LA-LA *
* C'EST SI BON, SO NICE
BABY, KISS, KISS, KISS *
* KISS ME
KISS, KISS, KISS *
* KISS ME, KISS, KISS, KISS
KISS ME *
* KISS, KISS, KISS
[ Chuckles ]
- I LIKE IT.
- GOOD.
I LIKE THE ORANGE,
AND I LIKE THE ICE CREAM.
GOOD. ALL RIGHT.
YOU GOTTA
GET RID OF THE CHERRIES
AND LOSE THE BANANA.
CHERRY AND BANANA? BUT THAT'S
A LITTLE BUÑUEL, A LITTLE DALI,
A LITTLE... YOU KNOW.
NO, THAT'S A LITTLE TOO OVERT,
YOU KNOW? WE SHOULD GO
A LITTLE MORE SUBTLE.
I THINK SOME WOMEN
MIGHT GET OFFENDED.
ALL RIGHT.
BUT I DUG IT. I DUG IT.
DON'T MAKE THAT
"HE DIDN'T DIG IT" FACE.
I DUG IT. JUST GOT A LITTLE
NASTY, LIKE YOU ALWAYS DO.
[ Laughs ]
ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
[ Chuckles ]
ALL RIGHT.
THE NASTY NELSON.
THAT'S ME.
AT LEAST THERE WASN'T
NO SAUSAGES IN THIS ONE.
[ Laughing ]
[ Intercom Beeps ]
YEAH?
[ Secretary ]
ANITA ON LINE ONE.
GREAT.
HEY, YOU.
NOW, DON'T BE MAD...
CAN I EXPLAIN TO YOU
WHAT HAPPENED? HAVE YOU
BEEN WATCHING THE NEWS?
OH, THEN YOU HAVEN'T
BEEN WATCHING THE NEWS.
THE BIG ACCIDENT IN MIDTOWN,
WHERE THE CABS BUSTED
INTO THE OTHER CAB...
AND KNOCKED IT INTO THE BUS
AND THE WATER MAIN BUSTED.
I WAS IN THAT. YOU HAVEN'T SEEN?
IT'S ON THE NEWS RIGHT NOW.
OH, JUST WENT OFF.
CHANNEL FOUR, JUST WENT OFF.
YEAH, BUT I WAS...
NO, I'M COOL.
I'M ALL RIGHT, YEAH.
MY NECK'S A LITTLE STIFF,
THAT'S ALL.
[ Laughs ]
NO, ACTUALLY, A MASSAGE
SOUNDS KIND OF FLY.
YEAH, I'M ALL WITH THAT.
OH, THAT TOO.
CAN I CALL YOU NEXT WEEK?
COOL. LATER.
[ Sighs ]
[ Intercom Beeps ]
WHAT'S NEXT?
CASTING FOR
THE BODY LOTION SPOT.
UH, TELL THE FELLAS
I MIGHT BE A LITTLE LATE
FOR LUNCH TODAY.
YO, MAN, I SAW SOMETHIN'
ON CABLE LAST NIGHT. FREAKED ME.
THERE WAS THIS WOMAN, RIGHT?
BABY HAD BO-DY.
SHE WAS LYIN' THERE,
TOTALLY NAKED, RIGHT?
YOU COULD SEE EVERYTHING.
BUT SHE HAD A DICK, MAN.
FUCKED ME UP!
IT WAS A-A 976 NUMBER
FOR HERMAPHRODITES...
YOU TALKIN' ABOUT 976-DICK,
"CHICKS WITH DICKS"?
- EWWW!
- [ Scoffs ]
HOW COULD YOU PUT SOMETHING LIKE
THAT IN YOUR MENTAL ROLODEX?
HE'S A CLOSET FREAK.
- YOU GOT PROBLEMS, MAN.
- YOU'RE COMIN' OUT!
- YEAH.
- NO, MAN, I WAS JUST,
YOU KNOW, KIDDING.
OH, MAN.
YO, THAT AIN'T REGULAR, MAN.
SEE, SOMETIME I FEEL LIKE
THERE'S A WHOLE WORLD OUT THERE
WE DON'T KNOW ABOUT.
LIKE THE SHIT
YOU READ ABOUT IN PENTHOUSE.
THAT NEVER HAPPENS TO ME.
MAN, STUFF LIKE THAT
NEVER HAPPENS TO ANYBODY,
EXCEPT FOR MARCUS.
HEY, THE ONLY REASON STUFF
LIKE THAT HAPPENS TO ME IS
I PAY ATTENTION TO WOMEN.
- Y'ALL DON'T PAY
ATTENTION TO WOMEN.
- WHOA, I PAY ATTENTION.
YOU HAVE TO WATCH THEM
AND STUDY THEIR MOVES.
GET OUTTA HERE, MARCUS.
- YO, I CAN'T DO THAT, MAN.
- THAT'S WHY YOU DON'T GET
NO PUSSY.
- EXACTLY.
- HEY, TYLER, THERE'S OTHER
THINGS IN LIFE BESIDES SEX.
COME ON. HOW ABOUT
SHARING, COMMITMENT?
YOU GOT TO GET IN TOUCH WITH
YOUR FEMININE SIDE, LIKE ME.
STARTIN' TO SOUND
A LITTLE ON THE SOFT SIDE.
STARTIN' TO SOUND SOFT.
- BORDERLINE BITCH.
- YOU KNOW WHAT YOUR PROBLEM IS?
YOU NEED MORE ROMANCE
AND LESS DOBERMAN PINSCHER.
THAT'S WHAT YOU NEED.
THAT'S TRUE. THAT IS TRUE.
YOU HAVE TOO MUCH DOG AND
NO ROMANCE IN YOUR LIFE.
WHOA, MARCUS,
DON'T EVEN TRY THAT, ALL RIGHT?
YOU AIN'T GOT NO ROMANCE.
UH-UH-UH, EXCUSE ME. EXCUSE ME.
I AM THE MOST ROMANTIC CAT
BOTH OF YOU KNOW.
- [ Groaning ]
- UH-UH-UH!
WHEN I MEET A WOMAN,
I AM FLOWERS, I AM CANDY,
I AM SOFT MUSIC.
- AND MR. MILK BONE.
- NO, I AM MR. ROMANCE
WHEN I MEET A WOMAN.
AND THEN ONCE I HIT IT,
I LOSE INTEREST.
BUT THAT AIN'T MY FAULT.
OH, SO, IN OTHER WORDS,
RIGHT AT THAT MOMENT OF ORGASM,
JUST ALL THE ROMANCE
JUST SKEETS RIGHT OUT OF YOU.
BUT YOU CAN'T PUT THAT ON ME.
THE ONUS IS NOT ON ME.
HI.
- HEY, HI. HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD. THANK YOU.
- WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
- I'M FROM HOLLAND.
NICE MEETING YOU.
NICE MEETING YOU TOO.
- BYE.
- BYE-BYE, CUTENESS.
I'M, I'M FROM DETROIT.
THAT SHIT MADE ME MAD, MAN.
BITCHES NEVER DO THAT TO ME,
MAN.
WELL, MAYBE IT'S BECAUSE YOU
CALL THEM BITCHES ALL THE TIME.
YEAH, MAN.
YOU NEED TO STRAIGHTEN UP,
SHOW SOME RESPECT. COME ON!
YO, MAN. EXCUSE ME.
EXCUSE ME, WAITRESS?
YEAH?
LOOK, UM, I ORDERED
THE DUCK, RIGHT?
YEAH.
WHAT VEGETABLE
COMES WITH THAT?
OOH, THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
IT'S SAUTEED ASPARAGUS SPEARS.
AND IT IS GOOD.
IT'S OUR SPECIAL.
OH, YES.
DELICIOUS.
THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
OH, GOD.
YOU'LL LOVE 'EM.
BYE-BYE.
THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
THANK YOU.
"THAT SOUNDS GOOD."
COME ON!
WHAT?
WHY DON'T SHE JUST COME OUT
AND CALL US JUNGLE BUNNIES, MAN?
- WHAT? WHAT?
- ASPARAGUS SPEARS!
IF WE WERE WHITE, IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN "ASPARAGUS TIPS."
RACIAL, MAN. RACIAL!
- OH, MAN, YOU'RE TRIPPIN' NOW.
- NO, YOU'RE TRIPPIN'.
DEFINITELY.
NO, YOU DEFINITELY...
* BOW-WOW-WOW, YIPPEE-YO
YIPPEE-YEA, BOW-WOW
YIPPEE-YO, YIPPEE-YEA *
[ Friend ]
YOU HAVE GOT TO PROCESS
SOME OF THIS ANGER, MAN.
[ Dog Barks ]
YO, UH, Y'ALL
EXCUSE ME FOR A MINUTE.
YOU NEED TO GET IN TOUCH
WITH TYLER, MAN.
SAY, "TYLER, I LOVE YOU."
WHAT? NIGGA, PLEASE!
GO TAKE A WALK.
[ Dog Barks ]
OHH.
I'LL GIVE YOU $20
FOR THAT LEASH.
TAKE IT, FOOL.
TURN DOWN THAT GOOD MONEY.
* [ Indistinct Singing ]
YES, BABY!
[ Marcus ]
KIRBY! KIRBY!
COME ON, KIRB...
[ Whistles ]
KIRBY!
DID YOU LOSE YOUR DOG?
OH, YEAH. I LOST A WHITE
SPRINGER SPANIEL WITH BROWN
SPOTS ON HIM, NAMED KIRBY.
REAL ENERGETIC, HAPPY DOG.
DID YOU SEE HIM?
OH, I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM.
I ONLY TOOK HIM OFF THE LEASH
FOR A COUPLE OF SECONDS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS HAPPENED.
KIRBY! HE'S LIKE
A FAMILY MEMBER
YOU KNOW?
OH.
OH, I KNOW.
I FEEL THE SAME WAY
ABOUT BRUTUS.
I LOVE MY BRUTUS.
I CAN SEE WHY.
DO YOU WALK HIM HERE
EVERY DAY?
YEAH, I DO.
COULD YOU DO ME A FAVOR?
MY NAME IS MARCUS GRAHAM.
HERE'S MY CARD.
IF YOU BUMP INTO KIRBY,
COULD YOU CALL US? AND I'LL
HAVE SOMEBODY COME PICK HIM UP.
OKAY. WELL, GOOD LUCK.
I SURE HOPE YOU FIND HIM.
THANKS.
KIRB! KIRBY!
WAIT. LET ME
GIVE YOU MY NUMBER.
'CAUSE I'M NOT GONNA
BE ABLE TO SLEEP UNTIL
I KNOW YOU'VE FOUND HIM.
DO YOU HAVE A PEN?
DO I?
[ Chuckles ]
I HAVE A PEN RIGHT HERE.
OH, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
BYE-BYE. BYE-BYE.
GOOD LUCK.
[ Dog Barking ]
KIRBY? KIRB?
KIRBSTER?
[ Woman Shouting ]
MARCUS! MARCUS!
I KNOW YOU HEAR ME,
YOU SLIMY, SLEAZY, SNEAKY,
SLITHERING SON OF A BITCH.
YOU WANNA KEEP IT DOWN?
GETTIN' READY TO HAVE
SOME COMPANY, OKAY?
OH, SO WHO'S
THE VICTIM TONIGHT?
YVONNE, I DON'T FEEL LIKE
PLAYIN' WITH YOU, OKAY?
STOP.
WHY DON'T YOU
JUST TELL HER THE TRUTH?
TELL HER YOU'RE GONNA USE HER,
THEN YOU'RE GONNA DUMP HER
LIKE YOU DID ME!
EXCUSE ME. EXCUSE ME.
I DID NOT DUMP YOU.
WE WENT OUT. IT WAS WHACK,
AND IT WAS YOUR FAULT,
AND I WISH...
LOOK, WHY DON'T YOU GET OVER IT
AND GO FIND ANOTHER MAN, HUH?
GET OUTTA HERE!
I HOPE YOU CATCH A DISEASE
AND YOUR DICK FALLS OFF.
OH, I WOULD EXPECT YOU TO SAY
SOMETHING CRASS LIKE THAT.
[ Doorbell Rings ]
DON'T FORGET I HAVE A COURT
ORDER FOR YOU TO STAY AWAY.
YOU AIN'T EVEN SUPPOSED TO BE
THAT CLOSE TO THE GATE.
COURT ORDER?
[ Doorbell Rings ]
I DON'T GIVE A DAMN
ABOUT NO COURT ORDER!
HEY. COME ON IN.
HI.
NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
NICE TO SEE YOU TOO.
[ Inhales Sharply ]
* [ Stereo: Indistinct ]
WOW. NICE PLACE.
THANK YOU.
WHERE'S KIRBY?
KIRBY! KIRBY!
OH, HE'S AT THE GROOMER'S.
HE GOT CAUGHT UNDER THIS TRUCK
AND GOT SOME GREASE ON HIS COAT.
OHHH. THANK YOU.
HE'S OKAY, THOUGH.
YOU LOOK GREAT. YEAH.
GOLD STAR FOR MARCUS.
DINNER WAS YUMMY.
[ Giggles ]
I NEVER MET A MAN
WHO COULD COOK SO WELL.
HOW'D YOU LEARN
HOW TO COOK LIKE THAT?
OH, WELL, YOU KIND OF
PICK THOSE THINGS UP,
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU'RE
ALONE AS MUCH AS I AM.
REALLY?
YEAH. SEE, UM...
MARCUS! MARCUS,
YOU KNOW YOU WRONG!
YOU NO-GOOD... MARCUS!
UH, LET'S GO IN THE LIVING ROOM.
WE'LL BE MUCH MORE COMFORTABLE
IN THERE.
[ Laughs ]
OKAY.
- COME ON.
- GIRLFRIEND!
GIRLFRIEND, HEY!
HEYYYY!
HEY! GIRLFRIEND!
WHOO-HOO!
KNOCK, KNOCK.
WHO'S THERE?
A SCARED LITTLE BOY
NAMED MARCUS,
AND HE'S JUST DYING
TO COME OUT.
HE'S BEEN HURT TOO,
HASN'T HE?
TELL ME ABOUT HIM.
TELL ME ALL ABOUT MARCUS.
WELL, I HAVEN'T
BEEN OUT WITH ANYBODY
IN ABOUT TWO YEARS.
NOT SINCE DEBRA. THAT'S
THE GIRL I ALMOST MARRIED.
UH, THE DAY OF MY WEDDING,
I WENT TO THE CHURCH
A LITTLE EARLY 'CAUSE
I HAD A BAD FEELING.
AND, UH, I GO IN THE BACK,
AND THAT'S WHEN I SAW IT.
SHE WAS ON THE GROUND
WITH THE BEST MAN...
[ Gasps ]
AND A PRIEST.
FREAKY.
YOU POOR BABY.
YEAH, THAT'S
WHEN I REALIZED THAT
YOU CAN'T TRUST ANYBODY.
YOU CAN TRUST ME.
I'M NOT READY FOR THIS.
I THINK I SHOULD
TAKE YOU HOME.
I THINK IT'S BEST.
[ Giggling ]
I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW HELPFUL
THIS HAS ALL BEEN, YOU KNOW?
GOLD STAR FOR CHRISTIE.
THANKS. YOU REALLY HELPED ME
IN... HERE. I FELT THAT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO THANK ME.
COME ON!
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO!
REALLY, I SHOULDN'T
COME INTO YOUR APARTMENT.
OH, COME ON!
OH, CHRISTIE, I SHOULDN'T
BE IN HERE, YOU KNOW, LIKE...
OH, MARCUS.
I'M NOT READY FOR THIS.
ARE WE BY OURSELVES IN HERE?
OF COURSE WE'RE BY OURSELVES.
COME ON!
OH, CHRISTIE!
MARCUS,
SPEND THE NIGHT WITH ME.
OH, CHRISTIE, NO.
IT'S JUST TOO SOON.
I CAN'T...
I JUST DON'T WANT
TO BE HURT AGAIN.
I WON'T HURT YOU.
PLEASE BE GENTLE.
YO, MAN, SO WHAT HAPPENED
WITH THIS GIRL LAST NIGHT?
MAN, SHE WAS BEAUTIFUL!
SHE WAS BEAUTIFUL,
BUT HER FEET WERE JACKED UP.
WERE THEY?
YEAH. OH, I PULLED
THE COVERS BACK...
YEAH?
IT WAS HAMMER TIME.
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN SOMETHIN'
WAS UP. HER SHOES HAD LITTLE
BUMPS ON THE TOP WHEN I MET HER.
BUT I THOUGHT MAYBE
IT WAS AN OLD SHOE OR SOMETHIN'.
YOU WOULD NEVER, EVER
THINK A WOMAN THAT FINE WOULD
HAVE HAMMER TIME IN HER SHOE.
COME ON, MAN. YOU DON'T
FUCK HER FEET. DAMN!
I HOPE I'M NOT OUT OF LINE,
BUT DON'T YOU THINK YOU'RE BEING
JUST A LITTLE BIT TOO PICKY?
YEAH, RIGHT.
WHAT HAPPENED
WITH TRACY, MAN?
GERARD, YOU MET THAT GIRL.
SHE'S NOT VERY SMART.
COME ON, MAN!
YOU DON'T FUCK HER BRAINS.
I'M LOOKING FOR PERFECTION.
HI, MARCUS.
HEY.
YO, MARCUS!
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
HEY, YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY
TO MEET LADY ELOISE
TO DISCUSS THAT MERGER, RIGHT?
HOW DO YOU KNOW
EVERYTHING THAT GOES ON?
I READ IT IN YOUR OFFICE
THIS MORNING.
HEY, MAN, YOU'RE NOT
SUPPOSED TO BE IN MY OFFICE
AND GOIN' THROUGH MY MAIL, OKAY?
NO, MAN, I WASN'T
GOIN' THROUGH YOUR STUFF, MAN.
HERE, HOLD IT UP, HOLD IT UP.
HOLD IT UP!
OH, YOU'RE GONNA READ IT
RIGHT THROUGH THE ENVELOPE?
I'M GONNA READ RIGHT
THROUGH THE ENVELOPE. IT SAYS...
"LUNCH TOMORROW...
AT HOULIHAN'S."
OPEN IT UP.
YEAH, "HOW ABOUT LUNCH AT..."
THAT'S VERY IMPRESSIVE!
TOLD YOU, MAN! TOLD YOU, MAN!
NOW, CHECK THIS OUT, MAN.
I'VE BEEN WORKING HERE
ABOUT NINE DAYS, YOU KNOW.
I'VE BEEN ON TIME
MOST OF THE TIME,
EVEN WHEN IT RAINS.
DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S ABOUT TIME
WE TALKED PROMOTION?
[ Laughing ]
MARCUS, COME ON, MAN.
I GET MY OWN OFFICE, MAN.
BRING MY HOS IN HERE,
WE HAVE A LITTLE PARTY,
SET THIS MOTHERFUCKER OFF, MAN!
MARCUS GRAHAM.
LADY ELOISE?
I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW EXCITED
YOU'VE GOT EVERYBODY UP HERE.
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE
LIKE A BREATH OF FRESH AIR.
I'VE NEVER SEEN EVERYBODY
SO EXCITED. IT'S...
LADY ELOISE?
I THINK YOU REQUESTED
TO SEE ME, MARCUS GRAHAM?
I KNOW.
MAY I HAVE A SEAT?
PLEASE...
KEEP STANDING.
THE REST
OF MY ADMINISTRATIVE TEAM
WILL BE ARRIVING TOMORROW.
HOWEVER, WHEN I DECIDED
TO TAKE OVER THIS COMPANY,
I CONSIDERED YOU
A PRIME ASSET.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WE NEED STRONG
DEPARTMENT HEADS...
TO OVERSEE THIS MERGER.
BEET JUICE?
OH, NO, THANK YOU.
IT KEEPS THE SKIN TIGHT.
AND NONE OF US
ARE GETTING ANY YOUNGER.
WELL, SOME WOMEN
HAVE A GIRLISH QUALITY
THAT LASTS A LIFETIME.
[ Laughs ]
I'VE ALWAYS HEARD YOU WERE
VERY BEGUILING TO WOMEN.
BUT MY SCHEDULE
IS ALSO VERY TIGHT.
MEET ME AT MY HOUSE TONIGHT.
TODD, SEE TO IT
THAT HE'S AT LAVENDER HILL.
GOOD EVENING, MR. GRAHAM.
GOOD EVENING.
LADY ELOISE HAS BEEN
EAGERLY ANTICIPATING YOU.
MARCUS GRAHAM,
LADY ELOISE.
MARCUS, DARLING.
[ Chuckles ]
WELCOME TO LAVENDER HILL.
LADY ELOISE, I CANNOT
BEGIN TO TELL YOU...
HOW HAPPY I AM
TO BE WORKING WITH YOU.
I GREW UP
USING YOUR PRODUCTS.
MY MOTHER USED
YOUR PRODUCTS, YOU KNOW.
IT'S LIKE YOU WERE
IN MY MEDICINE CABINET
ALL MY LIFE.
AND NOW I'M,
LIKE, WORKING WITH YOU,
AND IT'S VERY EXCITING.
[ Chuckles ]
I FIND IT VERY EXCITING AS WELL.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO A LONG,
STRONG, PRODUCTIVE RELATIONSHIP.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T WANT
TO BLOW MY OWN HORN,
BUT I'M REALLY QUALIFIED.
[ Laughing ]
YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE TO BLOW YOUR OWN HORN.
YOU SHOULD LEAVE THAT
FOR SOMEONE ELSE TO DO.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Snickering ]
[ Lady Eloise ]
MARCUS, DARLING!
[ Chuckles ]
[ Purring ]
WOULDN'T YOU LIKE TO GET
A LITTLE BIT MORE...
COMFORTABLE?
YEAH, SURE. WHY NOT?
[ Chuckles ]
WOULDN'T YOU LIKE
TO GET OUT OF THAT TIGHT SHIRT?
YEAH, I WAS JUST THINKING
ABOUT DOING THAT MYSELF.
YOU KNOW, IT'S, IT'S
A LITTLE BRIGHT IN HERE.
WOULDN'T YOU LIKE
TO DIM IT TO MAKE IT
A LITTLE MORE ROMANTIC?
[ Chuckles ]
OHHH.
[ Purring ]
COULD YOU GET IT
JUST A LITTLE DARKER?
* [ R&amp;B ]
- [ Elevator Bell Dings ]
- EXCUSE ME.
I'M SORRY TO BOTHER YOU,
BUT I JUST HAD TO COME OVER
AND SAY SOMETHING TO YOU.
YOU'RE BREATHTAKING!
YOU'RE THE MOST GORGEOUS WOMAN
I'VE EVER LAID MY EYES ON.
I HAD TO COME OVER
AND MEET YOU.
[ Laughing ]
I'M SORRY.
WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
I'M SORRY. IT'S JUST
THAT, UH, WHAT YOU SAID
WAS PRETTY PATHETIC.
THAT WAS NOT PATHETIC!
OH, COME ON. I MEAN,
IF I WALKED UP TO YOU
AND I SAID,
"EXCUSE ME, SIR.
I'M SORRY TO BOTHER YOU.
"BUT, WELL,
I JUST HAD TO MEET YOU...
"BECAUSE YOU ARE
THE MOST HANDSOME,
"THE MOST VIRILE MAN
I HAVE EVER SEEN...
IN ALL OF MY
ENTIRE LIFE, OOOH."
NOW, WOULD YOU BELIEVE ME?
HONESTLY, UH, YEAH, I WOULD.
BUT THAT'S JUST THE WAY I AM.
UM, I'M GOING TO WORK.
OH, OKAY.
OH, WELL, I'M GOING
THIS WAY TOO.
OKAY.
[ Laughing ]
HEY, IT'S NOT LIKE
I'M FOLLOWING YOU.
I'M GOING UPSTAIRS TOO.
I'M GOING TO THE 18th
FLOOR TOO.
OKAY, I'M SORRY.
YOU'RE AUDITIONING FOR ONE
OF THE COMMERCIALS UPSTAIRS.
YOU'RE A MODEL
OR SOMETHING?
NO, NO. I'M NOT A MODEL.
I'M GONNA GO WORK
FOR THE COMPANY.
REALLY?
MMM, MARKETING, YEAH.
THAT'S MY DEPARTMENT.
I'M MARCUS GRAHAM.
YOU'RE MARCUS GRAHAM?
MM-HMM.
THIS IS PRETTY FUNNY
THAT WE'RE MEETING LIKE THIS.
I'M SORRY.
I'M JACQUELINE BROYER.
OKAY. OKAY.
I'M A HUGE FAN OF YOUR WORK.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
YOU'RE VERY, VERY TALENTED.
YOU WAS TREATIN' ME
LIKE MY NAME WAS STANLEY
DOWN IN THE LOBBY.
TURNS OUT YOU'RE A FAN
OF MY WORK. I'M GONNA LET
YOU IN ON A LITTLE SECRET.
WHEN THIS WHOLE MERGER
GOES THROUGH,
I'M GONNA BE IN CHARGE
OF ALL THE MARKETING.
YOU ARE? MARCUS,
I'M AFRAID THAT THERE'S BEEN
SOME KIND OF MISUNDERSTANDING.
I'M SORRY. YOU SEE,
I'M IN CHARGE OF MARKETING.
[ Laughs ]
NO, THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
I'M SORRY.
[ Woman Sobbing ]
I'M THE LOGICAL CHOICE.
I'M ALREADY THE VICE PRESIDENT
OF MARKETING FOR CHANTRESS.
GOOD MORNING. THANK YOU.
YES, I KNOW.
BUT I'M DIRECTOR OF MARKETING
FOR LADY ELOISE, AND AFTER ALL,
WE ARE ACQUIRING YOU.
I HAD A VERY GOOD
INDICATION FROM SOMEONE
THAT THE JOB WAS MINE.
REALLY? FROM WHOM?
FROM LADY ELOISE.
LADY ELOISE. LADY ELOISE!
REALLY?
YES.
MARCUS, LADY ELOISE
DOESN'T MAKE ANY DECISIONS.
SHE'S... SHE'S
THE NAME ON THE PACKAGE.
NO, IT'S HER COMPANY.
THE LADY ELOISE, LADY ELOISE.
SHE HASN'T RUN THIS
COMPANY FOR 15 YEARS.
ALL OF THE DECISIONS
ARE MADE BY THE BOARD
OF DIRECTORS IN PARIS.
BUT IT'S LADY ELOISE.
SHE HAS NO POWER.
SHE'S A VERY SWEET WOMAN.
SHE'S A LITTLE DETACHED
FROM REALITY.
YOU SHOULD SEE THE WAY
SHE JUST, UH...
SHE THROWS HERSELF AT YOUNG,
HANDSOME, VIRILE MEN.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO IMPLY?
THAT I HIT IT? NO, I SEE WHAT...
MARCUS, DARLING.
HEY! HOW'RE YA DOING,
LADY ELOISE?
[ Whispering ]
I DON'T HAVE ANY PANTIES ON.
[ Mutters ]
LADY ELOISE, PLEASE,
WE HAVE A MEETING.
CAN WE JUST PLEASE GO?
[ Laughing ]
I'M SORRY.
IT'S WARM IN HERE.
JUST 'CAUSE SOMEBODY TAKE OFF
THEIR DRAWERS DOESN'T MEAN
THAT I DID SOMETHIN'.
* [ Indistinct Singing ]
SO, YO, MAN,
YOU'RE GONNA QUIT, RIGHT?
OF COURSE HE'S GONNA QUIT, MAN.
YOU CAN'T TAKE A SMALLER OFFICE.
STEP TO HER AND SAY,
"LOOK, GIRL, I'M OUTTA THERE."
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT
I'M THINKIN' ABOUT DOIN'.
THERE YOU GO!
OOOH! THERE SHE IS
RIGHT THERE.
[ Tyler ]
THAT'S HER?
[ Marcus ]
YEAH.
PSYCHE!
YO, YOU CAN'T QUIT, MAN.
YOU GOTTA STAY.
- YEAH, SHE'S BAD.
- HELLO, MARCUS.
- HELLO, JACQUELINE.
- YOU LOOK GREAT.
- AND SO DO YOU.
- THANK YOU.
THIS IS MY MAN TYLER,
AND THIS IS GERARD.
HELLO. HELLO.
THIS IS ANGELA LEWIS. SHE
WORKS IN OUR ART DEPARTMENT.
SHE'S VERY TALENTED.
I THINK THE TWO OF YOU
SHOULD BE WORKING TOGETHER.
EXCUSE ME, JACQUELINE,
IT'S THAT TIME.
GREAT. GREAT.
THANK YOU, TODD.
EXCUSE ME. NICE MEETING YOU.
MARCUS, WOULD YOU JOIN ME
FOR A SECOND? THANKS.
YEAH. COOL.
COME ON, GIRL, GET ON.
[ Growls, Laughs ]
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
I HAVE A VERY EXCITING
ANNOUNCEMENT TO MAKE.
SINCE 1948, THE NAME LADY ELOISE
HAS BEEN SYNONYMOUS...
WITH GLAMOUR, GRACE, SENSUALITY
AND STUNNING NATURAL BEAUTY.
IN THE NEXT CENTURY,
THAT TRADITION CONTINUES.
INTRODUCING THE NEW FACE
OF LADY ELOISE COSMETICS:
STRANGE.
[ Gasps, Murmuring ]
[ Murmuring Continues ]
[ Gasps, Screaming ]
[ Shouting In French ]
[ French Continues ]
VOILA!
[ Crowd Chanting ]
STRANGE! STRANGE! STRANGE!
YES!
MWAH!
COMMENT CA VA?
OH, MAGNIFIQUE.
CHAMPAGNE POUR TOUT LE MONDE!
[ Quiet Chattering ]
HEY. HI.
HI. HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD.
YOU LOOK A LITTLE BIT LOST.
CAN I HELP YOU?
OH, I'M JUST LOOKING
FOR JACQUELINE, BASICALLY,
IS WHAT I'M DOING.
YOU'RE INTERESTED
IN HER, RIGHT?
NOW, WHAT WOULD
MAKE YOU SAY THAT?
MOST MEN ARE.
I MEAN, LOOK AT HER.
SHE'S FANTASTIC.
I MEAN, IF I WERE A GUY,
I WOULD PROBABLY BE INTERESTED
IN JACQUELINE.
OH, IF YOU WERE A GUY.
NOT THAT I HAVE THOSE
THOUGHTS, BECAUSE I DON'T.
BUT I'M JUST SAYING
SHE'S ATTRACTIVE, AND I WOULD
PROBABLY GO OUT WITH HER.
I KNOW WHERE YOU'RE GOING.
YOU SEE OTHER GIRLS AND SAY,
"OH, SHE'S CUTE."
BUT GUYS DON'T SEE
OTHER GUYS AND GO,
"OH, LOOK AT HIS SHOULDERS."
WE DON'T DO THAT.
SURE YOU HAVE.
YOU'VE SEEN A MOVIE BEFORE,
AND YOU'VE SEEN A MAN
IN A MOVIE AND YOU'VE SAID,
"THERE IS A NICE-LOOKING MAN."
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE
HAVING THIS CONVERSATION.
I'VE GONE TO THE MOVIES,
AND I REMEMBER
I SAW BILLY DEE WILLIAMS
IN LADY SINGS THE BLUES.
HE CAME DOWN THE STEPS,
AND I THOUGHT HE WAS COOL. BUT
I DIDN'T WANT TO GET WITH HIM.
THAT'S A WHOLE ENTIRE...
HEY, WAIT A SECOND. I HAVE
SOMEONE YOU SHOULD MEET.
HEY, GERARD, COME HERE.
I MET SOMEONE
THAT'S PERFECT FOR YOU.
WHY DON'T YOU GUYS
COME, COME CHITCHAT? I'M...
[ Laughing ]
HI.
[ Clears Throat ]
GOOD EVENING, BOSS.
PLEASE DO NOT CALL ME THAT.
I WANT YOU TO THINK OF ME
AS YOUR COLLEAGUE.
SO TELL ME SOMETHING.
YOU EXCITED ABOUT
WORKING WITH STRANGE?
[ Laughs ]
STOP.
YOU KNOW I DIDN'T COME
UP HERE TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT NO STRANGE.
I CAME UP HERE
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT US.
I'M RAPPING. THIS IS MY
MACK-DADDY VIBE I'M GIVING YOU
IN ALL OF ITS SPLENDOR.
WHAT'S UP? YES!
OH, REALLY?
I MEAN, "ELEGANZA"
MACK-DADDY OF THE MONTH.
OH, I SEE. WELL, LET ME...
LET ME GET A GOOD LOOK.
CHECK IT.
LIKE JET MAGAZINE.
- WHAT'S UP?
- YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY WONDERFUL.
BUT I, I THINK THAT WE SHOULD
KIND OF MAKE THIS CLEAR...
RIGHT FROM THE START
SO THERE'S NO MISUNDERSTANDING.
YOU SEE... I DON'T DATE MEN
I WORK WITH.
WELL, THEN I QUIT.
YOU CAN'T QUIT,
BECAUSE... I NEED YOU.
NO, HON, WAIT ONE SEC.
YOU HAVE AN EYELASH
THAT'S GONNA GO IN YOUR EYE.
WAIT, COME HERE.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
HUH? YEAH?
YEAH, I'M FINE.
TRYIN' TO SEDUCE ME
ON THE SNEAK.
WHAT?
OH, THAT WAS VERY SEDUCTIVE
WHAT YOU JUST DID.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKIN' ABOUT?
YOU KNOW WHAT... OH...
YOU HAD SOMETHING IN YOUR EYE.
I SAVED YOUR EYE.
NO, NO, NO, NO. I KNOW
WHAT IT'S LIKE WHEN YOU HAVE
SOMETHING IN YOUR EYE.
I WAS A KID BEFORE.
YOUR MOTHER OPENS YOUR EYE...
YOUR WHOLE EYEBALL COMES OUT.
IT WAS NEVER...
LIKE YOU JUST DID.
COME ON NOW.
THAT WAS VERY SEDUCTIVE
WHAT YOU JUST DID.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
AND LET ME
ASSURE YOU OF SOMETHING.
WHEN I SEDUCE YOU,
IF I DECIDE TO SEDUCE YOU,
DON'T WORRY, YOU'LL KNOW.
YO, MARCUS!
HEY, WHAT'S UP, MAN?
YO, MAN, ME AND SOME
OF THE MINIMUM WAGE BROTHERS
DOWN IN THE MAIL ROOM...
WOULD LIKE TO KNOW, HOW LONG
DO YOU THINK IT'S GONNA TAKE YOU
TO BONE THAT NEW EXECUTRESS?
SEE, I NEED TO KNOW
'CAUSE WE GOT A LITTLE
OFFICE POOL THING GOIN' ON.
LOOK, THAT'S VERY CRASS.
MISS BROYER AND I
ARE COLLEAGUES,
AND I HAVE A GREAT DEAL
OF RESPECT FOR HER
AS A PERSON.
IT'S PROFESSIONAL.
TOTALLY PROFESSIONAL.
REMAIN PROFESSIONAL.
SO WHAT YOU SAYIN', MAN?
IT'S GONNA TAKE A WEEK?
NOT YOU, MARCUS!
YOU THE MAN! COME ON, MAN!
- I HATE IT.
- BUT THIS FRAGRANCE
TESTED VERY WELL.
JACQUELINE, I SAID I WANTED
THE ESSENCE OF SEX!
YES...
WELL, I THINK THIS IS IT.
YOU WOULD.
BUT LET ME SHOW YOU...
[ Gasps, Murmurs ]
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
- UNBELIEVABLE.
- THIS...
IS THE ESSENCE...
OF SEX.
VOILA!
[ Laughing ]
WHOO!
OH, LLOYD, COME ON.
LLOYD. WAIT, LLOYD!
WHO IS THIS?
LLOYD! HEY, MAN.
HEY, LLOYD.
[ Shouting Continues ]
LLOYD, LLOYD, WAIT.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT. HOLD IT.
COME ON, MAN.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
THE FRAGRANCE IS FINE.
NOBODY'S CHANGIN' ANYTHING.
THAT WOMAN DOESN'T
DESERVE HER OWN FRAGRANCE.
DO YOU THINK LIZ TAYLOR
WOULD'VE THROWN HER PANTIES
IN MY FACE?
YOU CAN ASK HER, LLOYD.
IT WAS A JOKE, LLOYD. IT'S...
HA-HA, HA-HA. I'M JUST
TRYING, I'M BEIN' FUNNY.
COME ON, HEY, LOOK.
COME ON, ALL RIGHT, LLOYD?
[ Laughing ]
OH, MARCUS,
YOU'RE A DEVIL!
BUT I LOVE YOU.
COME ON BACK.
[ Strangé ]
YOU MAKE ME FEEL RIDICULOUS!
IT IS MON IMAGE!
C'EST MON VISAGE!
ALLURE! AND YOU,
WHERE YOU BEEN, YOU?
I HAD TO GO...
OH, SHUT UP!
LOOK AT THIS!
THIS IS RIDICULOUS. WHY ARE
MY CONCEPTS BEING IGNORED?
I'M NOT A FOOL!
I KNOW WHAT THE PEOPLE WANT!
THEY WANT TO BE SHOCKED,
AND THEY WANT TO BE STUNNED...
AND THEY WANT TO BE JOLTED.
SO, I'VE PREPARED A LIST
OF NAMES FOR THE FRAGRANCE.
"WET SPOT." NO, SORRY.
I CROSSED OUT THAT ONE.
"LOVE PUSS." "PIG PUKE."
- "AFTERBIRTH."
- AFTER WHAT?
AFTER... BIRTH.
I'M SORRY.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID "BATH."
NO. IT'S ENGLISH.
B-I-R-T-H. BIRTH.
I WAS JUST MAKING
A DISTINCTION BETWEEN
"BIRTH" OR "BATH."
BIRTH, BIRTH, BIRTH! WHOO!
[ Strangé ]
THANK YOU, DARLING.
DON'T MAKE FUN OF ME, OKAY?
MY ENGLISH IS NOT SO GOOD.
OW.
"STEEL VAGINA."
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT ONE.
- YEAH.
- STEEL VAGINA. MARVELOUS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
[ Clears Throat ]
I...
UH, THOSE
ARE REALLY CREATIVE.
OH, THANK YOU.
BUT, UH, THE NAME OF THIS
FRAGRANCE HAS TO BE SOMETHING
THAT, THAT CATCHES THE EYE.
IT HAS TO INCITE PASSION,
AND IT HAS TO...
IT HAS TO BE ELECTRIC,
AND IT HAS TO SAY GLAMOUR
AND IT HAS TO SAY SEXY.
IT HAS TO SAY SMART.
IT HAS TO... IT HAS TO, UH...
WAIT A MINUTE.
STRANGE. STRAN... YOUR NAME
IS ALL OF THOSE THINGS.
YOU'RE-YOU'RE POWERFUL.
YOU'RE GLAMOROUS. YOU'RE SEXY.
YOU'RE INTELLIGENT. STRAN...
THAT'S WHAT WE SHOULD CALL
THE PERFUME! STRANGE! STRANGE!
STRANGE.
[ All Agreeing ]
STRANGE. STRANGE.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
I LIKE IT.
STRANGE.
[ All Agreeing ]
STRANGE. STRANGE.
STRUT, GIRL, STRUT.
GO ON, GIRL.
IT'S YOU, GIRL.
WORK IT, GIRL!
STRANGE, GIRL!
[ Laughing ]
YOU KNOW, UM, THANK YOU FOR
INTRODUCING ME TO GERARD.
WE'RE GOING OUT TONIGHT.
OH, NOW THAT'S
SOME GOOD NEWS.
THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
GREAT.
YOU REALIZE WE'RE NEVER
GONNA BE ABLE TO CONTROL
HER, DON'T YOU?
WHY WOULD YOU WANT
TO CONTROL STRANGE?
JUST LET HER DO WHAT SHE DOES,
AND WE'LL GET MORE COVERAGE.
STRANGE IS BUCK WILD.
[ Laughs ]
YES, YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
SO LISTEN,
WE'VE GOT THIS MEETING
IN NEW ORLEANS ON THE 24th.
ALL OF THE SALES REPS
ARE GONNA BE THERE.
MMM.
THERE'S A LOT OF WORK
TO BE DONE BETWEEN NOW AND THEN.
HMM, YEAH. OKAY, SO, WE'LL
HAVE DINNER OR SOMETHING
AND GO OVER IT.
MARCUS.
WHAT?
COME ON.
OH, STOP. HA-HO-HOLD ON.
EXCUSE ME. EXCUSE ME.
YOU'RE... WAIT A MINUTE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
IF WE WERE BOTH MEN,
WE'RE COLLEAGUES, WE COULD
HAVE A BUSINESS DINNER.
YOU'RE THE ONE FLIPPING THIS
INTO A MAN/WOMAN THING.
I JUST SAID DINNER, AND
LET'S DISCUSS OUR WORKLOAD.
THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
JUST DINNER?
JUST OUR WORKLOAD
OVER A MEAL.
WE'VE GOT
A HELL OF A LOAD.
OKAY.
DINNER?
DINNER.
OKAY, I'LL SEE YOU
AT DINNER.
GREAT.
* [ Soft Instrumental ]
[ Doorbell Rings ]
HEY.
HEY. YOU'RE HERE.
I WAS GONNA LEAVE.
I DIDN'T THINK ANYONE
WAS HOME.
OH, I'M SORRY. I DOZED OFF.
[ Chuckles ]
COME ON IN.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
YOU'RE ALL DRESSED UP.
YEAH, YOU'RE LOOKING
CASUALLY FINE TONIGHT.
LET ME GET
THAT COAT FOR YOU.
THANK YOU.
VERY NICE!
MARCUS, THIS IS A VERY NICE
PLACE YOU HAVE HERE.
UH, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU. CHECK OUT OVER HERE.
[ Jacqueline ]
THAT'S A BIG, WONDERFUL BED.
[ Marcus ]
YEAH, WELL, I NEED MY SPACE.
YEAH.
COOL. MUSIC.
- * [ Instrumental ]
- HAVE A LOOK AROUND.
YEAH.
GO CHECK OUT UPSTAIRS.
[ Jacqueline ] SO, WHAT YOU'RE
BASICALLY TRYING TO SAY IS,
MARCUS IS A...
[ Yvonne ]
A HO. HE'S A STRAIGHT-UP HO.
[ Jacqueline Laughing ]
HEY! HEY, DON'T...
HEY, COME ON, STOP.
HE'S GOT A SILVER TONGUE.
HE'S A NO-GOOD
BARKING MUTT.
REALLY?
NOTHIN' REALLY HAPPENED
BETWEEN US OR NOTHIN'.
COME ON. SHE'S CRAZY.
NO, NO. THIS IS
VERY INTERESTING.
NO, IT'S NOT. SHE'S BUGGED.
THIS IS VERY INTERESTING.
I AIN'T CRAZY!
HEY, GIRLFRIEND, GIRLFRIEND!
DON'T LET HIM DO IT TO YOU.
HE GOT A PLAN. WHAT-WHAT, YOU
ABOUT MY SIZE, HEIGHT, WEIGHT?
[ Scoffs ]
DOGGIE STYLE. DOGGIE STYLE.
I KNOW, GIRLFRIEND.
HEY, HEY, HEY!
I'M TRYIN' TO HELP YOU OUT.
YOU KNOW, IT'S A SISTER THING.
DAMN!
WOW! YOU LOOK GREAT.
THANK YOU.
YOU LOOK... NEAT.
- THANKS.
- COME ON IN.
- YEAH. THESE ARE FOR YOU.
- THANK YOU.
THIS IS WILD! MAN, DID YOU DO
ALL THE DECORATIONS YOURSELF?
MM-HMM, EVERY BIT OF IT.
I KNOW YOU THINK
IT'S A LITTLE WEIRD...
AND DON'T QUITE UNDERSTAND
IT, BUT IT'S REALLY...
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S ECLECTIC. YEAH.
ECLECTIC, YEAH.
SO YOU LIKE IT?
VERY INTERESTING.
WOW! UH...
OH, THAT'S A, UM, MASK.
A GOLI MASK.
I GOT IT FROM AFRICA.
NOW, THAT'S WEIRD,
'CAUSE I DIDN'T KNOW, LIKE,
AFRICANS WERE INTO HOCKEY.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
"GOLI" IS THE NAME
OF THE TRIBE. TRIBE.
- IT'S A JOKE.
- OH. HA-HA.
* [ Man Singing, Indistinct ]
YOU KNOW, THE SECRET
TO MY SALMON IS THE ROSEMARY
IN THE BUTTER SAUCE.
'CAUSE...
EXCUSE ME? YOU WERE...
YOU WERE SAYING SOMETHING?
I USE FRESH ROSEMARY
ON MY SALMON ALL THE TIME.
THAT'S WHY IT HAS THAT...
I'M SORRY, MARCUS.
MY MIND IS ACTUALLY
SOMEPLACE ELSE.
THE KNICKS GAME IS GONNA
START IN A FEW MINUTES.
DO YOU MIND IF WE EAT THIS
IN FRONT OF THE TV?
[ Laughs ]
NO, NOT AT ALL. SURE.
NO? GREAT.
[ Angela ]
OKAY, DO YOU WANT
ITALIAN OR INDIAN?
SO, LIKE, WOMEN
LIKE GUYS WHO JUST...
YEAH. DECIDE.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GONNA DECIDE.
I WILL CHOOSE,
UH... CHINESE.
NO.
OH, THAT'S COOL. I MEAN,
YOU KNOW, WHATEVER YOU SAY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
[ Laughing ]
[ Laughs ]
I'M BEING, UH, INDECISIVE.
YES, YOU'RE BEING
INDECISIVE.
OH. CAN I ASK YOU,
LIKE, A PERSONAL QUESTION?
SURE.
DO YOU LIKE KIDS?
I LOVE KIDS.
I-I PAINT KIDS.
SO, DO YOU WANT TO HAVE,
LIKE, A LOT OF KIDS
WHEN YOU GET MARRIED?
OH, I WANT A HUGE FAMILY.
AT LEAST TEN CHILDREN.
TEN CHILDREN?
MM-HMM.
THAT'S NOT A FAMILY.
THAT'S LIKE A AFRICAN VILLAGE.
THIS IS ABSOLUTELY RIDICULOUS.
ARE YOU WATCHING THIS?
THIS, THIS IS INCREDIBLE.
[ TV Announcer ]
...TO GET IT OUTSIDE.
[Announcer #2 ] MICHAEL JORDAN!
[ Announcer Continues,
Indistinct ]
I'M GOING
TO GET SOME ESPRESSO.
YOU WANT SOME?
HMM? NO. NO, THANKS.
[ TV Announcer ]
OH, WHAT A MOVE BY JORDAN!
[ Announcer ]
IT COUNTS.
HEY, LISTEN, MARCUS.
WHILE YOU'RE UP,
WILL YOU GRAB ME A BEER?
THANKS.
UH, ALL RIGHT.
I HAD A WONDERFUL EVENING.
THANK YOU. SO DID I.
YEAH, EVEN THOUGH WE
NEVER GOT TO EAT DINNER.
I KNOW. BUT NEXT TIME,
I'LL TAKE CONTROL. I'LL ORDER.
SO, NEXT WEEK, DINNER?
YOU GOT IT.
FOLLOWED BY HOT,
BUTT-NAKED SEX?
JUST KIDDING!
[ Laughing ]
I'M JUST KIDDING.
SO...
[ Clears Throat ]
NOW'S THE MOST DIFFICULT
PART OF THE EVENING.
THE KISS GOOD NIGHT.
YES, I KNOW,
BUT I GOT AN IDEA.
LET'S JUST COUNT
FROM FIVE BACKWARDS REAL FAST,
AND THEN LET'S GO FOR IT.
ALL RIGHT,
CLOSE YOUR EYES. GO.
OKAY. GO.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE,
TWO, ONE, GO.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
OOH. GOD, I'M SORRY.
I MISSED.
[ Laughing ]
GUESS I'LL HAVE TO DO IT
AGAIN, ALL RIGHT?
NO. NO. I'LL DO IT.
OKAY.
BYE.
GOOD-BYE.
GOOD NIGHT, ANGELA.
SEE YOU NEXT WEEK.
GOOD NIGHT. THANK YOU.
- BYE.
- ADIOS.
- [ Giggles ]
- ARRIVEDERCI. CIAO, BELLA.
BYE.
[ Speaks Oriental Gibberish ]
THAT'S KOREAN FOR, "I'M SORRY
I SHOT YOU, BUT I THOUGHT
YOU WERE ROBBING MY STORE."
[ Laughs ]
BYE-BYE.
WHAT AN INCREDIBLE EVENING.
DID YOU SEE
JORDAN'S LAST SHOT?
THE MAN MUST'VE BEEN
60 FEET UP, HUH?
YEAH, HE REALLY CAN JUMP.
UM,
[ Sniffs ]
WANT ME TO COME GET A CAB
WITH YOU OR SOMETHING?
NO, NO. I'M FINE.
BUT YOU CAN WALK ME
TO THE ELEVATOR.
OH, WHAT A TREAT.
YO, MAN, SHE A LESBO.
MAN, THE TERM IS "GAY,"
ALL RIGHT, TYLER?
ALL RIGHT.
JUST 'CAUSE A WOMAN
WON'T SLEEP WITH YOU DOESN'T
MEAN THAT SHE'S HOMOSEXUAL.
HEY, SHE'S NOT
A LESBIAN, OKAY?
YO, MAN, IT'S BEEN
ABOUT THREE WEEKS.
SO?
SHE'S NOT A LESBIAN, MAN.
YO, PERSONALLY, IF I WAS
DATING SOMEBODY THAT FINE,
I'D WAIT, WHAT,
EIGHT OR NINE MONTHS.
YOU CAN WAIT
EIGHT OR NINE YEARS,
AND YOU WOULDN'T NEVER
HAVE NO WOMAN THAT FINE.
[ Laughing ]
YOU WILD BOY!
BUT AT LEAST
MY LADY DIDN'T LEAVE ME
FOR NO DAMN GUARDIAN ANGEL.
WHY YOU DO THAT, MAN?
WHY YOU DO THAT?
I'D HAVE FUCKED THEM UP, BUT
THEY KNEW THAT KARATE SHIT!
HEY, COME ON, MAN. STOP, STOP.
YOU GONNA GIVE THE BROTHER
A HEART ATTACK. OKAY, SO...
BREATHE. BREATHE.
LET THE BROTHER RELAX, MAN.
I'M SORRY, MAN.
I WAS JUST PLAYIN'.
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHIN' THOUGH?
DID YOU BANG ANGELA YET?
WHAT?
AH, GOOD QUESTION.
GOOD QUESTION.
MAN, ANGELA AND I ARE JUST
TRYIN' TO GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER
ON A PLATONIC LEVEL, ALL RIGHT?
OH, OKAY. SO, IN OTHER WORDS,
YOU AIN'T HIT THE TWIZZER!
NOT A DROP.
TWIZZER? WHAT'S THAT? ANOTHER
ONE OF YOUR COLLOQUIALISMS
FOR A VAGINA, TYLER?
I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE GETTIN' AT, MAN.
YOU THINK JUST 'CAUSE
I HAVE A LOW SPERM COUNT
THAT I CAN'T FUNCTION NORMALLY.
BUT, SEE, I DON'T KNOW
WHY IT'S LOW. IT SHOULD BE HIGH.
YOU AIN'T SHOOTIN' NOTHIN'.
OHHH, MAN, WILL YOU STOP?
LEAVE THE BROTHER ALONE.
YOU SHOULDN'T
MAKE FUN OF THE AFFLICTED.
HE GOT A PROBLEM.
YEAH, HE GOT A "HANDICAPPED"
SIGN ON HIS BALLS.
STOP THAT, MAN!
YO, MAN,
A VERY WELL-KNOWN
DOCTOR TOLD ME...
THAT BY WEARING
THE PROPER UNDERWEAR,
MAN,
THAT WILL COOL MY TESTICLE
WALLS, MAN, AND THAT COULD
REVERSE MY WHOLE CONDITION.
OH, OKAY. WELL, LET ME
GET YOU SOME ICY HOT.
[ Laughing ]
OH, HOWDY DOODY. AT LEAST
I HAVE HAD SEX IN THE '90s.
AHHH! AHH.
"AHHH." WHAT'S THAT?
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M TALKIN' ABOUT.
YO, DON'T EVEN TRY.
YOU KNOW I GETS MINE.
OH, BROTHER, PLEASE.
HEY, LISTEN, YOU ARE
THE "NO-PUSSY-GETTINGEST,
TALKING-SHITTINEST" CAT I KNOW.
MARCUS, YO, DON'T EVEN TRY IT.
YOU KNOW ME... DE RIGUEUR.
AND ALL I'M SAYIN' TO YOU
IS THAT IF YOU AIN'T BANGIN'
JACQUELINE YET,
SOMETHIN' WRONG WITH HER,
MAN, OR SOMETHIN' WRONG
WITH HER TWIZZER.
THERE'S NOTHIN' WRONG
WITH JACQUELINE, AND THERE'S
NOTHIN' WRONG WITH ME.
IT'S GONNA TAKE
A LITTLE LONGER THAN I THOUGHT.
[ Takes Deep Breath ]
ARE YOU OKAY?
OH, YEAH, I'M FINE.
IT'S JUST THAT
THESE SALES CONVENTIONS
ARE REALLY BORING, YOU KNOW?
YEAH, THEY CAN BE PRETTY BORING,
BUT WE'RE GOING TO NEW ORLEANS.
HAVE YOU BEEN TO NEW ORLEANS?
NO. IT SEEMS LIKE IT'S A...
A SEXY TOWN.
YEAH, IT'S A REAL...
IT'S A ROMANTIC TOWN.
YOU KNOW? IT'S A KIND OF PLACE
WHERE YOU JUST TAKE SOMEBODY
THAT YOU LOVE...
AND JUST SIT BACK, RELAX,
THROW ON THE JAZZ...
AND JUST, JUST CHILL.
YOU KNOW?
MM-HMM.
THAT'S SOMETHING YOU CAN DO
WHEN JACQUELINE GETS TO TOWN,
YOU KNOW.
NOW, WHERE'D THAT COME FROM?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHERE DID THAT COME FROM?
WHO SAID THAT?
I THINK YOU SAID IT.
IT SOUNDED LIKE IT CAME OUT
OF YOUR MOUTH FROM NOWHERE.
I JUST... YOU KNOW, I...
I THINK YOU'RE COOL.
I LIKE YOU, AND I WAS
JUST BEING CONCERNED.
- ALL UP IN MY BUSINESS.
- I WASN'T TRYING TO PRY,
REALLY.
DO I LOOK LIKE THE KIND OF GIRL
THAT WOULD BE PRYING?
WELL, NOT FIVE MINUTES AGO,
BUT NOW YOU LOOK LIKE THE ONE.
IF YOU LOOK UP "PRY"
IN THE DICTIONARY, IT'D BE
YOUR PICTURE NEXT TO IT, LIKE...
[ Ship's Whistle Blows ]
* [ Jazz ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Laughing ]
AH, LOOK WHO'S
COOKIN' NOW! WHOO!
MARCUS! AAAH!
[ Squealing ]
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU?
STOP IT.
COME ON. WHAT?
STOP!
OKAY, OKAY, STOP IT, MARCUS.
I THINK THAT WE SHOULD GO HOME.
LET'S... LET'S GO HOME.
WELL, THAT WAS
PRETTY GREAT, HUH?
YEAH, PRETTY GREAT.
[ Laughing ]
WELL, YOU, UH,
YOU ENJOY THAT MINT.
I HOPE IT'S REFRESHING
AND CHOCOLATY.
[ Chuckles ]
MY KEY WON'T WORK.
SHIT.
HEY, MARCUS, WHY DON'T YOU
COME HERE FOR A SECOND.
I'M NOT PLAYING.
MY KEY REALLY IS NOT
WORKING, YOU KNOW?
[ Chuckles ]
PLEASE?
[ Panting, Moaning ]
* SPENDING TIME WITH YOU
LA, LA *
* FEELS LIKE HEAVEN
* LA, LA
* JUST CAN'T STAND IT, BABY
* OOH, IT FEELS SO GOOD
LA, LA *
* IT FEELS SO GOOD
* IT'S JUST LIKE HEAVEN
LA, LA *
* JUST LIKE
* JUST CAN'T STAND IT, BABY
* OOH, IT'S SO SWEET
* FEELS SO SWEET
OOH, IT'S SO SWEET *
* OOH, IT'S SO SWEET
* FEELS SO GOOD INSIDE
* JUST CAN'T STAND IT, BABY
* OOH, IT'S SO SWEET
* IT FEELS LIKE HEAVEN
[ Moaning Continues ]
* OOH, OOH
* WHEN I'M WITH YOU, BABY
* OH, SO SWEET
* LA, LA, LA, LA, LA
LA, LA *
* YOU MAKE ME FEEL
SO GOOD INSIDE *
* OHHH, AH, OHHH, AH, YEAH
[ Sighs ]
YES! YES.
[ Quiet Moaning ]
[ Car Horn Honking ]
[ Marcus ]
SHE'S AMAZING. SHE EVEN HAS
PRETTY FEET, THIS GIRL.
OH, YEAH?
HOW'S THE COOCHY?
MAN, THAT IS CRASS!
MAY I HELP YOU?
NO, WE'RE OKAY.
WE'RE JUST BROWSING.
HE'S TRIPPIN'.
YO, LOOK.
I'M A REALIST, RIGHT?
IF THE COOCHY'S GOOD,
EVERYTHING ELSE
FALLS INTO PLACE.
IT'S MORE THAN SEX
WITH THIS GIRL. I DIG HER.
YOU KNOW, HER SPIRIT
AND HER MIND AND EVERYTHING.
SHE'S BAD!
SHE COULD BE MRS. GRAHAM.
[ Gerard ] OH, YEAH?
YOU THINK I'M JOKIN'.
SHE'S THAT BAD, MAN.
[ Laughing ]
MARCUS IS IN LOVE.
YO! YO, I'M GETTIN' THIS,
MARCUS. STEP OFF.
THAT JACKET IS $1,800.
NO REFUNDS.
WHAT, YOU THINK
I CAN'T PAY FOR IT?
WELL, THERE IS
NO LAYAWAY PLAN.
HEY, WE'RE OKAY.
WE DON'T NEED ANY HELP.
WE DON'T KEEP CASH
IN THE STORE.
HE'S A SUCKER, MAN.
DON'T EVEN TRIP ON THAT.
RACIAL...
YEAH, YOU RIGHT, MAN.
DON'T EVEN TRIP ON THAT.
WAIT. NO REFUND?
WHAT'S HE THINK? WE GONNA
TAKE THE JACKET, WEAR IT,
STANK IT ALL UP
TO BE DAMNED AND THEN,
LIKE, GIVE IT BACK TO HIM?
WE CAN'T GET OVER THIS...
THERE'S A CERTAIN
GROUP OF PEOPLE...
WITH A NATURAL FEAR
OF BLACK PEOPLE.
THEY'RE PROGRAMMED,
YOU KNOW? LIKE, WATCH.
NOW!
SEE HOW FRIGHTENED HE WAS,
JUST FROM A BLACK MAN
SCREAMING "NOW" AT HIM?
[ Angela ]
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
[ Jacqueline ]
PEOPLE ARE GONNA LOVE THIS.
YOU THINK SO?
YES, I REALLY DO.
I THINK THIS IS GONNA BE
GREAT FOR HER IMAGE.
LOOK AT THIS ONE.
OH, ANGELA! WOW.
[ Laughs ]
YOU LIKE IT? REALLY?
YES, I LIKE IT.
I LIKE IT A LOT.
GREAT. THANK YOU.
GUESS WHAT.
MARCUS THINKS WE OUGHTA GO
TO THE CARIBBEAN TO SHOOT THIS.
- THE CARIBBEAN?
- MM-HMM.
THAT'S EXPENSIVE.
I KNOW.
BUT IT'S NICE.
NO, IT'S A NICE IDEA.
- WELL, YOU KNOW MARCUS
AND HIS BIG IDEAS.
- I DO.
YOU KNOW,
SPEAKING OF MARCUS, UM,
I HEAR HE'S GOT
A REAL... REPUTATION.
UH-HUH. BONY-T
TOLD YOU THAT, RIGHT?
[ Laughing ]
WELL, ANGELA...
I CAN CONFIRM THAT
MARCUS'S REPUTATION...
IS EXTREMELY
WELL-DESERVED.
YOU CAN CONFIRM IT?
LIKE, YOU AND MARCUS HAVE...
OH, GOD, THIS MAN...
HE'S WONDERFUL.
I MEAN, HE'S KIND OF...
OH, HE'S MAGNIFICENT.
AND HE JUST HAPPENS TO HAVE
THE BEST ASS I HAVE EVER SEEN.
HEY, BABY, YOU GOT A SEC?
MARCUS, HI.
OH, GOD.
HI.
[ Both Laughing ]
WHAT DID I WALK IN ON?
WHAT ARE Y'ALL TALKIN' ABOUT?
WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT WORK.
WORK.
YOU'RE BOTH BLUSHING.
SOMETHING IS UP. WHAT'S UP?
- ART. ART.
- IT'S A GIRL ISSUE. WHAT'S UP?
COME ON, TALK TO ME.
OH, GOD.
GIRLINESS.
NOTHING. NOTHING.
WHY YOU LEAVIN'?
IT'S GERARD.
IT'S TIME TO GO.
NO, GERARD HIT IT,
DIDN'T HE?
NO, NO. HIT IT?
GERARD COULD NOT HIT IT
IF HE HAD A BAT, OKAY?
OH, YOU WANT TO
KEEP IT A SECRET, HUH?
BUT YOU KNOW HE HIT IT.
IT'S GERARD, ISN'T IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
OH, HAVE YOUR LITTLE SECRETS.
THAT'S NOT WHY I CAME HERE.
I CAME HERE TO TELL YOU...
WHAT A WONDERFUL TIME...
I HAD IN NEW ORLEANS.
MARCUS, HON,
I DON'T THINK THAT WE SHOULD
DO THIS IN THE OFFICE.
- WHAT? STOP BUGGIN'.
- [ Mumbles, Indistinct ]
WHY DON'T WE GET ON TOP
OF THE DESK AND GET FRISKY
AND GO CRAZY, YOU KNOW?
UM... LISTEN.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING SERIOUS
ON ME, ARE YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKIN' ABOUT,
AM I GETTING SERIOUS?
WHAT IS THAT?
WELL, YOU KNOW.
WHERE YOU WANT THIS TO GROW
INTO A RELATIONSHIP,
WHERE, GOD, WE'RE
TOGETHER ALL THE TIME...
AND STUFF LIKE THAT,
ARE YOU?
EXCUSE ME.
[ Chuckles ]
I KNOW THAT YOU'RE NOT
TELLING ME THAT NEW ORLEANS
WAS A FLING.
NO. NO. NO.
I HAD A GREAT TIME
IN NEW ORLEANS.
- YOU KNOW I HAD A GREAT TIME.
- SO WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
WELL, I JUST THINK THAT
NEW ORLEANS WAS NEW ORLEANS,
AND WE SHOULD
LEAVE IT AT THAT.
[ Chuckles ]
OH, IT'S NOT LIKE I'M TRYIN'
TO PRESSURE YOU OR ANYTHING.
OH, NO.
NO. NO, NO, NO.
I'M NOT PROPOSING
OR ANYTHING.
OF COURSE NOT.
MY TUXEDO WASN'T IRONED
OR NOTHIN' LIKE THAT,
YOU KNOW.
I BELIEVE IN TAKIN' THINGS
SLOW TOO.
EXACTLY. THAT'S
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
I WAS JUST WONDERING
WHEN WE COULD SEE EACH OTHER
AGAIN, THAT'S ALL.
[ Sighs ]
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M KINDA BUSY RIGHT NOW.
I JUST FOUND OUT THAT I'M
GONNA HAVE TO BE SPENDING
A LOT OF TIME OUT OF TOWN,
SO I'LL GET BACK
TO YOU, OKAY?
YOU'LL GET BACK TO ME?
[ Chuckles ]
I DON'T HAVE MY SCHEDULE.
MY SECRETARY'S OUT OF TOWN.
HE WON SOME KIND OF OFFICE
POOL, SO... I'LL CALL YOU.
"MARCUS, WITH REGARDS
TO US DOING IT AGAIN,
I'LL GET BACK TO YOU."
THAT'S A...
THAT'S A NEW ONE ON MARCUS.
WELL, UH, JUST DON'T
MAKE ME WAIT TOO LONG,
'CAUSE IT'S NOT LIKE I GOTTA
SIT BY THE TELEPHONE TO WAIT
FOR SOMEBODY TO GET BACK TO ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
NO. NO. I REALIZE...
THAT YOU OF ALL PEOPLE
WILL NOT BE WAITING ALONE,
SO I WILL TRY
AND GET BACK TO YOU SOON.
YOU'RE GONNA CALL ME,
RIGHT?
[ Phone Rings ]
HELLO? YES? YES?
[ Man On Phone ]
HELLO? MR. GRAHAM?
YES. YES.
MISS BROYER HAS ASKED ME
TO TELL YOU THAT SHE IS FREE
THE EVENING OF THE 12th.
THE 12th
IS THREE WEEKS FROM NOW!
SORRY. THAT'S
HER FIRST OPENING.
SHOULD I PENCIL YOU IN?
YEAH. UH, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
[ Lady Eloise's Voice ]
MARCUS!
* BOW-WOW-WOW
YIPPEE-YO, YIPPEE-YEA *
* BOW-WOW
YIPPEE-YO, YIPPEE, YEA *
* BOW-WOW-WOW
YIPPEE-YO, YIPPEE-YEA *
* BOW-WOW
YIPPEE-YO, YIPPEE, YEA *
YO, BROTHER, MAN,
GOLD WATCHES, GOLD CHAINS.
YO, BROTHER,
YOU GOTTA SHOW SOME GOLD
TO GET THAT GIRL.
I'M COOL, Y'ALL.
I ALREADY HAVE A WATCH.
BUT THANK YOU. GUCCI.
BROTHER,
THAT'S A NICE WATCH!
THANK YOU.
WATCH YOUR BACK.
[ Car Horn Honking,
Siren Wailing ]
I'M GONNA CHECK YOU OUT AFTER.
CAN YOU TELL ME
WHAT TIME THE SHOW STARTS?
[ Woman Shouting, Indistinct ]
OF COURSE I AM.
BROTHER, PLEASE.
I JUST WANNA KNOW WHAT TIME
THE SHOW STARTS.
HOLD ON FOR A SECOND.
WHAT?
[ Mimicking
Hearing-Impaired Speech ]
WHAT TIME DOES THE SHOW START?
THE SHOW STARTED
A HALF AN HOUR AGO.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
YOU'RE VERY GOOD
AT THIS JOB.
I KNOW THIS.
SOME PUNK-ASS NIGGA.
YEAH. HI. WHAT TIME
DOES FLIGHT 97 FROM TORONTO
GET IN?
THREE HOURS AGO?
OKAY, WAS THERE
A JACQUELINE BROYER
ON THE PLANE?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, YOU CAN'T
GIVE OUT THAT INFORMATION? THIS
IS FLIGHT INFORMATION, RIGHT?
THEN WHY DO YOU
CALL IT "FLIGHT INF..."
FORGET IT. FORGET IT. THANK YOU.
[ Thunderclaps ]
CAN YOU CHECK TO SEE
IF THERE HAVE BEEN ANY ACCIDENTS
BETWEEN JFK AND MIDTOWN?
WHAT THE HELL IS 911 FOR?
WELL, I WANNA TALK
TO A SUPERVISOR.
[ Phone Beeps Off ]
- HELLO.
- OH, YOU FINALLY DECIDED
TO SHOW UP.
I HAD SOME MEETINGS
THAT RAN OVER, SO I HAD
TO TAKE A LATER FLIGHT.
YOU CAN'T
PICK UP A TELEPHONE
AND CALL SOMEBODY, RIGHT?
WELL, I WOULD'VE CALLED,
MARCUS, BUT THEY DIDN'T
HAVE A PHONE ON THE PLANE.
I WASTED $200 ON TICKETS...
JUST WASTED... AND IT'S
ALL YOUR FAULT, OKAY?
I'M SORRY. LISTEN,
WHY DON'T I JUST GIVE YOU
THE MONEY FOR THE TICKETS?
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH THE MONEY, OKAY?
YOU'RE BEING INCONSIDERATE.
YOU DIDN'T CALL ME. YOU DIDN'T
DO ANYTHING... I WAS CALLING
ALL OVER NEW YORK FOR YOU.
- YOU COULD'VE BEEN LAYIN' ON
THE SIDE OF THE ROAD SOMEWHERE.
- THAT'S VERY SWEET, VERY SWEET.
ONE OF MY TRICKS, OKAY?
I KNOW THE FLOWER THING.
LISTEN. I'M UPSET WITH YOU.
WHAT YOU DID WAS INCONSIDERATE,
AND I'M UPSET.
WELL, MAYBE
I SHOULD JUST GO.
YEAH, I'LL GO.
WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
LISTEN. LOOK, LOOK.
I HAD A LONG DAY.
YOU'VE HAD A LONG DAY.
AND I'M GETTIN'...
I'M TRIPPIN'. I'M BUGGIN' OUT,
AND MAYBE I'M GOIN' OVERBOARD.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
GO DRY OFF, AND LET'S
PUT THIS WHOLE THING BEHIND US?
LET'S SQUASH THIS WHOLE THING.
SO DOES THIS MEAN
THAT YOU FORGIVE ME?
THIS MEANS THAT I AM
BEING A BIT EMOTIONAL,
AND I ACKNOWLEDGE THAT.
WE SHOULD JUST SQUASH IT.
WELL, I THINK
IT MEANS YOU FORGIVE ME.
HMM?
- YOU DIDN'T HAVE NO CLOTHES ON
UNDERNEATH THE COAT.
- NO.
[ Chuckles ]
YOU'RE TOO MUCH.
SO YOU KNEW YOU WAS WRONG.
THAT'S WHY YOU CAME OVER
IN YOUR DRAWERS,
'CAUSE YOU KNOW
THAT WASN'T RIGHT.
JACQUELINE, JACQUELINE,
JACQUELINE.
[ Moaning ]
[ Both Mumbling,
Indistinct ]
WHOSE IS IT, HUH?
WHOSE IS IT?
IT'S YOURS. IT'S YOURS.
MMM. AAH, AAH.
MMM.
OH, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
I DON'T WANNA COME YET.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
[ Marcus: Prolonged Moan ]
OH, YEAH!
OH, YES! OH!
[ Toes Crack ]
WHOO!
[ Quavering ]
MM, MM-HMM.
WAIT, WAIT. HOLD. HOLD.
NO, NO. WAIT. DON'T DO NOTHIN'.
DON'T DO THAT.
[ Sighs ]
FFFFFFFFFF...
[ Continues ]
DON'T YOU SAY NOTHIN'. DON'T
SAY NOTHIN'. DON'T DO NOTHIN'.
NO. DON'T TOUCH ME.
DON'T TOUCH ME.
DON'T MOVE.
DON'T DO NOTHIN'.
JUST HOLD STILL.
WHOA, WHOA. HOLD IT.
NO. HOLD ON!
SWEET GOD. HOLD ON.
OH, SHIT.
[ Yells, Stifles Yell ]
[ Humming ]
YOU KNEW THAT I WAS COMING.
YOU KNEW I WAS.
[ Mumbling ]
I HAVE TO CALL MY MOTHER.
WHERE YOU GOIN'?
HOME. I HAVE TO GIVE
A SPEECH IN THE MORNING
TO THE BOARD OF DIRECTORS.
BUT THANK YOU.
YOU WERE GREAT.
GOD, MARCUS, I WAS SO TENSE
WHEN I GOT OFF THE PLANE,
BUT YOU REALLY RELAXED ME.
SO, MR. GRAHAM,
THANK YOU.
YOU REALLY HAVE TO GO?
MM-HMM.
I'LL CALL YOU
SOMETIME TOMORROW, OKAY?
GET SOME SLEEP.
CALL ME.
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
* OH, I MUST BE TOTALLY GONE
* COMPLETELY OUT OF MY MIND
* [ Continues, Indistinct ]
[ Chattering,
Laughter ]
- WOULD ANYONE CARE
FOR SOME DESSERT?
- UH, YEAH. I'LL HAVE TIRAMISU.
I JUST
WANT SOME COFFEE.
AND FOR THE LADY?
I AM ON A DIET.
VERY GOOD.
DIET? DIET,
"SCHMIET."
WHAT, ARE YOU CRAZY?
YOU LOOK GREAT. I CAN'T WAIT TO
GET YOU DOWN TO THE CARIBBEAN.
- I'M NOT SURE I'M GOING.
- WELL, YOU'VE GOTTA GO.
MARCUS HAS
PLANNED A WONDERFUL TRIP.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE A LOT OF FUN.
YEAH. I'M GONNA
MAKE A PHONE CALL, ALL RIGHT?
GO MAKE A PHONE CALL.
HEY. LISTEN.
I KNOW YOU'RE A LITTLE CONCERNED
ABOUT HOW THE LAYOUT WAS GONNA
BE, BUT I'M PICTURING YOU...
ON THESE BEAUTIFUL
WHITE-SAND BEACHES, RIGHT,
AND THESE POWDER-BLUE SKIES.
CRYSTAL BEAUTIFUL WATER.
YOU STAND IN THE MIDDLE OF ALL
OF THIS, LOOKIN' BREATHTAKIN'.
SO, WHEN ARE WE GONNA FUCK?
- WHAT?
- WELL, ACCORDING
TO JACQUELINE,
YOU ARE REALLY GREAT IN BED.
OH, JACQUELINE TOLD YOU
I WAS REALLY GOOD IN BED?
ACCORDING TO JACQUELINE,
YOU REALLY KNOW HOW
TO MOVE YOUR ASS, YOU KNOW?
[ Sucks Teeth ]
OH, SHE TOLD YOU I KNOW
HOW TO MOVE MY ASS IN BED?
OKAY. OKAY.
UH, WELL, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
MISS JACQUELINE HAS TOLD YOU,
BUT IT'S NOT THAT KIND OF PARTY,
AND I'D APPRECIATE IT IF...
- HEY, WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU? STOP THAT!
- [ Growls ]
STOP. STOP IT.
WILL YOU STOP IT?
GET OUT OF HERE!
MERDE! MAN,
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
YOU ARE GOING TO
TURN DOWN A PUSSY LIKE THIS?
STARING YOU SMACK IN YOUR FACE?
NO MAN CAN TURN DOWN THIS PUSSY.
WILL YOU STOP?
I DON'T KNOW ANY MAN
THAT CAN REFUSE THIS PUSSY.
STOP SAYING "PUSSY."
PEOPLE ARE EATING IN HERE.
PUSSY.
PUSSY, PUSSY, PUSSY!
PUSSY, PUS-PUS-PUSSY.
TRYING TO FIND OUR CAT.
WHERE IS THAT CAT?
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
STOP SAYING THAT.
YOU DON'T LIKE WOMEN?
YES, THAT'S IT.
I DON'T LIKE WOMEN.
I'M GAY.
YOU'RE NOT GAY.
- YOU'RE NOT GAY. YOU JUST
DON'T WANT TO FUCK ME!
- [ Onlookers Gasping ]
I KNOW A GAY MAN WHEN I SEE ONE.
I KNOW WHAT A GAY GUY
LOOKS LIKE.
MY BROTHER IS GAY.
AND YOU... HE'S GAY.
AND HE IS GAY. MERDE.
[ Continues In French ]
[ All Murmuring ]
MARCUS GRAHAM,
WHAT DID YOU SAY TO HER?
WHAT DID I SAY?
DO YOU REALIZE
THAT I HEARD THIS WOMAN
SCREAMING FROM THE BATHROOM?
HOW DARE YOU DISCUSS WHAT
I DO WITH YOU IN BED SEXUALLY
WITH THAT WOMAN?
AS SOON AS YOU LEAVE THE ROOM,
SHE STARTS GOING ON ABOUT HOW
SHE WANTS TO FUCK ME.
HOW COULD YOU TALK
ABOUT WHAT I DO WITH YOU
WITH THIS WOMAN?
SHE SAID THAT?
YEAH, SHE... AND I KNOW
YOU SAID IT, 'CAUSE...
SHE'S A LITTLE OFF.
SHE STARTED TALKIN' ABOUT HOW MY
ASS MOVES. I KNOW YOU SAID IT.
LISTEN. DON'T EXPECT ME
TO SLEEP WITH PEOPLE
FOR BUSINESS REASONS, OKAY?
YOU DID WITH LADY ELOISE.
EXCUSE ME.
THAT IS A RUMOR.
WE DO NOT KNOW IF I SLEPT WITH
LADY ELOISE. I HAD A CHITCHAT
WITH LADY ELOISE, OKAY?
OH, PLEASE, MARCUS.
OH, GOD.
"OH, PLEASE," MY ASS.
DON'T DISCUSS WHAT I DO
WITH YOU WITH OTHER PEOPLE.
[ Jacqueline ]
I'LL HANDLE THIS.
[ Horns Honking ]
OKAY, STRANGE,
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
WHAT PROBLEM?
I'M NOT GOING.
NOW, LISTEN. YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE YOURSELF ON THE PLANE,
OR I WILL NOT ONLY TAKE BACK
THE MILLION OR TWO
I AM PAYING YOU,
I WILL SUE YOU FOR
EVERY GODDAMN DIME YOU'VE GOT.
NOW, DO YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
ANDIAMO.
WHAT AN ABSOLUTELY
EXHAUSTING EVENING, HUH?
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH, MARCUS,
I DON'T FEEL VERY WELL.
DON'T TOUCH ME.
YOU MADE ME FEEL DIRTY, AND I
DON'T BELIEVE THIS WHOLE THING
IS HAPPENING TO ME, OKAY?
LOOK AT YOU. GOD, MARCUS,
GETTING YOURSELF ALL UPSET
AND WORKED UP OVER NOTHING.
NOTHING? THAT'S WHAT SEX IS TO
YOU? NOTHING? WHATEVER HAPPENED
TO CARING, SHARING, COMMITMENT?
I KNOW IT SOUNDS OLD-FASHIONED,
BUT SOME PEOPLE STILL THINK
THINGS LIKE THAT ARE IMPORTANT.
YOU'VE MADE IT PAINFULLY OBVIOUS
THAT YOU NOT ONE OF THEM PEOPLE.
WELL,
WHY DON'T I GIVE YOU A SECOND
TO THINK ABOUT IT, HUH?
OH, REALLY?
YEAH.
YEAH, I THINK...
I THINK YOU SHOULD
DO YOUR OWN THING.
OKAY, MARCUS,
IT'S OVER.
GOOD NIGHT.
* HE WILL NOT HURT ME
* [ Continues, Indistinct ]
[ Bony-T ]
MARCUS!
MARCUS! I DON'T BELIEVE
THE WAY YOU LET HER
DOG YOU OUT LIKE THAT.
YOU WALKIN' AROUND
WITH YOUR HEAD DOWN
AND MOPIN'.
WHERE'S YOUR PRIDE?
WHERE'S YOUR DIGNITY?
YOU THINK MALCOLM X DIED...
SO YOU COULD WALK AROUND
LOOKING LIKE A CHUMP?
HEY, BONY,
NOT TODAY, OKAY?
SAD, MAN. TSK.
FIRST THE FAT BOYS BREAK UP,
NOW THIS.
THERE'S NOTHIN'
TO BELIEVE IN ANYMORE.
* [ Continues, Indistinct ]
[ Chattering, Laughing ]
- * WHOA, IN MY HEART
- GOOD MORNING, MARCUS.
[ Chattering Continues ]
[ Scattered Whispering ]
SHH, SHH, SHH, SHH.
[ Woman ]
GOOD MORNING.
[ Women ] GOOD MORNING.
GOOD MORNING, MARCUS GRAHAM.
- GOOD MORNING.
- [ Women Snickering ]
* WHOA
* WHY DID YOU KEEP MY SOUL
* WITHOUT A SPARK
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
[ Laughter,
Chattering Continue ]
* I NEED LOVE
MARCUS, EXCUSE ME.
I NEED THE STORYBOARDS
FOR THE STRANGE SPOTS.
I'M SHOOTING NEXT WEEK.
- SHOOT WHATEVER
YOU WANT TO SHOOT.
- WHATEVER I WANT TO SHOOT?
IT'S YOUR SHOW.
I HAVE COMPLETE AUTONOMY?
- YOU THE MAN.
- [ Chuckles ]
THANK YOU.
BLESS YOU. BYE.
EXCUSE ME.
JACQUELINE?
YEAH?
CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR JUST A SECOND?
YEAH. SURE.
UM, I KNOW IT'S NONE
OF MY BUSINESS WHAT'S
GOING ON WITH YOU AND MARCUS,
BUT CAN YOU TRY TO
TAKE IT EASY ON HIM, PLEASE?
EXCUSE ME?
WELL, WHATEVER IT IS
YOU'RE DOING TO HIM, IT'S
STARTING TO AFFECT HIS WORK.
WHAT I AM DOING TO HIM?
YEAH.
WOW. UM, WELL,
IT SEEMS LIKE...
WHATEVER IT IS
I'M DOI TO HIM,
YOU ARE TAKING
RATHER PERSONALLY.
AM I MISTAKEN, HUH?
NO. JACKIE!
I'M JUST SAYING IT'S
JUST AFFECTING HIS WORK,
THAT'S ALL.
WELL, WE DON'T WANT
TO DO THAT.
THANKS, JACK.
WE HAVE SOMETHING VERY EXCITING
COMING UP. AFTER MONTHS OF
HARD WORK BY OUR CREATIVE TEAM,
YOU'RE ABOUT TO SEE
THE COMMERCIAL THAT WILL LAUNCH
OUR $18 MILLION PUSH...
FOR THE NEW STRANGE FRAGRANCE.
LIGHTS, PLEASE.
HOW IS IT?
I HAVEN'T SEEN IT.
I LET NELSON DO IT BY HIMSELF.
THIS IS MY VISION.
IT IS FABULOUS.
FABULOUS!
[ Laughs Heartily ]
[ Hissing ]
[ Cackling ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Screaming Continues ]
[ Bottle "Crying" ]
[ Announcer ]
STRANGE: IT STINKS SO GOOD.
THAT IS RIDICULOUS!
WELL, THE BOARD
WANTED ME TO LET YOU GO.
I CONVINCED THEM
TO GIVE YOU ANOTHER CHANCE.
WELL, AS AN EMPLOYEE,
I THANK YOU FOR SAVING MY JOB.
- AND AS YOUR LOVER, I THANK YOU
FOR RUINING MY LIFE.
- OH, COME ON, MARCUS.
I DIDN'T RUIN YOUR LIFE.
YOU RUINED YOUR LIFE.
I SAID THIS WAS GONNA HAPPEN.
I WAS JUST HOPING IT DIDN'T
HAPPEN WITH YOU.
THE ONLY THING
THAT I CAN SUGGEST IS...
PERHAPS YOU SHOULD
TAKE A FEW WEEKS OFF.
OKAY.
[ Church Bells Ringing ]
THERE'S THIS ONE KID
THAT YOU ARE GONNA LOVE.
HE IS SO CUTE.
HE'S REALLY GONNA
LIFT YOU UP. MARCUS!
I AM NOT GONNA
LET YOU SIT AROUND HERE
AND MOPE ALL DAY LONG.
NOW, SNAP OUT OF IT!
HAVE YOU BEEN LISTENING?
CUPID HAS HIS FOOT IN MY ASS.
I HAVE THE CURE FOR CUPID,
ALL RIGHT? NOW, WHEN I HAVE
PROBLEMS WITH MY RELATIONSHIP,
WHICH IS MOST OF THE TIME,
I FIND OUT THAT IT'S BETTER
TO TAKE THE FOCUS OFF MYSELF...
AND PUT IT TO OTHERS.
I DON'T WANNA BE AROUND
NO KIDS. I WANNA GO HOME
AND SIT IN MY HOUSE...
AND LOOK AT THE WALLS
AND LISTEN TO SADE.
THAT'S WHAT I WANNA DO.
AND THAT'S FUN?
NO, BUT THAT'S WHERE
MY HEAD IS AT RIGHT NOW.
THAT'S WHERE I NEED TO BE.
I DON'T WANNA GO IN HERE
AND PAINT. YOU CAN'T
PAINT MY MISERIES AWAY.
[ Chattering ]
[ Angela ] HI.
HI, ANGELA!
THANK YOU. EVERYBODY,
THIS IS MR. GRAHAM.
- [ All Laughing ]
- WHO DID THAT?
THESE CHILDREN ARE KIDS THAT
I TEACH ART TO WHOSE SCHOOLS
CAN'T AFFORD AN ART PROGRAM.
OH, SO NICE.
NOW, REMEMBER LAST WEEK,
WE SAW...
I'M GONNA
WHOOP SOMEBODY'S ASS.
SIT DOWN, MARCUS.
REMEMBER LAST WEEK,
WE LOOKED AT COLLAGES
FROM ROMARE BEARDEN, RIGHT?
[ All  YES.
AND THIS WEEK,
WHAT WERE YOU SUPPOSED TO DO?
BRING YOUR OWN COLLAGES.
[ Simultaneously ]
BRING OUR OWN COLLAGES.
WHO WANTS TO
SHOW ME THEIRS FIRST?
OH, BOY! KENNY.
AS-SALAAM ALAIKUM,
MY BROTHER.
ALAIKUM SALAAM.
- GREETINGS, MY NUBIAN PRINCESS.
- MY KING.
THIS IS THE SUN,
AND THESE ARE THE SUN RAYS.
AND THIS IS A BIG, GIANT, HUGE
HOLE IN THE OZONE LAYER. AND
THIS IS WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN...
TO PEOPLE AND ANIMALS
IF WE DON'T FIX UP
THE OZONE LAYER QUICKLY.
[ Angela ]
THAT'S VERY AFRO-CENTRIC.
YOU OUGHTA LIKE THIS, KENNY.
WHAT A LIVELY LITTLE THING
YOU ARE.
- OKAY. TELL US ABOUT THIS.
- THIS IS MY HOUSE.
THIS IS THE SUN.
THIS IS A SPHERE,
AND THIS IS A SHIELD.
THEN WE HAVE...
THEN, RIGHT HERE,
IS MY FISHBOWL.
AND THIS IS BLOOD.
THEN THESE ARE MY CLOTHES.
AND THESE ARE THE FISH.
WHY... THIS IS THE FISHBOWL
UP HERE, RIGHT? AND THESE ARE
THE FISH AND THIS THE FLOOR.
WHY AREN'T THE FISH
IN THE BOWL?
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT THEM THERE.
BUT THEY CAN'T
LIVE ON THE FLOOR.
ART CAN BE VERY ABSTRACT.
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO MAKE SENSE.
ONLY IN THE ARTIST'S MIND.
THANK YOU, KHANYA.
THANK YOU, KHANYA,
FOR YOUR INTERPRETATION.
[ Angela ]
OKAY. WHO'S GONNA BE NEXT?
YOU CANNOT TELL ME
YOU DID NOT HAVE FUN IN THERE
WITH THOSE KIDS.
I AIN'T SAYIN' IT WASN'T FUN.
I'M JUST SAYIN' I WASN'T
IN THE RIGHT MIND-SET.
MIND-SET? WHAT DO YOU MEAN? YOU
DIDN'T THINK ABOUT JACQUELINE
ONE TIME WHILE YOU WERE THERE.
THAT'S TRUE.
AND I BET YOU DIDN'T THINK ABOUT
THE STRANGE COMMERCIAL EITHER.
RIGHT?
YOU'RE RIGHT. THE KIDS ARE MORE
INSPIRATIONAL THAN I'VE BEEN.
THANK YOU.
I GOT AN IDEA.
WHAT?
I GOT AN IDEA
FOR THE STRANGE AD.
OKAY. SLOW IT DOWN.
RIGHT... RIGHT THERE.
- [ Machine Beeps ]
- [ Static ]
- OKAY. WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- WELL, I LIKE IT.
[ Women Screaming Offscreen ]
HOLD IT.
IS THAT A NIPPLE?
- [Marcus ] THAT'S NOT A NIPPLE.
THAT'S A SHADOW.
- THAT'S A NIPPLE.
- EXCUSE ME. THAT IS A SHADOW.
- I THINK IT'S A SHADOW
OF A NIPPLE.
COME ON. STOP PLAYING.
THAT'S A NIPPLE.
- THAT IS A SHADOW.
- I'LL BLOW IT UP.
IT'S A NIPPLE,
'CAUSE I'M DROOLING.
[ Laughs ]
YOU, UH, A LITTLE NERVOUS
ABOUT MEETING GERARD'S PARENTS?
NO, I'M NOT.
MM.
I JUST DON'T WANT THEM
TO THINK WE'RE A COUPLE,
YOU KNOW?
DON'T EVEN TRIP.
GERARD AIN'T EVEN THAT CLOSE
TO HIS FATHER, FIRST OF ALL.
YOU KNOW, I KNEW IT.
GERARD IS REALLY A FUN GUY,
ISN'T HE?
HE IS VERY MUCH FUN.
IT'S HIS FATHER AND HIS MOTHER
THAT ARE THE SQUARE ONES.
- [ Doorbell Rings ]
- I GOT IT.
HEY-HO!
[ Woman ]
HAPPY THANKSGIVING!
WHAT'S UP?
ANGELA'S OVER THERE.
HEY, MR. JACKSON!
HAPPY THANKSGIVING!
HOW YOU DOIN', HONEY?
YOU LOOK GREAT.
THANK YOU.
SO DO YOU.
THANKS.
MY, UH, PARENTS ARE HERE.
YOU LOOK
JUST LIKE YOUR DAD.
THANKS.
I BROUGHT YOU SOME CHITLINS.
OH! GERARD'S MOTHER...
ANGELA, GERARD'S MOTHER
BROUGHT US A WHOLE TROUGH
OF CHITLINS.
- [ Tyler ] I WANT A BOWL.
- THIS THE LITTLE GIRL
YOU BEEN TALKIN' ABOUT?
AGATHA?
ANGELA, ANGELA LEWIS.
MM-HMM.
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
- ISN'T SHE PRETTY? SHE LOOK
LIKE ONE OF MARCUS'S GIRLS.
- [ Groans ]
HEY, WHY DON'T... AGATHA, WHY
DON'T YOU GO IN THE KITCHEN AND
HELP MRS. JACKSON WITH THESE?
GO ON. Y'ALL GO IN THE KITCHEN.
CUTIE PIE.
- [ Mrs. Jackson ] ALL RIGHT.
- MR. JACKSON, COME HERE.
- HEY, BUDDY!
MAN, IT'S SO GOOD
TO SEE YOU. EVERY YEAR,
YOU DO SOMETHING NEW.
NOW, WHERE'D
YOU GET THE MUSHROOM SHIRT?
I'M TRYING TO IMPRESS YOU.
I KNOW. NOW, WHERE'D
YOU GET THE MUSHROOM SHIRT?
I GOT TO KNOW.
WELL, THE SECRET IS,
YOU GOT TO COORDINATE.
UH-HUH.
MOST PEOPLE DON'T COORDINATE.
SEE, YOU GOT TO COORDINATE.
THAT'S WHAT YOU DID.
INTERESTING.
SEE, I TOLD YOU
THEY DON'T STINK
WHEN YOU PULL THE MEMBRANE OUT.
- MAMA!
- SEE, WHEN YOU SAW ME,
YOU SAW THE MUSHROOM SHIRT.
I SAID, "MUSHROOM SHIRT."
BANG! MUSHROOM SHIRT. YOU CAN'T
STOP WITH THE MUSHROOM SHIRT.
YOU GOTTA GO ON.
I'D HAVE STOPPED
AT THE SHIRT.
NO, YOU GOTTA KEEP GOING.
LET ME SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
LOOK AT THAT.
OH, YOU GOT ON A MUSHROOM BELT.
GERARD, DID YOU KNOW YOUR POPS
HAD A MUSHROOM BELT ON?
- YES.
- BUT YOU DON'T STOP THERE, SEE?
YOU GOTTA KEEP GOIN'.
WHAT YOU GOT?
A MUSHROOM RING?
YES. GOOD IDEA.
LOOK WHAT I GOT.
DAH! GERARD,
DID YOU KNOW ON THE INSIDE
WAS SPECIAL MUSHROOMS?
YES!
MMM-MMM-MMM.
SIMPLY DELICIOUS, MARCUS.
I KEEP TELLIN' YOUR MOM
SHE SHOULD TAKE SOME
COOKING LESSONS FROM YOU.
ALL SHE DO IS COOK PORK.
I'LL BET WE'VE EATEN
EVERYTHING ON THE PIG...
FROM THE ROOTER
TO THE TOOTER.
- THE WHOLE PIG, HUH?
- YOU DIDN'T MARRY ME
FOR MY COOKING.
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT, BABY.
THAT'S WHY WE GOT
LITTLE JUNIOR OVER THERE.
BANG, BANG, BANG, BANG,
BANG, BANG, BANG!
MUST YOU EMBARRASS ME
IN FRONT OF MY FRIENDS
ON EVERY POSSIBLE OCCASION?
NOW, SEE... SEE THERE?
THAT'S YOUR SON.
- PRIVATE SCHOOL GOT HIM
ALL "SADIDDY" LIKE THAT.
- YEAH, MAN. CHILL.
IT'S YOUR FATHER. MR. JACKSON,
ANGELA MADE THIS MEAL. IT WASN'T
ME. I CAN'T TAKE CREDIT FOR IT.
[ Mr. Jackson ]
MMM. VERY GOOD.
[ Mrs. Jackson ] VERY GOOD.
HMM. GOOD PICK, JUNIOR.
[ Gerard ]
DADDY!
I TOLD YOU
THAT ANGELA AND I
ARE JUST FRIENDS.
MM-HMM.
[ Sucking Teeth ]
JUST FRIENDS, HUH?
YES, JUST FRIENDS.
JUST FRIENDS.
LEAVE IT ALONE, HON.
THEY'VE TOLD YOU THAT
500 TIMES. JUST LET IT GO.
FINE.
WE CHANGE THE SUBJECT.
NOW, MARCUS,
I HEAR A GIRL AT THE OFFICE
GOT YOU PUSSY-WHIPPED.
WHY DON'T YOU...
[ Sucking Teeth ] REVERSE IT?
DON'T BE PUSSY-WHIPPED.
WHIP THAT PUSSY!
- LOOK. BANG, BANG, BANG, BANG,
BANG, BANG, BANG, BANG, BANG!
- [ Mrs. Jackson ] OOH, DADDY!
YOU REALLY INSIST
ON STANDING AROUND ALL DAY
WITH A LONG FACE, ALL RIGHT?
MAN, MY PARENTS
BEEN IN THAT BATHROOM
DAMN NEAR AN HOUR, MAN.
SO WHAT?
WELL, THEY BEEN IN THERE
HITTIN' IT.
YOUR PARENTS ARE SMOKIN'
A JOINT IN MY BATHROOM?
NO. THEY BEEN IN THERE FUCKIN'.
[ Laughs ]
WHOO!
[ Sighs ]
DAMN. GOODNESS.
WHAT'S FOR DESSERT?
WOW.
I'M ALL RIGHT, MAN.
LET'S GO. LET'S GO EAT, MAN.
ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T
WANT ME TO GO WITH YOU?
NO, NO, NO. THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'D BETTER RUN MY PARENTS HOME
BEFORE THEY EMBARRASS ME
ANY FURTHER.
OKAY.
I HAD A GREAT TIME.
I'LL CALL YOU TOMORROW.
ME TOO.
BYE.
MRS. JACKSON.
[ Groaning ]
I CANNOT TELL Y'ALL
HOW MUCH FUN IT IS
TO BE WITH Y'ALL AND...
SO GOOD.
OH, A PIECE
OF COAT, I THINK.
OHH, BOY, THE RABBIT
IS GETTING OLD, BABY.
LOOKIE THERE.
WE'LL TEAR ANOTHER PIECE OFF
AND MAKE SOME EARRINGS.
WE'LL COORDINATE.
OH!
YEAH, THAT'LL WORK.
[ Tyler ] YO, YO, YO, YO.
GOT A HOOKUP
FOR TONIGHT.
WHO?
REMEMBER THAT LITTLE GIRL
I MET IN EMERGENCY?
YEAH.
BABY GOT
HER STITCHES OUT.
[ Grunts ]
YO, WELL, WHATEVER.
I'LL RAP TO YOU.
ALL RIGHT. I GOTTA GO.
OKAY, BUDDY.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
SEE Y'ALL LATER, ALL RIGHT?
[ Mumbles ]
SEE YOU LATER.
[ Mrs. Jackson ] BYE.
[ Angela ] SURE YOU DON'T WANT
ME TO HELP YOU WITH THE DISHES?
[ Marcus ]
I GOT IT. GO ON HOME.
[ Angela ] OKAY.
[ Mr. Jackson Shouting,
Indistinct ]
[ Angela ] WHERE'S MY COAT?
[ Chuckles ]
ANGELA?
YES?
I'M GONNA HAVE TO
TAKE YOU UP ON THAT OFFER.
THOUGHT SO.
YES.
CHITLIN JUICE EVERYWHERE,
AND I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN
HANDLE IT ALONE.
I AM SO TIRED, I DON'T CARE
IF I NEVER SEE ANOTHER CUP,
PLATE, AGAIN IN MY LIFE.
MY.
OH, MY FEET ARE KILLING ME.
CAN I TAKE MY SHOES OFF?
YEAH, YOU CAN. YOU'LL HAVE
THE WHOLE HOUSE SMELLIN'
LIKE FUNKY CORN CHIPS.
PLEASE. MY FEET
DO NOT STINK.
STAR TREK'S COMIN' ON.
I LOVE STAR TREK.
DO YOU REALLY?
YEAH. I'M A TREKKIE.
GET OUTTA HERE!
I'M A TREKKIE! LOOK AT CAP...
AIN'T CAPTAIN KIRK
THE COOLEST WHITE MAN
ON THE PLANET?
YOU KNOW, YOU CAN ALWAYS
TELL WHO'S GONNA GET KILLED
WHEN YOU WATCH THIS SHOW.
NOW, LOOK...
LOOK WHO'S BEAMIN' DOWN.
YOU SEE KIRK, McCOY,
SPOCK... AND YEOMAN JOHNSON.
NOW, DOESN'T YEOMAN JOHNSON
KNOW HE'S GONNA GET KILLED?
IF I WAS YEOMAN JOHNSON, I'D
SAY, "HEY, I'M NOT GOIN'.
I KNOW WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN."
IT'S AMAZING HOW YOU'VE
JUST SORT OF BROKEN DOWN
THIS WHOLE STAR TREK THING.
WELL, I'M A TREKKIE. THAT'S WHY
I BROKE IT DOWN TO THE BAREST
ESSENCE OF THE TREK.
I'M A TREKKIE.
I KNOW EVERYTHING
ABOUT STAR TREK.
WHAT'S CAPTAIN KIRK'S
FIRST NAME?
"CAPTAIN."
NO, IT'S NOT "CAPTAIN."
HIS NAME IS JAMES T. KIRK.
WHAT IS MR. SPOCK'S
LAST NAME?
HUH?
YOU DIDN'T EVEN KNOW THAT.
THE NAME IS SPOCK JENKINS.
ONE OF THE JENKINS BOYS
FROM VULCAN.
IT'S, UH...
WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT LATER.
* [ TV:
"Star-Spangled Banner" ]
HEY, WHAT ARE WE DOING?
WE'RE KISSING.
WE AIN'T SUPPOSED
TO BE KISSING.
WHY?
WE'RE FRIENDS.
SO? FRIENDS CAN KISS.
- * [ Rock Beat ]
- [ Woman ]
* YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH
* YEAH
YEAH *
TIME TO FEEL SOMETHING GOOD *
* LET YOUR HAIR HANG OUT, GIRL
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
* YEAH
* TIME TO GET CRAZY
YEAH, YEAH *
[ Whip Cracking ]
* [ Ends ]
IT'S GOOD. IT'S VERY GOOD.
CONGRATULATIONS, MARCUS.
OH, CONGRATULATE ANGELA.
IT WAS MOSTLY HER IDEA.
NICE GOING, ANGELA.
THANKS.
HEY, YOU.
YO, MAN, IT'S RACIAL.
EXPAND.
ALL RIGHT.
CHECK IT OUT.
THE WHITE BALL
DOMINATES EVERYTHING, RIGHT?
IT KNOCKS THE SHIT
OUT OF THE YELLOW BALL,
THE RED BALL, RIGHT?
AND THE GAME'S OVER
WHEN THE WHITE BALL
DRIVES THE BLACK BALL...
COMPLETELY OFF THE TABLE.
[ Grunts ]
- NOW, WHY IS THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW, BUT I'M SURE
YOU'LL TELL ME,
MY "BROTHA."
SURE. YOU RIGHT.
LOOK,
IT'S BECAUSE
OF THE WHITE MAN'S FEAR...
OF THE SEXUAL POTENCY
OF BLACK BALLS.
THAT ONE WAS KIND
OF INTERESTING.
THAT WAS INTERESTING.
- [ Tyler ] YOU SEE, WHAT WAS...
- I SEE WHERE YOU'RE GOING.
AND THE POOL TABLE IS EARTH.
THAT'S WHY IT'S GREEN.
OH, SEE, YOUR SHIT
IS COMIN' OUT NOW.
- AND THE WORLD, THEY USED
TO THINK IT WAS FLAT.
- SCHOOL HIM.
- WHEN YOU DO THE OPRAH WINFREY
SHOW, I'M GONNA BE FRONT ROW!
- IT'S NOT ABOUT JOKES.
- ME AND HIM ARE HERE.
IT'S NOT ABOUT...
- THAT ONE WAS KIND OF DEEP.
YOU WENT TO THE BOTTOM
OF THE OCEAN ON THAT ONE. YEAH,
BUT LOSERS GET THE BEER, SO...
- I'M GONNA GET THE BEER.
BUT SEE HOW OUR THING IS HERE?
- OH, YES.
WE'RE ON THE SAME WAVELENGTH.
WE'RE THE SAME CAT.
GET HIM THERE.
OKAY, I'LL GET HIM.
I'M GONNA WORK ON HIM.
FINE.
YO, MAN, HE'S GETTIN' WORSE. WE
GOT TO FIND HIM A WOMAN QUICK.
HE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
HEY, HOW ARE THINGS
WITH YOU AND ANGELA?
OH, WE'RE COOL, MAN,
YOU KNOW.
WE WENT OUT A COUPLE TIMES,
MAN, AND SHE WAS
GETTIN' SO INVOLVED.
- I SAID, "LOOK,
I'M JUST GONNA PULL BACK."
- HMM. COOL.
OH, YEAH, YEAH. I TOLD HER.
I SAID, "LOOK HERE, GIRL,
DO YOUR THING, SEE OTHER MEN,
'CAUSE I'M GONNA
SEE OTHER WOMEN," YOU KNOW?
I JUST DIDN'T WANT
TO BREAK HER HEART RIGHT OFF,
YOU KNOW? I JUST PULL OUT EASY.
OKAY. GOOD, GOOD.
SO YOU DON'T MIND IF SHE
GOES OUT WITH OTHER GUYS THEN?
OH, HELL, NO. WH...
OH, YOU'RE THINKING
OF HOOKING HER UP WITH TYLER?
NO, NOTHING LIKE THAT.
WHY YOU ASKIN', MAN?
I WAS JUST CURIOUS.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS SHIT.
WHY YOU ASKIN', MAN?
YOU CAN'T EVEN LOOK ME
IN MY EYE, CAN YOU, MARCUS?
DID YOU SLEEP
WITH ANGELA?
YEAH, I DID.
[ Sighs ]
WHY DO YOU ALWAYS HAVE
TO HAVE ALL THE GIRLS,
MARCUS?
YOU SAID A COUPLE OF SECONDS AGO
YOU DIDN'T CARE WHO SHE WENT OUT
WITH, NOW YOU'RE FLIPPIN'.
YOU'RE BEIN' A HYPOCRITE.
I DON'T WANNA
HEAR THAT BULLSHIT, MAN!
THIS IS DIFFERENT.
ANGELA IS A NICE GIRL.
SO I CAN'T BE
WITH A NICE GIRL?
NO.
'CAUSE ALL YOU'RE GONNA DO
IS DOG HER OUT LIKE YOU DO
EVERY WOMAN IN YOUR LIFE.
OKAY. TELL ME THIS, MAN.
WHY ANGELA? WHAT?
SHE HAS NICE FEET?
OH, IT HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH HER FEET OR ANYTHING
LIKE THAT, MAN.
I CARE ABOUT THIS GIRL.
MAN, YOU DON'T CARE ABOUT
NOBODY BUT YOURSELF, MAN!
[ Groans ]
SO WHEN WE CAN
RISE AS A PEOPLE,
WE RUNNIN' THINGS, YOU KNOW?
WHAT'D YOU DO, MAN?
GUESS.
[ Shower Running ]
MARCUS, COME QUICK!
I GOT SOMETHING
I WANNA SHOW YOU!
[ Marcus ] WHAT?
I WANNA
SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
GET OUT OF HERE.
I'M IN THE SHOWER!
MARCUS!
- STOP! HEY, HEY!
- COME ON.
I'M SOAKING WET. YOU'RE GONNA
MAKE ME CATCH A COLD OUT HERE.
I WANNA SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
NO, IT WON'T. LOOK.
TA-DA!
WELL,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
BLUE PEOPLE.
YEAH, THAT'S NICE. THE BLUE
PEOPLE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DO YOU LIKE IT?
YES, VERY MUCH.
OKAY, 'KAY, 'KAY.
LOOK AT IT...
AND TELL ME
HOW IT MAKES YOU FEEL.
HONESTLY, IT'S
MAKIN' ME KIND OF HORNY.
NO. FEEL.
AND I WOULD LIKE TO BE AND I
WOULD LIKE TO THINK I WAS THE
INSPIRATION FOR THAT BLUE MAN.
YOU SHOULD BE BLUE.
YOU'RE GONNA GET PAINT
ALL OVER ME.
[ Telephone Rings ]
EXACTLY.
THE PHONE'S RINGING.
TAKE THOSE CLOTHES OFF.
TAKE 'EM OFF. OFF.
[ Giggles ] NO.
[ Phone Beeps On ]
HELLO? JACQUELINE, HI!
HOW YOU DOIN'?
HE'S RIGHT HERE, ACTUALLY.
NO. NO,
WE WEREN'T BUSY AT ALL.
HERE HE IS.
OKAY.
HEY. YEAH.
NO, THAT WAS ANGELA.
SHE JUST STOPPED BY
FOR A SECOND.
UH-HUH. REALLY?
OH, THAT'S...
HEY, HEY. YOUR SPOT
TESTED THROUGH THE ROOF.
YEAH, SHE'S HAPPY.
UH-HUH.
YES, ABSOLUTELY.
ABSOLUTELY.
OH, THAT'S PERFECT.
GREAT. YEAH. PEACE.
HEY. HEY, THEY'RE SHOWIN'
THE SPOT TO THE BOARD OF
DIRECTORS ON FRIDAY NIGHT,
AND JACQUELINE
WANTS ME TO BE THERE.
GREAT.
WAIT. YOU DON'T HAVE
A PROBLEM WITH THAT, DO YOU?
NO, NO.
HEY, I WILL CALL HER,
AND I'LL TELL HER THAT...
YOU SURE?
COOL.
THAT'S BAD.
BLUE PEOPLE.
[ Speaking French ]
[ Men Chuckling ]
[ Continues In French ]
HEY, HEY.
LE PEACE. CHILL.
[ Continues In French ]
LES PLUMES.
YOU ARE BRILLIANT!
GOD, MARCUS, THEY LOVED IT!
THEY LOVED IT.
DID YOU
HEAR THE LITTLE FRENCHMAN
SCREAMING "MAGNIFIQUE"...
WITH A LITTLE BEAD
OF SWEAT RUNNIN'
DOWN HIS FACE, MAN?
- I KNEW I HAD THAT CAT.
- MARCUS, YOU ARE
INCREDIBLY TALENTED.
WELL, I THANK YOU.
LADY ELOISE THANKS YOU.
TELL HER I SAID "HEY."
I'M SURE STRANGE...
WOULD LIKE
TO THANK YOU PERSONALLY.
- YEAH, SHE'D LIKE
TO THANK THE HELL OUT OF ME.
- [ Laughing ]
I HAVE TO SAY,
IT'S VERY NICE
TO HAVE THE OLD MARCUS BACK.
I WAS KIND
OF WORRIED ABOUT YA.
REALLY?
YOU SEEMED, UM...
YOU SEEMED SO...
- I DON'T KNOW.
CAN I BE HONEST?
- PLEASE.
WELL, YOU SEEMED DESPERATE
AND UNSURE OF YOURSELF.
[ Chuckling ]
PATHETIC?
AHA.
KIND OF PATHETIC.
UH-HUH.
LOOK AT YOU NOW.
YOU'RE, UH...
YOU'RE RELAXED.
YOU'RE MORE CONFIDENT.
JUST LIKE THE MAN
I MET IN THAT ELEVATOR.
I GOT IT GOIN' ON AGAIN.
YEAH, YOU DO.
I LIKE IT.
I FIND IT
VERY ATTRACTIVE.
HOW'D IT GO LAST NIGHT?
IT WENT OKAY.
JUST OKAY?
IT MUST'VE GONE PRETTY WELL.
YOU DIDN'T GET HOME
UNTIL THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
I WENT FOR A WALK
SO I COULD SORT SOME THINGS OUT
THAT WAS IN MY HEAD.
- I WAS TRIPPIN' ON IT.
- LIKE THE FACT THAT YOU'RE
STILL IN LOVE WITH JACQUELINE?
ANGELA, I SAW THE WOMAN,
AND A BUNCH OF STUFF THAT
WAS IN ME I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
WAS STILL THERE CAME OUT.
THINGS HAPPENED, AND...
THERE'S CERTAIN THINGS YOU JUST
HAVE NO CONTROL OVER, ALL RIGHT?
REALLY? LIKE WHAT?
LIKE LOVE.
LOVE?
YOU KNOW,
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT LOVE?
WHAT DO YOU POSSIBLY THINK
YOU KNOW ABOUT LOVE?
YOU KNOW, I'M SICK AND TIRED
OF MEN USING LOVE LIKE IT'S SOME
KIND OF DISEASE YOU JUST CATCH.
LOVE SHOULD'VE BROUGHT
YOUR ASS HOME LAST NIGHT.
DIDN'T YOU JUST
HEAR ME SAY I WAS SORRY?
I HEARD YOU SAY YOU'RE SORRY.
YOU'RE SORRY, AND YOU'RE TIRED.
YOU DON'T LOVE ME.
YOU DON'T LOVE JACQUELINE.
- YOU ONLY LOVE YOUR DAMN SELF.
- HOW COULD YOU SAY
I NEVER CARED ABOUT YOU?
JACQUELINE SAYS
I'M A BETTER PERSON NOW,
AND I OWE THAT ALL TO YOU.
I'M OUTTA HERE.
I'LL GET THE REST
OF MY THINGS LATER.
LET ME JUST TELL YOU
ONE MORE THING. I MIGHT
NOT BE ALL GLAMOROUS,
AND I DON'T HAVE HAIR WEAVED ALL
DOWN MY BACK, BUT LET ME TELL
YOU ONE GREAT THING ABOUT ME.
I'VE GOT A HEART.
AND YOU KNOW THE BAD THING
ABOUT HAVING A HEART, MARCUS,
IS THAT IT GETS BROKEN
WHEN YOU DEAL WITH PEOPLE
LIKE YOU.
NOW, STAY THE FUCK
OUTTA MY LIFE!
[ Thunderclap ]
SHE LEFT YOU, HUH?
YEAH, SHE DID.
[ Sighs ]
I GUESS I SHOULD
FEEL HAPPY, BUT I DON'T.
I HATE TO SEE
ANOTHER PERSON
IN PAIN.
WELL, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THAT'S VERY NICE OF YOU, YVONNE.
GOOD NIGHT.
SO, UH, WOULD YOU
LIKE TO COME OVER
FOR A CUP OF COFFEE?
NOT EVEN IF JESUS
WAS POURIN' IT.
SOME MOTHERFUCKERS ARE SO BLIND
THEY CAN'T SEE A GOOD THING WHEN
IT'S STARIN' THEM IN THE FACE.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
LIFT YOUR BLACK ASS
OFF THE LEDGE AND FUCK YOU!
* THERE YOU GO AGAIN
* THERE YOU GO, THERE YOU GO
* THERE YOU GO
* AND HERE I COME
* HERE I COME, HERE I COME
HERE I COME *
* YEAH, YEAH, OH-HO
* FINE, FINE DAY
* IN YOUR BED, IN YOUR BED
IN YOUR BED *
* MAKING LOVE
* SWEET LOVE
* ONCE AGAIN, OH
I CAN'T DO THIS.
I HAVE CONDOMS.
NO, IT'S NOT THAT.
I GOTTA GO.
WHAT?
I'M IN LOVE
WITH SOMEBODY.
ANGELA, RIGHT?
MM-HMM.
SO NOW YOU THINK THAT
YOU'RE IN LOVE WITH ANGELA?
NO, NO, NO.
I KNOW. JUST AT THIS MOMENT,
I KNOW I'M IN LOVE
WITH THAT WOMAN.
MARCUS, IF YOU
ARE IN LOVE WITH ANGELA,
WHY ARE YOU HERE
WITH ME, HMM?
EXACTLY.
* LOVE SHOULD'VE BROUGHT YOU
* BROUGHT YOU HOME LAST NIGHT
* YOU SHOULD'VE BEEN WITH ME
* SHOULD'VE BEEN
RIGHT BY MY SIDE *
* BABY
* [ Stereo: Rap ]
[ Knocking ]
OH, SHIT! DAMN IT!
HOLD UP!
YO, WHAT'S UP, MAN?
COME ON IN.
WHAT'S UP?
WELCOME TO THE PENTHOUSE.
IT'S KIND OF SMOKY
IN HERE, CHIEF.
NO, NO, NO. WAIT, WAIT.
THAT AIN'T SMOKE, ALL RIGHT?
THAT'S AROMA.
- [ Knocking ]
- YO, CAN YOU GET THAT FOR ME?
THAT MIGHT BE A SURPRISE.
[ Tyler ]
WHAT'S UP, MAN?
WHERE YOU GOIN'?
[ Door Closing ]
YO, MAN. TALK!
WHAT'S UP, MAN?
HEY. HOW YOU DOIN'?
SO, YOU SEEN ANGELA LATELY?
NO. I HEAR SHE'S OVER
AT BARTON AND DOBBS NOW.
YEAH, I HEARD
SHE GOT PROMOTED
TO CREATIVE DIRECTOR.
REALLY?
WHERE'D YOU HEAR THAT?
BONY-T TOLD ME.
HEY, LOOK, MAN...
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO SAY ANYTHING.
YES, I DO.
I... I'M REALLY SORRY,
GERARD.
I'VE KNOWN YOU ALL MY LIFE,
MAN. YOU'RE LIKE MY BROTHER,
YOU KNOW?
I LOVE YOU,
AND I DON'T WANNA
GO THROUGH THIS, MAN.
LISTEN. IT HAPPENED,
AND I'M SORRY.
AND I FEEL BAD.
HOW LONG ARE YOU GONNA
HAVE ME STANDING HERE BEGGING?
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY.
YOU GONNA MILK
ALL THE APOLOGIES
OUT OF ME.
IT'S COOL.
MY MAN.
ALL RIGHT, MAN.
[ Wheezing Cough ]
YO, MAN! WHAT'S UP, MAN?
Y'ALL GONNA LET A GIRL
COME BETWEEN US, MAN? WHAT'S UP?
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE HERE, MAN.
WE'RE BOYS, MAN. WE DON'T
HANG OUT NO MORE, NOTHIN', MAN.
THIS SHIT HURT, MAN.
MAKE UP NOW, MAN.
WE JUST, YOU KNOW, MADE UP, MAN.
WELL, THEN HUG.
WE HUGGED JUST NOW. WE HUGGED
AND GAVE EACH OTHER A PAT.
- AND WE BOYS AGAIN.
- ALL RIGHT. THEN GIVE IT TO ME.
- WE JUST HUGGED ALREADY.
- NO, MAN. I WANT A BIG,
MOTHERFUCKIN' HUG, MAN.
DAMN, MAN.
I LOVE Y'ALL, MAN.
* IS IT MY TURN
TO WISH YOU WERE LYING HERE *
Y'ALL READY TO EAT?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
* I DIDN'T DREAM YOU
- * [ Continues, Indistinct ]
- YO, IS THAT MY SHIT?
[ Sirens Blaring ]
DAMN! MY PENTHOUSE!
* OR EVEN IMAGINARY EMOTIONS
* TELL MYSELF ANYTHING
* IS IT MY TURN
TO HOLD YOU BY YOUR HAND *
* TELL YOU I LOVE YOU
* AND YOU NOT HEAR ME
* IS IT MY TURN
TO TOTALLY UNDERSTAND *
* TO WATCH YOU
WALK OUT OF MY LIFE *
* AND NOT DO A DAMN THING
OH-HO *
* IF I COULD GIVE AWAY
[ Trails Off ]
NO. IT'S ALL WRONG.
YOU KNOW THAT MEMO I SHOWED YOU?
REFER TO IT AND SHOW ME
A NEW MOCK-UP IN THE MORNING.
THIS IS WAY OFF.
WE ARE NOT GONNA SHOOT THIS
UNTIL IT'S RIGHT.
ANGELA!
COME ON!
HI. WE'RE LOOKIN'
FOR ANGELA...
FORGET THAT.
WHAT?
UM, EXCUSE ME
FOR A SECOND, PLEASE.
WHAT ARE YOU TWO DOING HERE?
ANGELA!
ANGELA.
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU IN SO LONG.
FOUR MONTHS AND TWO WEEKS,
TO BE EXACT.
THANK YOU.
WE MISS YOU.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
I MISS YOU TOO,
AND I'VE BEEN WORKING.
I GOT THIS NEW JOB.
IT'S VERY DEMANDING,
AND IT REQUIRES LONG HOURS. I
HAVEN'T HAD TIME TO TEACH CLASS.
I'M SORRY.
YOU ALWAYS HAD TIME
FOR US.
[ Chuckles Nervously ]
I KNOW.
LET ME
TELL YOU SOMETHING, OKAY?
YOU KNOW WHAT I HAD TO DO?
I HAD TO REARRANGE
MY PRIORITIES IN LIFE.
ANGELA HAD TO START
LOOKIN' OUT FOR ANGELA.
HOW'D YOU GET HERE,
ANYWAY?
OUR NEW TEACHER BROUGHT US.
YOUR NEW TEACHER?
WELL, WHERE IS SHE?
- [ Both ] HE.
- [ Angela ]
WELL, WHERE IS HE?
UM, I THINK
WE BEST GET GOIN' NOW.
GOOD-BYE,
MY QUEEN.
OKAY.
PEACE.
MY BROTHER.
THAT'S PRETTY LOW,
USING THE KIDS, MARCUS.
WHAT ELSE COULD I DO? LOOK,
I BEEN SENDING YOU LETTERS,
ANGELA, AND I KNOW YOU GOT 'EM.
MM-HMM. I'M JUST
NOT REAL BIG ON WORDS
ON PAPER THESE DAYS.
OKAY.
I KNOW I FUCKED UP.
YOU'RE DAMN RIGHT,
YOU FUCKED UP.
YOU HURT ME.
I MISS YOU.
NO. I REALLY, REALLY MISS YOU.
I'VE NEVER MISSED ANYBODY
IN MY LIFE, AND I MISS YOU.
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT YOUR LOVE. IT'S
ABOUT THE FACT YOU CAN'T LOVE ME
THE WAY I DESERVE TO BE LOVED.
THAT'S WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
YOU THINK I'D COME DOWN HERE
AND BOTHER YOU...
UNLESS I WAS READY
TO BE EVERYTHING YOU WANTED
IN A RELATIONSHIP?
I WANT TO BE STRAIGHT UP
ABOUT EVERYTHING. I WANT TO
HAVE A MONOGAMOUS RELATIONSHIP.
YOU ARE MY BEST FRIEND.
I'M MISERABLE WITHOUT YOU. I
EVEN QUIT MY JOB BECAUSE OF YOU.
DID I ASK YOU
TO QUIT YOUR JOB?
WHY YOU DOIN' THIS?
DOING WHAT?
BEING ALL STIFF AND COLD
AND HIDIN' BEHIND YOUR WORK.
I'M TAKING CARE OF
MY BUSINESS, AND I SUGGEST
YOU TAKE CARE OF YOURS.
LISTEN,
I KNOW HAVING A GREAT JOB
IS COOL AND ALL OF THAT,
BUT YOU USED
TO HAVE A GOOD TIME.
YOU USED TO BE WITH THESE KIDS,
AND ME AND YOU USED TO HAVE FUN
AND WE HAD A GREAT LIFE.
- YOU HAD EVERYTHING.
- GIVE ME ONE REASON WHY
I SHOULD TAKE YOU BACK.
ONE.
I DIDN'T THINK YOU COULD.
DO YOU STILL LOVE ME?
'CAUSE I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
I MISS YOU.
I'M SCARED.
AND I'M MISERABLE.
I CAN'T BREATHE WITHOUT YOU.
I CAN'T BREATHE.
NOW, WE SHOULD JUST GO TO
YOUR PLACE AND GET YOUR THINGS
AND GO TO MY PLACE.
NO, NO. I'M NOT MOVING INTO YOUR
HOUSE THIS TIME. I'M STAYING
IN MY PLACE WITH MY OWN THINGS.
I WANT 24/7. THAT'S
HOW COMMITTED I AM.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, NO.
I'M NOT DOIN' IT.
IF YOU EVEN TURN
AND LOOK AT HER,
I WILL BREAK YOUR FUCKIN' NECK.
I'M NOT LOOKIN' AT THAT WOMAN.
I WAS LOOKIN' AT THIS WOMAN,
THINKIN' ABOUT THE FUTURE.
THAT'S YOU IN 15 YEARS.
YOU BETTER STILL
LOVE ME IN 15 YEARS.
DID YOU SEE?
SHE'S BY HERSELF.
I'M PLAYIN'. I'M PLAYIN'.
* YOUR LOVE'S SO EXCITING
BOY, I CAN'T DENY IT *
* SINCE YOU FOUND
A PLACE IN MY HOME *
* GIVIN' ME A FEELIN'
OOH, IT'S SUCH A FEELIN' *
* I FEEL THAT
WE NEVER WOKE UP *
* HOW CAN I EXPLAIN IT
* DID YOU HEAR
WHAT I'M SAYIN' *
* YOU BRING SO MUCH JOY
TO MY HEART *
* WORDS CANNOT EXPRESS
SO MUCH HAPPINESS *
* IF I CAN BE
FOREVER BY YOUR SIDE *
* YOU'RE THE BEAT
IN MY HEART, BABY *
* AND I WILL ALWAYS BE TRUE
TO YOU *
* AND I WILL LOVE YOU
FOREVER *
* IF I COULD JUST MAKE LOVE
TO YOU *
* MAKE LOVE TO YOU
* TELL ME WHAT'S WRONG
WITH ME, BABY *
* DIDN'T I TREAT YOU RIGHT
* RIGHT, RIGHT
* DIDN'T I DO IT ALL
MY BABY *
* BELIEVE ME, BABY, BABY
* IT'S GONNA BE SO RIGHT
* IF IT'S ALL RIGHT
IF IT'S ALL RIGHT *
* TELL ME
IT'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT *
* IF IT'S ALL RIGHT
IF IT'S ALL RIGHT *
* BOW-WOW-WOW
YIPPEE-YO, YIPPEE-YEA *
* BOW-WOW
* BOW-WOW-WOW
YIPPEE-YO, YIPPEE-YEA
BOW-WOW, YIPPEE-YO, YIPPEE *
* YEA
* HOW COULD SHE DO THAT
TO ME *
* SHE LET A LOAD OUT ON ME
* [ Continues, Indistinct ]
* LOVE SHOULD'VE BROUGHT YOU
BROUGHT YOU HOME LAST NIGHT *
* YOU SHOULD'VE BEEN WITH ME
* SHOULD'VE BEEN RIGHT
BY MY SIDE *
* BABY, IF YOU CARED ANYTHING
FOR ME *
* THEN LOVE WOULD'VE BROUGHT
YOU HOME TO ME LAST NIGHT *
* THERE YOU GO AGAIN
* THERE YOU GO, THERE YOU GO
* THERE YOU GO
* AND HERE I COME
* HERE I COME,
HERE I COME HERE I COME *
* HEY
* OH-HO
* RIGHT BY ME
* IN YOUR BED, IN YOUR BED
IN YOUR BED *
* MAKING LOVE
* ONCE AGAIN, OH
* DON'T WANT A DIAMOND
DON'T WANT A FORTUNE *
* DON'T WANT YOU NEAR MY HEART
* I DON'T WANT YOU
NEAR MY HEART *
* DON'T WANNA KISS YOU
TURN AROUND AND MISS YOU *
* STOP IT, BABY
BEFORE I START *
* TO THE END OF THE ROAD
* STILL I CAN'T LET GO
* IT'S UNNATURAL
* YOU BELONG TO ME
I BELONG TO YOU *
* I WANNA GO
* TO THE END OF THE ROAD
* STILL I CAN'T LET GO
* IT'S UNNATURAL
* YOU BELONG TO ME
I BELONG TO YOU *
* GO TO THE END
* OF THE ROAD
* STILL I CAN'T LET GO
* IT'S UNNATURAL
* YOU BELONG TO ME
I BELONG TO YOU *