1
00:02:55,090 --> 00:02:58,060
跟   蹤   者

2
00:02:55,090 --> 00:02:58,060
第一季  第八集

3
00:00:01,570 --> 00:00:05,000
{\an8}街區聚會

4
00:00:08,020 --> 00:00:08,590
比爾
Bill.

5
00:00:08,770 --> 00:00:09,640
馬克
Mark.

6
00:00:09,840 --> 00:00:11,130
你是喜歡胸還是喜歡腿
You a, uh, breast or a thigh man?

7
00:00:11,130 --> 00:00:13,490
他還沒笨到在大庭廣眾下回答這種問題
Oh, he knows better than to answer that in public.

8
00:00:14,710 --> 00:00:15,830
都可以  謝謝
It doesn't matter. Thank you.

9
00:00:15,830 --> 00:00:16,630
是
Yeah.

10
00:00:17,270 --> 00:00:18,710
整個乘客位的窗戶都被砸了嗎
So they took out the whole passenger window?

11
00:00:18,710 --> 00:00:19,510
有東西被偷嗎
Did they take anything?

12
00:00:19,510 --> 00:00:21,070
沒  沒丟任何東西
No. Nothing was taken.

13
00:00:21,370 --> 00:00:22,780
只是窗戶被砸了
Just busted the window.

14
00:00:22,780 --> 00:00:24,320
只是隨機破壞嗎
Just random vandalism?

15
00:00:25,120 --> 00:00:25,950
你報警了嗎
Did you call the police?

16
00:00:25,950 --> 00:00:26,940
何必費那事呢
Why bother them?

17
00:00:27,190 --> 00:00:28,320
他自己把窗戶換了
He fixed the window himself.

18
00:00:28,320 --> 00:00:29,940
這家伙手很巧呢
He's actually pretty handy, this one.

19
00:00:29,950 --> 00:00:31,480
有他在身邊是個好幫手呢
He's good to have around, you know?

20
00:00:31,600 --> 00:00:33,140
你還拍我屁股
You better watch that smack.

21
00:00:33,150 --> 00:00:34,040
好玩嘛
It's funny.

22
00:00:55,470 --> 00:00:57,040
叫上蘭登  咱們回家
Get Landon. Let's head home.

23
00:00:59,350 --> 00:01:00,730
蘭登  走了  寶貝
Landon, come on, baby.

24
00:01:00,730 --> 00:01:02,310
走吧  咱們回家  小伙子
Hey. Come on. Let's go inside, buddy.

25
00:01:02,310 --> 00:01:02,960
那是誰
Who was that?

26
00:01:02,960 --> 00:01:03,890
先回家再說
Let's just go home.

27
00:01:07,150 --> 00:01:07,740
進來吧
Come on.

28
00:01:15,420 --> 00:01:16,470
到底是怎么回事
What is going on?

29
00:01:17,240 --> 00:01:18,830
能不能晚點再說  親愛的
Can we not right now, honey?

30
00:01:25,450 --> 00:01:27,500
沒事的  咱們回你房間去  好嗎
It's ok. Let's go in your room, ok?

31
00:01:29,070 --> 00:01:31,430
"國王的宮殿是世界上
"The emperor's place was the most gorgeous palace

32
00:01:31,440 --> 00:01:32,480
最美的宮殿
in the world,

33
00:01:32,610 --> 00:01:34,680
全由上等瓷器建成
built entirely of fine porcelain,

34
00:01:35,130 --> 00:01:36,980
精致卻易碎
so precious but so brittle,

35
00:01:36,980 --> 00:01:38,730
輕輕一碰都可能會碎
so delicate to the touch

36
00:01:38,730 --> 00:01:41,180
所以你必須非常非常小心"
that you had to be very careful indeed."

37
00:01:56,860 --> 00:01:57,880
克里斯蒂娜
Christina?

38
00:02:00,360 --> 00:02:01,280
克里斯蒂娜
Christina?

39
00:02:08,140 --> 00:02:09,090
克里斯蒂娜
Christina?

40
00:02:13,540 --> 00:02:14,410
馬克
Mark!

41
00:02:14,900 --> 00:02:17,740
克里斯蒂娜  蘭登  你們沒事吧
Christina, Landon. You ok?

42
00:02:17,740 --> 00:02:18,790
沒事
Yeah.

43
00:02:23,680 --> 00:02:27,600
{\an8}納粹

44
00:03:05,500 --> 00:03:06,490
有情況就給我打電話
Call if anything happens.

45
00:03:06,490 --> 00:03:07,230
謝謝
Thanks.

46
00:03:09,950 --> 00:03:11,290
理查德一家在過來的路上了
The Richards are on their way up.

47
00:03:11,290 --> 00:03:12,030
很好
Great.

48
00:03:12,910 --> 00:03:14,630
前任光頭黨和他的拉美裔妻子
Former skinhead and his Latina wife

49
00:03:14,630 --> 00:03:16,010
被光頭黨跟蹤
are being stalked by skinheads.

50
00:03:16,020 --> 00:03:17,660
聽上去這女人喜歡壞男人啊
Sounds like a woman who likes a project.

51
00:03:17,660 --> 00:03:18,850
等會我跟妻子聊
I will talk to the wife,

52
00:03:18,850 --> 00:03:20,630
你去詢問丈夫  之后咱們再做比較
you interview the husband. We'll compare later.

53
00:03:20,630 --> 00:03:22,510
為什么  你不相信那個人已經改過自新了
Why? You don't think the guy's completely reformed?

54
00:03:22,510 --> 00:03:24,530
我只是她在不受丈夫的影響下說出自己的看法
I just want her perspective free of her husband.

55
00:03:25,620 --> 00:03:27,390
你覺得他是否改過自新了  杰克
You tell us if he's reformed, Jack.

56
00:03:27,840 --> 00:03:28,850
人是會變的
People can change.

57
00:03:29,130 --> 00:03:32,820
是  但這是個漫長的過程而且會反復
Yes, but it's a process and requires a lot of rewiring.

58
00:03:32,820 --> 00:03:34,590
我覺得這是往前兩步
I find that it's two steps forward.

59
00:03:34,590 --> 00:03:36,110
再退后十步
And 10 steps back.

60
00:03:36,600 --> 00:03:38,490
謝謝  貝絲  祝好運
Thanks, Beth. Good luck.

61
00:03:40,110 --> 00:03:41,880
這群光頭黨把你作為攻擊目標
This group of skinheads is targeting you

62
00:03:41,890 --> 00:03:44,040
是因為你曾經也是光頭黨
because of your past affiliations with them?

63
00:03:44,280 --> 00:03:46,430
我不認識這些人  他們是本地的
I don't know these guys. They're local.

64
00:03:46,550 --> 00:03:49,320
我多年前加入了一個在里弗賽德的組織
I was with a group out in Riverside years ago,

65
00:03:49,590 --> 00:03:51,480
但他們肯定知道我已經退出了
but they must know that I left the movement,

66
00:03:51,580 --> 00:03:53,590
在他們的字典里  退出意味著我就跟
and in their book, that makes me as bad

67
00:03:53,590 --> 00:03:55,360
那些少數民族一樣  甚至比他們還可恨
or worse than any minority.

68
00:03:55,360 --> 00:03:56,590
你認為他們是怎么找到你的
How do you think they found you?

69
00:03:56,590 --> 00:04:00,440
我不知道  我很久前就拋棄那種生活了
I don't know. I left that life behind a long time ago.

70
00:04:01,140 --> 00:04:03,190
我更名改姓  搬到了這里
I changed my name, I moved out here,

71
00:04:03,190 --> 00:04:04,100
重新開始
started over.

72
00:04:04,860 --> 00:04:06,120
{\an8}憎恨

73
00:04:09,440 --> 00:04:10,740
我在用激光祛紋身
Getting them lasered off.

74
00:04:11,630 --> 00:04:13,220
已經做了21次  還要繼續
21 sessions and counting,

75
00:04:13,430 --> 00:04:14,660
疼得要死
and it hurts like a bitch.

76
00:04:14,660 --> 00:04:15,910
88是什么意思
What's the 88 mean?

77
00:04:15,920 --> 00:04:18,370
字母表中第八個字母是H
The eighth letter of the alphabet is "H".

78
00:04:20,020 --> 00:04:21,020
代表希特勒萬歲
Heil Hitler.

79
00:04:21,980 --> 00:04:23,330
為什么我們要被分開問話
Look. Why are we being questioned separately?

80
00:04:23,340 --> 00:04:25,050
你們不是對犯罪嫌疑人才這樣呢嗎
Isn't that something you guys do to suspects?

81
00:04:25,050 --> 00:04:27,500
我們這樣才能獲得對事件最清晰的認識
It's how we get the clearest understanding of events.

82
00:04:27,500 --> 00:04:30,490
馬克說他們已經跟蹤他三周了
Mark said that they've been following him around for 3 weeks,

83
00:04:30,500 --> 00:04:32,610
但他們從來沒到我們家里
but they've never come to our home

84
00:04:32,610 --> 00:04:34,030
或是街區來過
or our neighborhood before.

85
00:04:34,030 --> 00:04:35,470
馬克說我們很安全
Mark said we'd be safe.

86
00:04:35,470 --> 00:04:37,500
通常這些組織都會遵守一定的規章
Often, groups are bound by code.

87
00:04:37,500 --> 00:04:39,930
幫派也有一些不會跨越的底限
There are certain boundaries gangs won't cross.

88
00:04:39,930 --> 00:04:41,040
馬克也是這么說的
That's what Mark said,

89
00:04:41,040 --> 00:04:42,650
但這次他們越線了
but they have crossed them.

90
00:04:45,160 --> 00:04:46,010
什么案子
What is it?

91
00:04:46,230 --> 00:04:49,540
前任新納粹光頭黨成員  說自己被幫派跟蹤
Ex-neo-Nazi Skinhead, claims he's being gang stalked.

92
00:04:49,540 --> 00:04:51,030
你好像很不爽啊
Why the attitude?

93
00:04:52,030 --> 00:04:53,500
你招惹過這群人嗎
You ever mess with these guys?

94
00:04:54,890 --> 00:04:56,000
他們無惡不作
They're bad news.

95
00:04:56,000 --> 00:04:57,460
高中的時候就因為我兄弟看了他們一眼
They attacked my brother back in high school

96
00:04:57,460 --> 00:04:58,890
就被他們揍了
just for looking in their direction.

97
00:04:58,890 --> 00:05:00,460
那個兄弟  高個那個
Which brother, the tall one

98
00:05:00,460 --> 00:05:02,240
還是那個屁股很翹的弟弟
or the younger one with the cute butt?

99
00:05:02,360 --> 00:05:03,250
是弟弟
Younger one.

100
00:05:03,840 --> 00:05:05,250
他屁股一點也不翹
There's nothing cute about him.

101
00:05:05,340 --> 00:05:07,600
別擔心  你屁股也很翹
Don't worry. Your butt's cute, too.

102
00:05:09,170 --> 00:05:10,880
這些人為什么要騷擾你
So why are these guys harassing you?

103
00:05:11,140 --> 00:05:12,890
他們認為你背叛了他們嗎
Do they feel betrayed by you?

104
00:05:13,050 --> 00:05:14,280
是  必須的
Well, yeah. They have to,

105
00:05:14,580 --> 00:05:16,950
不然他們就得面對現實  面對自己的真實面目
or they'll have to face the truth of who they really are.

106
00:05:17,480 --> 00:05:20,310
你把所有時間都用來憤怒  憎恨他人
You spend all your time pissed off, hating people

107
00:05:20,380 --> 00:05:21,880
就因為你被灌輸的那些東西
because of stuff you've been told

108
00:05:21,970 --> 00:05:25,020
又或者自己的生活不順
or because things just suck

109
00:05:25,020 --> 00:05:26,820
而非得怪在別人頭上
and it's got to be someone else's fault.

110
00:05:26,820 --> 00:05:27,900
你是怎么突然變了呢
What's changed in you?

111
00:05:28,270 --> 00:05:29,560
我遇到了克里斯蒂娜
I met Christina.

112
00:05:30,950 --> 00:05:32,690
他跟你講過多少他過去的事情
How much has he told you about his past?

113
00:05:33,430 --> 00:05:34,760
他很誠實
He's honest.

114
00:05:36,190 --> 00:05:37,590
他告訴我的那些  并不是我愛上的那個人
What he told me didn't fit with the guy

115
00:05:37,590 --> 00:05:38,910
身上所具有的東西
that I fell in love with.

116
00:05:39,220 --> 00:05:41,170
他跟他父親之間有很多問題
He had a lot of issues with his father.

117
00:05:42,010 --> 00:05:43,220
他的憎恨都是后天的
His hate was learned,

118
00:05:43,220 --> 00:05:44,950
我知道那都是可以忘卻的
but I knew that it could be unlearned.

119
00:05:46,210 --> 00:05:48,090
他真的很努力想要成為更好的人
He really wants to be a better man,

120
00:05:49,050 --> 00:05:51,430
每一天他的行為都向我證明他已經變了
and he's proving to me every day that he's changed,

121
00:05:52,850 --> 00:05:55,670
但我看得出過去還是對他影響很大
but I can tell that this is taking a toll on him.

122
00:05:57,430 --> 00:05:58,560
你能幫我們嗎
Can you help us?

123
00:06:01,430 --> 00:06:02,770
問她話的那個人是誰
Who's she talking to in there?

124
00:06:04,060 --> 00:06:06,210
我上司  貝絲·戴維斯副隊長
My boss Lieutenant Davis.

125
00:06:06,260 --> 00:06:07,280
她是亞洲人
She's Asian.

126
00:06:07,520 --> 00:06:09,080
美籍越南裔
Vietnamese American.

127
00:06:10,310 --> 00:06:11,410
有問題嗎
Is that a problem?

128
00:06:11,920 --> 00:06:12,570
可能吧
Could be.

129
00:06:12,580 --> 00:06:13,420
為什么
How so?

130
00:06:14,560 --> 00:06:16,450
我認為沒多少人會同情
I don't think many people are gonna be too sympathetic

131
00:06:16,450 --> 00:06:19,840
我是誰  我到過什么地方
to who I was, where I been.

132
00:06:20,050 --> 00:06:22,850
你不能指望人們全盤接受你的過去  馬克
You can't expect people to be ok with your past, Mark.

133
00:06:23,570 --> 00:06:26,160
說實話  我就不認同  但這并不意味著
Honestly, I'm not, but that doesn't mean

134
00:06:26,160 --> 00:06:29,010
我會束手旁觀不去幫助你和你的家人
I won't do everything I can to help you and your family.

135
00:06:29,420 --> 00:06:31,440
南加州的新納粹勢力很廣
Neo-nazis in Southern California run

136
00:06:31,440 --> 00:06:34,650
從組織松散的光頭黨
the gamut from loosely organized Skinhead groups...

137
00:06:34,650 --> 00:06:37,190
他們針對執法機關進行襲擊和仇恨型犯罪
assaults, hate crimes, targeting law enforcement...

138
00:06:37,190 --> 00:06:40,200
到針對政治團體的有組織犯罪
to organized crime to political organizations

139
00:06:40,200 --> 00:06:41,570
但他們卻自稱沒有使用任何暴力手段
that claim to be nonviolent.

140
00:06:41,680 --> 00:06:44,000
光頭黨源自"雅利安國"組織
Skinheads have their roots in the Aryan Nation,

141
00:06:44,000 --> 00:06:45,870
而該組織又源自于加州監獄系統
which started out of the California Prison System,

142
00:06:45,870 --> 00:06:48,390
這地方簡直是光頭黨的哈佛
AKA the Harvard for Skinheads,

143
00:06:48,390 --> 00:06:51,550
現在他們組織嚴密  行動協調且受過良好教育
but today, they're highly organized, coordinated, educated.

144
00:06:51,560 --> 00:06:53,380
能夠意識到自己是少數派
Wise to the fact that they're in the minority.

145
00:06:53,380 --> 00:06:56,070
他們更傾向于顛覆或騷擾
They're more apt to subvert and harass

146
00:06:56,070 --> 00:06:57,770
而非公然襲擊或者破壞
than brazenly attack and harm.

147
00:06:58,060 --> 00:07:00,410
你可以說他們是專業跟蹤者
You might say skinheads are professional stalkers.

148
00:07:00,570 --> 00:07:02,230
他們知道如何鉆法律的空子
They know how to bend the law without breaking it.

149
00:07:02,230 --> 00:07:04,240
他們通過招募年輕人的多少來評級
They grow their ranks by recruiting young,

150
00:07:04,240 --> 00:07:05,510
一般都是問題青少年
usually troubled teens.

151
00:07:05,510 --> 00:07:06,850
給一個不合群的人信仰
Give a loner something to believe in,

152
00:07:06,850 --> 00:07:08,390
讓他成為團體的一個部分
a community to be a part of,

153
00:07:08,390 --> 00:07:09,430
這對那些問題青年來說吸引力很大
it's a powerful thing.

154
00:07:09,430 --> 00:07:10,670
看看這個人
I mean, look at this guy.

155
00:07:10,850 --> 00:07:14,170
我知道他曾是鬧心的白人至上和種族主義者
I know he was a white supremacist and a racist, disgusting,

156
00:07:14,170 --> 00:07:17,020
但他已經竭盡全力去改變自己的生活
but he's gone to great length to change his life.

157
00:07:17,540 --> 00:07:18,780
拜托  杰克
Come on, Jack.

158
00:07:18,850 --> 00:07:21,380
你真以為這種內心的偏執會消失嗎
You really think that kind of embedded bigotry goes away?

159
00:07:22,000 --> 00:07:22,920
我相信他
I believe him.

160
00:07:23,420 --> 00:07:24,310
令人震驚
Shocker.

161
00:07:24,610 --> 00:07:26,860
本  從幫派和販毒組織開始查
Ben, start with gangs and narcotics.

162
00:07:26,860 --> 00:07:29,140
詹妮絲  調出去年所有的仇恨型犯罪記錄
Janice, pull up all the hate crimes in the last year.

163
00:07:29,140 --> 00:07:30,520
我想拿到一份光頭黨名單
I want a list of Skinhead groups,

164
00:07:30,520 --> 00:07:32,190
相關組織  姓名  地址
affiliations, names, addresses.

165
00:07:32,190 --> 00:07:33,550
找找看誰才是幕后黑手
Let's find out who's doing this.

166
00:08:26,510 --> 00:08:27,300
爸爸
Dad?

167
00:08:27,700 --> 00:08:30,120
嗨  你還好嗎
Oh. Hey. You ok?

168
00:08:30,510 --> 00:08:31,610
我睡不著
I couldn't sleep.

169
00:08:32,000 --> 00:08:33,540
我想看電視
I wanted to watch TV.

170
00:08:35,060 --> 00:08:36,860
爸爸告訴你個好事
Well, now let me tell you what.

171
00:08:39,090 --> 00:08:40,740
想和爸爸媽媽一起睡嗎
You want to sleep with your mom and me?

172
00:08:45,970 --> 00:08:47,700
你快點到媽媽身邊去
Why don't you go crawl in bed with your mom, ok?

173
00:09:10,560 --> 00:09:11,960
很長時間不見了  馬克
It's been a long time, Mark.

174
00:09:12,560 --> 00:09:13,530
你看起來不錯
You look good.

175
00:09:15,430 --> 00:09:16,280
你是誰
Who's this?

176
00:09:17,400 --> 00:09:18,350
朋友
A friend.

177
00:09:19,090 --> 00:09:20,390
你覺得你安全嗎
You think you're safe?

178
00:09:20,890 --> 00:09:22,990
只要我們想  就可以隨時弄死你
We can get to you whenever we want.

179
00:09:23,250 --> 00:09:24,980
是嗎  我已經叫警察了
Yeah? Well, I've already called the cops.

180
00:09:25,390 --> 00:09:27,320
他們可沒法及時趕到拯救你的妻女
They won't make it in time to save your family.

181
00:09:30,030 --> 00:09:32,840
馬克  馬克  有人在外面
Mark, Mark, someone's outside.

182
00:09:33,250 --> 00:09:34,490
親愛的  別站在窗前
Honey, get away from the window.

183
00:09:34,490 --> 00:09:36,230
她一動就得死
She moves, she dies.

184
00:09:36,250 --> 00:09:37,580
等等  別動
Wait, wait, don't move!

185
00:09:39,950 --> 00:09:42,850
求你們  別這樣
Please. Don't do this.

186
00:09:45,200 --> 00:09:47,800
要你妻子活還是你混血孩子活
Your wife or your half-breed kid.

187
00:09:47,800 --> 00:09:48,630
爸爸
Dad!

188
00:09:48,790 --> 00:09:49,890
你自己選
You choose.

189
00:09:49,910 --> 00:09:51,380
不  快停下
No! Just stop!

190
00:09:52,410 --> 00:09:54,200
你的命是我的
Your life belongs to me.

191
00:09:56,260 --> 00:09:57,230
趴下  趴下
Down, down!

192
00:10:00,000 --> 00:10:00,780
你還好嗎
You ok?

193
00:10:00,980 --> 00:10:01,750
我沒事
I'm ok.

194
00:10:02,850 --> 00:10:04,890
蘭登  蘭登
Landon? Landon.

195
00:10:05,960 --> 00:10:06,780
你沒事吧
Are you all right?

196
00:10:24,300 --> 00:10:25,600
他叫查德·休伊特
His name's Chad Hewitt.

197
00:10:25,600 --> 00:10:27,670
查德·休伊特  好吧
Chad Hewitt. Ok.

198
00:10:27,670 --> 00:10:29,560
我知道是他  是他的聲音
I know it was him. That was his voice.

199
00:10:29,950 --> 00:10:31,340
我以為他還在監獄
Thought he was still in prison.

200
00:10:31,380 --> 00:10:32,790
我會讓本去追蹤他
I'll have Ben run him down.

201
00:10:33,570 --> 00:10:35,090
我們今天會一直待在這里
We'll keep a presence here today.

202
00:10:35,340 --> 00:10:36,210
我們和你的鄰居談過
We spoke to your neighbors,

203
00:10:36,210 --> 00:10:37,610
解釋了一下情況
explained the situation.

204
00:10:37,730 --> 00:10:38,920
什么鄰居
What neighbors?

205
00:10:39,070 --> 00:10:40,250
他們現在都恨死我們了
They hate us now,

206
00:10:40,810 --> 00:10:42,710
覺得我嫁給了一個光頭黨
think I'm married to a Skinhead.

207
00:10:44,250 --> 00:10:45,710
這是跟蹤者的典型手法
This is what stalkers do.

208
00:10:46,110 --> 00:10:47,160
他們孤立你
They isolate you,

209
00:10:47,160 --> 00:10:48,710
讓你失去安全感
they remove your sense of safety.

210
00:10:48,710 --> 00:10:51,260
你脆弱而孤獨的時候更容易受到驚嚇
It's easier to terrorize you if you're vulnerable and alone.

211
00:10:51,490 --> 00:10:52,990
他們昨晚差點殺了我們
They were gonna kill us last night.

212
00:10:52,990 --> 00:10:55,710
但最后他們沒動手  這很能說明問題
But they didn't, and that tells us volumes.

213
00:10:55,860 --> 00:10:57,270
他們不是想殺了你
They're not trying to kill you,

214
00:10:57,960 --> 00:10:59,040
不然他們就動手了
or they would have.

215
00:10:59,040 --> 00:11:00,930
不是他們  是他
Not them. Him.

216
00:11:01,220 --> 00:11:03,010
他們有個幕后主使
One guy's behind all of this.

217
00:11:04,310 --> 00:11:06,460
查德·休伊特在科克倫監獄服刑11年
Chad Hewitt did 11 years in Corcoran,

218
00:11:06,460 --> 00:11:08,880
8個月前被釋放  就在村里住了下來
released 8 months ago, settled in the valley.

219
00:11:08,920 --> 00:11:10,090
網上沒什么蹤跡
Not much of an online presence,

220
00:11:10,090 --> 00:11:11,880
但他似乎又組建了一個新的組織
but it looks like he started his own group,

221
00:11:11,880 --> 00:11:15,140
南加州社會主義同盟
The Southern California Confederated Socialists.

222
00:11:15,140 --> 00:11:16,570
政治團體
A political organization.

223
00:11:16,570 --> 00:11:18,490
我們自行改過自新的光頭黨
Our self-reformed Skinhead is being stalked

224
00:11:18,490 --> 00:11:19,790
被一個剛出獄的光頭黨跟蹤
by a prison-reformed Skinhead.

225
00:11:19,790 --> 00:11:20,800
查查他的底
Let's check him out.

226
00:11:23,170 --> 00:11:24,520
你有多了解查德
How well do you know Chad?

227
00:11:24,860 --> 00:11:26,110
是我招募的他
I recruited him.

228
00:11:28,450 --> 00:11:30,610
我招他進來的時候他還只是一個青少年
Guy was just a teenager when I brought him in.

229
00:11:31,020 --> 00:11:32,620
我把他從地痞那里救出來的
Saved him from some bullies.

230
00:11:33,960 --> 00:11:35,180
我教他如何打架
I taught him how to fight,

231
00:11:35,180 --> 00:11:36,340
給他信心
gave him confidence.

232
00:11:37,300 --> 00:11:39,730
教他學會忠誠
I taught him loyalty and one truth

233
00:11:39,740 --> 00:11:41,120
還有一條真理
above anything else...

234
00:11:42,040 --> 00:11:44,550
沒有家庭你就一文不值
You are nothing without family.

235
00:11:46,810 --> 00:11:48,370
好的  知道了
Ok. Got it.

236
00:11:49,540 --> 00:11:51,290
本和貝絲在調查查德·休伊特
Ben and Beth are checking out Chad Hewitt.

237
00:11:51,290 --> 00:11:53,360
鑒證科在調查扔進窗子的磚塊
S.I.D. has the brick that came through the window.

238
00:11:53,450 --> 00:11:54,310
他們在追查手機的位置
They're tracing the cell,

239
00:11:54,310 --> 00:11:55,640
最后肯定會查出是一次性手機
which will inevitably lead to a burner

240
00:11:55,640 --> 00:11:57,100
因為光頭黨都非常小心
because these guys are careful.

241
00:11:58,190 --> 00:11:58,970
怎么了
What?

242
00:12:00,430 --> 00:12:02,860
鄰居家的監控錄像
Security cameras on the neighbors' houses.

243
00:12:03,240 --> 00:12:05,290
有沒有可能案發時有攝像頭在運作
What are the chances one of them was actually working

244
00:12:05,300 --> 00:12:07,070
記錄下了光頭黨的樣子
and caught the skinheads on camera?

245
00:12:13,750 --> 00:12:14,560
有什么能幫你的嗎
Can I help you?

246
00:12:14,830 --> 00:12:16,640
你昨晚聽到或看到什么了嗎
Did you see or hear or anything last night?

247
00:12:16,640 --> 00:12:18,670
沒有  我也不會
Nope, and I'm not gonna be the one

248
00:12:18,670 --> 00:12:19,760
幫助光頭黨的人
helping out a skinhead.

249
00:12:19,760 --> 00:12:21,540
你是說理查德先生嗎
Are you referring to Mr. Richards?

250
00:12:22,900 --> 00:12:24,890
我從來不用監控設備
I never felt the need for security cameras.

251
00:12:24,890 --> 00:12:26,140
這個社區很安全
This is a good neighborhood,

252
00:12:26,550 --> 00:12:28,180
或是說曾經很安全
or--or was.

253
00:12:29,870 --> 00:12:30,920
馬蒂  閉嘴
Shut up, Marty.

254
00:12:31,240 --> 00:12:33,490
我們是想查看一下您家里的監控錄像
I'm here about the security cameras on your property.

255
00:12:33,510 --> 00:12:35,430
看起來某一個很可能拍攝下了
Looks like one in particular might have recorded

256
00:12:35,430 --> 00:12:36,460
昨晚的案發場景
our crime scene last night.

257
00:12:36,460 --> 00:12:39,070
我不想卷入光頭黨間暴力報復中
I don't want to get caught in skinhead on skinhead violence.

258
00:12:39,070 --> 00:12:40,260
我可不想被他們盯上
I don't want them coming for me.

259
00:12:40,260 --> 00:12:40,880
聽著  我會調取監控
Look. I'll look back through

260
00:12:40,880 --> 00:12:42,450
一有發現就告訴你
the footage myself and let you know.

261
00:12:42,450 --> 00:12:44,120
請務必盡快
As soon as possible, if you would.

262
00:12:44,200 --> 00:12:45,170
謝謝了
I'd appreciate it.

263
00:12:46,380 --> 00:12:47,210
我理解您的猶豫
Look. I get your hesitance...

264
00:12:47,210 --> 00:12:49,070
先去申請搜查令再來吧
Go get a warrant, and we'll talk.

265
00:12:58,080 --> 00:12:59,900
我們要找的是希特勒式狂熱份子嗎
Not what I expected of wannabe Hitler.

266
00:12:59,910 --> 00:13:02,160
他父親因為癌癥去世了  沒有別的家人
Well, his father died of cancer and no other family.

267
00:13:02,160 --> 00:13:03,910
查德繼承了房子跟財產
Chad inherited the house and some money,

268
00:13:03,910 --> 00:13:05,560
同時還在派科依瑪有一家單車行
also owns a bike shop in Pacoima.

269
00:13:14,230 --> 00:13:15,230
{\an8}南加州社會主義同盟會

270
00:13:19,580 --> 00:13:21,690
有警察找你
Hey. It's the police.

271
00:13:25,490 --> 00:13:26,920
你們的消息不可靠
You got some bad intel.

272
00:13:27,280 --> 00:13:28,650
這里沒有光頭黨
No skinheads around here.

273
00:13:28,660 --> 00:13:30,510
這里每個人都留著頭發
Full heads of hair everywhere I look.

274
00:13:30,810 --> 00:13:33,060
你是某個白色人種優越論組織的領導者  對嗎
You're the leader of a white supremacist group, correct?

275
00:13:33,090 --> 00:13:34,330
是白人分離論
White separatists.

276
00:13:34,330 --> 00:13:35,420
兩者是有區別的
There's a difference.

277
00:13:35,420 --> 00:13:37,510
要怎么在洛杉磯實現種族分離  先生
How does one separate the races in l.A., sir?

278
00:13:37,520 --> 00:13:39,310
你不是光頭黨成員  明白了
You're not a skinhead. Got it.

279
00:13:39,310 --> 00:13:41,380
我們調查你是因為懷疑你
We're investigating you on suspicion

280
00:13:41,380 --> 00:13:43,000
跟蹤了馬克·理查德
of stalking Mark Richards.

281
00:13:43,000 --> 00:13:44,030
你昨晚給他打過電話嗎
Did you call him last night?

282
00:13:44,940 --> 00:13:47,520
去給你媽媽幫忙  快去
Hey. Go help your mom. Go.

283
00:13:49,330 --> 00:13:50,740
那是我女朋友的孩子
That's my girlfriend's kid.

284
00:13:51,330 --> 00:13:53,010
他不習慣跟不友善的人來往
He's not used to unfriendlies.

285
00:13:53,010 --> 00:13:55,480
理查德一家遭到光頭黨的襲擊
The Richards family has been targeted by skinheads.

286
00:13:55,480 --> 00:13:57,060
你跟他們脫不了干系
You clearly associate with them.

287
00:13:57,680 --> 00:14:00,070
我們是非暴力的政治組織
We're a nonviolent political organization.

288
00:14:00,440 --> 00:14:02,160
中間大部分人都有家庭  有孩子
Most of us have families, kids.

289
00:14:02,160 --> 00:14:04,510
我們只想給他們創建一個更好的世界
We--we just want a better world for them.

290
00:14:04,520 --> 00:14:06,670
你最后一次見馬克·理查德是什么時候
When was the last time you saw Mark Richards?

291
00:14:06,740 --> 00:14:08,000
你是指馬克·伊萬斯嗎
You mean Mark Evans?

292
00:14:08,660 --> 00:14:10,690
改名換姓  也改變不了自己是誰
Changing your name doesn't change who you are.

293
00:14:11,620 --> 00:14:13,510
所以你知道我們在說誰
So you know who we're referring to.

294
00:14:14,010 --> 00:14:15,980
是的  馬克把我從高中招募出來
Yeah. Mark recruited me out of high school.

295
00:14:16,590 --> 00:14:17,940
他曾經是光頭黨成員
Now he was a skinhead.

296
00:14:18,580 --> 00:14:20,050
他教會我如何去認識這個世界
He taught me about the world,

297
00:14:20,220 --> 00:14:21,650
了解它的不公正
its injustices.

298
00:14:21,660 --> 00:14:24,890
他真的想去改變社會  糾正它的錯誤
He really wanted to change society and its wrongs,

299
00:14:24,890 --> 00:14:26,530
我相信我們可以辦到
and I believed that we could do it.

300
00:14:26,920 --> 00:14:28,560
我曾經是他引以為傲的戰士
I was his proud soldier.

301
00:14:29,210 --> 00:14:30,560
他已經改過自新了
He's moved on.

302
00:14:30,980 --> 00:14:32,130
也許你也該放下過去
Maybe you should, too.

303
00:14:33,980 --> 00:14:35,270
這就是你來這里的原因嗎
Is that why you're here,

304
00:14:36,290 --> 00:14:38,600
來給我智慧箴言嗎
to give me that pearl of wisdom?

305
00:14:40,660 --> 00:14:41,950
我也已經放下了過去
Look. I've moved on.

306
00:14:42,850 --> 00:14:44,840
馬克讓我的人生偏離了正軌
Mark sidelined my life.

307
00:14:44,840 --> 00:14:46,480
我因為他進了監獄
I went to prison because of him.

308
00:14:46,480 --> 00:14:48,570
你進監獄是因為你把人弄昏迷了
You went to prison because you put a man in a coma.

309
00:14:48,570 --> 00:14:50,220
我不喜歡你們來這里
Look. I don't appreciate you coming here,

310
00:14:50,220 --> 00:14:52,250
把自己當客人
guesting in my home,

311
00:14:52,250 --> 00:14:54,370
在孩子面前拿著手槍警徽招搖
waving your guns and your badges around the kids,

312
00:14:54,380 --> 00:14:55,630
對支付你們薪水的一般民眾
and leering in judgment

313
00:14:55,640 --> 00:14:58,070
妄下判斷
of the very people who pay your salaries.

314
00:14:58,070 --> 00:15:00,120
我們很樂意帶你回局里詳談
We'd be happy to discuss this downtown.

315
00:15:01,990 --> 00:15:04,860
你們二位對我個人和我的信仰評頭論足
You two sit in judgment of me and my beliefs,

316
00:15:05,680 --> 00:15:07,330
但至少它們正直誠信
but they come with integrity.

317
00:15:07,370 --> 00:15:08,160
而你們的呢
Do yours?

318
00:15:08,160 --> 00:15:09,450
所以你一個正直的光頭黨成員
So you're a good skinhead?

319
00:15:09,450 --> 00:15:10,510
注意一點
Hey. Watch it!

320
00:15:11,820 --> 00:15:12,750
那個詞
That word...

321
00:15:13,990 --> 00:15:17,220
這些孩子已經因自己信仰被折磨得夠慘了
These kids already get enough torment for their beliefs,

322
00:15:17,710 --> 00:15:19,090
現在他們還得在自家燒烤聚會上
And now they have to hear that word

323
00:15:19,090 --> 00:15:22,780
聽到有色人種的洛杉磯警方說出這個詞
from the colorful LAPD at their own barbecue?

324
00:15:25,100 --> 00:15:27,630
舉個例子  警探  如果我跟你說
For instance, detective, if I were to tell you

325
00:15:27,630 --> 00:15:29,010
從哪里來回哪里去
to go back to where you came from...

326
00:15:29,020 --> 00:15:32,050
不管是墨西哥  還是中國
what, Mexico, China...

327
00:15:33,820 --> 00:15:35,110
會讓你覺得不好受嗎
would that hurt your feelings?

328
00:15:36,360 --> 00:15:38,430
那么你們憑什么可以評價我
So what gives you the right to judge me

329
00:15:38,430 --> 00:15:39,660
評價我要捍衛的東西
and what I stand for?

330
00:15:40,300 --> 00:15:42,110
憑你脖子上的刺青  先生
That tattoo on your neck does, sir.

331
00:15:42,540 --> 00:15:44,670
它說明你信仰的是仇恨與偏見
It tells me you stand for hatred and bigotry

332
00:15:44,670 --> 00:15:46,370
崇尚種族分裂的世界
and believe in a world of separation.

333
00:15:47,060 --> 00:15:48,340
我有道理這么評價你
I'm ok with judging that.

334
00:15:48,340 --> 00:15:51,200
本  休伊特先生  這是對你的警告
Ben. Mr. Hewitt, this is your only warning.

335
00:15:52,280 --> 00:15:53,960
離馬克和他的家人遠點
Stay away from Mark and his family.

336
00:15:54,830 --> 00:15:55,620
我們走
Let's go.

337
00:16:06,510 --> 00:16:08,270
才放手讓你上場五分鐘而已
I let you out of the bullpen for 5 minutes...

338
00:16:08,270 --> 00:16:10,660
抱歉  我剛剛做得太過了嗎
I'm sorry. Was I too much back there?

339
00:16:11,820 --> 00:16:13,570
不不  做得很好
No. No, you were good.

340
00:16:14,090 --> 00:16:15,070
你相信他嗎
Do you believe him?

341
00:16:15,090 --> 00:16:17,030
他把自己被拋棄的怨念
He's all abandonment issues wrapped up

342
00:16:17,040 --> 00:16:18,760
以謹慎隱藏的憤怒展露
in carefully concealed rage.

343
00:16:18,760 --> 00:16:20,040
我不覺得這件事是因為馬克離開了
I don't think this is about the group

344
00:16:20,050 --> 00:16:22,010
所以組織要報復他
wanting revenge on Mark because he left.

345
00:16:22,030 --> 00:16:23,280
這是查德和馬克的私人恩怨
This is about Chad and Mark.

346
00:16:23,280 --> 00:16:25,390
查德顯然有戀父情節
Chad's clearly got daddy issues.

347
00:16:25,630 --> 00:16:26,560
誰沒有呢
Who doesn't?

348
00:16:26,830 --> 00:16:28,450
他把馬克當成父親
He saw Mark as af father figure,

349
00:16:28,530 --> 00:16:30,010
他們的關系牢不可摧
impossible bond to break.

350
00:16:30,010 --> 00:16:31,010
不是牢不可摧
Not impossible.

351
00:16:31,370 --> 00:16:33,140
"沒有家人你就一文不值"
"You're nothing without family."

352
00:16:33,970 --> 00:16:34,730
什么
What?

353
00:16:36,420 --> 00:16:37,730
馬克說過的一句話
Something Mark said.

354
00:16:38,560 --> 00:16:39,550
他離開了兄弟會
He left the brotherhood,

355
00:16:39,550 --> 00:16:40,860
娶了別的種族的妻子
he marries outside his race,

356
00:16:40,870 --> 00:16:41,720
跟他教給查德信仰
he rejects everything,

357
00:16:41,720 --> 00:16:43,350
背道而馳
he taught Chad to believe in.

358
00:16:43,610 --> 00:16:45,590
就好像弗蘭肯斯坦博士
It's like Dr. Frankenstein turning his back

359
00:16:45,590 --> 00:16:47,190
拋棄了自己創造的科學怪人
on the monster he created.

360
00:16:47,420 --> 00:16:49,820
那科學怪人想要什么
And what does the monster want?

361
00:16:49,820 --> 00:16:51,150
他是怨恨性跟蹤者
He's a resentful stalker.

362
00:16:51,250 --> 00:16:52,810
覺得被拋棄了  但更重要的是
He feels rejected, but more than that,

363
00:16:52,810 --> 00:16:55,160
他覺得自己被辜負了
he feels personally wronged.

364
00:16:55,160 --> 00:16:56,880
當得知馬克的新生活后
Discovering what Mark did with his life

365
00:16:56,880 --> 00:16:58,410
查德一定備受打擊
must have been a real blow for Chad.

366
00:16:58,420 --> 00:17:00,730
這很可能是他創建這個組織的初衷
It's probably why he started the group in the first place.

367
00:17:01,060 --> 00:17:02,540
現在他想利用這支力量
Now he wants to use that army

368
00:17:02,540 --> 00:17:04,550
來毀掉馬克的生活
to destroy the life that Mark created for himself.

369
00:17:04,550 --> 00:17:06,800
科學怪人想讓馬克重返兄弟會
The monster wants Mark to return to the brotherhood.

370
00:17:06,850 --> 00:17:08,260
他不相信他已經徹底改過自新了
He doesn't believe he's reformed.

371
00:17:10,040 --> 00:17:12,900
各位  今天向法官遞交
Guys, submit an emergency protective order

372
00:17:12,920 --> 00:17:14,780
針對查德的緊急保護令
against Chad to the judge today.

373
00:17:14,780 --> 00:17:15,950
今晚牢牢看好他
I want him served tonight.

374
00:17:16,110 --> 00:17:18,380
這樣他不能靠近他們100碼之內
So he can't come within 100 yards of them.

375
00:17:18,520 --> 00:17:19,810
他幫派的其他成員呢
What about the rest of his gang?

376
00:17:20,160 --> 00:17:21,490
貝絲  現在有空嗎
Hey, Beth. You got a sec?

377
00:17:21,490 --> 00:17:24,360
有的  威爾克斯警探  進來吧
Yeah. Detective Wilkes, come on in.

378
00:17:26,320 --> 00:17:29,000
我知道你今天早上
I, uh, understand you paid a visit

379
00:17:29,000 --> 00:17:30,590
拜訪了查德
to Chad hewitt this morning.

380
00:17:30,820 --> 00:17:32,440
沒錯  你怎么知道的
That's right. How'd you know that?

381
00:17:32,540 --> 00:17:33,780
我是特別小組的成員
Well, I'm part of a task force

382
00:17:33,790 --> 00:17:34,970
專門負責監視他
that's been surveilling him

383
00:17:34,970 --> 00:17:36,310
到現在已經有兩個月了
for a couple of months now.

384
00:17:36,470 --> 00:17:38,020
休伊特在山里
Hewitt's been building a group of neo-nazis

385
00:17:38,020 --> 00:17:39,610
成功建立了一個新納粹組織
in the valley successfully.

386
00:17:39,610 --> 00:17:41,900
他把暴力的成員和黨派成員分隔開了
He keeps the violent members compartmentalized

387
00:17:41,900 --> 00:17:44,070
但是  他確實在組建軍隊
from the political, but, yeah, he's building an army,

388
00:17:44,070 --> 00:17:44,760
所以我們想把他們擊垮
and we want to take it down.

389
00:17:44,760 --> 00:17:46,480
他利用自己的軍隊來跟蹤一個家庭
He's using that army to stalk a family.

390
00:17:46,480 --> 00:17:47,530
我們正在努力保護那家人
We're trying to protect them.

391
00:17:47,540 --> 00:17:48,980
特別小組努力保護的
The task force is trying to protect

392
00:17:48,980 --> 00:17:50,340
是整個社區
an entire community.

393
00:17:50,510 --> 00:17:51,900
反正你們的目標不也是光頭黨嗎
Isn't your guy a skinhead anyway?

394
00:17:51,900 --> 00:17:54,380
他改過自新了  不同以往
He's reformed. He's not that guy anymore.

395
00:17:54,390 --> 00:17:56,120
江山易改  本性難移
Well, people only change so much,

396
00:17:56,150 --> 00:17:57,200
不是嗎  杰克
don't you think, Jack?

397
00:18:00,200 --> 00:18:02,070
你是在讓我們遠離查德嗎
Are you telling us to stay away from Chad?

398
00:18:02,070 --> 00:18:03,830
我認為這沒必要變成一場競爭
I don't think this has to become adversarial.

399
00:18:03,830 --> 00:18:04,760
那就別插手
Then stay out of it.

400
00:18:05,010 --> 00:18:06,710
我這是在努力根除這些黨羽
I'm trying to cut the head off this beast,

401
00:18:06,710 --> 00:18:08,470
而不是以小罪名把休伊特關起來
not get Hewitt on some misdemeanor

402
00:18:08,470 --> 00:18:10,290
六個月后又把他放出來
so he can just get back out in 6 months.

403
00:18:10,290 --> 00:18:11,720
如果你們現在驚動他
And if you spook him now,

404
00:18:11,720 --> 00:18:13,310
他可能會打消原本的計劃
he may pull back from his plans.

405
00:18:13,310 --> 00:18:15,250
那正好  因為這正是我們的職責
Well, good. Because that's what we do here,

406
00:18:15,250 --> 00:18:17,230
希望能阻止他鬧出人命
and hopefully we stop him from killing someone.

407
00:18:18,570 --> 00:18:19,530
還有事嗎
Anything else?

408
00:18:21,560 --> 00:18:22,470
談話愉快
Always a pleasure.

409
00:18:27,340 --> 00:18:29,040
我不得不遠離小區
I had to get out of the neighborhood.

410
00:18:29,550 --> 00:18:31,500
我開始有種被禁錮的感覺
I was starting to feel all cooped up,

411
00:18:31,500 --> 00:18:33,260
所以我就把他帶來運動場
so I just brought him to the playground.

412
00:18:34,360 --> 00:18:37,690
他看著很好  已經交上一些朋友了
Well, he seems fine. I mean, he's already made a few friends.

413
00:18:39,940 --> 00:18:40,840
我不知道  不清楚
I don't know. I don't know.

414
00:18:40,840 --> 00:18:43,690
我可以和我姐姐談談  看能不能和她住
I might talk to my sister, see if we can stay with her.

415
00:18:44,360 --> 00:18:47,450
馬克希望我們去  是啊
Mark wants us to. Yeah.

416
00:18:47,540 --> 00:18:48,320
我去拿
I got it!

417
00:18:57,900 --> 00:18:59,260
你是在找這個嗎  小家伙
Hey. You looking for this, little guy?

418
00:19:01,130 --> 00:19:02,980
我也在想該怎么辦
Yeah. I'm trying to figure out what to do.

419
00:19:11,210 --> 00:19:15,280
我回頭再打給你好嗎
Um, I got to call you back, ok? Ok.

420
00:19:16,320 --> 00:19:17,200
蘭登
Landon?

421
00:19:19,650 --> 00:19:20,560
蘭登
Landon?

422
00:19:21,590 --> 00:19:22,410
蘭登
Landon?

423
00:19:27,240 --> 00:19:28,890
我爸爸也有這樣的紋身
My dad has one of those.

424
00:19:30,100 --> 00:19:31,740
他說這代表的是壞事
He says it means a bad thing.

425
00:19:32,090 --> 00:19:33,020
不是壞事
Aw, it's not bad.

426
00:19:34,720 --> 00:19:37,340
這是一種力量和強大的標志
It's a symbol of strength and power

427
00:19:38,390 --> 00:19:39,470
就像你爸爸一樣
just like your dad.

428
00:19:42,560 --> 00:19:44,420
別急  小家伙
Ah. Don't be in such a hurry, buddy.

429
00:19:45,730 --> 00:19:47,200
你喜歡摩托車嗎
Do you like motorcycles?

430
00:19:48,370 --> 00:19:49,850
因為如果你想騎摩托
Because, you know, if you want to ride a motorcycle,

431
00:19:49,860 --> 00:19:51,550
你該讓你爸爸來找我
you should tell your dad to come see me.

432
00:19:53,810 --> 00:19:55,830
蘭登  過來這里
Landon, get over here!

433
00:19:58,350 --> 00:19:59,580
你有個很勇敢的兒子
You got a brave boy there.

434
00:20:01,300 --> 00:20:02,210
你想做什么
What do you want?

435
00:20:02,480 --> 00:20:03,740
我只是在陪陪他
I was just keeping him company.

436
00:20:05,020 --> 00:20:06,280
他一個人在這
He was here all alone.

437
00:20:07,100 --> 00:20:09,560
社會上到處是可怕的人
Society is full of unsavory people.

438
00:20:09,820 --> 00:20:11,630
作為母親  你應該更加小心
As a mother, you should be more careful.

439
00:20:13,480 --> 00:20:14,560
放過我們
Leave us alone.

440
00:20:15,800 --> 00:20:17,200
很高興見到你
It was nice to meet you.

441
00:20:17,540 --> 00:20:18,650
我也是  小家伙
You, too, buddy.

442
00:20:30,200 --> 00:20:31,680
保護令已經生效
The protective order's in effect.

443
00:20:31,680 --> 00:20:34,150
如果他接近你或你的家人  我們可以逮捕他
If he comes near you or your family, we can arrest him.

444
00:20:34,150 --> 00:20:35,390
我想和查德談談
I want to talk to Chad.

445
00:20:35,390 --> 00:20:37,190
說不定他和我能把這事情談妥了
Look. Maybe he and I can just hash this out.

446
00:20:37,190 --> 00:20:39,280
和他見面是沒有好結果的
Nothing good can come from that meeting, Mark.

447
00:20:39,280 --> 00:20:40,910
聽著  他想要的是我
Listen. He wants me.

448
00:20:40,910 --> 00:20:43,880
和他聯系會變成一種無聲的支持和肯定
And contacting him would be tacit encouragement.

449
00:20:44,060 --> 00:20:45,710
他只會繼續追著你和你的家人
He'll only keep coming after you and your family.

450
00:20:45,710 --> 00:20:48,290
不不不  他是利用我的家人來接近我
No, no, no. He's using my family to get at me.

451
00:20:48,290 --> 00:20:49,300
他這招還是我教的
Look. I taught him that.

452
00:20:49,300 --> 00:20:51,070
請你耐心點  先生
You need to show a little patience here, sir.

453
00:20:51,950 --> 00:20:52,770
你是誰
Who are you?

454
00:20:53,540 --> 00:20:55,920
這位是搶劫兇案組的威爾克斯警探
This is detective Wilkes from robbery homicide.

455
00:20:55,920 --> 00:20:56,860
兇案組
Homicide?

456
00:20:57,060 --> 00:20:58,590
我知道這對你來說不容易
I know how difficult this is.

457
00:20:58,730 --> 00:21:00,560
當跟蹤的受害者開始預測
Stalking victims can often find themselves

458
00:21:00,560 --> 00:21:02,060
下一場跟蹤事故時
in a traumatic cycle where they start to

459
00:21:02,060 --> 00:21:04,060
他們常感到重復性受挫
anticipate the next stalking event.

460
00:21:04,060 --> 00:21:06,060
這種感覺  和創傷后精神障礙類似
The experience, it's not unlike PTSD.

461
00:21:06,060 --> 00:21:07,790
這會導致不理智的行為
It can lead to irrational acts.

462
00:21:08,060 --> 00:21:08,940
我并沒有失去理智
I'm not irrational.

463
00:21:10,140 --> 00:21:12,140
我只是不喜歡坐以待斃
I just don't like sitting around doing nothing.

464
00:21:12,180 --> 00:21:13,670
其實有件事你可以做
Well, there's something that you can do.

465
00:21:13,880 --> 00:21:16,000
洛杉磯警察已經在調查查德
LAPD has been investigating Chad,

466
00:21:16,000 --> 00:21:17,640
但還有關于他的事我們并不清楚
but there's still a lot we don't know about him,

467
00:21:17,640 --> 00:21:19,110
他的組織  以及其中的運作方式
his group, how they operate.

468
00:21:19,460 --> 00:21:21,950
你可以幫我們把查德關上很長一段時間
You could help us put Chad away for a very long time.

469
00:21:22,140 --> 00:21:24,280
如果我這么做  會被威脅一輩子
Look. I do that, I'm marked for life,

470
00:21:24,660 --> 00:21:27,060
不僅是查德  還有一切的光頭黨
not just by Chad but by every skinhead out there.

471
00:21:27,060 --> 00:21:28,510
是你一手造成的問題
You created this problem.

472
00:21:28,630 --> 00:21:30,060
你肯定能做些什么
There's something that you can do about it.

473
00:21:30,160 --> 00:21:31,340
你覺得這是我的報應嗎
You think I deserve this.

474
00:21:31,340 --> 00:21:32,260
沒有人這么想
No one thinks that.

475
00:21:32,260 --> 00:21:33,700
是  我就是這么認為
Uh, yeah, I do.

476
00:21:34,130 --> 00:21:35,230
這是你犯的錯
It is your fault, and you can do

477
00:21:35,230 --> 00:21:36,060
你可以做些事來補救
something to fix it.

478
00:21:36,060 --> 00:21:37,710
我這是在給你一條出路  馬克
I'm offering you a solution here, Mark.

479
00:21:37,710 --> 00:21:39,120
威爾克斯警探  夠了
Detective Wilkes, enough.

480
00:21:40,060 --> 00:21:40,670
馬克
Mark.

481
00:21:42,060 --> 00:21:43,130
你要相信我們
You got to trust us.

482
00:21:52,060 --> 00:21:53,920
弗蘭克讓蒂姆過來玩
Frank let tim come over and play.

483
00:21:54,060 --> 00:21:55,250
上帝保佑他
God bless him.

484
00:21:55,520 --> 00:21:57,370
我想讓你們立刻出發去你姐姐家
I want you guys to head over to your sister's.

485
00:21:57,490 --> 00:21:59,240
好嗎  他的一些東西我已經打包好了
All right? I packed up some of his stuff.

486
00:21:59,310 --> 00:22:00,670
我不會讓你一個人留在這的
I'm not leaving you here alone.

487
00:22:01,060 --> 00:22:02,450
咱們在一起更安全
We're safer if we're together.

488
00:22:03,760 --> 00:22:05,040
這東西拆不下來
It's not coming off.

489
00:22:05,550 --> 00:22:07,020
我們只是少個螺絲刀
We just need a screwdriver.

490
00:22:08,440 --> 00:22:10,270
他們從不允許我進去那里
I'm not supposed to go in there.

491
00:22:14,550 --> 00:22:16,550
就算為了我  好嗎
Please just do this for me, all right?

492
00:22:16,550 --> 00:22:18,490
我得確保你和蘭登的安全
I need to know that you and Landon are safe.

493
00:22:18,510 --> 00:22:19,840
呆在我身邊
Being around me right now,

494
00:22:20,670 --> 00:22:21,700
一點也不安全
it isn't safe.

495
00:22:27,450 --> 00:22:28,280
找到了
Here we go.

496
00:22:32,550 --> 00:22:34,570
這里一定有螺絲刀
There has to be a screwdriver in here.

497
00:22:34,720 --> 00:22:36,930
快點  免得被我爸爸看見
Hurry before my dad sees you.

498
00:22:42,180 --> 00:22:43,220
這東西真奇怪
That's weird.

499
00:22:43,580 --> 00:22:45,550
那放回去  咱們去問問我爸
Put it back, and let's go ask my dad.

500
00:22:45,550 --> 00:22:46,760
你會給我惹麻煩的
I'm going to get in trouble.

501
00:22:48,230 --> 00:22:50,440
這里有一個
Hey. Here's one.

502
00:22:54,550 --> 00:22:57,760
他難道不會跟著我去我姐姐家嗎
Then he will just follow me to my sister's house, won't he?

503
00:22:57,930 --> 00:22:58,810
下一步呢
Then what?

504
00:22:58,830 --> 00:22:59,580
我不知道
I don't know.

505
00:23:01,140 --> 00:23:01,990
蘭登
Landon!

506
00:23:02,350 --> 00:23:03,070
蘭登
Landon!

507
00:23:04,900 --> 00:23:05,700
蘭登
Landon!

508
00:23:06,120 --> 00:23:06,920
你還好嗎
Are you ok?

509
00:23:06,990 --> 00:23:09,410
蒂姆  蒂姆  你還好嗎
Tim, Tim, are you all right?

510
00:23:09,800 --> 00:23:11,190
好了  快點  大家都進去
All right. Let's go. Everybody inside.

511
00:23:11,190 --> 00:23:12,130
快  快點
Come on, come on.

512
00:23:51,640 --> 00:23:52,440
有人嗎
Hello?

513
00:24:29,690 --> 00:24:31,470
馬克·伊萬斯
Mark Evans. Heh.

514
00:24:32,680 --> 00:24:34,000
我剛剛看到你兒子了
Hey. I just met your son.

515
00:24:40,790 --> 00:24:42,470
我還在想你會不會變了
See, I wondered if you'd changed,

516
00:24:44,190 --> 00:24:45,290
不過我知道你沒變
but I knew you hadn't.

517
00:24:46,020 --> 00:24:47,310
別動我的家人
Leave my family alone.

518
00:24:51,190 --> 00:24:52,000
果然
There you are.

519
00:24:52,840 --> 00:24:54,010
我就知道你會這樣
I knew you were in there.

520
00:25:00,190 --> 00:25:01,540
別動我的家人
Leave my family alone.

521
00:25:13,180 --> 00:25:15,180
馬克去查德的店揍了他一頓
Mark went after Chad at his shop,

522
00:25:15,180 --> 00:25:16,850
大約一小時前自首了
turned himself in about an hour ago.

523
00:25:17,150 --> 00:25:18,550
爆炸的事有什么線索
What do we know about the explosive?

524
00:25:18,660 --> 00:25:20,800
拆彈小隊說是自造的  業余水平
Bomb squad said it was homemade, amateur hour.

525
00:25:20,800 --> 00:25:21,820
引爆裝置漏洞百出
Trigger device was faulty.

526
00:25:21,820 --> 00:25:23,910
所以才沒有人受傷或遇害
Only reason no one was seriously injured or killed.

527
00:25:23,910 --> 00:25:24,830
那孩子們呢
What about the kids?

528
00:25:24,850 --> 00:25:27,340
蘭登有輕微劃傷
Landon suffered a few shallow lacerations.

529
00:25:27,340 --> 00:25:29,700
鄰居家的孩子沒事  就是嚇壞了
Neighbor's kid's ok. They're both shaken up.

530
00:25:30,080 --> 00:25:31,110
他們真是幸運
They were really lucky.

531
00:25:31,930 --> 00:25:34,120
他在我家后院放了炸彈
He planted a bomb in my backyard.

532
00:25:34,970 --> 00:25:36,710
差點害死我兒子和他的朋友
He could have killed my son and his friend.

533
00:25:36,710 --> 00:25:38,110
馬克  我們無法證明那個裝置
Mark, we can't prove that Chad had

534
00:25:38,110 --> 00:25:39,830
跟查德有關
anything to do with that device.

535
00:25:40,250 --> 00:25:41,720
我不在乎你們能否證明
I don't care what you can prove.

536
00:25:42,440 --> 00:25:44,040
你可能會被以襲擊罪名起訴
You could be brought up on assault charges.

537
00:25:44,040 --> 00:25:45,050
你知道那意味著什么嗎
Do you know what that means?

538
00:25:46,050 --> 00:25:46,860
坐牢
Jail time.

539
00:25:48,360 --> 00:25:49,940
揍他一頓害得自己坐牢  值得嗎
Was cold cocking him worth it?

540
00:25:52,760 --> 00:25:54,240
我跟克里斯蒂娜聊過
I talked to Christina.

541
00:25:54,930 --> 00:25:56,110
她很擔心你
She's worried about you.

542
00:25:58,050 --> 00:26:00,480
我讓她帶著蘭登去她姐姐家了
Told her to take Landon over to her sister's.

543
00:26:02,300 --> 00:26:04,840
這件事只有你死我活才能結束
This isn't gonna end until one of us is dead.

544
00:26:05,600 --> 00:26:07,150
我們就這樣
It's just how we operate.

545
00:26:07,160 --> 00:26:07,820
我們
We?

546
00:26:09,710 --> 00:26:11,190
這就是兄弟會的行事風格
It's the brotherhood's way.

547
00:26:12,760 --> 00:26:14,050
我們說結束就能結束
This is going to end when we end it,

548
00:26:14,050 --> 00:26:15,710
但是你得放聰明點  馬克
but you need to be smart, Mark.

549
00:26:16,410 --> 00:26:18,000
你的家人都指望著你呢
Your family's depending on you.

550
00:26:22,900 --> 00:26:24,470
查德·休伊特會起訴嗎
Is Chad Hewitt gonna press charges?

551
00:26:24,470 --> 00:26:25,210
不會
No.

552
00:26:25,300 --> 00:26:26,940
他說他不希望馬克被送進監獄
He said he didn't want Mark to go to jail

553
00:26:26,940 --> 00:26:28,740
他覺得見到老朋友很開心
and it was good to see his old buddy.

554
00:26:29,050 --> 00:26:30,050
他好像在保護他一樣
It's like he's protecting him.

555
00:26:30,050 --> 00:26:31,900
他希望馬克回歸兄弟會
He wants Mark to come back to the brotherhood.

556
00:26:31,900 --> 00:26:33,700
馬克去找他  讓他有正當理由繼續糾纏
Mark's attack validated his stalking.

557
00:26:33,700 --> 00:26:35,020
正中他的下懷
It's exactly what he wanted.

558
00:26:36,370 --> 00:26:37,500
你還愿意跟我說話
So you're talking to me.

559
00:26:37,760 --> 00:26:38,620
這是好事
That's a good thing.

560
00:26:39,050 --> 00:26:40,560
我只是在工作
I'm doing my job.

561
00:26:41,400 --> 00:26:42,770
如果你能保持專業態度
If you can keep it professional,

562
00:26:42,770 --> 00:26:44,080
那我也可以
I can keep it professional.

563
00:26:44,080 --> 00:26:45,110
跟特倫特說吧
Tell that to Trent.

564
00:26:45,270 --> 00:26:46,690
別說這個  杰克
I'm not going there, Jack.

565
00:26:46,730 --> 00:26:48,640
但是你也沒有趕我離開洛杉磯
But you're not kicking me out of L.A. either.

566
00:26:50,040 --> 00:26:50,900
謝謝你
Thank you.

567
00:26:51,160 --> 00:26:51,890
謝什么
For what?

568
00:26:52,460 --> 00:26:53,420
讓我留下
Letting me stay.

569
00:27:05,110 --> 00:27:06,550
我們知道查德孤立了馬克
We know that Chad's isolated Mark

570
00:27:06,550 --> 00:27:07,870
還威脅了他的家人
and intimidated his family,

571
00:27:07,870 --> 00:27:09,250
但是他很小心
But he's been very careful.

572
00:27:09,350 --> 00:27:10,640
一直游離在法律底線內
He's acted within the law,

573
00:27:10,730 --> 00:27:11,650
不留下任何證據
doesn't leave any evidence,

574
00:27:11,650 --> 00:27:12,980
而且實行間接跟蹤
and he's stalked by proxy.

575
00:27:13,170 --> 00:27:14,770
但是給馬克家裝炸彈
Booby-trapping Mark's house,

576
00:27:15,140 --> 00:27:16,570
跟以往情況不太一樣
that seems different to me.

577
00:27:16,890 --> 00:27:18,130
是行為激化了嗎
It's an escalation?

578
00:27:18,550 --> 00:27:19,250
顯得很粗心
It's sloppy.

579
00:27:19,400 --> 00:27:22,780
我們終于拿到搜查令  可以看鄰居的監控錄像了
Hey. The warrant for the neighbor's surveillance video finally went through.

580
00:27:22,910 --> 00:27:24,050
有錄到光頭黨的人
We've got Skinheads.

581
00:27:30,270 --> 00:27:31,610
根本看不出什么人
Can't really make out any faces.

582
00:27:31,610 --> 00:27:33,110
但是有這個
But there's this.

583
00:27:34,270 --> 00:27:35,560
看得到車牌
We have a license plate.

584
00:27:35,970 --> 00:27:37,930
車是查德·休伊特的
The car belongs to Chad Hewitt.

585
00:27:40,270 --> 00:27:43,090
取證組搜了他的車
S.I.D. just finished searching his truck.

586
00:27:43,090 --> 00:27:47,200
沒有武器  沒有電擊槍  完全查不到有力證據
No weapons, no lasers, no evidence against Chad.

587
00:27:47,200 --> 00:27:48,710
可是他的車出現在了現場
But we have his truck at the scene.

588
00:27:49,790 --> 00:27:51,630
兩個光頭幫的人自首了
Two skinheads just turned themselves in.

589
00:27:51,830 --> 00:27:53,270
說是他們開了查德的車
They say they were driving Chad's truck

590
00:27:53,270 --> 00:27:54,680
整件事跟他沒有任何關系
and claim they alone are responsible

591
00:27:54,680 --> 00:27:55,990
是他們襲擊了理查德一家
for the attack on the Richards.

592
00:27:55,990 --> 00:27:57,200
這案子查不下去了
You guys are blowing it.

593
00:27:57,200 --> 00:27:58,880
你們根本沒有有力證據
You have no case against this guy.

594
00:27:58,880 --> 00:28:00,590
把他帶來這里風險很大  懂嗎
You realize the stakes of just bringing him in here?

595
00:28:02,270 --> 00:28:03,060
讓他招了就行
I'll break him.

596
00:28:15,730 --> 00:28:17,680
你手上根本沒有證據
You realize you don't have anything to hold me on.

597
00:28:18,610 --> 00:28:20,700
我們聊聊  純聊天
We're just talking, a civil chat.

598
00:28:20,930 --> 00:28:22,200
要請你的律師來嗎
Would you like your lawyer present?

599
00:28:22,780 --> 00:28:23,650
不用
I'm fine.

600
00:28:29,060 --> 00:28:31,860
來跟我說說  怎么會選擇這樣的生活
Tell me, how'd you get into this life?

601
00:28:33,780 --> 00:28:37,470
馬克很有說服力
Mark was very persuasive.

602
00:28:37,680 --> 00:28:39,660
他教會了一個整天被人欺負的男孩
He showed a kid who got his ass kicked every other day

603
00:28:39,660 --> 00:28:40,910
什么才叫真正的力量
what real power was.

604
00:28:41,690 --> 00:28:43,650
是他造就了如今的我
Shaped me into the man I am today.

605
00:28:44,130 --> 00:28:45,970
你似乎還很尊敬他
Seems to me like you still respect him,

606
00:28:46,290 --> 00:28:48,230
似乎還希望他在你的組織里
like you still want him a part of your gang.

607
00:28:48,400 --> 00:28:49,940
我從不會背叛家人
I never turn my back on family.

608
00:28:50,890 --> 00:28:52,410
我們血液相通
His blood is my blood.

609
00:28:52,490 --> 00:28:53,710
那你為什么要殺他
Then why'd you try to kill him?

610
00:28:53,710 --> 00:28:54,600
我沒有
I didn't.

611
00:28:54,630 --> 00:28:55,880
如果發現炸彈的是馬克
If Mark would have found that bomb,

612
00:28:55,880 --> 00:28:56,890
他可能會被炸死
he could have been killed,

613
00:28:57,160 --> 00:28:58,820
而你就是殺死自己導師的兇手
and then you would have lost your mentor.

614
00:28:59,080 --> 00:29:01,100
炸彈是懦夫才用的
A bomb is the tool of a coward.

615
00:29:01,880 --> 00:29:03,510
我很坦蕩
I have nothing to hide.

616
00:29:04,010 --> 00:29:05,620
不必逃避任何事
I have nothing to run from.

617
00:29:07,070 --> 00:29:09,340
馬克背棄了他教會你的一切
Mark completely rejected everything he taught you.

618
00:29:09,700 --> 00:29:11,480
這不會讓你產生懷疑嗎
That didn't create a doubt in your mind

619
00:29:11,480 --> 00:29:14,290
他給你的所謂力量只是過眼云煙
That the power he gave you was nothing but air?

620
00:29:14,350 --> 00:29:15,200
絕不會
Never!

621
00:29:16,390 --> 00:29:18,690
如果我周圍的是血統純正的家人
When I'm surrounded by my pureblood family,

622
00:29:18,690 --> 00:29:20,090
我很確定
I know it's real.

623
00:29:20,200 --> 00:29:22,010
馬克卻不這樣認為
It wasn't real to Mark.

624
00:29:23,140 --> 00:29:26,240
你去坐牢  可他袖手旁觀
You went to prison, and he left you behind.

625
00:29:30,010 --> 00:29:31,120
我知道你在干什么
I know what you're doing.

626
00:29:31,870 --> 00:29:33,920
你們這些二等人種都會這招...
It's what you subraces try to do...

627
00:29:34,930 --> 00:29:36,380
想挑撥離間
Turn us against each other.

628
00:29:37,270 --> 00:29:38,610
他不會開口
He's not gonna break.

629
00:29:39,740 --> 00:29:40,950
這可說不好
I don't know about that.

630
00:29:40,950 --> 00:29:42,100
耐心等待吧
Give here a minute.

631
00:29:42,220 --> 00:29:44,150
單憑一個女人的愛戀
All it took was the love of a woman,

632
00:29:44,750 --> 00:29:46,210
就能讓你在他心里變得一文不值
and you meant nothing to him.

633
00:29:47,060 --> 00:29:48,020
他背棄了你
He abandoned you

634
00:29:48,020 --> 00:29:50,260
和你憎恨的二等人種在一起
to be with one of those subraces you hate so much.

635
00:29:50,260 --> 00:29:51,290
單憑一個女人的愛戀
That's all it took.

636
00:29:53,760 --> 00:29:55,830
你知道我看著你的時候看到了什么嗎
Do you know what I see when I look at you?

637
00:29:57,390 --> 00:29:59,690
那個每天在學校受盡欺負的小男孩
I see that scared little kid who got his ass kicked

638
00:29:59,690 --> 00:30:02,100
總日擔驚受怕  沒有了馬克的保護
every day at school, and without Mark there to protect him,

639
00:30:02,100 --> 00:30:03,150
一旦事態發生變化
when push came to shove,

640
00:30:03,150 --> 00:30:04,750
他立馬又變回以前那個愚弱的小孩
he turned right back into that little kid.

641
00:30:04,750 --> 00:30:05,620
你錯了
You're wrong!

642
00:30:06,540 --> 00:30:08,530
我比他強大得多
I am stronger than he ever was,

643
00:30:09,220 --> 00:30:10,380
絕對比他那下賤的西班牙老婆
and I'm sure as hell smarter

644
00:30:10,380 --> 00:30:11,580
聰明幾萬倍
than some hab.

645
00:30:16,910 --> 00:30:17,940
問完了嗎
Are we done here?

646
00:30:22,220 --> 00:30:22,780
問完了
Done.

647
00:30:27,580 --> 00:30:28,930
又得從頭查起了
Back to square one.

648
00:30:44,410 --> 00:30:45,600
臭光頭黨[西語]
Cabeza rapada.

649
00:30:46,410 --> 00:30:47,510
你跟我說什么呢小子
What did you say to me, boy?

650
00:30:47,510 --> 00:30:50,050
要想住在洛杉磯  最好學點西班牙語
You should learn spanish if you're gonna live in Los Angeles.

651
00:30:50,210 --> 00:30:51,290
拜拜了  光頭黨
Adios, Skinhead.

652
00:30:51,620 --> 00:30:53,470
我要殺了你這西班牙賤貨  你死定了
I'm gonna kill your Mexican ass. You're dead!

653
00:30:54,510 --> 00:30:55,680
這里需要支援
We need backup now.

654
00:30:55,990 --> 00:30:56,900
銬好了
Here you go. Yeah.

655
00:30:57,390 --> 00:30:58,050
抓住了嗎
Got him?

656
00:30:58,620 --> 00:31:01,510
你被捕了  罪名是惡意威脅警方人員
You're under arrest for making a threat against a police officer.

657
00:31:01,910 --> 00:31:02,810
把他帶下去
Get him out of here.

658
00:31:03,120 --> 00:31:05,190
趕緊走  這邊
Let's go! This way.

659
00:31:08,120 --> 00:31:09,410
惡意威脅能關他四年
Criminal threat gets him 4 years.

660
00:31:09,410 --> 00:31:11,410
你這么做只不過是給你的受害人
All you've done is bought your victim

661
00:31:11,410 --> 00:31:12,580
爭取到一點茍延殘喘的空間
a little breathing room.

662
00:31:12,580 --> 00:31:13,620
有點不對經
There's something else.

663
00:31:13,800 --> 00:31:15,870
我覺得關于爆炸案  查德沒說謊
I think Chad was telling the truth about the bomb.

664
00:31:16,410 --> 00:31:17,220
炸彈不是他放的
He didn't set it.

665
00:31:17,220 --> 00:31:18,410
那就是光頭黨的黨羽
Then it was one of his Skinheads.

666
00:31:18,410 --> 00:31:20,180
不  查德不會授權的
No. Chad wouldn't have authorized that.

667
00:31:20,180 --> 00:31:21,690
他極其蔑視安設炸彈的行為
He was contemptuous about the bomb,

668
00:31:21,690 --> 00:31:22,800
覺得這樣有失身份
like it was beneath him.

669
00:31:22,800 --> 00:31:24,500
沒錯  他不想殺了馬克
Right. He doesn't want to kill Mark.

670
00:31:24,500 --> 00:31:25,360
他想讓他重回組織
He wants him back.

671
00:31:25,360 --> 00:31:26,130
沒錯
Exactly.

672
00:31:26,170 --> 00:31:27,480
好吧  那炸彈是誰放的
Ok. So who set it?

673
00:31:27,630 --> 00:31:29,660
鄰居們的攝像頭什么也沒錄下
The neighbors' security cameras didn't catch anyone.

674
00:31:29,660 --> 00:31:31,600
安置炸彈的是能不知不覺地
The bomb was planted by someone who knew how to get

675
00:31:31,600 --> 00:31:32,910
潛入他家的人
in and out without being noticed.

676
00:31:32,910 --> 00:31:35,760
熟知社區里各個攝像頭的位置
Someone who knew about those cameras in the neighborhood,

677
00:31:35,860 --> 00:31:36,760
以及避開它們的途徑
how to avoid them.

678
00:31:38,060 --> 00:31:39,730
所以是社區里的人干的
So it was someone from the neighborhood.

679
00:31:39,800 --> 00:31:41,370
所有人都以為自己很了解馬克
Everyone thought they knew Mark.

680
00:31:41,370 --> 00:31:44,160
也許馬克過去的暴露  觸發了一些情緒
Maybe finding out about Mark's past triggered something.

681
00:31:44,160 --> 00:31:45,220
本  把詹妮絲叫回來
Ben, pull Janice.

682
00:31:45,220 --> 00:31:46,500
我們得著重觀察鄰居們
We need to focus on the neighbors,

683
00:31:46,500 --> 00:31:48,690
任何有心理以及精神病史的人
Anyone with priors or a history of mental illness.

684
00:31:49,000 --> 00:31:50,410
杰克  去找馬克  把他帶走
Jack, go get Mark, get him out of there.

685
00:31:50,410 --> 00:31:51,140
我和他一起去
I'll go with him.

686
00:31:51,880 --> 00:31:53,110
不  不用了
No. Not necessary.

687
00:31:53,500 --> 00:31:55,600
走吧  杰克  正好聯絡一下感情
Come on, Jack. It will give us an opportunity to bond.

688
00:31:55,600 --> 00:31:56,370
真的不用了
I'm good.

689
00:31:56,370 --> 00:31:57,010
走吧
Come on.

690
00:32:01,500 --> 00:32:02,210
好  在哪呢
Yeah. Where is it?

691
00:32:03,390 --> 00:32:04,560
好的  我會帶上
Ok. I'll grab it.

692
00:32:04,780 --> 00:32:06,500
好  我們一會見
Yeah. All right. I'll see you soon.

693
00:32:08,500 --> 00:32:10,650
我也愛你  親愛的  拜拜
I love you, too, sweetheart. Bye.

694
00:33:40,260 --> 00:33:41,290
我去找馬克
I'll get Mark.

695
00:33:42,870 --> 00:33:43,580
拉森
Larsen.

696
00:33:43,610 --> 00:33:44,530
你們找到馬克了嗎
Do you have Mark?

697
00:33:44,530 --> 00:33:45,690
我們剛到  你們查到了什么
Just landed. What do you got?

698
00:33:45,690 --> 00:33:47,390
霍華德·葛靈杰  住在對面街
Howard Granger. Lives across the street

699
00:33:47,390 --> 00:33:49,000
薩特街10331號
at 10331 Sutter.

700
00:33:49,180 --> 00:33:50,410
沒有犯罪前科  但他在警局有檔案
No criminal record, but he did file

701
00:33:50,410 --> 00:33:51,640
十年前的案件報告
a police report 10 years ago.

702
00:33:51,640 --> 00:33:53,100
他被一群人襲擊了
He was attacked by a group of men.

703
00:33:53,240 --> 00:33:54,620
那是種族性犯罪  杰克
It was racially motivated, Jack,

704
00:33:54,620 --> 00:33:56,120
被歸類為仇視性犯罪
classified as a hate crime.

705
00:33:56,150 --> 00:33:57,460
警方一直沒找到嫌疑人
They never found the suspects.

706
00:33:57,460 --> 00:33:59,490
仇視性犯罪的受害者住在
Victim of a hate crime living across the street

707
00:33:59,490 --> 00:34:00,920
改過自新的光頭黨對面
from a reformed skinhead?

708
00:34:01,110 --> 00:34:03,170
他可能處于精神崩潰狀態
He could be experiencing a psychotic break, Jack.

709
00:34:03,170 --> 00:34:04,320
也許會產生幻覺
He could be delusional.

710
00:34:04,600 --> 00:34:05,370
要小心
Be careful.

711
00:34:05,370 --> 00:34:07,440
沒人  有打斗的痕跡
Gone. Looks like there was a struggle.

712
00:34:07,760 --> 00:34:09,520
派點人手過來  馬克不見了
Get some units out here. Mark's missing.

713
00:34:19,260 --> 00:34:22,720
霍華德·葛靈杰  洛杉磯警察
Howard Granger? LAPD.

714
00:34:26,260 --> 00:34:27,940
里面有人影移動
There's someone moving around in there.

715
00:34:31,960 --> 00:34:33,050
你從后面包抄
Go cover the back.

716
00:34:39,990 --> 00:34:40,780
警察
Police!

717
00:35:20,260 --> 00:35:20,820
你還好嗎
You ok?

718
00:35:20,820 --> 00:35:21,580
沒事
Yeah.

719
00:35:39,980 --> 00:35:41,070
他突然冒出來了
He came out of nowhere.

720
00:36:38,260 --> 00:36:39,630
你們為什么要保護他
Why are you protecting him?

721
00:36:41,770 --> 00:36:42,780
放下武器
Put the weapon down.

722
00:36:42,860 --> 00:36:44,040
他是光頭黨
He's a Skinhead!

723
00:36:45,260 --> 00:36:46,510
他不比我好
He's no better than me!

724
00:36:48,430 --> 00:36:49,390
放開他
Get off him.

725
00:36:50,140 --> 00:36:51,580
你們為什么要保護他
Why are you protecting him?

726
00:36:52,010 --> 00:36:54,410
他就該死  他們都該死
He deserves to die. He they all deserve to die.

727
00:36:54,490 --> 00:36:55,740
我最后說一遍
I'm not gonna ask you again.

728
00:36:56,260 --> 00:36:57,320
放下武器
Drop your weapon.

729
00:36:59,260 --> 00:37:00,850
他不比我好
He's no better than me.

730
00:37:05,260 --> 00:37:06,490
他不比我好
He's no better than me.

731
00:37:18,960 --> 00:37:19,670
你沒事吧
You ok?

732
00:37:20,700 --> 00:37:22,010
傷口不深  死不了
It's not deep. I'll live.

733
00:37:52,680 --> 00:37:53,410
你沒事
Hi.

734
00:37:59,260 --> 00:38:01,000
這給你  拉森警探
Excuse me, Detective Larsen.

735
00:38:17,260 --> 00:38:18,090
謝謝
Thank you.

736
00:38:42,020 --> 00:38:42,680
本
Hey, Ben.

737
00:38:45,850 --> 00:38:47,140
你今天的表現很棒
Really nice job today.

738
00:38:48,610 --> 00:38:49,400
謝謝
Thanks.

739
00:38:51,660 --> 00:38:52,460
晚安
Good night.

740
00:39:32,260 --> 00:39:33,260
謝謝
Thank you.

741
00:39:33,260 --> 00:39:35,040
馬克同意跟我們合作
Mark's agreed to work with us.

742
00:39:35,550 --> 00:39:37,640
他會幫我們讓查德把牢底坐穿
Looks like he's gonna help put Chad away for good.

743
00:39:39,570 --> 00:39:40,860
你的傷怎么樣了
How's your wound?

744
00:39:40,920 --> 00:39:43,660
沒事  我有止痛藥還有紅酒
Fine. I got pain pills and wine.

745
00:39:45,260 --> 00:39:46,510
這組合真讓人擔心
That scares me.

746
00:39:55,760 --> 00:39:58,020
我知道你和杰克之間有一段過去
I know you and Jack have a past.

747
00:40:00,040 --> 00:40:02,330
如果你不想說  那就沒關系
You don't want to talk about it, that's fine,

748
00:40:03,970 --> 00:40:06,920
但你不覺得伊森
but don't you think Ethan

749
00:40:07,260 --> 00:40:08,840
有權見見自己的父親嗎
has a right to see his father?

750
00:40:10,870 --> 00:40:12,190
是杰克告訴你的嗎
Did Jack tell you that?

751
00:40:12,370 --> 00:40:13,170
不是
No.

752
00:40:15,040 --> 00:40:16,470
但這是真的  不是嗎
But it is true, isn't it?

753
00:40:18,260 --> 00:40:19,350
沒錯  這是真的
Yeah, it's true.

754
00:40:23,260 --> 00:40:25,100
而且事情很復雜
And it's complicated.

