Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
Created time 14.07.03 23:22:27
女子監獄 第二季 第六集
我覺得愛是什么啊
What do I think love is?
看見他就讓你覺得很緊張
It's like when someone makes your stomach feel all tight,
卻又輕飄飄的  你懂吧
but floaty at the same time, you know?
臉都笑抽筋了
And your cheeks hurt from smiling.
一直笑得別人以為你有病
And you smile so much that people think something's wrong with you.
愛云淡風輕
Love is light.
是包容
Acceptance.
是激情
Fire.
痛苦
Pain.
刻骨銘心的痛苦
Horrible pain.
你卻忍不住一再親近
That you want again and again.
還有做愛 And also, fucking.
不間斷深入地  操得下不了地 Twenty-four seven, deep-dick, can't-walk-right fucking.
我啊  一談到愛情根本停不下來 Well, you know me. I got so much to say about love.
有一年啊  那個華爾街高富帥帶我坐直升機去了華盛頓 And one year, this Wall Street guy flew me in a helicopter to D.C.
真的嗎 For serious?
情人節男人干嘛都有可能  他們最愛這個節日了 Valentine's Day makes guys go crazy. They love it.
男人最恨情人節了 Men hate Valentine's Day.
至少看上去沒有啊 They don't act like they hate it.
那是因為你長得美  跟索菲婭·沃加拉一樣 That's because you look like Sofia Vergara.
《摩登家庭》女主角
她的胸倒貨真價實 Them things is real.
有次我看見她在翠貝卡區跑步 I once saw her jogging in Tribeca.
伊恩好久沒來看我了  他要是明天來看我就好了 Ian hasn't visited in so long. It'd be nice if he showed up tomorrow.
可他只有一輛小摩托  騎過來太冷了 But he's only got a Vespa and it's too cold to ride this far.
有一次亞迪爾送了我花  從他親戚葬禮上順的 One year, Yadriel got me flowers. He stole them from his cousin's funeral.
-好甜蜜呀  -拜托 - It was so sweet. - Please.
情人節就這樣  要是不扮成完美情人 Valentine's Day was invented to make people feel like shit
就會死一樣 if they're not part of some perfect couple.
沒錯 True.
迪艾保說這世上沒有完美情人 Diablo says there are no perfect couples,
但每一對都各有其美 but each couple is perfect in its own way.
情人節還被關著  一定很難受吧 It must be hard. Being locked up on Valentine's Day.
沒別的意思 That's all.
謝謝  費歇爾  你真為我們著想 Aw. Thank you, Fischer. That was really empathetic of you.
-要來塊餅干嗎  -好啊  謝謝 - You want a cookie? - Oh, sure. Thank you.
-你要喝點水嗎  費歇爾  -沒事 - You need some water, Fischer? - No. I'm fine.
就知道她沒口活過 I knew she didn't swallow.
嗨 Hi.
你明晚訂了哪里 Where'd you make reservations for tomorrow night?
什么 Wait, what?
我正假裝我們是一對情人啊 I'm trying to pretend like we're a normal couple.
這樣啊 Oh.
我在洛倫佐餐廳訂了兩個座位 Um, well, I got us a table for two at Lorenzo's.
就在壁爐旁 The one by the fireplace.
等不及給你看我的新裙子 I can't wait for you to see my dress.
很性感卻不浪蕩 It's sexy, but not slutty, you know?
迫不及待 I can't wait to see it.
再給去我拿包面粉好嗎 Mamita, can you get me another bag of flour?
給你 Here.
-這是啥  -是清單 - What's this? - It's a list.
要哄你的岳母開心啊  知道嗎 Wanna keep the mother-in-law happy, right?
我想著或許可以借用一下你的假肢 I figured I might as well make use of Sleepy Hollow
免得再節外生枝 before the other shoe drops.
明白嗎 Get it?
由于無法避免的維修因素  淋浴要限制在30秒內
這就是維給我們爭取來的  用這種破龍頭洗澡 So this is what Vee negotiated for us? Using these broke-ass showers?
-這什么破談判啊  -你說呢 - Man, that's some broke-ass negotiation. - You think?
你們知道洗澡時間太長對人不好吧 You do know that long showers are bad for you.
對表皮細胞什么不好 Mess with your keratinocytes and whatnots.
蘇珊娜  你他媽給我閉嘴 Hey, Suzanne? Shut the fuck up.
為什么要我離開圖書館 Yeah, why the hell would I leave the library?
那是監獄里最好的工作了 It's the best job here.
因為那兒錢少  付不了房租  吃不上紅酒牛肉 Because books do not pay the rent. Books do not bourguignon the beef.
我們有大生意要做 We are starting something.
我不想去保管處 I don't wanna join custodial.
-但我還是想要你去  -不行  我不去 - And yet I am still asking you. - No way. No.
-快點快點  -給我閉嘴 - Oh, come on. Come on! - Shut up!
當年你跑過來跟我說 You know what? Do you know how easy it would've been
"維  把我從教養院弄出去吧" for me to say no when you came to me and said,
我完全可以不幫你  知道嗎 "Vee, get me out of this group home"?
"我不想再見到那寄養父親的狗臉了" "Save me from this sick fuck-faced foster father I got!" Huh?
-這不公平  -公平  醒醒吧 - That's not fair. - Fair? Girl, please.
哪有什么公平  你以為是排排坐吃果果 Fair's where you go get you some cotton candy.
坐著旋轉木馬嗎 Where you ride the Tilt-A-Whirl.
我在找杰克 I'm looking for Jack.
他不在這兒 He's not here.
他每年都給我買巧克力 He buys me chocolates every year.
我們有固定的收入 We're on a fixed income, of course.
但他說今晚要喂鴨子 But he's gotta treat his Duckie right, he says.
要是他找不到我  那就浪費了 And if he can't find me, they'll be wasted.
操  我要是變這樣  就直接掐死我 Fuck. Kill me in my sleep if I ever get like that.
聽著  你給我好好想想  然后照我說的做 Look. You're gonna think about it, right? And then you gonna do as I say.
痛啊 Ah!
就是很放松  懂嗎 It's just chilling, you know?
跟人一起玩  開些很冷的玩笑啊 Kicking it with somebody, talking, making mad stupid jokes.
一點都不想睡覺 And, like, not even wanting to go to sleep,
這樣就會有那么段時間見不到對方 'cause then you might be without 'em for a minute.
而你一刻都不想分開 And you don't want that.
美國陸軍  霍恩菲爾茲駐地  多國戰備中心  德國  巴伐利亞
一  二  三  開始 Ein, zwei, drei, go!
就快... And...
好了  誰下一個  誰下一個 And done! Who's next? Who's next?
厲害 Whoo!
你贏不了我的 You can't beat me.
我不可超越 I am untouchable.
可我覺得你很親近 I think you are very touchable.
找間屋子好嗎 Get a room.
說德語  白癡  再說一遍 German, fool. Talk it.
是"旁建"  "旁間" Zing? Zinger?
是"房間"  你好歹住在這里  尊重它的語言 Das Zimmer. You're part of a community. Respect its language.
我爸才是這圈子的 My father's part of a community.
我不過是他隨你們四處反恐時 I'm the unfortunate appendage he drags about
攜帶的一個拖油瓶而已 wherever your fight against terror takes him.
他在說傻話 He's just talkin' smack.
那你這些年搬過多少次家 How many times have you had to move in your short little life?
數不清了 Too many.
但是我不會再搬了  我爸答應我了 But this is the end of the road. My pops promised.
怎么用德語說 How do you say,
"我真想看你們倆做女女之愛啊" "I'd like to watch as you two make sweet, sweet lady love," in German?
沒門  混蛋  沒門 Nein, motherfucker. Nein.
這活兒太操蛋了 This job is bullshit.
哪有  這是道有獎勵的考驗題 No. 'Tis a rewarding puzzle.
哪兒來的考驗  就是收拾電器 Ain't no puzzle. Makes electrical look good.
真不敢相信我竟然聽了那老婊子的話 Can't believe I let that old bitch talk me into this.
你還是別背后指摘帕克小姐的不是 I wouldn't speak ill of Miss Parker's methods.
她耳里肯定聽不得這些話 She wouldn't tolerate such words.
聽著  沃森有權利 Hey, now, Watson got the right
表達她對新工作的不滿 to express her discomfort for her new job.
就算你覺得打掃衛生沒什么問題 Just because cleaning quiets your discombobulation
不代表別人就都一樣 doesn't mean it does so for everyone.
說得好  掃把  說得好 Point well made, Moppet. Point well made.
你真是蠢 You such a dumbass.
沃森  你看著很累啊 Hey, Watson, you look a little tired.
要不我晚些時候去給你按摩下股四頭肌 Maybe I could come by later and massage your quads?
他媽給我滾遠點 Get the fuck out of here.
不管你們這里要干什么勾當 You know, whatever y'all got going on in here.
接手了保管處  我都要分一杯羹 You know, taking over custodial. I want a piece.
我會睜只眼閉只眼  這樣什么都看不見 I use it to cover my eyes. That way, you know, I won't see anything.
明晚  我會用我的手  讓你的情人節爽歪歪 Tomorrow night, I'm going to put the "V" in your Valentine.
沒錯  盡情操我 That's right. Fuck me.
沃倫  誰陪你過今年的情人節 Hey, Warren, who gonna be your Valentine this year?
你不總是去勾搭誰嗎 You always battin' them freaky blacks at somebody.
不不 Oh, no.
今年我要愛一個值得我愛的人  真的 No, this year I'm loving someone who deserves me. Me.
廢物 Loser.
閉嘴 Shut up!
無所謂了  要我說  這是一年中最難過的時刻 Whatever. Depressing-ass time of year, you ask me.
媽的 Motherfucker!
我操  你尿褲子了 Shit. You pissed your pants?
我去給你找塊尿布 I'm gonna go find you a diaper.
請注意  探訪時間開始 Your attention, please. Visiting hours are now open.
所有犯人均可進入探訪室 All prisoners are free to go to the visiting room.
明天是佛羅倫薩·亨德森的生日 Tomorrow's Florence Henderson's birthday!
什么 What?
情人節啊  是佛羅倫薩·亨德森的生日 Valentine's Day. Florence Henderson's birthday!
我們每年都有裸體慶祝派對 We should be having our annual naked Brady-thon celebration
我會伴著陽光天樂隊的歌跳脫衣舞 and I should be doing some kind of a striptease to Sunshine Day.
也許...也許...再抹點油 And then maybe something... Maybe something with Wesson Oil, that...
帕波 Piper.
你好 Hi.
嗨 Hi.
我聽說了你奶奶的事 I heard about your grandma.
萊瑞 Larry...
我想要我的家 I want my home.
從這兒出去后 When I get out of here,
我想回家 I wanna come home.
這可不是小事啊 That's quite the statement.
你確定嗎 You sure about that?
我確定 Yeah, I'm sure.
我不是在問你 Well, I'm not asking you.
我是在問未來的帕波  那個重獲自由的帕波 I'm asking Future Piper. Free Piper.
你能保證你依舊想回家嗎 Can you guarantee that you still will?
未來的帕波希望能回家 Future Piper hopes so.
可是現今的萊瑞不能靠希望活著 Present Larry can't live on hope.
我可以靠吃芥末豆花生黃油餅干 Wasabi peas and peanut butter pretzels, apparently,
但希望是不夠的 but not hope.
拜托別在這兒提這些東西 Please don't mention those things
除非你藏了什么東西要給我 unless you're hiding some up your butt for me.
帕波 Piper,
有個《都市郵報》的記者  安德魯·南斯 this reporter from CityPost, Andrew Nance.
他... He, um...
問我這里是否有資金異常的問題 He asked me about financial irregularities here.
比如憑空出現的銷售商  從未建起的樓等 Uh... Vendors that don't exist, buildings that were never built.
于是我就想  "去你媽的 And I was like, "Fuck that.
為什么要他寫  我來寫" "Why should he write it? I'll write it."
寫什么 Write what?
一篇文章  靠你從內部挖掘信息 An article. With you investigating from the inside.
新聞自由權并非只有自由人才有  是吧 Freedom of the press shouldn't only be a privilege of the free, right?
-你覺得怎么樣  -天哪 - What do you say? - Oh, my God.
我的天  萊瑞  我的上帝 Oh, my God, Larry. Jesus Christ!
-怎么了  -你又來了 - What... - You're doing it again!
你說什么啊 What are you talking about?
我們要曝光這個地方  帕波 We'll fucking expose this place, Piper.
你就是月亮  萊瑞  不要再做月亮了 You're the moon, Larry. You have got to stop being the moon!
月亮怎么了 What's wrong with being the moon?
它不能自己發光 It doesn't have its own light.
是啊  怎么了  那你就是太陽了 So, right. So, what? That makes you the sun?
你就是太陽了  是不是啊  帕波 Are you the sun, Piper? Huh?
你是全太陽系的中心 You're the center of the solar system
而我就是塊毫無生氣的石頭 and I'm just a dead hunk of crap rock!
帕波  你的一切依舊到處都是 How am I supposed to become my own planet, Piper,
我要怎么成為獨立的星球 when your shit is still everywhere?
你倒是往前看了 You get to move on.
你還操了艾麗克斯或是誰  我卻止步不前 You get to fuck Alex or whoever's next, and I'm stuck.
我深陷在你的衣服鞋子里 I'm stuck with your sweaters and your shoes
還有他媽什么絲芙蘭代銷店淘來的東西 and your goddamn Sephora fucking outlet store worth of products!
你無處不在 You are everywhere.
就像活在石棺里 It's like living inside a sarcophagus.
要是我的東西太礙事了你可以送去波麗那兒 Well, take my stuff to Polly's if it's so in your way.
還有你其實是想說"陵墓"而不是"石棺" And you mean "mausoleum," not "sarcophagus."
不要再對我指手畫腳了 Don't tell me what I mean!
至少人們還能在月亮上行走 At least people can walk on the moon.
太陽呢  一靠近就只會燃成灰燼 Anyone gets near the sun, they burn right up.
維說她年紀大了  我才不信呢 Vee says she's too old. Don't believe it for a second!
那女的曾經怎么對我啊 What that woman did to me...
江山易改本性難移 People don't change.
你能不能快點啊 Hurry it up, will you?
我盡力了媽  火星濺得我臉都疼 I'm trying, Ma. The sparks are burning my cheeks!
那就把頭轉過去  你哥呢 Then turn your head! Where's your brother?
他有幽閉恐懼癥  呆在林子里守著入口呢 He got claustrophobic. He's in the woods, guarding the entrance.
媽媽  我好難過啊 I'm just so sad, mamochka.
真遺憾她離你而去  瓦斯里 I'm sorry she left you, Vasily,
但我相信你也是活該 but I'm sure you did something to deserve it.
我以前會看她入睡 I used to watch her sleep
祈禱我能強大起來  不再毀掉一切  媽媽 and pray for the strength to stop ruining everything, Ma.
那有用嗎 And how did that work out for you?
今天不做工  明天再來 No work today. Come back tomorrow.
杰克說他會在這兒 Jack said he would be out here.
我看他上了輛出租車 I saw him get into a taxi.
出租車  就在外面嗎 A taxi? Out here?
真不可思議 Imagine that.
謝謝你  女士 Thank you, young lady.
你能不能快點啊 Hurry it up, will you?
媽媽 Mama!
受夠了你惡心的抱怨 You and your disgusting whining!
想要你的女人回來  就去追 If you want your woman back, go get her.
趕緊把東西遞給我  快點 Now hand up the shit. Come on!
等你出去時 When you get out of here...
想過家里會有誰等著你嗎 who do you imagine yourself going home to?
《犯罪》里的費歐娜·艾波 Fiona Apple in the Criminal video.
問得太傻了 Stupid question.
你呢 What about you?
我一直以為是萊瑞 I always thought it would be Larry,
如今看來得重新考慮了 but I think it's time to re-imagine.
這個愚蠢操蛋的節日 This stupid fucking holiday.
你要是愿意  我能讓你忘記這一天 Listen, if you want, I can help you forget what day it is.
甚至是你的名字 You know, or your name, for that matter.
你也知道我的答案  不要 You know, no.
我不想在你的做愛比賽里 I am not interested in being a prize,
做一個價碼低得不可思議的戰利品 albeit a shockingly-undervalued one, in your little sex game.
好吧 Fine.
我失去了我愛操縱人  漂亮又變態的前任 I lost my manipulative, gorgeous, psychopath ex
又失去了我貼心又有點不著邊的未婚夫 and my sweet, kind, unfocused fiance.
我沒有家了 I don't have a home anymore.
不  查普曼  你有 Yeah, Chapman, you do.
這傻逼電線 This shit pile.
真他媽甜蜜啊 Home sweet home.
聽著  我不得不承認 Look, I gotta say,
你那不著邊的未婚夫說的什么文章  還真有點道理 your unfocused fiance is on the right track with this article shit.
我都不知道多少次修這個儀表板的短路了 I mean, this is like my 20th time trying to fix a short in this panel alone.
根本沒人花錢管 Nobody's spending money here.
加列戈說你找我 Hey. Gallego said you were looking for me?
喬  這些通話  真是太有意思了 Joe, these phone calls. They're amazing!
聽這個 Listen.
我說看著他  不是操他 I said to keep an eye on him, not fuck him!
不過是菊花入而已  不算的呀 It was only in the ass. That don't count.
我要告訴媽媽 I'm telling Mom.
這么勁爆 Whoa.
是吧  太有意思了  這么多不同的生活 I know! Anyway. It's so interesting. All these lives.
就跟讀狄更斯似的 It's like reading Dickens!
不錯  這挺積極的 It's good. Showing initiative.
也許這樣菲格就不會再盯著我了 Maybe it'll help get Fig off my ass.
你知道她要求我執行記過配額嗎 You know she asked me to impose a shot quota?
太荒唐了 This is ridiculous.
你能站出來對抗她真厲害 I love that you stand up to her.
你跟那誰怎么樣了 So, how are things going with... What's his name?
他們不去了  他穿太多背心了 They're not going. He wore a lot of vests.
這樣 Ah.
也挺常見的 Well, that happens.
哦對了  我在一個樂隊里... You know, I play in this band...
你玩樂隊啊 You're in a band? Wow!
是啊 Yeah?
就是小打小鬧 Yeah. It's no big deal.
明晚我們有演出  你要不要來 We play in town tomorrow night. You wanna come?
我要看著情人節派對 Oh, I'm working the Valentine's party.
我能幫你調開 I'll get you off.
幫你調開值班時間 I'll get you off the schedule.
可以幫你換班  小事情 I can get your shift covered. It's fine.
我挺喜歡聽音樂的  一定很棒 Well, I do love music! That'd be awesome.
-謝謝  -那好 - Thanks. - Great.
-那到時候見  -好 - I'll see you there then! - Okay.
我在海滋客工作時和我老板有過一腿 I had this thing with my boss at Long John Silver's.
后來我發現他老婆超級辣 And then I found out his wife was wicked hot.
所以感覺還不錯 So that was nice.
"你怎么知道我不開心"  愛麗絲說 "'How do you know I'm mad? ' said Alice.
"一看就知道"  貓說  "不然你也不會來這里" "'You must be, ' said the Cat, 'or you wouldn't have come here.'"
你真他媽對 Mmm. Shit. You right.
路易斯·卡羅一定蹲過牢 Lewis Carroll must have gone to prison.
RJ的媽媽就叫愛麗絲 RJ's mom was named Alice.
是嗎  她也掉進兔子洞了 Oh, yeah? She fall down a rabbit hole?
-不是  是毒窟  -這樣 - No. A crack hole. - Ah.
然后她發現一塊石頭  上面寫著"吸了我" She found a little rock. Said "Smoke me," on it.
這不好笑  那東西很厲害 That's not funny. That shit was serious.
"吸了我"  真有你的 "Smoke me." You a dumbass.
杰弗遜  趕緊說再見吧  你得去保管處了 Jefferson. Say goodbye. You're on custodial now.
現在就要去了 Already?
-什么  你要走了  -是啊 - Wait. You leaving? - Yeah.
還記得我跟你說維在策劃什么事嗎 Remember, I told you Vee was getting something together?
但是你為什么要離開圖書館呢  你喜歡這里 But why would you leave the library, man? You know you love it here.
你不明白 You don't understand.
我欠她 I owe her.
她或許也能把你換過去吧 She could probably get you transferred, I bet.
不會的 Nah.
我自己心里有數 No, I know when I got it good.
好吧  那我們晚飯見了 Okay. Well, I'll see you at dinner.
怎么樣 Anything?
再高點 Higher maybe.
等等 Wait.
腿抽筋了 Leg cramp.
抱歉 Sorry.
好了 Okay.
太棒了 That's nice.
-是嗎  -嗯 - Yeah? Yeah? - Yeah.
不行 No.
沒感覺了 It's gone.
就跟你說交叉式行不通 I told you scissoring wasn't a thing.
說到愛情  有這么一句話 There's a saying about love.
關于愛情有好多句話呢 There's a million sayings about love.
我想到了其中一句 I'm thinking of the one that says,
"愛不是互相凝視對方 "Love is not about staring at each other,
而是望向同一個方向" but staring off in the same direction."
我不喜歡這句 I don't like that one.
我更喜歡看著你 I love staring at you too much.
我渴了 I'm thirsty.
我給你擦 Let me get that.
很好 Oh, yeah.
我還要 More.
搞什么 What the fuck?
-不過是這個而已  -在違禁物清單上 - Just this. - It's on the list.
-只是水煙  -少來  艾麗卡 - It's fucking vapor! - Give me a break, Eliqua.
卡普托今天盯著我  放回車里去  下一個 Caputo's up my ass today. Put it in your car. Next.
現在搜身是強制的了 Pat-downs are mandatory now.
跟你開玩笑的 I'm just kidding.
才不想碰你的假肢呢 I don't wanna touch that peg-leg shit.
情人節快樂  下一個 Happy Valentine's Day. Next.
看看這些破玩意兒 Look at this shit.
幸好你長得漂亮 You're lucky you're pretty. You know that, right?
這個上面寫了啥 What does that one say?
"伊恩"  以防萬一他來了  我真傻 "Ian." In case he shows up today. Stupid.
媽逼 Shit.
真高興我們是一家人 I'm so glad we're family.
-情人節快樂  -謝謝 - Happy Valentine's Day. - Thanks.
今天有給我做什么愛心晚餐嗎 Are you cooking up something special for me today?
屋子里聞著真香 The house smells great.
這就是你想要我做的嗎 That's what you're gonna expect me to do?
給你做飯  當你的家庭主婦 Cook for you? Be your little housewife?
別想了  不可能 It's not happening.
沒有  我以為我們是在扮演... No. I thought we were playing the...
我無所謂你煮不煮飯 I don't care if you cook.
抱歉  我今天心情不太好 Sorry. I've just been depressed today.
不想再玩裝正常的游戲了 I don't want to play the normal game anymore
因為我們永遠不可能像正常情侶那樣 'cause I don't know how we ever are gonna be normal.
就是想告訴你  如果你想找人說說話 Well, just so you know. Counselors can be a great resource
或哭一場  你可以找輔導員 if you feel like you need to talk or cry or something.
-誰是你輔導員  -海利 - Who'd you get? - Healy.
這樣 Oh.
-有什么不對嗎  -沒有 - What's wrong? - Nothing.
我只是覺得沒有哪個姑娘真心喜歡他 I just get the sense that none of the girls really like him.
但你很堅強  都會過去的 But you're tough, you'll be fine.
你有沒有覺得最近我們燒斷了很多保險絲 Have you noticed we've been blowing a lot of fuses around here lately?
你才發現這兒都快散架了嗎 You're just noticing this place is falling apart?
監獄難道沒有基礎設施的預算嗎 Doesn't the prison have a budget for infrastructure?
當然有 Sure.
那上個季度的電器預算哪去了 And what happened to the electrical budget from last quarter?
說是要加護A區柵欄和卸貨平臺 It went to "upgrading the A block grid and loading dock panel."
真的嗎  我們真加護了 Really? We did that?
預算報告是這么寫的 That's what the budget report says.
-那我們做了嗎  -這個嘛 - So we did it? - Okay.
-真加護了嗎  -不然呢 - So it happened? - Why not?
我不明白 I don't understand.
相信我  你不想懂的 Trust me. You don't want to.
好了  時間到了  恭喜你剛掙了11分 Congratulations. Hour's up. You just earned another 11 cents.
好  各位  海豚式 All right, everybody. Dolphin pose.
我覺得我能幫你完成這個海豚式 You know, I think I can help you with the dolphin pose.
關鍵就在于保證你的骨盆放在... The trick is to make sure that your pelvic basin is just right...
離我遠點 Get away from me.
我去  謝謝紅媽 No way! Thanks, Red.
紅媽  上帝保佑你 Red! Bless you!
現在  再做一次海豚式 Now, let's return to dolphin pose.
莖茶 Kukicha tea.
看看誰回來了 Well, look who's back.
無意打擾  姑娘們  繼續你們的海豚吧 Sorry to interrupt, girls. Continue with your dolphins.
操  剛搞了個4分的 Fuck, just bagged a four-pointer.
我們差不多平手 We're almost tied.
聽著 Listen up.
不要再毫無意義地賭氣了 This angry nonsense has to stop.
很快我們就需要互相幫助 We're going to need each other soon.
所有人 All of us.
我沒開玩笑  尼古拉斯 I'm not kidding, Nicky.
我們必須團結一致  這樣才能更強大 We have to stick together. We're stronger together.
所以你就想再收買她們 So you try to buy their love back?
謝謝紅媽 Thanks, Red.
干嘛要問我 Why are you asking me that?
你不該和我說話  你不該... You shouldn't be talking to me. So... You shouldn't be...
-14罐護足粉  -有了 - Fourteen foot powders. - Check.
-20管牙膏  -有了 - Twenty Effergrips. - Check that.
還記得我們賣煙那會兒么 Remember when we sold smokes?
我發誓我再也不投給自由黨了 God, I swear I'm gonna vote Libertarian.
我得去趟車里  等會兒就回來 I gotta run to my car. I'll be right back.
我能出去一會兒么 Mind if I step out for a moment?
我他媽才不管呢 I don't give a shit.
我猜猜 Let me guess.
"維  你把美味姐弄去保管處我很不爽" "Yo, Vee, I'm just so mad since y'all got Taystee transferred to custodial.
"這樣我只能一個人在圖書館玩兒奶了" "Just left me in the library with my titties in my hand."
猜對了嗎 Close?
你漏了一句 No, you left out,
"要是你害她惹麻煩  我就殺了你" "If you get her in trouble, I'll kill you."
-真的  -你試試 - Really? - Bet.
-你要怎么殺我呢  -我會想到辦法的 - And how would you kill me? - I'll figure it out.
我知道她覺得自己欠了你  可我明白 I know she thinks she owes you, but from what I heard,
你不過是個利用迷途小孩  只顧自己的惡霸 you're just a bully who uses lost kids for her own shit
等他們沒用了就扔到一邊 and then dumps 'em soon as the heat comes down.
你他媽就是個吸血鬼 You're a fucking vampire.
曾經有個小孩  叫哈羅·瓊斯 There was this kid growing up. Name was Haro Jones.
他那雙手臂啊  我喜歡得... He had these arms. I just wanted to...
只想從上舔到下... lick the length of his arms.
有一天我在公園里 And then one day I walked into the park.
看見他手伸進杰米拉·拉金的裙子里 Found his hand up Jamela Larkin's skirt.
真是傷透了我的心 Broke my poor fool heart.
聽著女人  我他媽才不管你過去的故事... Look, lady, I don't give a fuck about your little stories and shit...
美味姐... Taystee...
永遠... will...
不會... never...
喜歡... love...
你 you.
她永遠不會喜歡你 She will never love you.
不是你想要的那種 Not the way you want.
我不需要她喜歡我 Yo, I don't want her like that.
我只想照顧她  僅此而已 I'm just looking out for her. That's all.
爸爸  他媽幾個中國兵在我窗外抽煙來著 Yo, Pops, some fucking Chinese soldiers was just smoking right outside my window.
抱歉 I'm so sorry.
怎么了  媽媽呢 What? Where's Mom?
她沒事 She's fine.
我們被調回美國了 We're being transferred back to the States.
我也不知道為什么  但已經定了 I don't know why, but we are.
什么 What?
抱歉 Sorry.
讓你失望了  珀比 I let you both down, P.
我也不知該說什么好 I don't know what to say.
在這兒了 All right.
天哪... Jesus! The...
你越界了  查普曼 You're out of bounds, Chapman.
你不說出去  我就不說 Well, I won't tell if you don't.
把我們當犯人一樣對待 Treating us like we're prisoners.
我聽說這里曾經想建個體育館 Hey, you know, I heard that there were plans to build a gym here.
你知道后來怎么樣了嗎 Do you know whatever happened to that?
還不是老樣子 What always happens.
我來接手吧 I'll take it from here.
就是找一根出問題的電線 Just looking for a faulty wire.
為什么要問麥克斯韋體育館的事 Why are you asking Maxwell about a gym?
聽說最近你的問題有點多啊 From what I hear, you're full of questions lately.
你知道的  我一直很關心 You know that I have always been interested
他人的安全與健康 in the health and safety of others.
我還努力幫你去看你奶奶 I'm trying to help you with your nana.
所以我再問一遍  為什么你問這些問題 So again, why are you asking all these questions?
"新聞自由權并非只有自由人才有" "Freedom of the press shouldn't only be a privilege of the free."
這他媽扯什么犢子 What the fuck does that mean?
關新聞什么事 What does the press have anything to do with this?
我想開辦一份監獄簡報 I'm starting a prison newsletter.
-一份簡報  -對 - A newsletter? - A newsletter.
一份...由犯人撰寫的...簡報 A newsletter... written by the prisoners...
由文章和專欄組成 with articles and op-ed pieces.
所以我試著走出自己的世界 That is why I've been trying to get out of my bubble
開始了解這個地方 and get to know this place.
我們...這里是我們的家 We... This is our home.
我們應該加強彼此之間的交流 We should all be communicating more.
犯人啊  守衛啊  管理人員 Inmates, guards, administration.
這份簡報可以幫助 This could really,
我們更了解彼此  了解這里 really help us get to know each other and this place better.
當然需要您的同意 Pending your approval, of course,
主編大人 Mr. Editor-in-Chief.
別捧過頭了 Don't oversell it.
-一份簡報  -對 - A newsletter? - Mmm.
好吧  不是說我同意了 Okay. I'm not saying yes.
明天給我幾篇例文看看 Show me some sample stories by tomorrow.
明天  當然可以 Tomorrow? Sure. Okay. Yeah.
以前姑娘們都很喜歡我 The girls used to like me.
她們還會喜歡你的 They will again.
我的姑娘們都怎么樣 Hey, hey, hey. How my girls doing?
怎么又板起臉了 Why you got your famous pouty face on?
我不明白你在干嘛 I don't understand what you doing.
是嗎  有多少次你都不理解我在干嘛 Yeah? And how many times have you not understood my methods
最終不都搞懂了 only to have everything be made clear?
是嗎  那警察追RJ那次呢 Yeah, like when the cops were after RJ?
這么早就放大招了 God damn! You done gone for the nuclear option early.
為什么你不愿意談RJ Why don't you ever wanna talk about RJ?
因為都過去了  姑娘 Because it's in the past, girl.
而我活在現在  你也應該這樣 I live in the now. So should you.
庫茲尼克夫婦誠邀您參加他們女兒 安吉拉·庫茲尼克和克里斯托弗·麥克拉倫的婚禮 2月14日周五  下午4點
一整天我都他媽在洗廁所  為你辯護 All damn day I've been scrubbing toilets, defending you.
可我都不再相信你了 And I don't even believe in you anymore!
-美味  -不 - Taystee. - No!
你沒有任何計劃 You don't have a plan.
你只是想證明你還能使喚我 You just wanna prove that you can order me around.
但是不行  不行了 But no, not anymore.
-打開箱子  -什么 - Open the box. - What?
打開箱子 Open the box.
媽的  我告訴你  我不想再保潔了 Man, I told you. I'm done cleaning.
你在干嘛 What are you doing?
什么  煙草 What? Tobacco?
清潔劑去哪兒了 But where's the cleanser?
艾·沃
就好像是踏進浴缸 Okay, it's like getting into a bath,
水就像溫暖的巧克力布丁 but the water is like warm chocolate pudding.
還有史密斯樂隊演奏《今夜不眠》 And The Smiths are playing There Is a Light That Never Goes Out.
到處都是暖暖的燈光 Oh. There's warm lighting all over
五個男人幫你按摩 and there're like five dudes massaging you.
而且你還有個披薩 And you have a pizza.
她說的沒錯  你還有個披薩 She's right. And you also have a pizza.
我從那個有胡子的希臘妞那兒弄了點私酒 Hey, I got some hooch from that Greek chick with the beard.
-真不錯哎  -是吧 - That's pretty good! - Yeah?
費歇爾今天外出  有自己的活動 Fischer's out today. Apparently having her woman time.
是嘛 Oh.
喬呢 Where's Joe?
他也不在 He's out, too.
讓這些姑娘開什么派對 Let 'em have their stupid little party
又不留足夠人手管理 and then don't put enough muscle on.
太典型了 So typical.
布羅尼科斯基  控制著點 Bronikowski, leave room for Jesus.
不然我分分鐘就關了派對 I will shut this thing down in a heartbeat.
你說好不好笑 You know what's funny?
雖然我在女子監獄工作 I'm in a women's prison,
可我卻一點都不了解女人 but I don't understand women at all.
我告訴你  本尼特 I'll tell you something about women, Bennett.
女人啊  你要讓她們覺得你投入了很多感情 With women, you make 'em think you're meeting them halfway,
可實際上呢 when really what you're doing is
你只投入了10%到15% you're meeting them about 10% to 15% of the way.
女人數學都不好  記住這點 Women are really bad at math. Don't forget that.
我會的  先生 I won't, sir.
-杰克有打電話嗎  -誰 - Did Jack call yet? - Who?
聽我說  達婭 Listen, Daya.
雖然我們沒法做平常情侶  但是... I know we can't be normal, but...
別說了 Shh.
帶我出去  現在 Take me somewhere. Now.
她們更大了 Wow. They're bigger!
快點 Let's go.
怎么了 What is this?
嘿 Yo!
閉上眼睛 Close your eyes.
-為什么  -閉上 - What? Why? - Close 'em.
張開嘴 Open your lips.
少張點 Less.
-美味...  -快點 - T... - Do it.
什么  香煙 What? What's this? A cigarette?
要做生意了  珀比  維擬定好了銷售計劃 We in business, P! Vee's got a whole sales plan.
我們有報酬  我跟你說 We getting paid! I told you.
要有錢了啊 Next-level Mr. Miyagi shit, son!
讓你爸爸想辦法啊 Tell your father to fight!
沒用的 Won't help.
是你爸想要我們走 Your father wants us gone,
我們就得走 we're gone.
那我和你一起走 Then I'm coming with you.
你不會喜歡新澤西的 Don't think Jersey's for you.
我愛你  珀比 I love you, Poussey.
聽著 Look.
操你很爽 You're fun to fuck,
不過也就這樣了 but that's it.
你是我一生所愛 You're the love of my life.
你的奶子真心不錯  我會記住的 You have killer tits. I'll remember those.
昨天你還說你愛我 Yesterday you loved me!
怎么今天就這樣了 How can you just shut down like that?
我是老手了 I've had a lot of practice.
真是意想不到的驚喜 Well, that was unexpected.
抱歉我之前心情不好 Sorry. I was in a mood before.
你真貼心 You're the sweetest man.
給你 Here.
還有條狗 Look at the dog!
真棒 This is so great.
你的也很棒啊 So was this.
這個 Mmm. This.
干嘛偷偷摸摸的 Sneaky, sneaky man.
致我的愛人
情人節快樂  那對小孩就是我們  情人節快樂  馬上就能快樂  你知道我是誰
你看  我們也能成為普通情侶 See? We can be a normal couple.
不過你把"情"字寫錯了 Except you misspelled "Valentine's."
不  我不會 No, I didn't.
是門德斯寫的 Mendez did.
你們好 Hi.
我們準備創辦一份簡報 I was wondering if I could ask you a few questions
所以能問你們幾個問題嗎 for a newsletter we're starting.
辦簡報  祝你們好運 A newsletter? Okay, good luck.
你看  今天是情人節 So, since it's Valentine's Day,
你覺得愛是什么 what is love to you?
你們怎么定義愛 How would you define love?
這問題真他媽蠢 That's a retarded fucking question.
好吧 Okay. Um...
換個問題 How about this?
上一次你們見到 When was the last time
大規模的水管修繕是什么時候 you saw any major plumbing work being done around here?
我想想 Hmm.
-大概04  05年吧  -04  05年 - '04-'05, maybe? - '04-'05.
有個叫唐娜·庫索的胖妞一周內弄壞了三個馬桶 This fatso named Donna Cusio broke three toilets in one week.
真他媽一團糟啊 It was a mess, man.
我想也是  太肥了肯定 I bet. Big, big woman.
我是卡佳  請留言 This is Katya. Leave a message.
寶貝 Hi, honey.
是我 It's me.
我打來就是想祝你情人節快樂 I just wanted to call and wish you a happy Valentine's Day.
你愿意 Would you like...
和我 to dance...
跳支舞嗎 with me?
我是為你學的 I learned that for you.
我是一個好男人  卡佳  你會明白的 I'm a good man, Katya. You'll see that.
我一定會讓你自豪能嫁給我這個傻蛋 I'm gonna make you really proud to be married to this big galoot.
我發誓 I swear to...
什么叫菲利斯不存在 The fuck you mean there's no Ferris?
說的是《春天不是讀書天》的情節
聽我說 No, okay. Hear me out.
菲利斯只是 Ferris is just a projection
卡梅隆假想出來的  表現他不敢反抗專橫的爸爸 of Cameron's inability to stand up to his domineering father.
但問題就在這里  卡梅隆根本沒離開過房間 But here's the mind-fuck. Cameron never actually leaves his room!
記得嗎  他病了 Remember, he's sick.
于是他想象出一個理想化的自己  菲利斯 He invents this idealized self, Ferris.
還給他弄了個三十歲的女朋友 Plus his, like, 30-year-old girlfriend.
然后想象出了之后一系列的冒險 And then imagines this epic adventure
追車  游行  打球等等 with car chases, parades, ball games, blah, blah, blah.
所以逃學的一天 So this day off
只是他身體與意識的脫離... is actually just the day off from his rigid coherence to mind-body alignment...
你他媽就不能給我閉嘴嗎 Would you please shut the fuck up?
抱歉  只是我看的一個理論而已 Sorry. It's just a theory I read.
下次直接坐她臉上  她就閉嘴了 Next time, just sit on her face. It shuts her right up.
我會記住的 I'll keep that in mind.
為什么故意不理我 Why are you ignoring me?
為什么不理我  說啊 Why are you ignoring me? Spit it out! Come on!
你之前一直獨裁這個小團體 Look, you've been lording over this group
就跟希拉里一樣 like some Hillary Clinton dictator.
-什么  -可我們想要民主 - What? - And we wanna be a democracy.
你說我是希拉里·克林頓 Are you calling me Hillary Clinton?
要是你也穿得下褲套裝 If the pantsuit fits.
聽著  我們不帶你玩了 Look, we're done with you. Right?
你們不帶我了 Y'all are done with me?
真是搞笑啊  琳恩 That's really funny. That's really funny, Leanne.
如果我是希拉里 'Cause if I'm Hillary Clinton,
那你們就是賤人  毒鬼  只知道喝思樂冰 then y'all must be some sister-wife, tweaker, Slurpee-drinking,
沒文化  沒爹的拖車癟三 fourth-grade reading level, Daddy-on-COPS, trailer trash nothing!
你們知道嗎  我無所謂 And you know what? It's okay
因為你們從來對我都不算什么 'cause you ain't never even challenged me anyway.
其實  你們誰都不行 Actually, you know what? None of you did. Not one.
你老是和比你差的人打網球 You keep playing tennis with someone worse than you
你就永遠打不好  所以謝謝 and you ain't never gonna get better. So thank you.
-你還打網球  -這是比喻  你個傻逼 - You play tennis? - It's a metaphor, you potato with eyes!
不好意思要說臟話了  你們吃屎去吧 You know what? Pardon my French, but you can eat my shit.
婊子 Whore.
婊子  婊子 Whore. Whore.
剛才可真尷尬 Man, that was awkward.
-安琪  -嗯 - Angie? - Yeah?
給我拿點飲料 Go get me some punch.
派對不錯 Great party.
聽著  我們很高興 Listen, we are so happy
你和達婭有如此美好秘密的特殊時光 that you and Daya are having such fun, special, secret times together.
我們也很欣賞你對她這么好 And we really admire you providing for her so well.
盡管是這種情況 You know, despite the circumstances.
我們只想讓你知道 And we just wanted to let you know
我們將以沉默來表達對你的完全支持 that we support you 500% with our continued silence.
鑒于如此  下次你再夾帶私貨進來時 Considering as such, in your next round of leg-based contraband,
我們有幾個要求 we had a couple requests
這樣我們能更愉快地保持沉默 that could make our aforementioned silence a little bit more comfortable.
我呢  想要一個iPod隨身聽 I mean, I, personally, request an iPod Shuffle.
裝點后朋克啊  趕時髦樂隊啊 You know, loaded with alt and post-punk, Depeche Mode,
滅跡樂隊之類的歌 Erasure...
我想要悠忽飲料  還有無酒精含氟漱口水 And I need Yoo-hoo and ACT Fluoride Rinse for my teeth.
我想要個手機  帶攝像頭  謝謝 A cell phone. With a camera. Thank you.
情人節快樂 Happy Valentine's Day.
-謝謝  -好吧 - Thanks. - Okay.
你這招太他媽損了 You know, that's a fucking low blow,
就算是你這賤貨  尼古拉斯   真的 even for a filthy sewer rat like you, Nichols. Really.
你告訴別人我有陰虱 You told people I have crabs.
你才發現啊 You just found out about that?
你這是作弊 It is cheating!
沒事  羅瑞格茲在波士頓被砸時也沒哭啊 Come on. A-Rod doesn't cry when he gets plunked in Beantown.
他還不是撐住了  去盜二壘 He sucks it up and tries to steal second.
我也想舔舔  上二壘啊 I've been trying to both suck and steal second,
要是大家都覺得我有陰虱我還怎么上啊 but I can't because everybody thinks I have cooties!
說到上壘  你多少分了 Speaking of a set, how many you got?
Thirty-six.
剛洗澡時剛給波克插了雙指 After I gave Pirkle the double shocker in the showers just now.
真的  你上了波克 Really? You Pirkled?
是啊  一遍又一遍 Oh, I Pirkled and then I Pirkled again.
-感覺怎么樣  -很粗糙 - And? - It was gnarly.
陰蒂好大 It's macroclit.
-就像給小孩口活似的  -我的天 - It was like blowing a toddler. - Oh, my God!
-很不舒服  -太他媽有勁了 - It was so uncomfortable. - That's fucking hilarious.
36  那我們倆打平了 Oh, God! So 36. We're tied.
-是的  -沒錯 - Yep. - Yeah.
-要不就到此為止吧  -要不別再玩兒了 - Hey, do you wanna just stop? - Have you considered maybe we just stop?
-我是無所謂啦  -你要想繼續我也可以啊 - Because I could do that. - I don't have to but if you want to.
-因為我們都操了...  -不少了 - 'Cause we both fucked... - Lots.
還記得我們當初為什么要比這個么 Remind me why we did this to ourselves in the first place.
因為我無比好勝 Because I am insanely competitive.
而我因為上癮所以得時刻滿足需要 And I need to feed my addictive tendencies at all times.
吃餅干大賽 Cookie-eating contest?
你認識我嗎 Son, have you ever actually seen me?
-你肯定會輸  -滾開 - You are going down. - Get out...
謝謝大家  這是送給科拉的 Thanks, guys. That was for Cora.
我們會想念你的笑聲  玉米狗  現在休息一會兒 We're gonna miss your laugh, Corndog. And we're gonna take five.
你來了  我們正好要休息一會兒 Hey! You made it! We're just going on break.
你看上去和平時不太一樣 Wow. You look so different.
工作時我還是想比較正經點 Well, you know. I like to keep things profesh at work.
我給你在吧臺留了個高位 I saved you a stool with a view.
其實我需要一張桌子 Actually, we're gonna need a table.
-我不知道你要來  -我說了這應該挺好玩的 - I didn't know you were coming. - You heard me say it sounded fun.
希望你不介意我跟別人提了你的演出 I hope you don't mind I told some of the guys about your show.
我差點趕不過來 I almost didn't make it.
現在賣方不肯劃掉 Get this, the sellers are now refusing to drop
突發置換這一項 the replacement contingency!
你他媽能別提房子的事兒了嗎 Would you shut up about real estate?
我當初要你搬進來你不肯 I asked you to move in with me and you said no.
所以你現在沒資格說話 So you have no talking rights here.
不錯  像雙重約會 This is nice. Like a double date!
-我們不是一對  -我們不是一對 - We're not together. - We're not together.
我們還需要一把椅子 Actually we're gonna need another chair.
為什么 Why?
你看著像基佬 You look like the Gay Edge.
你好啊 Hey!
留位
就好像是  你更是你自己了  平時都是... It's like you become more you. Which normally is like...
可是現在好了  那個人 But now it's okay... because the person, like,
不管是誰  他包容你的一切 whoever, they chose to take all that on.
所有奇奇怪怪的方面 All that weird stuff.
無論是不好的還是隱藏的特質 Whatever's wrong or bad or hiding in you.
突然都沒關系了 Suddenly it's all right.
你不再覺得自己是個怪胎了 You don't feel like such a freak anymore.
萊瑞 Larry!
月亮敢這樣嗎 Would the moon do this?
我贏了 I won!
萊瑞  很高興見到你 Larry! Good to see you, mate.
身上有些味道抱歉  剛宰了頭鹿 Sorry about the stink. I killed a caribou!
腌在菠蘿汁里野味就能淡點 Less gamey marinated in pineapple juice.
還讓精液更美味 Also, makes your spunk taste good.
所以寶貝你有福了  這是什么 So you're in luck, babe! What's that?
這是... Oh. It's, uh...
是帕波的東西 It's Piper's stuff.
哥們  一起吧  我們正要出去吃點拉面 Aw. Brother. Come on, we were just heading out for some ramen.
現在有保姆能偷點閑  東西讓門童看著 You know, we have a babysitter! I'll leave these with the doorman.
不用了  皮特  我得... No, Pete. Really, I should... I...
這可是情人節啊  混蛋  一起來 It's Valentine's Day, asshole! Come join us.
我在你垃圾桶里找到這個 I found this in your trash.
這是... And this is...
你一直提起的那個人 the guy you always talking about?
我知道愛一個 Yeah, I know something about loving people
不知回報的人的滋味 who aren't smart enough to wanna be loved back.
但我知道個秘密  我告訴你 But I learned a secret that I can tell you.
他們都不值得愛 They don't deserve it.
他永久地毀了我的這個節日 He's ruined this day for me forever.
大家都不知道我們不在一起了 Nobody knows that we're not together.
可是你知道啊 Yeah, but you do.
-是  我知道  -對了 - I do. I do know. - Yeah.
你知道最瘋狂的是什么嗎 You know what is crazy?
就是經歷了這一切一切 I still wanna believe in all of this stuff.
我還愿意相信這些東西 Even after everything that's happened.
-是不是很可悲  -不不 - Isn't that sad? - Oh, no.
我覺得這是勇敢 I think that's brave.
謝謝 Thank you.
說真的  你覺得我該隆胸嗎 Seriously. Do you think I should get fake tits?
是的 Yeah. Probably.
伊恩
混蛋 Asshole.
你知道我最難過什么嗎 You know what gets me?
我們在這里浪費了最美好的年華 We're wasting the best years of our lives in here.
我們的胸不會比現在更美 Like, our tits are never gonna look better.
我們的翹臀也不會比現在更美 Our asses are never gonna look better.
沒人上我  沒人吻我 You know, no one's touching my ass. No one's kissing my lips.
傻瓜  我來吻你 Shit. I'll kiss your dumb lips.
再來一次 Do it again.
-不行  -不行不行 - No! - No! No.
不行 No.
過來 Come here.
沒事的 It's okay.
珀比  過來給她們看看什么才是真正的鬼步舞 Yo, P. Come and show these fools how to cabbage patch for real.
不用了 Nah. I'm good.
別裝得什么事都沒有一樣 Man, don't act like everything fine. Like this...
行了  你吃千層面 Yo. I don't interrupt you
吃得正爽的時候我也沒打攪過你啊 when you going to town on a bunch of spaghetti. Damn!
回你那維媽身邊去好了 Yo, why don't you head on back to old Erykah Badu over there?
我就當沒聽見這句 I'm gonna forget you said that.
我又不在乎你聽沒聽見 I don't give a fuck what you forget or remember!
媽逼這下好了  多謝啊 Oh, shit. Great! Thanks a lot, man.
你走開 You should leave.
珀比 Poussey!
這是我和你爸之間的事 This is between me and your father.
喂 Hey!
-喂  -干嘛 - Hey! - Well?
-我們不走  -跟美國人說去 - We're not leaving. - Talk to the Americans.
操你媽逼  你這個混蛋  都是你 Fuck you. Fuck you, man. This is your doing. You!
喝酒了吧  孩子 Been drinking, little girl?
珀比  別這樣 Poussey, please.
你無權決定我的生活 You don't get to decide what happens to my life!
你沒這個權利 Not you!
我愛她 I love her.
所以你必須回家 And that is why you're going home.
我受夠了  我哪兒都不去 I'm done. I'm not going anywhere.
抱歉  中校 Pardon us, Oberstleutnant.
請繼續享用冰激凌 Enjoy your ice cream.
你知道嗎  現在有些治療項目 You know, there are programs
可以糾正你女兒有問題的取向 that can change your daughter's confused predilections.
謝謝  但她沒事 Thanks, but she's fine.
我的女士 My lady.
派對真有意思啊 Fun party.
沒男人  沒酒  沒點像樣的吃的  也沒有粉 A party with no men, booze, real food or drugs.
還好我們年紀大了  無所謂了 Good thing we're too old for any trouble.
沒錯  花園搗騰得怎么樣了 Right. How's the gardening going?
天氣轉暖  就能真正用了 Once the thaw comes, we'll really get going.
我本想喊你加入 Well, I'd ask you to join,
不過看著你有自己的事兒 but you clearly have your own hobbies.
我們得有人 We gotta have people.
你知道這樣不會有善終 You know this will not end well.
你真笨 You're retarded.
你呢  查普曼 What about you, Chapman?
就好像一次漫長的旅途后  終于回家 It's like coming home after a long trip.
這就是愛 That's what love is like.
就像回家 It's like coming home.
謝謝你問我 Thanks for asking.