Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
Created time 14.07.04 19:01:13
女子監獄 第二季 第九集
查普曼辦理手續  查普曼辦理手續 Chapman to processing. Chapman to processing.
我知道我說了要烤的  斯科特 I know I said toasted, Scott.
但如果你在上面蓋張紙巾的話 If you cover it with a paper towel,
等我檢查完蛀牙  它就還是熱的 it'll still be warm when I finish the cavity search.
坐N號線  謝謝 Take the n train. Thank you.
走吧 Off you go.
咳一下 Cough.
你可以用力點  撐開你的粉菊花 You can do better than that. Shake out that pink.
我難道會想把監獄里的東西帶出去嗎 What could I possibly be trying to take out of prison?
這是規矩  別問道理  站起來 It's procedure. Don't look for logic. Stand up.
換上這些衣服 Change into these.
趕緊的  有些人還想吃百吉餅呢 Hurry up. Some of us have bagels to eat.
你是否了解等你回來后 Do you understand you will be subjected to
需要接受尿檢并且上述檢查的費用 a urinalysis upon your return and said test
需由你自己承擔 is your own financial responsibility?
我明白 Yes.
你不可以購買  銷售  擁有  使用 You may not purchase, sell, possess, use,
消費或給予任何毒品  大麻  酒精 consume, or administer any narcotic drugs, marijuana, alcohol,
或任何形式的麻醉品 or intoxicants of any form
也不得前往非法出售  分發   or frequent places where such articles are
使用或贈送以上物品的地點 unlawfully sold, dispensed, used, or given away.
-你說的真溜  -多謝夸獎 -That was really impressive. - Thanks.
我在腦子里搭著《撲克臉》的調說的  便于記憶 I sing it to the tune of poker face in my head to remember.
嘎嘎小姐唱的  你想聽嗎 Lady gaga? You wanna hear?
不用了  沒關系 No, that... That's okay.
走吧  小鳥  自由的飛翔吧 Go ahead, little bird. Fly free.
帕波 Pipette!
那是接你的車嗎 Is that your ride?
我以為你是雅皮士而不是嬉皮士 Pegged you more for a yuppie than a hippie.
所有來訪者必須向警官報告
犯人  48小時后見   See you in 48 hours, inmate.
快到綠色機器里來 Come inside the green machine!
-怎么了  -為什么聞起來像天婦羅 - What? - Why does it smell like tempura?
沒錯  植物油  慢慢熟悉吧 Oh, yeah, vegetable oil. Get hip to it.
是內莉跟我們家前面那家鐵板燒店換來的 Neri barters with this teppanyaki place up the road from us.
友希很喜歡內莉仙女外套 Yuki loves neri's fairy coats.
怎么了 What's up?
難以相信她死了 Just can't believe she's dead.
了解  了解 I know. I know.
如果能讓你感覺好點的話 If it makes you feel any better,
你并沒有錯過太多 you didn't miss much.
她就是睡了幾天 She just slept for a few days,
然后就永遠地睡了過去 and then the sleep stopped being temporary.
我都沒機會跟她道別 I didn't get a chance to say goodbye.
我替你說了 I told her for you.
她知道的  帕波 She knew, Piper.
準備走了嗎  請系好安全帶 Ready? Seat belts, please.
下一個 Next.
三瓶達什太太牌的調味粉 Three Mrs. Dash's table blend,
四瓶檸檬汁  五瓶阿斗波粉   four lemon juices, five adobo powders,
外加兩瓶洋蔥粉 and two onion powders.
哇  山雀大媽 Whoo-wee, chickadee.
你現在還要用這些調料做什么 What do you need with all these spices these days?
這可不管你的事 Oh, that's none of your business.
你肯定有很多私房錢  是吧 You must have a pretty hefty fund, huh?
你那些沒用的兒子終于洗心革面了嗎 Those no-good sons finally doing the right thing?
達米特里是不是中彩票大獎了 Dmitri hit it big with a scratcher ticket?
不要談論我的家人 Don't you dare talk about my family.
雖然現在經濟形勢不太好   Maybe your little market turned around
不過可能你的小店生意好轉了吧 in spite of the economy and everything.
犯人  請保持隊伍前進   Let's keep the line moving, inmates.
-調料給我  -好 - The spices, please. - All righty.
很高興看到你找到了自己的生活方式 It just warms my heart to see you finding your way in here,
和一群老年人共同生活 settling in with the aarp crowd.
園藝似乎是個挺舒服的活 Gardening looks like a comfortable little life.
下一個 Next.
妮琪  妮琪 Nicky. Nicky!
我需要你幫忙 I need a favor.
那得看你能出多少 Well, that's gonna cost you.
你要什么 What's your price?
燕麥餡餅 Oatmeal pies.
那小東西雖然 The little debbie ones that
會讓你沾上滿手油漬 leave that oily residue all over your hands,
但還是非常美味 but are still somehow delicious.
成交 Done.
我要你明天帶所有姑娘們去溫室房 I need you to bring all the girls to the greenhouse tomorrow...
在晚餐的時候 At dinnertime.
那你得給我兩盒 That'll run you two boxes.
如果你想聽我的意見  你這方法完全不對 And if you want my opinion, you're going about this all wrong.
這一次會非常特別的 This is going to be really special.
你即使在難吃的蛋糕上面加一層糖衣 You know, another layer of icing on a shit cake
也不會讓它變得好吃 doesn't make it taste good.
我聽不懂你在說什么 I don't understand what you...
你知道你還有什么話沒說嗎  紅媽 Well, you know what you haven't said, Red?
498號  干擾警務人員執行公務 498! Interfering with a staff member in performance of duties.
難道你的男朋友沒教你 Didn't your boyfriend teach you
要怎么對待警官的嗎  下垂妹 how to treat a staff member, Floppy Tits?
一次警告 That's a shot!
母豬  你襯衫上是什么東西   Hey! What's on your shirt there, Pigpen?
是屎  眼淚還是薯片 Shit? Tears? Potato chips?
330號  不衛生 330! Being unsanitary.
記過  我不喜歡你的表情 Shot! I don't like your face.
312號  傲慢  記過 312. Insolence. Shot!
賤人們  我門德斯回來了   Mendez is back, bitches.
他來這里干什么 What the hell is he doing here?
約翰  這真是個美好的早晨 Why, yes, John, it's a beautiful morning.
甚至很平靜 Peaceful, even.
先生您知道的  他危及到犯人們的安全 He endangers the inmates, and you know it, sir.
他出現在這里甚至是不合法的  是吧 I mean, it can't even be legal to have him here, can it?
-你要不要先坐下來  -不用 - Would you like to have a seat? - No.
他的停職結束了  所以我們必須得面對 His suspension is up, so we're gonna have to deal with it.
還有  只跟你說 And between you and me,
管理層有人覺得我們需要人手 some of the administration feel there's a job to do.
沒有別人能勝任這個位置 No one else is up to the task.
我能夠 I'm up to the task.
很好  證明一下 Good. Prove it.
我會的 I will.
何不說說來這的原因   用你自己的話說 Why don't we start with why you're here. In your opinion.
有不只一個人 Well, it was... suggested to me...
建議我要來看看 by more than one person.
那么馬澤爾博士 So... Uh, Dr. Maser...
叫我克莉絲就好  我不是博士 Oh, just "Chris," Please. I'm not a doctor.
或許這不是個好主意 Maybe this was a bad idea.
山姆  感覺不爽沒有關系 Well, it's okay to be uncomfortable, Sam.
我會鼓勵你接受這種感覺 It's a feeling I would encourage you to embrace.
接受它嗎  我都活在這感覺中 Embrace it? I live it.
我對整個生活都感到不爽 My whole life is uncomfortable.
所有這些女人  罪犯  白癡般的官僚們 All these women, criminals, bureaucratic idiots.
我在自己家甚至都沒有家的感覺 I don't even feel at home in my own home anymore.
現在我在一間暀W掛著 And now I'm sitting in an office
古怪青蛙油畫的辦公室里坐著 with some weird painting of frogs,
而這些畫我猜本應該是舒緩心情的 which I'm guessing is supposed to be soothing.
山姆  我覺得你的壓力很大 Sam, I'm hearing a lot of stress.
沒錯  大到甚至都無法形容 Yeah, well, that doesn't even begin to cover it, okay?
你喜歡你的工作嗎 Do you like your job?
以前喜歡過  真的 I used to. I really did.
我覺得自己很能干 I felt useful.
是什么改變了 And what changed?
我知道就見鬼了 Hell if I know.
我變老了 I got older.
或許我在乎的更少了 Maybe I care less.
或許看得多了  知道我沒辦法改變現狀 Maybe I've seen enough to know that I won't make a difference.
知道這是在浪費時間 That it's all a waste.
你知道 You know...
有時候我們總從一個角度看問題  會困住 sometimes we get stuck seeing things from one perspective,
但如果我們能稍微改變看問題的角度 but if we can just shift our perspective even a little bit,
一切就會大不相同 makes all the difference.
就這樣嗎 That's it?
這就是你高達75美元一小時的建議嗎 That's your fancy, $75-an-hour advice?
你對我的收費感到不爽嗎 Are you uncomfortable with the amount I charge?
我以為我們剛剛已經說明 I thought we just established
我對一切都感到不爽 that I'm uncomfortable with everything!
你一直是這樣易怒嗎 Are you always this quick to anger?
你一直是這樣高人一等的賤人嗎 Are you always a condescending cunt?
抱歉  我真的抱歉 Oh, I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
我想我們的工作不好做啊 Well, I think we have our work cut out for us.
我的鞋子有點緊 My shoes feel tight.
我要說的是這個人叫海因里希·德萊塞 But I'm saying this guy, Heinrich Dreser,
他應該被直接歸到壞人那一類 deserves to be right up there on the bad-guy shelf.
我們的伙計海因里希 So, our buddy Heinrich
拜耳  德國著名藥企
在拜耳負責管理海洛因的藥物開發 oversaw the development of heroin at Bayer.
拜耳公司在1900年代初期將這種藥物 Yep. So, the corporate suits at Bayer sold this shit over the counter
作為非成癮性的嗎啡替代品放到柜臺出售 as a non-addictive morphine substitute in the early 1900s,
你知道為什么他們稱它為海洛因嗎 and you know why they called it heroin?
因為當他們開始測試這藥物的時候 'Cause when they started testing it,
人們說這藥會讓他們感覺很英勇 people said it made them feel heroic. Right?
我想站在這里作為恢復好的人  鼓勵大家 I'd like to stand up here and be all inspiring and recovered
告訴你們我戒掉了 and tell you I'm over it,
不過我每天還是非常想念 but I miss it every fucking day, you know?
海洛因是我一生的愛   Uh, heroin is the love of my life,
她是我的最佳女友 she's my best girlfriend...
她是我的靈魂伴侶 she's my soul mate,
因為沒有東西比她能讓我感覺更好受 'cause, you know, she makes me feel better than anything.
最后我要說一句 So, in closing, uh...
操他媽的德國人 fuck the Germans.
好了  今天就講這些  孩子們 Okay, that's it for today, kids.
努力接受你所不能改變的現實 Strength to accept what you cannot change,
神奇仙塵  獨角獸之類的 magical fairy dust, unicorns, etcetera.
你是羅莎對吧 Hey. Rosa, right?
多謝你還記得我的名字 How kind of you to remember.
你讀過這本書嗎  關于患癌兒童的 Did you read this? It's about kids with cancer.
我不知道為什么這個傻逼作者想寫這樣的書 I don't know why the sick fuck wanted to write about this.
總之我想你會對這本書感興趣 Anyway, I... I thought it might be right up your alley.
我的人生已經足夠壓抑了 I got enough depressing shit in my life.
我不想讀的書也那么壓抑 I don't need it in my books, too.
那么你的逃避方式是什么   So, what's your escape, then, huh?
是吃止疼片  還是喝酒 Is it pain pills, booze?
每個人時不時都需要幫助應對現實 Everybody needs a little bit of help with reality now and then.
關于現實那件事 The thing about reality...
就是它明天早上依然會等著你 is it's still there waiting for you the next morning.
不錯的演講  辯論隊肯定會喜歡你 Nice talk. They must've loved you on the debate team.
是啊 Oh, yeah.
我曾連續兩年在原創辯論賽中拿第一 I was first place Original Oratory two years running.
直到我弄傷了教練的腳趾被開除 You know, until I got expelled for breaking my coach's toe.
一言難盡  現在說不清楚 Long story, not for now.
可以找一天聊聊 Maybe one day.
好的  當然 Uh, yeah, sure.
我來這是幫你減輕負擔的 I am here to unburden you.
拿到我的東西了沒 You got my goods?
你已經拿到大部分了 You got most of them already.
雖然我俄語說的不溜  但在西語和英語中 Ooh, I'm not fluent in Russian, but in Spanish and English,
"大部分"就意味著不是全部 "Most of them" Means not all of them.
歌洛麗婭  你了解我的   Gloria, you know me.
其余的很快就到 The rest will be here soon.
我是一個言出必行的女人 I'm a woman of my word.
而我是一個要求按時交貨的女人 And I'm a woman who gets paid on time in full.
瑞澤尼科夫  你越界了 Reznikov, you're out of bounds.
你叫我什么來著 What did you call me?
馬上回到界內來 Get back in bounds right now.
你什么時候開始關心我站哪了 Since when do you care where I am?
記過一次 That's a shot.
307號  拒絕服從警務人員的命令 307, refusing to obey an order from a staff member.
他現在是你的走狗嗎 He's your bulldog now?
不是  別看我 Oh, no. Don't look at me.
他沒鏈子拴著  我也不想被他咬 He's off leash, and I don't want to get bitten, either.
回見 I'll see you around.
別讓我再抓到你在廚房邊上 Don't let me catch you anywhere near the kitchen again.
你知道該怎么做 You know the drill.
你會是個了不起的父親 You're going to make a great father.
你還好嗎  親愛的 You okay, hon?
我很好  謝謝 Fine, yes. Thank you.
這需要適應  他們是這么說的 It's an adjustment. That's what they say.
你的生活費到了嗎 Your commissary come through yet?
-沒有  -沒有嗎  我也是 - No. - No? Me, either.
我昨天進來后就沒刷過牙 Haven't brushed my teeth since we came in yesterday.
我開始感覺像是穿了一件兔毛衫 Starting to feel like an angora sweater in there.
這里有個叫卡拉的女人  她會幫你整理 There's this lady in here, Carla, she'll wanna do that for you.
我以前來過  我能行 I've been around before. I got it.
我要去洗手間 I gotta take a leak.
你是帕克嗎  我是朗達 You Parker? Rhonda.
給你帶了一些東西  算是見面禮 Brought you some stuff, a little welcome basket.
我們早餐時見 We'll see you at breakfast.
我不吃早飯 I don't eat breakfast.
早飯會讓我腸胃不適 It upsets my stomach.
現在你要吃了  You eat it now.
我們走 Let's go.
想要點嗎 Want some of this?
不用了  謝謝 No, thank you.
里面有三支牙刷  她們只是在炫耀 Three toothbrushes in here. It's just showing off.
給你  拿一支吧 Here. Take one, please.
謝謝 Thank you.
牙膏也給你 Get some toothpaste, too.
你真好 You're very kind.
你有分配到工作嗎 You got assigned a work detail yet?
廚房 Kitchen.
那是個好工作 That's a plum gig.
是的  就像在家一樣 Yes, feels like home.
我家里開了一家小店  我負責做吃的 My family, we own a small market, and I serve food there.
是嗎  你是個好廚師嗎 Yeah? You a good cook?
我很會做菜  還有聽著 I am very good. And get this.
我用的原料跟這里的廚房用的一樣 I use the same produce people that the kitchen here uses.
不過如果他們當初敢給我這里拿到的那種破爛貨 Although, if they delivered me the shit they send here,
我會把東西扔回他們臉上 I would throw it in their faces.
他們知道要給我好東西 They knew to give me the good stuff.
他們欠我的 They owed me.
現在他們真的欠我了 Now they really owe me.
海王星  真是愚蠢的名字 Neptune. Stupid name.
我告訴過他們海王星應該賣海鮮而不是水果 I told them Neptune is for seafood, not fruit.
你認識供應商嗎 You know a vendor?
不只是認識  他們是因為我來這的 Know them? They're here because of me.
而我進這里也是因為他們 And I'm here because of them.
你得利用這點  讓你的監獄生活好過些 You need to use that. Make your life here better.
就是因為犯法才讓我進了監獄 Breaking rules got me in here.
沒錯  我不是要對你指手畫腳 Yeah, well, I'm not telling you what to do, you know.
我只是在告訴你如何生存 I'm just telling you how to survive.
下一個 Next.
只要一支  我剛發現 Only one. I just learned I like a smoke
我讀完中篇小說后  喜歡抽上一支 after I read my sexy-time novellas.
感覺棒極了  但 It feels glamorous, but like,
我仍然不是一個真正的煙客 I'm still not a real smoker, you know?
沒錯  好了 Yeah, all right.
請確保將這本書重新放到合適的書架 Just make sure you reshelve this book in its proper place.
我們這里是按照杜威狗屁分類法擺放的 We on Dewey decimal and shit in here.
別讓我在超自然現象區找到水上運動的書 Don't let me find no aquatic sports over in paranormal phenomena.
-明白  -好 - Got it. - All right.
操 Fuck you.
多謝了  真是量多的一天 Oh, thanks, man. Heavy flow day over here.
我把你手弄傷了嗎 I break your hand?
快回去干活 Get back to your job.
我按了門鈴  是不是很奇怪 Hi, I rang the bell. Is that weird?
我不想直接走進來 I didn't wanna just walk right in.
沒關系  不用這樣 It... It's fine. You're fine. Wow, it's...
你真的回來了  太瘋狂了 You're actually here. It's crazy.
是啊 Yeah.
不許接觸 No touching!
抱歉  我只是想讓你的過渡平穩些 Sorry. I'm just trying to ease your transition.
變化太多太快對你不宜 Too much, too fast can be a shock to the system.
就像戰俘們終于有東西吃的時候 Like when POWs finally get to eat,
他們會吃太多導致把胃撐破 and then they eat too much and their stomachs explode?
-不過我們倆可以接觸  -是的  你好 - We can touch, though. - Yeah, hello.
你好  很高興見到你 Hello, good to see you.
我的天啊 Oh, my God.
直到離開一段時間之后 You never remember what home smells like
你才會記得家里的味道 until you've been gone for a while.
我記得以前總會 I remember that I always used
在從露營回來時有這種感覺 to think about that when I got back from camp,
身上都是我朋友的味道 that I was smelling what my friends smelled.
是什么味道 What's it like?
你的味道 You.
洗衣粉的味道 Laundry detergent. That, um...
那些在安托保羅杰店里買的蠟燭的味道 Those candles from Anthropologie.
安托保羅杰 一家以人類學的法語名稱命名的美國零售商
還有咖啡的味道 And... coffee.
咖啡  來點咖啡吧 Coffee? Coffee?
好的 Sure.
這些都是我的東西嗎 Hey, is this all... is this all my stuff?
是的 It's your stuff.
我怎么會有那么多衣服  天吶 Why do I have so many clothes? My God.
我真的覺得需要所有這些東西嗎 Did I really think that I needed all of these?
天啊  我的羊絨衫 Oh, my God. Oh, my God, my cashmere sweater!
萊瑞  我的褲子裝在哪袋 Larry, which one has all my pants in it?
那些可能已經在波麗家了 Those are probably over at Polly's already.
她怎么樣 Oh, how is she?
-波麗嗎  -是的 - Polly? Um... - Yeah.
她很好  我想她過的挺好 She's fine. She's fine, I think. You know?
她明天可能來不了 She's probably not gonna make it tomorrow.
她正在給孩子做睡眠訓練 She's sleep training the baby and...
她說這個訓練真的很辛苦 she said it's been... It's been really tough on her, so...
我對塞萊斯特的去世真的很遺憾 Hey, I'm sorry about... sorry about Celeste.
多謝了  布魯姆 Thanks, Bloomer.
沒事 Oh, it's fine.
不  感覺不好 No, it's not fine.
不好  你記得媽媽的那個枕頭嗎 It's not. Do you remember that pillow that Mom had?
枕頭背后有一只奶牛 The one with the cow on its back
奶牛的腿都朝上的 and its legs were all up in the air?
在奶牛下面寫著  "我很好  真的" Uh, under the cow it says, "I'm fine, really."
多么傻逼的枕頭 What a stupid fuckin' pillow.
現在我在用這個枕頭 Oh, I have it now.
味道真不錯 That's really good.
沙發座套  這座套真的很舒服 Ooh, upholstery. Upholstery is really good.
如果你想的話可以住在這里 You, uh... you could stay here... if you want.
你這聲音聽著連逢場作戲都不像 Wow. You couldn't even try to make that sound like you meant it.
不過算你走運 Well, lucky for you,
我的休假令上面要求我要和爸媽一起居住 it's in my furlough paperwork that I have to stay with my parents.
如果你們想的話  我可以在車里等你們 You know, I can wait in the car if you guys would like...
不  你想要什么  萊瑞 No. What do you want, Larry?
我不知道 I don't know.
好吧  瞧見了吧 Okay, see, that's exactly
我就不想把未來兩天浪費在這上 how I do not wanna spend these next two days.
如果我不能陪著奶奶 If I can't be with Grandmother,
我至少要為了她好好享受這次旅行 I'm going to at least enjoy this trip for her.
你知道我們要去做什么嗎 You know what we're gonna do?
斑點豬餐廳  好嗎 The Spotted Pig. Right?
漢堡和黑麥曼哈頓 Burgers and rye Manhattans.
這就是我們要做的事  誰和我一起 That's what we're gonna do. Who's with me?
你不是不應該喝酒嗎 Aren't you not supposed to drink?
萊瑞·亞伯拉罕·布魯姆   Larry Abraham Bloom,
接下來48小時我是自由身 I am free for the next 48 hours.
別像個娘們似的毀了它 Do not ruin this by being a pussy.
求你了 Please.
我能吃東西 I could eat.
瞧見了嗎  很好  卡爾你呢 See? Great. Cal?
不錯  聽起來很好  我喜歡你的想法 Yeah, you know, this sounds great. I like where your head's at.
很高興知道你的內心仍然 It's great to know that you're still
是一個想違法的罪犯 a rule-breaking criminal at heart.
不過有一件事 But there's this one thing...
感謝你的到來 Thank you for coming.
-很高興見到你  -非常感謝 - Oh, good to see you, darling. - Thanks so much.
-很高興見到你  -謝謝 - Nice to see you. - Thanks.
非常感謝你的到來 Thank you so much for coming.
是的  她真的很好   She was great, yes.
不  她沒有別的孫女 No, she doesn't have another granddaughter.
真的是我  就是那個重罪犯 That's actually me. The felon.
不  我出來了  但只是暫時的 No, I am out. I'm just not out-out.
這叫做休假 It's called furlough.
是的  暫時的 It's temporary, yeah.
48小時 Forty-eight hours.
很高興他們能信任我 It... It was nice of them to trust me.
不  瞧見了嗎  沒有手銬 No, see? No handcuffs.
親愛的  你還能撐的下去嗎 How are you holding up, dear?
你覺得這還要多久 How much longer do you think this is gonna be?
不久  一個小時左右 Not long. An hour or so?
好吧  我還在想或許能 Okay, well, I was thinking that I might...
大家會在7點到房子里 Everyone's coming back to the house at 7:00,
所以我們要在那之前趕到 so we have to be there before then.
葬禮在明天中午  所以早飯要吃好 Funeral's tomorrow at noon, so eat a good breakfast.
大家看到你都很高興 Everyone's very excited to visit with you.
所以他們都像看動物園的獅子一樣盯著我看 So they can all stare at me like a lion in a zoo.
親愛的  這對大家來說都是困難的一天 Been a difficult day for everyone, dear.
你好  瑪麗  感謝你的到來 Hello, Mary. Thank you for coming.
塞萊斯特很鄙視她  她總是穿中跟鞋 Celeste despised her. She always wore kitten heels.
你知道奶奶對中跟鞋的態度 You know how Grandmother felt about them.
鞋子中的奇葩 "The boiled carrots of footwear."
你是把手指插進插座了么 Stick your fingers in a fucking socket?
你頭發是怎么回事 What's wrong with your hair?
老天啊  囚犯  你有什么毛病 Jesus Christ. What's wrong with you, inmate?
你是在冥想嗎   You meditating?
快去拿點食物  吃點肉長點身子 Get some food. Put some meat on your bones, shit.
我不吃東西 I'm not eating.
我看的見  用我常人的眼睛就能看見   I can see that, by my normal-people eyes.
你眼睛那么小很難看清吧 Bet those slits make it hard for you to see, huh?
我會向管理部門投訴你的 I will report you to the administration.
女士們  囚犯蘇蘇 Ladies! Inmate... "Soso"?
soso也有馬馬虎虎之意
你搞笑呢吧 You're shittin' me, right?
囚犯蘇蘇看來違反了監獄的基本規定 Inmate Soso here seems to be violating essential prison regulations
并且拒不服從指令  對不對 with her insubordinate attitude, does she not?
接招吧  打小報告的 Take that, you tattletale.
我正在發動絕食抗議 I am staging a hunger strike
抗議這個監獄里糟糕的條件 in protest of the reprehensible conditions in this facility!
我邀請大家參與進來  來擁護 I invite you all to join in, in standing up...
212號  參加或慫恿進行團體示威 Oh, 212! Engaging in or encouraging a group demonstration!
蘇蘇  我們去談談你的加班工作吧 Let's go talk about a little extra work duty, shall we, Soso?
大家...請小聲點 Just... keep it down, please.
不敢相信你居然把時間浪費在生菜上 Can't believe you're wasting your time on lettuce.
你知道我多久沒吃過 Do you know how long it's been since...
能咬的嘎?響的蔬菜了嗎 I had a vegetable that actually crunched?
喝慢點  餓鬼 Whoa, easy there, Tiger.
真是太美味了 Mmm. But it's so delicious.
你在干什么 What are you doing?
我想念你 Mmm. I missed you.
我也想你  帕波 I missed you, too, Pipes.
你想 You wanna...
不  我不知道 No, I don't... I don't know, I...
得了吧  萊瑞 Oh, come on, Larry.
你上一次射在真正的陰道里 How long has it been since you came in a real live vagina
而不是自己手上  已經有多久了   and not in your hand? Huh?
-好吧  -來吧  我們上樓 - Okay. - Come on, let's go upstairs.
不  我要去下衛生間 No, I need to... I'm gonna use the bathroom.
我想你不應該喝酒  親愛的 I don't think you're supposed to be drinking, honey.
你知道"應該"是什么意思嗎   What's "Supposed to," Anyway, you know?
是誰定的這些規矩 Who makes those rules?
我相信你這個情況下   I believe it's the Federal
規矩是聯邦懲教局定的 Department of Corrections in this case.
去他們的 Fuck 'em.
任何人都不愿看你因為在休假期間 The last thing anyone needs is you getting your sentence extended
違反一些愚蠢的規定而使刑期延長 for some silly furlough violation.
真的嗎  爸爸 Really, Dad?
是其他人不愿看到 Is that the last thing that anyone needs,
還是你自己不愿看到 or is that the last thing that you need,
因為你拒絕去監獄探訪自己唯一的女兒 because you refuse to come visit your only daughter in prison
你不希望因為這事讓自己的良心 and you'd rather not have that weighing on your conscience
受到更多譴責  是嗎 for any longer than it has to?
帕波  我們現在能別說這些嗎   Piper, can we not do this now, please?
我母親過世了 My mother has died.
好吧  對不起 Fine. Sorry.
塞萊斯特非常以你為傲 Celeste was so proud of you.
從你出生的那刻起 From the moment you were born.
現在很難想象這是真的 It's hard to imagine that's true anymore.
真的  我甚至覺得因為我生了你  她更喜歡我了 It was. I even think she liked me more for having fathered you.
親愛的  對不起   I'm sorry, honey.
我只是不能看到你那個樣子 I just can't see you like that.
哪個樣子 Like what?
你是我的寶貝女兒 You're my little girl.
監獄里的那個女人  不是真正的你 That woman in there, that's not who you are.
那就是我自己 That's exactly who I am.
萊瑞 Larry?
我在里面 I'm in here, hello?
停停  帕波 Hey, hey, hey! Pipes...
好了  帕波  別在這兒 Okay. Piper, not here. What if...
天吶  帕波  你確定嗎 Piper. Jesus, Piper. Oh, God, are you sure about this?
門鎖了嗎  門有沒有鎖上 Is the door locked? Is the door locked? Is the door locked?
該死  我的天 Shit. Oh, my God.
干我 Fuck me.
好吧  把你腿抬高 Okay. Okay, just move your leg over.
好  像這樣嗎 Okay. Like that?
-你好了嗎  -是的 - Are you okay? - Yeah.
好 Okay.
-該死  -怎么了 - Shit. - What? Oh.
-該死  -沒關系  我來幫你 - Fuck. - It's okay. Let me help.
抱歉  我一直想著你爸突然闖進來 I'm sorry. I can't stop thinking about your dad walking in.
別  別  天吶  帕波  你不用 No! No! Oh, Jesus, Piper, you don't have to...
該死  拜托  這太奇怪了   Oh, fuck. Come on, this is weird.
我們還在服喪 We're mourning. We're...
我們那么久沒做了  我們甚至不在一起 Ah... We haven't done this in so long. We're not even together.
萊瑞  閉嘴 Larry. Shut up.
該死  我睡了別人 Fuck, I slept with someone.
-真的嗎  -對不起 - Really? - I'm sorry.
你在我幫你的軟雞巴口時決定跟我說這個 You decide to tell me that with your flaccid dick in my mouth?
噓  半硬了 Ssh! It was a semi.
現在別在我面前維護你的雞雞 Do not defend your boner to me right now.
抱歉  我知道這件事 I'm sorry. I know this is...
你很難接受 tough for you.
你有沒有什么想問我的或者 Is there anything you wanna ask me or...
不  上帝  我沒有   No. God, no.
可能吧  是我認識的人嗎 Maybe. Is it someone that I know?
是的 Yes.
夠了  別的我不想知道 That's it. I don't wanna know anything else.
求你別跟我說其他的 Please don't tell me anything else.
沒錯  能在腦子里回想的感覺更糟 Yeah, well, it's much worse when you can imagine it in your own head.
相信我 Trust me.
這下真的結束了  對嗎 This is really over, isn't it?
我也不想變成這樣 I don't... I don't want it to be.
是的  你想 Yes, you do.
但真的說出來  感覺很糟糕 But it feels so shitty actually saying it.
我知道 I know.
該死  我會想你的 Fuck, I'm gonna miss you.
我愛你 I love you.
我也愛你 I love you, too.
你明天不用來我奶奶的葬禮 You don't have to come to my grandmother's funeral tomorrow.
謝天謝地 Oh, thank God.
是啊 Yeah.
你起早干活又不會有小紅花拿 You ain't gonna get a gold star for showin' up early.
那個警衛  真是個非常可怕的男人 That guard, that awful, awful man.
哪一個 Which one?
新來的那個警衛   That new guard.
壞版的伯特·雷諾茲  但更流氓 D-list Burt Reynolds but more rapey.
伯特·雷諾茲  著名演員   曾獲金球獎最佳男配角獎
黃胡 Pornstache.
沒錯  他讓我加班干活 Yeah. He gave me extra work duty.
他因為我有信念而懲罰我 He's punishing me for believing in something.
這里的人們可不喜歡信仰   Well, people don't like conviction around here. Okay?
這是不行的  先生 No, sir.
我會給他們好好瞧瞧的 Well, I'm gonna show them.
很快就沒人會吃東西了  他們會看到的 Soon, no one will be eating, and then they'll see.
我們為什么不吃東西 Why ain't we eating?
為了抗議這里的條件 In protest of the conditions in here.
那真是太傻逼了 Well, that's just super stupid.
真弱智  又下賤又殘忍又傻逼 And dumb. And mean and cruel and stupid.
沒錯  我說了傻逼兩次 And, yeah, I said "Stupid" Twice,
就是為了強調這事有多傻逼 only to emphasize how stupid that is.
別去說花木蘭了 Hey, leave Mulan alone.
其實我叫布魯克  布魯克·蘇蘇 It's Brook, actually. Soso.
你知道嗎  你是對的  蘇蘇 You know what? You're right, Soso.
看看這地方  雖然我們是罪犯 You know, look around this place. We're criminals,
但那并不意味著我們 but that don't mean we don't
不應該受到正常人一樣的待遇 deserve to be treated like normal people.
一點也沒錯 Exactly.
你什么時候開始關心監獄條件了  琳恩 Since when do you care about the conditions, Leanne?
一直以來都關心 Since always.
沒人喜歡像動物一樣活著 Nobody likes to live like an animal.
那么你想加入我嗎 So, you wanna join me?
這取決于今天的午餐供應什么 It depends on what they're serving for lunch today,
但我會考慮的 but I'll think on it.
好的  如果你想知道的話 Okay. You know, I could tell you more about
我可以多跟你講講以前的有效監獄絕食 the efficacy of prison hunger strikes historically, if you want.
那聽起來真的很有趣 That sounds real interesting.
太棒了  星際寶貝 Great. Lilo and Stitch
星際寶貝  迪斯尼公司動畫片
想讓自己挨餓來拯救世界  真的是 starving themselves to save the world. This is...
她是莉蘿  對吧 She's Lilo, isn't she?
莉蘿  星際寶貝中的女主角
那你在說我是史迪奇了   So, you're saying that I'm Stitch,
史迪奇  星際寶貝中的怪獸主角
你這個沒有朋友的怪物 you friendless freak?
沒人喜歡你 No one likes you.
你們迷路了嗎  我們早飯還沒做好呢 Aw, are you guys lost? We ain't ready for breakfast yet.
但今天我們有奶油麥片粥  適合老人家的 But today, we have cream of wheat. Yay. Old-people food.
你媽媽沒有教你要尊老嗎 Didn't your mother teach you manners?
你們這些老家伙為什么脾氣總那么暴躁 Why you old people always gotta be so cranky all the time?
就是  你們是來教我們狗屁德育課的嗎 Yeah, you here to teach us a morality lesson and shit?
我們是來拿走屬于紅媽的東西 We're here to collect what belongs to Red.
我們什么也不知道 Well, we don't know nothing about that, so...
你真可愛啊 Aren't you cute?
你是不是被卷入了你男友的毒品交易 Did you get caught up in your boyfriend's drug game?
你想知道我犯了什么事嗎 You wanna know what I did?
我用切肉刀割了我老公的雞巴 Cut my husband's dick off with a butcher knife,
用的那把刀甚至都不鋒利 and it wasn't even sharp.
我仍然能夠夢到那個畫面 I still dream about it,
好多血  血滴到我拳頭上的樣子 all the blood, the way it flopped around in my fist.
那可是我的人生杰作 Hmm. Best thing I ever did.
年紀大了被人低估真是太讓人失望了 It's so disappointing being underestimated as you age.
我不知道發生了什么事   I don't know what happened.
沒人會告訴新來的人 Nobody tells the new girl.
前一天她還在掌管一切  當著老大 One day, she was running things, large and in charge.
后一天就消失不見了  再見朗達 And the next, poof, gone. So long, Rhonda.
她身上肯定出了什么大事 Something major must've happened for her
才被關押到重刑監獄  對吧 to be sent down to max, no?
是啊  誰知道這里的規矩是怎么樣的 Yeah, well, who knows how stuff works around here?
你聽說昨晚安妮塔心臟病發作的事了嗎 You hear Anita had a heart attack last night?
和我們住一起的那個意大利人嗎 The guido who rooms with us?
可能她動脈里的肉醬太多了 Probably too much ragu in her arteries.
說到這事 Speaking of...
把你手放進去 Put your hand in.
天吶  那太不衛生了 Oh, God. That's unsanitary.
只管做就是了 Just do it.
拉出來 Pull.
我勒個去 Holy shit.
對白人女孩來說還算不錯吧 Not too bad for a white girl, hmm?
真的很不錯  你已經開始賣了嗎 Not too bad at all. You selling already?
一點點  四處賣賣  試試深淺 A little. Here and there. Testing the waters.
我可不想沖昏頭腦辦壞事 I don't wanna get in over my head.
幾個月之后你就會成為這里的老大了 Shit, you gonna be running things around here in a few months.
到時候見分曉  我要穩扎穩打 We'll see. Slow and steady.
但我謝謝你的建議 But I do thank you for your advice.
維  抱歉打擾你 Hey, Vee, I'm sorry to bother you,
那個沒眉毛的女人 but the one without the eyebrows,
她沒拿到錢 she ain't got her money.
根據你的吩咐  我想你是要親自處理 Figured you'd wanna deal yourself like you told us.
我馬上去 I'll be right there.
我得走了  我們等一會兒再聊 I better get going. We can talk more later.
我真是大開眼界  紅媽 I'm impressed, Red.
紅媽幫我對付了門德斯  Red helped me with Mendez.
整個監獄都知道了嗎 Does the entire prison know?
沒別人了  寶貝  我保證  你要放松 That's it. I promise. Babe, you need to relax.
他回來了你怎么還能假裝一切都很好 How can you act like everything is fine when he's back here?
他會毀掉我們的生活   He could ruin our lives.
他會毀了我的生活 He could... He could ruin my life.
一切都會好的  紅媽在我們這邊 Everything's gonna be fine. Red's on our side.
門德斯甚至都沒試著跟我談話 And Mendez doesn't even try to talk to me.
很好  我肯定他們會 Good, I mean, I'm sure they probably...
我肯定他們會告訴他盡可能遠離你 I'm sure they probably told him to stay as far away as possible.
只是感到有一點奇怪 Just feels a little weird since,
畢竟他喜歡我  you know, he's in love with me or whatever.
至少也該試著跟我打個招呼 You would think that he'd try to say hi.
好了  我 Okay, you know, I...
我要去告訴卡普托  門德斯是孩子的爸爸 I'm gonna tell Caputo that Mendez is the father.
但你那是撒謊 But that's a lie.
他沒有和你做過愛嗎 But didn't he have sex with you?
-做過  -好了  那他就是罪犯 - Yeah. - Okay, so he's a criminal,
他應該被關進監獄 he deserves to go to prison.
但你也和我做過  不管怎么說以前做過 But you have sex with me. Used to, anyways.
那不一樣  我是愛你的 That's different. I... I love you.
他也一樣 So does he.
你現在是在為他辯護嗎 Are you actually defending him right now?
我只是無法相信 I just can't believe that
你要把一個無罪之人送進監獄 you would send an innocent man to prison.
抱歉  你在說什么  整個 I'm sorry, what? The whole...
整個計劃就是把他送進監獄 The whole plan was to send him to prison.
所以你才會和他做愛  難道不是嗎 I mean, that's why you fucked him in the first place, was it not?
只不過這事沒成功 It's just... It just didn't work.
我不知道我在做什么  她們把我說服了 I don't know what I was doing. They talked me into it.
你知道我媽有時多嚇人 You know how scary my mom can be.
但我花了點時間來反省  他是無辜的 But I've had time to reflect, and he's innocent.
拜托  達婭 Oh, come on, Daya, you know
你知道他應該被關進監獄 he deserves to go to prison for something.
生活就是這樣的 This is... This is just how life works.
我需要時間考慮 Well, I need time to think.
在沒和我商量過之前  你不許做別的事 Don't you go doing nothing without talking to me.
聽到了嗎 You hear me?
你是要我打完飛機還是怎么樣 Now, you want me to finish or what?
好的 Yes.
求你了  特別紅燈 Red light special, please.
你們這些人就像"不要吸毒"的三維廣告 Man, you people are like a 3D "Don't do drugs" Ad.
暗號不對嗎 Ain't that the code?
該死  你要那么多嗎 Damn, you want that many?
它不是就是這個價錢嗎 Isn't that what it costs?
你在說什么 What are you talkin' about?
那東西 The stuff.
你可以說香煙這個詞 You can say, "Cigarette."
什么  不是  我要特別的東西 What? No. The special stuff.
我知道黑妞們在賣 I know the black girls are selling it.
你是說我們看起來都一樣嗎 You saying we all look alike?
拜托  我的整張臉都很痛    Come on, my face is all achy.
我想暫時失去知覺 I need to not feel it for a while.
那就去小賣部買點阿司匹林  滾出去 Then go buy some aspirin from commissary. Get out of here.
這些我就留下了  因為你浪費了我的時間 And I'm keeping these for my time.
快走 Go.
有一個圣誕節  我第一次被允許 This one Christmas, I was allowed to help Grandmother
幫奶奶制作她非常著名的糖果曲奇 make her really famous sugar cookies for the very first time.
我想你們大多數這些年來 I think most of you have probably
都收到過她做的一罐餅干 received a tin of her cookies over the years.
如果沒收到  說明奶奶不喜歡你們 If you didn't, Grandmother didn't like you.
我只是隨便說說 I'm just sayin'.
不管怎樣  5分鐘不到我就陷入了麻煩 Anyway, it took less than five minutes for me to mess up,
我在生面團里倒了太多小蘇打 and I poured too much baking soda into the dough
我馬上哭了起來 and I immediately started crying.
我以為我徹底毀了圣誕節 I thought I had completely ruined Christmas.
但奶奶并沒有吼我 But instead of yelling at me,
她告訴我一切都會沒事的 Grandmother told me that they were gonna be fine,
她當時說的更好聽 and she said better, even. And then...
她對我說  帕波  生活就是由錯誤組成的 And then she said to me, "Piper, life is made in the mistakes."
現在回想起來  她肯定在我走后重新做了 In retrospect, I'm sure she remade them after I left, you know?
抱歉 I'm sorry.
沒事的  沒事的 It's okay. It's okay.
這女人叫塞萊斯特  是吧 I mean, the woman's name was Celeste, for God's sake.
抱歉  抱歉  神父 Uh, sorry. Sorry. Sorry, Father.
我不知道在場的各位 Um, I don't know if any of you
是否聽過這些東西的演奏 have ever heard one of those things played before.
我是說鋼片琴 A celeste, I mean,
celeste亦有鋼片琴之意
但那有種神奇而飄渺的感覺 but it is this magical, ethereal experience.
所有這些鋼板發出的聲響聽起來就像 All these steel plates that ting and sound like,
我說不清楚  就像 I don't know, like,
就像是大海突然開始奏樂 if an ocean were to suddenly make music.
其實那并不太像奶奶 Um... That's... That's not really like Grandmother,
但她非常特別 but she was, she was special.
即使你知道自己只是茫茫人海之中 She... She made you feel like
毫不起眼的小人物 there was something important about you
她也會讓你感到 even when you knew you were nothing
自己擁有不平凡之處 but a polyp in the sea of human mundanity.
說了很多關于大海的比喻 Lot of ocean imagery here.
但聽著  重點是奶奶是個了不起的女人 But look, the point is that Grandmother was a wonderful woman.
那是我要說的重點 That's the point I'm trying to make.
她應該得到紀念 And she should be celebrated.
我的妹妹帕波在這里  真的非常不可思議 And my sister, Piper, is here, and that is truly incredible
因為嚴格地說她受到聯邦政府的監護 because she is technically a ward of the federal government.
或是剛從非洲回來的  凱西阿姨 Or... just returned from Africa, Aunt Kathy.
不管怎樣  今天是感恩生命的一天 Um... Either way, today is a day to celebrate life.
今天是值得慶祝的一天 Today is a day to celebrate today.
所以 And that is why...
我想不出更合適的時間來做這事 that is why I can't think of a better time to do this.
來吧  來吧  我可愛的灰樹花 Come on. Come on, my little hen of the woods.
朋友們  家人們 Friends, family...
-快做些什么  -戀人們 - Do something. - ... lovers,
我記不住名字的年長親戚們 older family friends that I can never remember the names of,
內莉和我準備結婚 Neri and I are getting married...
就在此刻 right now...
在座的各位都將成為我們的見證人 with all of you as our witnesses.
我們的朋友都來了  帕波也休假了 Our friends are here, Piper's on furlough,
我們的好友山姆  上周為我們受戒 our buddy, Sam, got ordained last week just for us.
謝謝你  山姆 Thank you, Sam.
內莉的家人也來了 Neri's family is here.
后面的帕姆和喬 Pam and Joe in the back.
伙計們  你們太可愛了  真棒 Hi, guys. You're so cute. You are awesome.
感謝你們的到來  愛你們 Thank you for coming. Love you. And...
我相信塞萊斯特 I think that Celeste...
會對我們免費蹭花和食物感到開心的 would be pleased with our judicious use of the free flowers and food,
或許會有一點點不滿 if not a tiny bit judgmental.
我覺得她會稱贊我們的精神  對吧 And I think that she would admire our spirit, right?
帕波 Pipes.
我們去大快朵頤吧 We're gonna eat the world.
抱歉了  老媽 Sorry, Mom.
你在干什么啊 Yo, what the hell are you doin'?
我要和你談談  我覺得維在販賣毒品 I need to talk to you. I think Vee's bringin' in drugs.
珀比  每天重復同樣的對話 P, ain't you bored of
你難道不覺得無聊嗎 havin' the same damn conversation every day?
反正我覺得會無聊 Shit, I know I am.
你給我聽著  好嗎  有一個冰妹 Yo, just listen, all right? One of them meth heads...
停  你何不聽話別再說三道四了 No! Why don't you listen and stop running your mouth?
誰在乎她在做什么  那是她的事 Who cares what she's doing? That's her business.
她一直對我很好 She's been real good to me,
我可不想背棄她 and I am not about to turn away from that.
維是我的家人 Vee is my family.
我以為我才是你的家人 Thought I was your family.
你倆都是我的家人 You both are my family, yo, like...
如果我們倆 What if we was...
如果我們倆同時掉進海里 What if we was drownin' in the middle of the ocean,
你只能救我們之中的一個 and you could only save one of us?
為什么我不能把你們都救了 Why can't I save both of you?
我不知道  因為你不能 I don't know. Because you can't.
因為船上沒有足夠位置 'Cause there's not enough room in the boat.
難道是全世界最小的船嗎 It's, like, the world's tiniest boat or some shit?
沒錯  好吧  就是這樣 Yes, okay? Yes.
就像是給小孩坐的小木筏  好吧 It's like a little raft for kiddies and shit, all right?
-你能回答我的問題嗎  -聽好了  珀比 - Can you just play the game with me? - Listen up, pussy.
我愛你  但我受夠了 I love you, but I am done
我不想再翻來覆去聽你說這屁事 as a burnt burger talkin' about this shit.
別再跟我或跟別人說維的事 No more talkin' about Vee to me or to anyone.
珀比  那女人不是鬧著玩的 And, P, that woman don't play around.
別妨礙她 Don't get in her way.
也別妨礙我  聽到了嗎 Or mine. You hear?
聽到了 Yeah.
怎么了  德蓋特 What happened, Doggett?
你知道我有時候會發瘋 You know I get mad sometimes.
我知道我一直是個惡霸  我知道 I know I've been a bully. I know.
但是我真的很想重新開始 But I was really trying to turn a new leaf.
求你了 Please...
別送我去關禁閉  求你了  海利先生 Please don't send me down to SHU, Mr. Healy, please.
那里真的很可怕 It is truly awful down there.
德蓋特  你是不是總是容易生氣 Doggett, have you always been quick to anger?
你是什么意思 What you mean?
是不是憤怒的那個你就在外表之下 I mean, does it sit right below the surface?
在不經意間就突然爆發連自己都會大吃一驚 Does it bubble up and surprise you when you're not expecting it?
你這里是不是像打鼓一樣 Do you have a pounding right here?
感覺就像血管要爆裂一樣 Like, feels like a vein's gonna explode?
是的 Yeah.
你是靈媒嗎 Are you a psychic or something?
不是 No.
那你怎么此刻像在我腦袋里一樣 How are you in my head, then, right now?
因為我自己也暴躁易怒 Because I've had anger issues of my own...
我發現換個角度看問題 and what I've found is that a change of perspective
能讓一切變得不同 can make all the difference.
你的意思是不是向左看而不是向右看 Do you mean, like, looking left rather than right kind of thing?
正是這樣 Exactly like that.
我不把你送去關禁閉 Instead of me sending you down to SHU,
我要你每周來見我一次 I want you to come and visit me once a week.
我們做什么 What would we do?
說話 Talk.
我們要談什么 What will we talk about?
我可以為你的一些問題提供建議 I could counsel you through some of these issues.
好的  謝謝 Yes, thank you. Yes.
你真的是太好了  海利先生 That's so awfully nice of you, Mr. Healy.
我是個好人  那是事實 I'm a nice guy. That's the truth.
或許她們遲到了 Maybe they're runnin' late.
這里是監獄  她們現在不會迷路的 Nah, it's a prison. They didn't get lost in the moment.
愛拿什么拿什么 take whatever.
不是  我是說為什么你老為難我 No, I mean, Jesus, why you fucking breaking my balls?
伙計  說服她們可要 Man, this took way more convincing than
比兩盒燕麥餡餅的價錢高得多 two boxes of oatmeal pies are worth.
請坐  我想我們可以享受一頓家庭聚餐 Please, sit. I thought we could enjoy a family meal together.
是你做的嗎 You made this?
你沒有廚房還怎么做這些東西 How the fuck you do this without a kitchen?
我是個優秀的即興廚師 I'm a good improviser.
況且我還有這些女惡霸的幫助 And I had some help from the baddest bitches around.
聞起來棒極了  紅媽 It smells wonderful, Red.
并不代表好吃 Doesn't mean it tastes good.
爸爸今晚要爛醉如泥了 Ooh! Daddy's getting blotto tonight, huh?
感謝你能來  我知道你不一定要來的 Thank you for coming. I know you didn't have to.
紅媽  你得讓我們知道你的秘訣 Hey, Red. Got to let us in on the secret.
這太瘋狂了 I mean, this shit is crazy.
你們是我的家人 You're my family.
在座的各位對我來說都很重要 All of you are very important to me.
過去幾個月以來 And I... let a lot of things
我讓很多事情影響了我們之間的關系 get in the way of that these past few months.
我真的 I truly...
老家伙們  給我來點那個吃的好嗎 Golden oldies. How about I get some of that slop down here, huh?
說真的  給我上菜吧 Seriously. Food me.
我正在給大家講話呢 I'm trying to have a moment.
閉嘴吃你的東西吧 Now shut up and eat.
謝謝 Thank you.
正如我所說的 As I was saying,
我意識到我從未說這句最重要的話 I realize I never said the most important thing...
我很抱歉 I'm sorry.
紅媽  我們沒有你也也過得還好 You know, Red, we've done okay without you.
我知道  但我希望你過得更好 I know you have, but I want you to do better than okay.
沒錯  但或許我們并不懷念某些部分 Yeah, but maybe there are some parts that we didn't miss so much.
比如受你擺布 Like being pushed around.
或是被燒傷 Or burned.
吉納  我不知道是否能用言語表達 Gina, I don't know that I'll ever have the words
我對你的遭遇有多么后悔 to express the regret I feel for what happened to you.
我犯了錯 I made a mistake.
我希望你接受我的道歉 I hope you accept my apology.
好的 Okay.
我愿意讓我們之間變得更加民主 I'm willing to make this more of a democracy,
如果這是大家所希望的 if that's what you all want.
我只是希望我的家人能回到我的身邊 I just want my family back.
過來抱抱  紅媽 Oh, get over here, Red.
諾爾瑪  我親愛的諾爾瑪 Norma. My dear Norma,
這么多年來你一直在我身邊 you've been by my side for many years.
你站在我身邊  聽我的指揮 You stood beside me, listened to me,
幫我拔去肩膀后面奇怪胎記上的胎毛 plucked the hair out of that weird mole on the back of my arm.
你是我最好的朋友  我很想你 You're my best friend, and I miss you so much.
謝謝你能再給我一次機會 Thank you for giving me another chance.
那我呢 What about me?
你沒有什么特別的話要跟我說嗎 Don't you have a special dedication for me?
大波  謝謝你一直讓我看著不順眼 Boo, thank you, for always being a pain in my ass.
從現在開始  讓我們團結一致 Let's stick together from now on, huh?
你想要什么 What do you want?
聽說你在這里 Hear you have a pretty good system
搞了個不錯的小生意 worked out for yourself in here.
諾爾瑪  給這位好女士拿張表格 Norma... get the nice young woman a form.
寫下你要的東西  我會盡力的 Write down what you want, and I'll do my best.
雖然我們最近訂單有點超負荷 We're a little overwhelmed with orders lately, though.
我不是來這下訂單的  我是來買你公司的 I ain't here to place no orders. Here to buy the company.
抱歉  概不出售 It's not for sale, sorry.
你都不想聽下報價嗎 You don't even wanna hear the offer?
你可以試試看 Try me.
你可以住在最低安全級別的舒適區域內 You get to stay in cozy minimum security.
并且我們也不會打斷你的肋骨 Oh, and we don't break your ribs.
親愛的  你選擇挑起了 You, my dear, have chosen
一場無法贏得的戰爭 the one fight in here that can't be won.
跑去告訴你老媽 Go run to your mommy,
跟她說紅媽要跟她談談 tell her Red needs to talk to her,
然后我們大人們自然會討論的 then the adults will discuss this.
你知道那是個極其愚蠢的決定  對吧 You know that's a real stupid move, right?
我很高興幫你邀請她來 I mean, I'm happy to go get her for you.
反正今天已經有夠無聊了 Today has been kind of boring, anyhow.
去吧  去吧  快去 Go. Go, go, go.
不好意思  或許我真的是個白癡 I'm sorry. Maybe I'm just an idiot.
因為我想了很久也沒想明白 'Cause I'm having a hard motherfucking time understanding
三個老女人是怎么來這里偷了我們的東西 how three little old ladies come in here and stole from us.
她們真的很嚇人 They was really scary.
就是  她們其中有個人看著像迪斯尼的女巫 Yeah, and one of 'em looked like a Disney witch.
你知道嗎  快從我面前滾蛋 You know what? Go! Get... Get out of my face.
紅媽向你表示道歉 Red sends her apologies.
我討厭這個廚房 I hate this kitchen.
這他媽是什么 What the fuck is this? Huh?
這是什么 What is this?
你以為自己能在這里偷偷抽這東西嗎 You think you can just get away with this shit in here?
你以為我會視而不見嗎   You think I'm gonna turn a blind eye?
以為我是個娘們嗎 Think I'm a pussy?
是時候要像以前一樣搜查了  女士們 It's time for a good old-fashioned search, ladies.
這是什么 Oh, what is this?
非法違禁品嗎 Illegal contraband?
囚犯  你那么安靜  現在沒話說了嗎 You're awfully quiet, inmate. Got nothing to say now?
你害怕了嗎  你他媽就應該害怕 You scared? 'Cause you fucking should be!
這里歸我管理  我是老大 I'm in control! I'm in charge!
-我操  -停停停  伙計 - Fuckin'... - Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Buddy!
我們要整死你們  把你們全部整死 We are gonna fucking crack down on you! On all of you!
你會害自己被炒的  伙計 Hey! You're gonna get yourself fired, pal.
沒事了  行了 It's okay. Come on.
你還好嗎  來吧  我們走 You all right? Come on. Let's get you out of here.
女士們  都沒事了   Everything's okay, ladies.
把這里整理干凈  好吧 Just clean this shit up, all right?
抱歉打擾你們了  走吧 Sorry for the fuss. Come on.
你沒事了  伙計  走吧 You're all right, buddy. Come on.
現在女士們先生們   And now, ladies and gentlemen,
新娘和新郎第一次閃亮登場 for the very first time, the bride and the groom.
真的很高興你能來  帕波 It's so wonderful that you could be here, Piper.
你還好嗎 How are you doing?
挺好  我很好 Fine. I'm fine.
如果朱莉像你這個樣子的話 We would be so heartbroken for our Julie
我們會很傷心的 if she were in your position.
你知道嗎  我們剛還在說 You know what, we were just talking earlier
你曾經是個多么棒的孩子 about what a wonderful kid you were.
總是在報紙上看到你  一直很成功 Always in the newspaper for something and always achieving.
親愛的  我們只想告訴你   We just want you to know, dear,
我們覺得你還是原來那個你 we still see you as that person.
我相信你很渴望做回自己 I'm sure you're anxious to return to your old self.
事實上  我不渴望 I'm not, actually.
出租
好了 Well, now.
我等的黑美人終于來了 There's the black beauty I've been waitin' for.
我能幫你嗎 Can I help you?
妹子  我覺得應該反過來說才是 I think that's the other way around, sistah.
老天啊  難道我在這里 Jesus. Can't even brush your teeth around here
都不能安安靜靜刷個牙嗎 without getting into something.
你到底要干什么 What do you want, man?
找到另一個走私路子對你而言值多少 How much would it be worth to you to find another route in?
取決于這個路子到哪的 Depends on where the route goes.
你懂得  除非我知道能得到什么 Oh, now, you know I can't give you information
否則我不能把信息告訴你 unless I know what I'm getting for it.
我應該對這個有興趣嗎 And I'm supposed to be interested in that?
我知道紅媽是怎么把違禁品運進來的 I know how Red's importing contraband.
有興趣嗎 Interested in that?
而且我還知道警衛們快發現你們了 'Cause I also know that the guards are hot on your trail.
所以你需要一個新的掩護  對吧 So you're gonna need a new cover, right?
我要煙草收益的2成 I want 20% of tobacco intake.
你真是個自以為是的拉拉  不是嗎 You are a smug little dyke, aren't you?
不不不  我是又壯又聰明的拉拉 Oh, no, no, no, no, no. I am a big, smart dyke.
是的  夫人 Yes, ma'am.
1成 10%.
成交 Got yourself a deal.
你是不是把你的野狗栓回去了 Did you get your pack of wild dogs under control?
她們一直很聽話 They're always obedient.
那就好  我不想在這里再見到她們 Good. Then I'll look forward to never seeing them in here again.
紅媽  你以為是誰下的命令   Who do you think gave the order, Red?
你是我的朋友 You're my friend.
我不記得我們有交換過友誼手鏈 I don't remember us exchanging woven bracelets.
你不能奪走我的生意  這是我創立的 You're not taking over my business. I started it.
拜托  難道我們不能分享嗎 Come on. Can't we share?
當初難道不是我給你出的主意嗎 Didn't I give you the idea in the first place?
現在一下子就成了你的了嗎 Now all of a sudden, it's yours?
你對朗達做了什么 What did you do to Rhonda?
以后就這樣好了 Here's what's gonna happen.
你繼續接受訂單并出貨 You're gonna keep taking orders and filling them.
我的人負責配送和收錢 My girls will be distributing the goods and collecting the payments.
我會告訴海利的 I'll tell Healy.
紅媽 Oh, Red.
你那么做的話 You do that,
我會保證你的下場就和朗達一樣 and I will make sure that you end up exactly like Rhonda.
你休想把我的生意奪走 You are not taking this from me.
你犯的第一個錯誤就是沒有后援 Your first mistake is not having backup.
動手 Go ahead.
我有個禮物要給你 Hey, I got a gift for you.
亂說  我生日都沒到 Shit, it's not even my birthday.
第一次免費  如果還要的話就跟我說 First one's free. Let me know if you want more.
當我說證明給我看的時候   When I said prove it,
我意思是像泰勒教練那樣 I meant it in a Coach Taylor kind of way.
泰勒教練  《勝利之光》中的經典角色
而不是恐嚇囚犯  讓自己停職 Not a "Terrify all the inmates, get yourself suspended" Way.
抱歉  先生  我也不知道自己是怎么了 Sorry, sir. I don't know what... I don't know what got into me.
本尼特  現在麻煩事夠多了 I don't have time for any more headaches
我沒時間再處理更多的頭痛事了 on top of everything else right now, Bennett.
我知道  只是記過配額指標 I understand. I'm just... just under a lot of stress
以及一些私事  讓我感到很有壓力 with the shot quota and some, uh... some personal stuff.
好吧  你的私事 Yes, and your personal crap
應該和你的小玩具一起放在家里 belongs at home next to your tchotchkes.
但問題就在這兒  先生 Well, that's the thing, sir,
我并不能把那件事放在家中 I... can't exactly leave this stuff at home.
你想跟我說什么 What are you trying to tell me?
迪亞茨懷孕了  達婭娜 Diaz is pregnant. Dayanara.
什么 What?
肯定是門德斯的 Must've been Mendez.