Why are there so many people died today?
(Luk: The 8319th night)
Luk, dinner is ready
Coming
Hurry
AImost done
Give me a minute
One minute
Hello?
Yes
Yes¡­ Speaking¡­
Tomorrow afternoon?
Yes, okay¡­ no problem¡­
Yes, I got it¡­
Then I'll bring all my works  to your comic books company
May I have your address please?
Yes, IFC. (International Finance Centre)
Yes, I got it¡­
IFC in Kwun Tong?
Okay¡­
Room 1804 to Room 1808
Yes, use the door at 1806, okay
I totally got it¡­
Thanks¡­
(Dinner is ready.)
(Give me a minute.)
Julia
Shit!
Damn!
I've a problem
Hi, Julia?
Well, there's only one set of  lingerie left in the dresser
Wonder if there's a sex maniac
broke in last night and stole them¡­
except for this set?
Fortunately, this is the set I like most
No way, Julia doesn't  like me being frivolous
Julia, could you spare me a few minutes?
I sincerely apologize to you
Yesterday I missed our big day
because today is so important to me
Today will bring change to my career¡­
Today will bring change to my fate
Sounds good, that's it
Hello?
Ju¡­ Julia
Sorry
I'm moving, I'll call you once settled
You better get ready  to go to the publisher
How do you know that?
I overheard a little and I guessed so
You stilI have stomach gas
You better eat before you go
Stomach gas goes up, you burp
Stomach gas goes down, you fart.  Both are not nice
The reception here is bad.  I'll call you later, bye
Spongy Chicken
One please¡­
Okay, just a sec
Be careful¡­ it's hot
Thanks
Hey, that's mine!       Sorry
That one is mine.       Okay¡­ thanks
The spongy chicken is good.       Yes
Waiter, one please
Okay¡­ be careful, it's really hot
Bill please
Thanks
The fish maw is delicious
You've been fooling around
putting no effort in educating yourself
Fish maws are so expensive,  how could they serve them here?
That's just pig's skin
Pig's skin?
I order Spongy Chicken for the ham
Ham?
Then why don't you go to a steak house  and order ham steak instead?
You've come to a tea house  to order spongy chicken
just for the ham?
Did I tell you not to eat the side dish?
I'm just telling you to eat the ham first
You stilI don't get it
The stuffing of spongy chicken  is leftovers from yesterday
The maw is just pig's skin
The ham is the most precious ingredient
Is that right, kid?       Yes¡­
You're wrong!
The best part of Spongy Chicken  is the fish maw
Maw is spongy tissue
It absorbs all the essence  and juice from chicken and ham
That's why it's called Spongy Chicken
Am I right, kid?
I agree¡­
I've told you it's not fish maw,  it's just pig's skin
Kid, do you think it's  fish maw or pig's skin?
Answer me!
In a word¡­ it's spongy tissue
Everybody's happy now
You'd better put a sponge in it
to absorb the juice¡­
then you can just eat the sponge
I don't want to carry on this  nonsense argument with you
Go eat your spongy tissue!
It's your ham, pig!
Here's your spongy tissue!
I'm warning you¡­       What?
Don't ruin my spongy tissue
Pick it up!
You ruin my ham in the first place
Eat it!
And don't shit it out!
Spongy Chicken!
Spongy Chicken! Go to hell!
Damn you, you dare break my head!
Let's share the taxi, where are you going?
My workplace, Kowloon Funeral Parlor
Think it's bad luck?
Not at all¡­ I do respect you
You serve the people and the spirits too
Kowloon Funeral Parlor, please
Hi, I'm looking for  the Chief Editor, Mr. Chan
Follow me, please
Are you Luk?       Yes
Chief Editor, Mr. Chan¡­ I presume?
Hello
Cheat Editor?
Here're all my works
We must have all these synopsises
I've the traditional Chinese version
simplified Chinese version
I've also considered the Asian markets
The Japanese version
the Korean version
and English version, too
So we can send it to Pixar  or Dreamworks in the near future
But I read really slow
No problem, I talk fast
Then you tell me the story
I'm going to tell the story.  Go ahead
This is a story¡­
with a bright and shiny beginning¡­
but with a dark and eerie ending
Go on
It's a story with a  bright and shiny beginning¡­
but with a dark and eerie ending¡­
It's a story about  the impermanence of life
That's why everybody should buy insurance
Mrs. Ho, unfortunately  your husband has passed away
But fortunately he did buy  insurance from our company
However¡­unfortunately¡­
his agent, Mr. Kwan
has also passed away last week
But fortunately, I'm the one  responsible for your case now
So you don't have to  worry about anything anymore
Mrs. Ho, the death benefit of  your husband has been issued
Mom, it's one million.       Yes
Exactly. A well-planned husband,  even though he is dead
can still show the benefits  of buying a life insurance plan
It makes a misfortunate event  less misfortunate
My husband disliked  all the insurance agents
except Mr. Kwan
Mr. Kwan has really helped us a lot
How did Mr. Kwan die?
He was crushed by a collapsed sick tree
(Sick tree collapsed, crushed a man.)
You see, life is so impermanent
But there's one thing for sure,  we'll all die eventually
Buy insurance, you'll sure win
Mr. Kwan really helped us a lot
Good men die young
Like my husband, he got no friends
Mr. Kwan was the only one  who remembered his birthday
and sent him birthday card every year
He's so sincere¡­
In fact, Mr. Kwan could have  done better than this
If he had asked your husband to buy  a plan with bigger death benefit
and make your husband's  death more worthwhile
The two of us have to rely on  each other from now on
That's the reason you have to  rely on insurance plan
Are you asking me to buy insurance?
I am asking both of you to buy insurance
In case there's anything happen to you,  your son can rely on that
Or the other way round,  you'll stilI get a cheque
Please consider the accident  and life insurance for children
When you read the news, you'll find  so many accidents invoIving kids
such as mistakenly drinking acid,  shampoo, melamine-contaminated milk¡­
Sudden death when playing videogames¡­
Losing their fingers by door¡­       Mom!
Head got stuck in portable desk¡­
Eye got pierced by pencil¡­
And¡­
strangled by windows blinds strings
You see, life is so impermanent
Look, there's a guy  dropped his $1 ,000 note
How unlucky!
That other guy is lucky
There's a bank note  waiting for him to pick up
See how he jeopardize his life just to
pick up the bank note
But the main point today is  ¡°Life is impermanent¡±
Mrs. Ho, there're always  expenses after a misfortune
Excuse me
Hello?
Sis, come over to my place for  New Year's Eve dinner tonight
Okay¡­ I am having a meeting now
Hold on¡­ just one word
Have you read the latest issue  of the ¡°Super Tabloid¡±?
I know that macho guy on the cover page
We'll talk about this later
You bought another car again?
I bought this after contemplation
There's a hole in the ozone layer
Really?
This is an environmental friendly car
Where's your old car?  I took it to a scrap yard
You took a mint condition car to scrap yard?  And you say that's environmental friendly?
Mrs. Cheung drives the same car
Which Mrs. Cheung?
The wife of Jackie Cheung  (famous HK singer)
The salesman told me so
Really?
Hello?
Didn't you get my text message?  Why didn't you reply?
I have an appointment tonight
Appointment? Where? For what? With whom?
New Year's Eve dinner is tonight,  what's more important than family reunion?
Okay¡­
Send me your sister's address
Start the dinner without me.  Don't wait with empty stomach
Bye
The car engine is quiet
I can even hear my brother-in-law's  voice from your phone
Right, I've brought you  some red packets envelopes
Gift from your insurance company?
Now you're somebody's wife
You've got to initiate  and prepare everything yourself
Don't act if you are still single  and needed to be taken care of
I think¡­ not too suitable
Why? You're not going  to give out red packet?
I'd like to use those with  my husband's last name printed on it
It's my luck to have such a good husband
I have adopted his last name.  He's a dentist
He's rich and handsome
I don't have to work at all,  feel like the luckiest woman in the world
I really have to thank God
for giving me such a rich husband
Well, give them back to me then
I want them, what makes you think I don't?
I'll use yours to pack  those under a hundred dollars
For those over a hundred
I'll use those with  my husband's last name printed on it
People will stilI know  I'm giving out big red packets
Right!
Aren't we going to your place?
This is my place, I've just moved in
Surprise!
How do you like it? Is this okay?
It's okay!
Very good indeed!
Wait, have you bought home insurance yet?
Of course I'll buy it from you
It's sisterhood
Without your support
I wouldn't have met my dentist  husband in the university
If our family can have  a big feast in such a big house
it'll be great
But Mom and Dad are too stubborn
They like to compare  my husband with yours
Honey!       Honey!
Sis!
My husband is so handsome today
Honey, I've told you to put  raw food on the lower shelf
and cooked food on the upper shelf
Will you fix it for me, please
Honey, the dinner is ready,  we can start any time
Let's wait for bro-in-law.       Sure
Comfy, honey?
Ah, harder
Yes¡­ right there
What are you guys doing?
Stop it, my elder sister is here
Right
Remember to buy home insurance  from my sister
But I just bought it from my patient
Okay¡­ I'll buy an extra one¡­
I'm too busy to take your call now
Please don't leave any message  if no reply is needed
Mom and Dad are too stubborn
They like to compare  my husband with yours
Why is your sister taking so long?
I'll check it out
Sis, are you okay?
I'm almost done
Is your sister okay?
She is a bit upset
You go and buy soy sauce,  let me talk to her
You've been taking so long,  is there anything wrong?
Honey, we run out of soy sauce
Why don't you dash off to buy some?
Order taken, my wife commander
Let me go buy it,  I need to shop something anyway
I'm telling you, watch over my sister
I only have one sister
Sis, come with me
We are sisters,  I'll let you use my favorite
Try taking it with you  walking down the street
See how many people  can't take their eyes off you
By then, you shall regain your confidence
No need. My stuff is in my own bag
Just put them over here?
I said NO!
I'll put my whole bag into yours
I'm ready to go
Take care of my sister
This one?
Excuse me.       Sorry
That girI is pretty?
This is the one that your sister uses
Not the one we just saw
I mean the one that you  had lunch with in Central District
But I won't tell my sister
She's living in her dream
Sis, you're really a good sister
You wish her to keep on dreaming, right?
Please don't let her know
I don't have a dream to live in
But I do want to sit in a luxurious  environmental friendly car
I don't have that money
You can pull more teeth from  your patients' mouths to get that money
Drive your car over there
I'll wait for you  by the garbage bin ahead
Thief¡­
Why don't you catch him?
You're nuts
Get my bag for me
I can't. I'm so scared.  You go get it yourself
That's your wife's bag!
Hey, are you hurt?
Your bag is inside her bag
I'm at the Harbour Drive¡­
Miss¡­
The bag is mine
He¡­ he snatched my bag
Yes, I¡­
Maybe you'd have a drink to calm down
Thanks, honey
Sis
Thanks
Bro-in-law is here!       Let me¡­
Hello¡­
Long time no see.       How are you?
Happy New Year¡­
Do you need such a big house?
It's necessary¡­        Necessary?
Do I need to take off my shoes?
Never mind
Have a seat¡­
Fatty
What's up, bro-in-law?
That's expensive
You are knowledgeable,  it's quite an expensive one
Do you have Danny Summer's  and Cai Qin's CDs?
Dinner Winter and Cuisine  are available now
Come on, dinner is ready
You sure know how to do wordplay, bravo¡­
Sis, long time no see
Look at your hairdo, you have taken  at least 3 hours to set it
Just like a noble lady
Noble lady
Honey
I phoned you a couple of times
You didn't answer your phone,  where have you been?
A little kiss
You drank at the nightclub again?
Bro-in-law, have a seat
We don't have family reunion everyday
In such a big house of my husband¡­
Let's enjoy our New Year Eve's dinner
Bro-in-law, mix the sauce first
Okay
Honey, let me do that for you
I know what you do like  and what you don't
You know I don't like you going  to nightclub, why you go there?
Sis, let me cook some cheese sausages  and cheese balls for you
Cheese sausages are fatty,  and so are cheese balls
Honey, you're fat
Honey, some people look nicer  with some extra pounds
while some people look nicer when slim.  I think you look nice when you're fat
Just eat as much as you can,  don't worry. Trust me
Bro-in-law!
Let me cook some fatty beef for you
Honey, so fat and so old
Shut up!
Never mind him, let's eat
Let's eat
I don't come here to be slapped
You guys are just flirting,  don't take it too hard
Can I pretend I haven't been slapped?
Or I have been hit by a cheese ball?
Actually I'm starving
Shall we start dinner?
If she doesn't apologize
I will leave
I am leaving now
Why should I apologize to you?
I sacrifice the fun of  hanging out with pretty chicks
just come here to be with you old guys¡­
That's fine with me
Right, I did drink and dance
But you don't have to disgrace me  in front of your family
Despite you know how I hate  those nightclubs, you still patronize them
Despite you know how I hate  dining with your family
I'm still here
What's wrong with my family?
It's you who told me  your sis and her husband¡­
What's wrong with you¡­
You hit my sis?
Sis, are you okay?  Shame on you for hitting a woman
Does it hurt?  Then I'll hit a man. Stand still!
Honey, are you okay?
You hit my husband?
Sorry, I¡­
That's enough!
I am gonna fight back¡­
Look at you, you just  messed that all up, bastard
You are the one to be blamed on
Bastard!
What the hell! Are you nuts?
Dare you bully my sis¡­
You shameless punk!
Don't come over¡­ I'll stab you
Scared?¡­ I'll strangle you to death!
I hate being hit in the head by sausages
I'll strangle you to death¡­
Stop that!
Aren't you gonna help?
Why did you stab my armpit?
You hit my sis¡­
You get lost¡­
Why did you stab my armpit?
Stop that¡­
Blackmail me!
Environmental friendly car!
Honey!       What is it?
Are you okay?
You wanna attack me with hot water?
You'd know what you have done
Why did you attack my sis?
She blackmailed me first
Why did you blackmail my husband?
He has other woman, he cheated on you
Why did you do that?
Am I not good enough?
You loved your Hi-Fi better than me
You are scum!
You are scum too!
Dare you hurt my wife¡­
Let me tell you
I used to play a good husband  in front of your family
to give you honour
I even pretended to enjoy
the companion of your sis and her husband
What else do you want from me?
What did you say?
Do you know what you are talking about?
Of course I do
I can say that again,  even in reverse, bitch
You called me a bitch,  why did you marry me then?
You cheated me and made me marry you
Before we got married, you told me  how virtuous you would be
Afterwards, all you do  is spending extravagantly
You just keen on buying cars
Do you know how many Hi-Fi speakers  I have given up because of you?
When we get married,  your parents wanted my money
After that, you want my money
Now I want a divorce,  your sister wants my money
You are all thieves¡­
Thieves!
What a nasty mouth¡­
You eat now!
Dare you call my dad a thief?
Dare you call my mom a thief?
Damn¡­
Dare you say that¡­
Thieves¡­
Honey, I'll be gone¡­
if I don't go to the hospital in time
It hurts so much¡­       Sorry, honey
It hurts.       Go to hospital now
Don't touch the chopsticks¡­
Sis, wait for me
Won the fight but lost the family
Bro-in-law sat alone  in the house with remorse
Could someone die in this story?
Okay¡­ which one you want dead?
Whoever, just trying to be commercial
Well¡­
How about¡­
(Fighting at the year end dinner)  (in a disharmony family.)
This sounds more commercial?
Higher the death toll,  the more commercial
Sure¡­ I could die too if you want
I'll talk to my boss, I'll let you know
Thanks¡­
What is it?
999 emergency report center
Police, help¡­
Someone threw bottles of  liquid¡­ from above¡­
It's corrosive liquid¡­  many people got hurt¡­
It splashed all over, it's everywhere¡­
Where's you location?
IFC in Kwun Tong?
Not in Central, in Kwun Tong
Kwun Tong IFC?
Do you know you'll be charged
for making false reporting
999 report center is for  people who are badly in need
It's not for prank call
I'm not kidding
I'm just trying to be a good citizen
I've joined Junior Police since I was six
I recorded every episode of  ¡°Junior Police¡± (TV program)
Now you're trying to  defame me for false reporting?
Neither me nor my family got hurt
I still take time to report this¡­
Miss, can I borrow your phone?
Isn't there a phone?
Sir, can I borrow your phone  to call the police?
I'm now talking to them right now
I will let the victim  talk to you directly
Hello? Is it the police?
Thanks, sir
Thanks
The ambulance will be here soon
You're welcome¡­
Bye
Aren't you staying with me  till the police arrive?
You're a big man,  no need for companionship
You have to give your testimony too
So troublesome?
I used your phone, they can trace back
Don't go!       Don't ask me¡­
I know nothing about this
Hello?       Is it Luk?
Who is it?
It's Ling Ling,  Luk's primary schooI classmate
It's you, Ling Ling! You're so lucky
I won't be able to answer your call  if you call me 10 sec later
Are you okay?       Okay¡­
Then come to my wedding banquet tonight
We haven't met for years,  you have no excuse for not coming
Please come to check out my Mr. Right
Okay¡­ I will come
I need to dress-up now, I got to go
See you tonight.       Ok, see you tonight
Cancel this phone number
Write this down¡­
I've already lost my phone
It's done. This is the new phone
The sim card is inside
This is your new phone number¡­ remember
64897123
The service will commence after one hour
An hour later?
Can I borrow your phone?
I should tell my girIfriend  about the new number
I already have a girIfriend
I'm not available at the moment,  please leave your message
Hello? Ju¡­ Julia?
Nothing special, I just got a new phone
I want to tell you¡­
This voice mail box is full
Thanks
Here's your receipt
Excuse me, please go to Kowloon City,  Yin Yang restaurant
Hello? Mr. Chan
Yes, I'm Luk
Yeah, I'm still waiting for your call
I just want to let you know  that I've lost my phone
My new phone number is 6489¡­7123
Yes¡­
I'll text you my new phone number
Thank you
This afternoon around  4 o'clock in Kwun Tong
someone threw corrosive liquid  from a building
More than 20 people were injured
The police is now investigating  the buildings in the area
No suspect has been arrested yet
The police is now calling on witnesses  to phone the hotline 87654321
Besides, in this case¡­
there's a victim who  was hit by a hard object
unfortunately got run over  by an ambulance
He's pronounced dead at the scene
There's a homicide case  in Kowloon City this morning
Two men's quarrel over Spongy Chicken  led to a fatal fight
One of them got killed by a hard object
A suspect has been detained by the police  for further investigation
(Argument over a dish of Spongy Chicken)  (turned into a fight!)
What the hell! Is that true?
Excuse me, I'm getting off here
Okay
$58, thanks
Here's $60, keep the change
Thanks
Come on, what are you rushing for?
Why did you slam on my car?
I'm asking you if you are rushing to hell!
Are you rushing to hell?
(Two drivers fought over cutting in line.)
Hey, kid
If you want to smoke and watch  pornography, that's fine with me
but please don't wear your schooI uniform
It's none of your business
Honey!       Hi!
Hey¡­
You guys want to kiss in public place,  that's fine with me
but come on, please don't hold her breast
Here is a public area
It's none of your business
Everybody get closer, right, thanks¡­
Excuse me, you two
You just blocked them, please stand out
No¡­ go inside
It's a video, give me some motion
As I say ¡°action¡±,  then you guys walk out, okay?
You, stand here.  I'm not standing with him
Miss, you're not standing with him?  That's fine
Just walk away from him  when I say ¡°action¡±
The front roll could stand up first
Right, sit down after I count to three
Action!
Motion
Wedding banquet, my ass
The bridegroom said,  only cup noodle could be ordered
But not for crabmeat noodle
Shit! Shouldn't hold any  wedding banquet if you are broke
Go to Dongguan hanging out with chicks
would be happier
It doesn't matter¡­ Take Two
One more
You guess how long they will last?
I've found a prophet to predict that
They will divorce in 49 days
Which prophet?       Mr. Profit
(Chan & Lee's Wedding)
They don't want to sit at the same table,  how could I arrange then?
Just tell them go sit at the head table
Here comes a guest. Welcome!       Welcome!
I was the classmate of the bride
Please autograph¡­
Table 9 for primary schooI  classmate, please
This is for the bride and groom
Cut¡­
Sorry, the camera was not rolling
Please do it again
Action!
This is for the bride and groom
Please say something nice  to the newly-weds
Wish you guys¡­
happily ever after
Till death do you guys apart
Brat! You just care to play  and won't go to washroom
You hold your pee till the last minute,  then you give me the ultimatum
Son, do it like last time
I don't want to pee in the sink
Why¡­
Why it's not me?
Congratulations¡­        Thanks
I'm your wife's primary schooI classmate,  my name is Luk
Thanks for coming
Keep talking as if  I am not here, be natural
You are great¡­
I did have a crush on your wife  when we were little
but I didn't have a chance
What a pity!       You are the winner
Right, where's your wife?
She said she's tired¡­
and she's got to change and make-up
Welcome¡­
Bride's side or bridegroom's side?
I'm the bridegroom's ex-girIfriend,  so what do you think?
The bridegroom!
Congratulations
Please shoot my mother first¡­
Thanks
I thought you won't come,  why are you here now?
So are you surprised?
Did you forget that  you promised to marry me
How about playing mahjong
I know what I'm short of
Miss, what's your size?
P0
Did you say D or C?
Get a G cup for this lady
G?       Right
But G-cup has to go with some accessories
Look at these
Spongy bra pad, it's economical
but they're too thick  for the sweaty summer
Some customers would prefer these
regardless of the price
Silicon gel.       What are those?
Silicon gel, same material  for breast implants
Touch it
It feels so genuine
Yeah, if you wear T-shirt or blouse
you can use the ¡°full moon¡± pads
If you wear strapless
you can use the ¡°half moon¡± pads
If you wear deep-V,  you can use the ¡°new moon¡± pads
During the promotion period
you can buy the combo,  all 3 types of pads in one box set
You can wear them in any occasions
to meet the challenge of being  judged by any kind of people
Satisfaction guarantee.  Regain your confidence
Give you a 12% off discount
I'll take the combo
Do I look different today?
You're heavy make-up
Look downward
Let me introduce my friend to you
Luk
Marietta
You two should play mahjong
Mahjong can't be played  byjust two persons
Buddy¡­
You can't play alone
I've found someone  to play mahjong with you
I'lI get one more for you
No need
Rocky, will you accept my challenge?
Worry about losing to me again?
What did you say, Luk Po?  You think I'm afraid of you?
By the way, what business are you guys in?
Why? Is it related to mahjong?
I'm in contemporary art
I like to meet with people  from alI walks of life
I'm a tourist guide
Hong Kong Kowloon¡­
We loved Hong Kong¡­
I'm a dance teacher
Good toes¡­
Naughty toes¡­
Pluck this flower¡­
Pick that star¡­
I'm a nurse in a plastic surgery clinic
I'm so scared
Don't be scared, many people  have tried ¡°botox¡± before
No, I'm scared of  those paparazzi waiting outside
How could I leave here?
Mrs. Cheung, don't be afraid.  I have an idea
Just lie down, get the shot
Are you sure they can't recognize me?
As long as you put on this wig,  let me help you
No one could recognize you
I'll take you out from the back door
Yourjob is kind of unique
So you have seen the  weakness of human nature?
This is my name card
I've just changed my phone number
This is the new number
Let's meet some other time
So you can tell me  some inspirational stories
Who's gonna throw the dice?       Me
Your turn
What's the matter? Looking for friends?
No¡­ the bride has taken  so long to get changed
I haven't seen any of  my primary schooI's classmates
Primary schooI's classmates?  They might have changed so much
How could you recognize them?
Win on ¡°self-draw¡±, it is ¡°one suit¡±
So soon? Are you cheating?
What did you say?
What? You used to play sly trick
That's how you stole  Angelina Baby from me
Tell me, are you thinking of her  when you kiss me?
Who's ¡°her¡±?
What's wrong?
Luk Po said you enjoy watching her  photo-collection in the washroom
This book's not mine
Angelina Baby!
Luk Po!
I'd like to ask¡­
Who's Angelina Baby?
The one that took away my bridegroom
Peter
Will you marry me?
I have something for you
You even got our  wedding invitation card ready?
Kiss
Angelina and Peter?
You're gonna marry that bitch?
Why?
I've no choice, she's pregnant
Didn't you say she has  gone through an abortion?
Yes, but¡­
She's pregnant again
How could it be possible? You bastard!
You guys have such a  complicated and messy relationship
Just like entangling lines  in a relationship chart
Miss, that's pretentious
In fact they're trying to harm you
What did you say?
Tapping on someone's shoulder  when playing mahjong is bad luck
You should watch your mouth
AIthough it's the first time we meet
I do understand how sorrowful you are
My girIfriend has dumped me this morning
Here's tissue paper, hope it'll help
A guy that brings tissue paper along  must be tender-loving-care
It's your girIfriend's loss
Your girIfriend missed a Mr. Right
Hello?
How are you doing in the wedding banquet?
I haven't seen that bitch yet
I'm now playing mahjong
Regarding you¡­
I do have a tender-loving-care  guy for you
Wait
No way¡­
He passes, give it to me
He's too shy
I'll text you his phone number later
He is¡­
a tender-loving-care young man  who brings along tissue paper
Don't try to fooI me!
I'm hanging up, I need to play mahjong  to relieve my stress
Bye¡­
(A tender-loving-care young man who brings)  (along tissue paper. Phone number: 64897123.)
6 pairs and a half! Suck! All in pairs
Go for ¡°all pong hand¡± then?
Are you teasing me?  I won't go for¡° all pong hand¡± though
Dare you break them up
Break you up!       Pong!
Break you up!       Pong! ¡°South¡±!
Are you kidding?
It's the saddest time in my life£»  you are ready to claim for ¡°big 4 winds¡±?
Are you guys trying to set me up?
Of course not¡­
Bystander, is he claiming  for ¡°big 4 winds¡±?
Isn't it?
It's not right for you to ask me
And it'll be wrong for me to answer you
Buddy, wait¡­
If someone discards an honour tile  and you're claiming for a win
then you have to  declare it loud and clear
And, look at the camera,  remember to smile
Smile
Don't think about that,  just break them up
Break you up!       Are you that nosy?
Break them up
Who's playing now?  May I know who is playing now?
I'm playing! Break you up!
Again
Break them up!
Who's playing now? You or she?¡­
¡°6 stones¡±
I'm not gonna break these two up
¡°7 stones¡±!       ¡°Hu¡±! (Winning)
You're so cunning to have  a ¡°ready hand¡± for a ¡°7 stones¡±
Huh? I have to pay double?
It's lucky that it's  just a ¡°chicken hand¡±
You're wrong, here's a  ¡°all flowers¡± and a ¡°seat season¡±
Three ¡°fans¡±. (points)
Lost again
You used up my tissues
Should you leave such a grieving place?
Yeah, why should you stay here?
Shouldn't let people  sow salt on your wound
I'm here to ¡°work¡±
What?
You switched that off and I'll tell you
Okay, already off
Do you know what this is?
What?
Botulinus
What an awful name!
That's Botox
It's used in plastic surgery clinic  for wrinkle elimination
You have tried that?
Kind of
But this one's been refined
It's highly concentrated
It could kill if taken orally
I'm wondering in which dish  I should put this
so that no children will be hurt
According to my experience, children run  around after having the shark's fins
You can't do that!
Why?
Let me do it
Do you know what this is?
Coke.       Of course not
I drank the coke last night
Now, it's highly  concentrated flammable liquid
inside this classic coke bottle
So cooI
Is there any technical name for that?
You know shit about that!  You failed your chemistry though
You just know luring other's girIfriend
Angelina Baby!
When the time comes, you guys better  find a safe place to hide
You must take good shot of me
I will¡­
Thanks for coming to our banquet
Cheers!
Ladies and gentlemen,  I loved Angelina Baby!
I'm not trying to discourage you
But I think you're so stupid
You wouldn't be able to see it  even I've taken good shot of you
He's always like this,  he's just up to kindergarten level
Watch me
Hope you will enjoy the dinner. Cheers!
Okay, let's greet on the newlyweds
Congratulations¡­
Ladies and Gentlemen¡­
Let's share the romantic  story of the couple
Here it goes!
It's not the groom?
Angelina Baby¡­
Great!
You two, don't do anything
No one can stop what  Marietta is going to do
If you kill all my audience
no one can see me  being the martyr of loved
Your way will only harm the others  while yours will only harm yourself
Mine will do both
My way is most harmful. Use mine
Bro, you should say something
You are deploying biochemical lethal stuff,  plunging people into abyss of misery
You are such a fooI,  kicking yourself against the pricks
You are so evil
You force others to  share your obscene clip
Wicked, tacky and indignant
Bro, I'd like to ask¡­
Why is your pen having a light?
You¡­  You are taking sneaky shot on us?
Taking sneaky shot?       Let me go¡­
I got the proof of you guys' crime
You guys wilI have the same ending
Damn¡­
Dare you say that again?
I'm not
I fxxk you all fxxking bastards
You¡­       Damn you!
Too shameful!
What's happening?
Is it on show or on fire up there?
Is someone got chopped up?
Give way¡­       Luk¡­
Who are you?
I'm Ling Ling.  Why are you coming from up there?
(Chan & Lee's Wedding)
I don't know¡­
What happened up there?  Congratulations¡­
Hope you'll give birth soon
I am busy right now,  please leave a message
Julia!
Julia, it's me
I don't know why I'm so pissed today,  all the bad things are coming to me
I must be out of luck
You left at good timing
I don't want you to  get invoIved in my bad luck
Anyway, all the best
Julia?       Hello¡­
Oh, Mr. Chan
Come to ¡°Against All Odds Club¡± now
Club?       Karaoke
It's karaoke or club?
It's ¡°Against All Odds Karaoke Club¡±, okay?
Boss is waiting for you here
Okay, I'll be right there
(A man was killed in a)  (wedding banquet conflict.)
Boss, I've been so down lately
My mom is sick,  I've to pay for my sis' tuition fee
Yesterday, a boss asked me  to be his mistress for 3 months
But I miss you so much
So I'm still thinking about that¡­
Then you'd tell your other clients  that you've been so down lately
your mom is sick and you've to  pay for your sis' tuition fee
Yesterday, a boss asked you  to be his mistress for 3 months
But you miss him so much
And you're still thinking  about that, okay?
How's that?
Louder! Clap hands!
Louder! Boss, you sing so well
Boss is over there
What's up? Did you listen to my singing?
Don Guo, you sang so well
It's good though.       It's nice
Piss off¡­
Boss¡­
What's it?       He's the cartoonist
Hi, boss
You are the cartoonist?
Your look is funny though
How would you like to get drunk tonight?
Brandy, red wine, women, cannabis¡­
We've everything here
Boss is asking how  you would like to get drunk
Boss¡­ well¡­
May I tell the story before I get drunk?
Okay, Punk
you should learn this,  that's what we call professional
Give him a drink
Shouldn't you thank boss?
Drink up.       Thanks¡­
Boss, I'd like to start now
Go ahead¡­
In this story,  there shouldn't be anyone die¡­
but so many people died at the end
It's a story with  a bright and shiny beginning
and with a dark and eerie ending
This story tells 4 kinds of people
First kind, those who  think they are being well
but in fact they are just too befuddled
Second kind, they are being well  because they are befuddled
Third kind¡­
they fail to appreciate that  they have been being well
Lastly, they don't know whether  they are being well or not
because they've never thought of that
The End
Funny?
Is it funny?
Is that good?
Good, it's very good
Okay, get on to work tomorrow
Make your story into comics
Or even cartoon movie will do, right?
Shouldn't you say thanks to your boss?
Drink it.        Drink up!
Cheers¡­
Cheers!
Be careful!
Hello? Julia
I'm so happy¡­
Yes¡­ I'm gonna have my own comic
Hello? Why don't you say something?
Why don't you care about me?
Are you upset?
But I'm so excited now¡­
I'm gonna have my own comic
In fact I'm so upset
because I can't live without you
Sorry, man
He just sat with Don Guo
Nice meeting you¡­
Donna Dragon¡­
Say hello to Donna Dragon
Hi, Donna Dragon¡­
You guys should say hello to Don Guo too
Hi, Don Guo¡­
Get lost!       Go, take a seat
Come on, have a drink
Yours?       Yes
Has your venereal disease healed?
Yes¡­ No, I never had that!
Are you asking for a fight?
I'm¡­ still finding who your Cicisbeo is
I don't have one
If not? Why did you  kick me out of our home?
I told you a thousand times,  I was going through menopause
Just an excuse
I haven't done that with  anyone for so many years
Tonight, I want to do it with you¡­
to have finger-guessing game!
Drink!
Hi
Your cigarettes?
Take the whole pack
Just now¡­ thanks.       For what?
You praised my story
I say it's good because it's good
Someday I will name a character
after you
You know my name?
Fong May Fong
I've something to tell you
Can we find a quiet place for that?
I just want to find a quiet place to talk
I just want to have a talk
What are you trying to say?
I do have something to say, but¡­
I can't think of the main point
How could you be a writer?
I could if I'm not distracted
Now I got it
What drug did you take? You're so cute?
Fong, don't do it here
Where do you want then?
No¡­ don't get me wrong¡­
I mean, don't work here anymore
Do you have money then?
No
You've no money, I wouldn't be your girI
Then let me tell you a story
What story?
Once upon a time,  there's a little match girI
No¡­ should be a princess
But she doesn't know her true identity
This princess goes to a bad schooI
Her classmates are from alI walks of life
None of them are good stuff
The teachers there just won't give a damn
What they care most is not the students,  but the tuition fee
The princess is so lost and miserable
Hoping someone may help her,  but her hope is in vain
Until one day
she's met a prince
The prince is so nice  and willing to give her everything
So the princess is willing to  give whatever the prince wants
But, one day¡­
the prince turns into a frog
While the princess  turns to compensated-dating
Excuse me, I'm not  into compensated-dating
I'm a sex-worker
Then I do wish that¡­the sex worker
will turn back into a princess tomorrow
What makes you think I'll listen to you?
My heart
I guess, my wish is not that demanding
Do you have demanding wishes?
Yes
I'd like you to quit smoking  after this pack
Are you trying to mess with me?
What do you want?
I will chop you up!
It's occupied.  What kind of attitude is this?
Someone's still inside¡­
Mr. Chan
Take your time¡­ I'm going back to work
What do you want then?
What do you mean?
It's been so many years,  you've never given in to me once
If I don't give in,  would you be standing here alive?
You, traitor,  shouldn't say the other way round
I'm gonna settle this with you
Don't know who owes who
Let's talk about that inside.  Let's go
Buddy!
Don Guo has something to announce
I've been loving Donna Dragon  for so many years
Today, Donna Dragon finally  promised to re-marry me
We wilI have the  wedding ceremony tomorrow
Why tomorrow? Tonight's still young
Okay!
Starting from tonight,  your boss is my boss
My boss is your boss
We are brothers and sisters then
Our bosses are having  a good time together
We small potatoes should  also enjoy ourselves
It'd be frustrated
during the bad times
Losing all the hope
and fooling around
Just like a dead man walking
Life is like the waves in the sea
There would be ups and downs
Good luck or bad luck
You stilI have to live everyday anyway
30% depends on fate,  70% depends on effort
You've to fight in order to win
(A tender-loving-care young man who brings)  (along tissue paper. Phone number: 64897123.)
Hello¡­
Julia? You finally called me
Could someone die in your story?
That's why we say, life is impermanent
Are you rushing to hell?
Hello?
(Fireworks in nightclub)  (caused devastating fire.)
The meal is ready
Give me one minute
But I'd like a better world
You just go ahead then
I'll leave them here,  you take this to someone who have say
Spongy Chicken.       One please¡­
Well¡­ no thanks
There's nothing else, just these
Leave that to others
Spongy Chicken
Why did you slam on my car?
I am asking you, are you rushing to hell?
Bro, my wife is gonna give birth
Give me one minute. We're just earning  our livings. I'll leave in one minute
Congratulations
I'm married.  Thanks for coming, have a seat
Granny, look here.       Luk!
Ling Ling?
You are so slim that  I can't recognize you
Congratulations¡­        Thanks¡­
Where's the groom?       He's downstairs
Isn't here Chan & Lee's Wedding?
It's such a coincidence, all three floors  are booked by ¡°Chan & Lee's wedding¡±
Then why are you here?
The washroom downstairs is packed,  so I try this floor
Let's go¡­
Hello?       Luk?
I'm Mr. Chan, I'm in karaoke with boss
Don't say that I won't give you a chance
Will someone die in your story?
I do want a better world
Fong May Fong
Do I know you?
You dropped your student ID
It's yours.       Thanks
I like your schooI uniform
Don't get me wrong,  I'm an old boy of your schooI
I did have 2A's and 4B's in HKCEE
So the legend is true
One has to be self-reliant
Try your best, don't waste yourself
Julia?
Why is there no one died today?