Congratulations, Mr. And Mrs, Ma,
Your twins is really lovely,
Look. their noses are exactly like yours.
Yea, everybody from my family has a big nose,
It's be even better if they're fraternal twins,
If our daughter has a nose like yours
who wants her?
Isn't it great with two dragons now?
Give me the two dragons then,
Sergeant!
Sign in at the register.
Call the headquarter, tell them I've got Crazy K,eung
They look exactly the same
Its difficult to separate them
K,nock on wood and reword yourself!
Don't talk about splitting them apart,
The convict escaped!
Be good. my son
Who are you?
Who is it? Why are you here?
Return my son to me
How dare you lay a hand on me?
Please don't... K,eung, The child is innocent
Don't do anything rash
Open fire!
Give me back my son!
How dare you fight over something with me? Get lost
Go away!
You bastard!
Freeze. How could that impact not kill you?
You animal! You wouldn't even leave mercy on a child?!
Cordate Telosma
I will sing for you
Hey. boss! You still haven't gone home when it's so late at night.
Are you looking for someone to drink with you?
You don't drink, I drink!
The infant is missing, Only a wheelchair remains,
Keep searching! - Got it.
You can't even protect a baby.
What kind of policemen are you?
They're crying in such sorrow
Will they be in America for good?
Pass them a handkerchief!
Thanks!
Yuen Ting, when did you had a baby with Yiu?
Let me hold him, Who'd have a baby with him. I found him in the streets
He's so cute
Hey. kid! Fork over your protection fee
Take this. idiot!
Stay there. you little bastard
How did this happen?
Hey!
Hi!
He was molesting me!
What? Who dare to do that!
Stay there!
He just suddenly wanted to beat me up. Die-Hard.
Fight back!
Sure!
C'mon.
Come and hit me!
Finish it and leave
There they are!
Beat him up!
Go to hell!
Don't hurt the innocent.
Happy birthday, Yau Ma
Happy birthday. - Thanks, Mom!
A pretty girl!
Love remains in our dreams
Heart-to-heart with no regrets
Each day, we meet and share our lives together
Our hearts come close for eternity
Nothing to consider regardless of the situation
Nice
Nice sale for the night.
Cheers - Cheers
Is this good to drink?
-Split it amongst the brothers -Split it amongst the brothers
Brother Wai, let's take a look at the photos!
Brother Wing. your driving technique is much better than Speedy K,uen's
From now on. with your reputation in Princess Margaret Road and the Eastern Corridor
they can't even be considered racing
no matter how hard they step on the pedal without your seal of approval
Alright let's give a toast to Brother Wing
Cheers
Die-Hard. over here!
What's wrong with you? Why are you all dressed up?
We're going to make it big
Of course, it'd have to look cool
Where's the weapon?
Brought 'em right here!
I still don't understand why you have insist on dressing up?
Negotiation!
Iron Wing was trying to seduce my girlfriend!
You have a girlfriend? I didn't know that
Did I ever need to tell you about it? Am I required to write a report as well?
She's gorgeous
This Filipino maid is your girlfriend?
What bad taste! Doesn't she look like Maradonna?
Maradonna's a soccer player
If you're coming to open negotiations. please go ahead!
You still tak e me as your boss after all.
Brother Wing. Iet's sing a duet! C'mon...
Alright
Don't be shy. Brother Wing
Bring her up to a room and get it done,
Forget about the mood and the atmosphere
This room has been book ed for 3 days already
Sorry Sir
It's a full house tonight
Sing!
Can destiny give results to love?
Can an oath guarantee that love is real
Spending time apart doesn't mean it's either good or bad
The song hasn't even finished! Get back  to where you are.
Die-Hard.
No other way. okay?
We're here to negotiate, We won't need any tables, ok ay?
Why are you standing there lik e an idiot?
Go back  up to sing! -No more singing,
Who said so?
I did,
And just who do you think  you are?
I'm Tarzan. He's my bodyguard, Die-Hard
I've never heard of your name,
Who are you to talk to me?
Are you guys scared of being outnumbered?
Not that many!
Go get the microphone! - Yes!
You tak e the microphone!
I can't sing.
I'm here to flirt with you no  I'm here to save you
Save me? You or him?
Take the speakers away,
Die-Hard
How to fight with the microphone?
How dare you lay a finger on my girl?
Boss...Die-Hard. come and save me!
Damn you!
Why haven't you draw your weapons?
Freeze!
Don't move!
Are you alright?
I paid $800 to rent this suit, what do you think?
Don't move! Don't move...
Don't move!
My hand hurts!
I went a little overboard
Are you alright? Don't be afraid.
Are you Die-Hard? - Yes!
I can knock down 5 people with my bare-hands
My bullets can hit another...
Whatever....but anyway, it's alot
Come forward if you are willing to sacrifice for your boss
Come forward!
Go away! - We're leaving, boss,
Leaving?! Who's going to compensate for my loss?
I'm not letting go that easily
Pass me your gun. Let me show off a bit with it
We've had enough of that
You did. not me
This gun is too light
Stop nagging!
k neel down. k owtow and apologize
It's a fak e?
What are you doing?
It cost me a few dollars, what do you expect,
Let's run.
Get them.
Shut the door. Pull the latch down!
Don't run!
Stay!
Damn you!
Iron cloth!
It's cool now.
Die-Hard.
Your turn, -ok ay
What now? You can't beat me. What a shame!
How can you maintain a good name?
Get up!
Excuse me!
Damn you!
Die-Hard. I'm coming to save you!
Why's it always like this?
Great! Great!
Who are you to compete with me? Look at yourself
Twice as shorter than me
You're not any better, baldy!
Ah Wai
You're Ah Wai
In our profession, we only beat the big one
You wanna embarasse yourself again?
Can't be as worse as you
Hold on! Hit the left leg, will ya?
Leave me the right leg to control the gas when the car is racing
What did you say? A car race
Lik e you wanna compete with me?
I'll kick  your ass, lron Wing!
You know what happened to Speedy Kuen?
His broke his ribs last time in the last race
Speedy K,uen is nothing!
His car headlights can't even spot our pumps on Princess Margaret Road
Any drivers can beat him,
Who do you think you are?
I am k nown for my driving sk ill in Macau racetrack s
Princess Margaret Road is nothing to me
Fine, I'll race you in Macau
How much will you wage your bets on?
Mak e it 3....
30. 000? Deal!
You kidding me? I am talking about 300.000,
Sure! 300.000 is nothing to me
300, 000?!
I'll keep your l.D. cards
Get your money
I'll meet you at the pier in the morning after tomorrow
Let's see who'll win in Macau
What are you to race with him? You can't even start your engine
Do you guys remember me?
Hop, ma'am! - Jump in!
Thanks,
Thanks so much for that.
I've been work ing at the karaoke for the past few days
Iron Wing is always coming to watch my performance
If you weren't there
he would have harassed me to sleep with him
It's alright, It was my pleasure
Is your name really Die-Hard?
Yes
This is such a weird name, What about you?
Tarzan!
Don't you k now him?
Never been introduced
Didn't you say she's your girl?
Sooner or later, she'll be my girl
Damn you! Get outta here, I need to talk  to you,
Die-Hard... Die-Hard!
Don't let a girl ruin our friendship
I'm about to get her,
I can risk my life for you You should know what you've got.
Do you think there's a possibility that Maradonna would ever like you?
Look at the color of her hair, will ya?
She's make you a cuck olded.
Never say never.
nothing...nothing is impossible
Damn you
I am here to mak e a living, I don't want people recognize me.
What's your name again?
Barbara!
Miss Barbara, please tell our hero
Would you ever fall for him?
Him?!
Keep those words to yourself
I got it
My boss hardly fall for girls
Take good care of him for me!
Take her out, I am heading home
Mr, Ma
Is it your first concert in Hong Kong?
Y es, it is!
How can I raise $300,000?
Where's my money, Chan?
Didn't you use my car to race last time?
How much will you pay for that?
Dude, you bet on that too!
You won and you took your share of the bonus
That was my boss' car, The engines all fell apart
That couldn't ever cover the repairing cost
What are you trying to say?
This car just had a respray
Damn you
You wanna show your boss this picture?
Don't even blackmail me with that
My boss didn't know Susan at the time when I got romantic with her
Is that so? But there's no date indicated in this photo
Tarzan! Print another few copies, it's on him,
We'll send a copy to everyone in the hotel
Sure, I'll mark  it down!
Fine, My boss' will be transferred to another post in Japan next week
Let's see how you're gonna blackmail me
You're never repairing my cars anymore
After today. just forget about it,
I'll go tak e a leak, the washrooms here are very nice
Hurry up! We'll have to leave once we grab the money
I'll be quick.
So you think  you're better with a bigger car, eh?
I'm sorry
Mr, Ma, Here we are
I didn't know the washrooms are in the car
So you're living it up. huh? Pretending to have good taste?
Are you messing around with me? How dare you,
Ouch! My ass
Hey. k id! You've got it all wrong. I don't lik e playing with these,
Then what is it that you play with?
Tarzen. Why are you squatting there?
Q.uit fooling around, Stop pretending you have good taste, will ya?
Dare to hit me?!
Damn you. That's ridiculous,
Sorry
Welcome Mr. Ma
This way ,
Is this a mirror?
It's not 200,000. it's 400.000 shares
Yau Ma
Do you still recognize your uncle?
Uncle Tong
Wow. Iong time no see. Come over here ,
Look. you still recognize her?
She's your childhood playmate. Tong Sum
She used to play the flutes with you
Come and give a greeting, daughter dear.
This is how encounters are supposed to be
She's a nurse
She knew you were back  so she quit her job to take good care of you
I'm not sick
Since it's your first time back in Hong Kong
You can easily catch endemic
You're an internationally famous conductor
If you get sick
you can't do anything. and
Uncle. I'll go get a change of clothes, Alright, we'll do more catch up later
Pull that lower
I have a boyfriend
I'm finding you a husband, not a boyfriend
What about R ocky?
Stallone?
No, Frankie Lok
I call him R ocky
Rock y tells people to work  hard too
Hold this first aid kit
Your dad is even more powerful than R ocky
I'm handling seven at a time in the mark et
I hope it work s out between you and him
Then our business with the Ma's family would be fine
This is struggling to succeed
The mark et's quiet bad nowadays
Yau Ma, My daughter is look ing for you
Remember to "feel by touch". now get in there
It's all up to you, daughter dear
Alright, just leave them there
Sigh. there's a lot of medicine
I thought Uncle was just jok ing
So nurses dress this sexy nowadays?
You're exposing everything
The top part
Actually, I never tak e any medicinal products and vitamin pills since I was at a very young age
If I k new it earlier, I wouldn't bring so many over
Come, have a seat,
Wearing a sk irt so tight is gonna affect your blood circulation
Wrong posture is problematic too
Your spine must be hurting right now
How do you k now?
Come, get into bed
Already?!
Don't be nervoue, tak e it slow. Take it easy.
I'm all yours -your hand
Do whatever you want,
Here. raise your leg
Relax
It's almost done?
Isn't it easier with my clothes off?
Patience!
Isn't this what you would call "foreplay"?
I'm doing some warm up for you
To help your blood circulation
Are you ready?
relax... is it getting comfortable yet?
Hey... fell asleep already?
It must be tiring for you to twist this hard
I grew up and learnt here
Never thought of leaving this place
I've never heard people wanting to sneak  back  to the mainland
That's what mak es us cool
We're the first ones. aren't we?
We may get listed in Guinness Book  of World R ecords
Is there any cash prize?
I'd have to split everything with you. Hold onto this
Me again? What about you?
I'm calling Barbara
Did she give you her number?
I can check the white page, stupid!
Damn you
I'd have to give you a lot of credit here
You wok e up
It was so comfortable last night,
Can I get you any drinks, missy?
Well. aren't you a little late, boss?
Don't bother me, You go talk  to him
What's up with him?
I don't wanna talk  about it. ask  him
Where's the money?
Tarzen. it's time to pay up!
You pay
The money's with you
Right,
Mak e it cheaper, yea?
Just pay him,
You stole this boat
And it costed you nothing. You're making a fortune here!
Call me when you get to Shantou
Hey. what's Barbara's last name?
Barbara? Of course it's Bar.
Snaky Sun. do we have enough gas for the boat?
Yes!
Something's wrong, Snak y Sun betrayed us
No boat?
No, but a lot of people came to send us off,
They are too friendly
Check it out, run!
Where did you throw away my phone book?
You can call 1 08 for the number, R elease the ropes!
They're down there!
Hurry up!
Start it, Start the boat!
Freeze!
Crap... we can't make it
Why don't you say goodbye to our boss before you leave?
Return ashore
You're funny,
Get back  ashore. I can't swim,
Stewed celery with vegetable, plus an egg. - What?
I said "Bullshit"
Sit still
Block  the boat...
Can't
Stewed celery with vegetable, plus an egg
What the hell was that?
Put on your lifejacket and stop standing here with bullshit
Get them....
Jump into the cars and get them
Yes!
Sit still and hang in there
it's so eye-catching if we sailed to the high seas like this
what are you doing?
This is so springy, I feel lik e sailing,
I feel weird since I arrived in Hong Kong,
But... I was never on a boat.
I am not sure if this is seasick.
Dad said he'll lend you this car
So it's more convenient for you
It's useless
I'm unfamiliar with the roads here, I'd be lost.
Gimme a buzz if you're lost
It's shaking like crazy,
It's shaking a lot because we're close to the seas
I think you oughta sit a little further down
The waves around here are crazy
Stop him. stop him.
You're too careless
Pull over and I'll beat him up to death Be careful
Go to hell!
That's a huge grouper!
Let it go, We're running for life,
Go to hell
Got it
A barge!
Tarzen
Got one
Hit them. Hit them, you idiot!
They've slowed down. go get them down.
Die-Hard. I'll go first
We haven't arrive Shantou yet. Hold on for a bit,
I'll get them down for you
Die-Hard. I'm alright, No need for revenge
Shoot us eh? Shoot us with fish gun?
I can't drive. Help
Look ahead...
A dead end!
Help!
Sigh... what luck!
Have a look!
Tarzen
Great. great!
Watch out!
Are you blind? Watch out for pedestrians!
Be careful of the car!
Brother Wing!... Are you ok ay?
Get the bill!
Sorry for getting you all wet...
We're ashore now
Why don't you go change and,
we'll drink somewhere else
It's alright, I'm afraid you'll go back to the boat
Thank you!
It's fine
we'll find somewhere distance from the sea
What are they doing? Drama practice, perhaps
Tarzen
Tarzen... Tarzen...
Are we there yet? It's so noisy!
No, you're still in Hong Kong,
You're luck y. only some minor scratches
and the bumper is slightly dented
All parts of lron Wing fell apart
Most likely, a total loss
Brother Wing... Brother Wing...
Shut up
I can't even hear his heartbeat
Are you a doctor?
What are you talk ing about?
Are you blind? Don't I look lik e one?
Fine, we don't need you,
We've got an expert with supernatural power to help our young master
Get out of the way!
Supernatural power?!
This kind a medical technology is so behind
You can go now
Excuse me. everybody step back
I don't wanna hurt you with my force.
Out of breath?
No, my energy hasn't transferred yet
Get out of the way. It's very powerful
It's alright now
Get on with it...
Get on
Dude, I've practiced feat of strength too
Let's see whose energy is more powerful
Stop interrupting, I'm saving a life here
Wow. That's too much!
Eat slowly, it's hot
Damn you.
Hey! Don't stop my boss from eating
This hospital is protected by us
Hey brother. you're stepping into a death trap
We'll move, brother
Alright!
My little bro...
Don't move!
If you can leave this hospital,
then I'll denounce my title as Tso, the legal advisor
I was gonna use Wing to do something
Look what you did to him
I k now your driving skills aint that bad
You'll take his place
To do what?
Don't ask
From now on. k eep you cell phone on in the next 24 hours
On call
Otherwise, prepare to receive Tarzan's corpse!
Let's go
Mood. What I want are the emotions
Simply reading the notes to play is too robotic
There's no mood, No heart that anyone will appreciate,
Look at,
My hand. my face, my eyes, my feet
Follow my body language to play music
express the emotion inside the music
ok?!
I need your feelings! Fuse it...
with the music
Hello
Tong Sum. where are you? Speak up!
I'm busy right now, R ocky
Are you with another man?
How would I have another boyfriend?
I'm not lying to you
I'll call you again in a few days
I'm helping my father with some business
Tong Sum!
Is that him?
You're ditching me for a street performer?
My dad's business is collapsing
That's the mood I'm looking for!
But use your instruments to express your feelings. not your stools
Instruments eh?
Run! Or he'll beat you up to death!
Dare to flirt my girl?
Tarzen treated you so well
The least you could do is give him a visit
Who says women are soft-hearted?
I've begged for the whole day without any response
No gas
You can buy gas anytime
But confidence can't be bought
Take him as a friend
And give him some moral support
I'm afraid he'll go insane if I go see him
Go insane?
You can cure him and he can have "A Better T omorrow"!
"Why me"?
Which movie are you talking about?
I k now, Chow Yun Fat has starred in Why me
I k now movies very well
Table for two
Two? This way please!
Aren't you seated already?
Don't mention Tarzan
I'm also not too fond of you
Don't you start laying the blame on me
Sir. please don't lean against the glass
You're pressing against the gentleman on the other side
Mister... please don't lean against the glass
It's no good for you to press against the gentleman on the other side
Can you settle down?
Didn't your mom tell you about table manners?
You and him are birds of a feather
People do change
Alright, I love music. do you?
Music?!
Are you done singing?
What's music?
What else have you got to say?
Who was that just now?
My boyfriend
He's like an angel from hell
He's my partner in the fitness gym
What? Aren't you a nurse?
I don't care about his occupation
It's about the click
Then, what shall I say to him?
Say whatever you want to say
I understand the hearts of men very well
With the way you treat him
He's bound to have a fight with me
Hey. they're not talking to you
Go explain it to him
I'm so lost lately
Other than the fact that you're not as manly as him
I've actually gotten quite fond of you
What's the use if you're fond of me?
I didn't say it, Someone else did!
But you should see him
Fine! Then. I'll go with you to visit him
I'm taking no responsibility if anything happens
Don't worry, I'll take care of everything
Bring us the bill please
Ok ay, coming
Wait for me at the door. I'm going to the washroom
Why don't we head home earlier for today? I have a rehearsal to attend
and
Here's your bill, sir!
I didn't order anything, What's the bill for?
Something's wrong with my eyes
Sir. here's your bill!
He's not that mean after all
Here comes your partner again
Go hide yourself
What about it? - Go hide
Tong Sum
You jerk! Stay there!
You're mock ing on my girlfriend, jerk!
Easy there, R ocky! Don't be stupid
You jerk...
Don't get so rash!
Tong Sum. I want you do know
what a real man is - R un
He'll k ill you
I'll knock you out, you street performer!
Stand still. Tong Sum
What's going on. buddy?
Don't hit him. get me instead
Missy, why are you so nice to a stranger?
Get away!
Run. I'll hold it for you.
Hurry up and run!
Missy
You're hurting my male ego by saying that here
Muscles!
Here's your change, mister!
Keep the change
This sport wear... Hold her
Hold it
Are you done yet?
I don't k now you.
I don't k now you either
Sorry!
What took you so long!
What are you scared for?
Didn't pay the bills? -I did!
There aren't your clothes
You stole this after walk ing around?
What? Steal what?
Playing coy with me. aren't you?
What a nice car
You are using your customer's car in your garage. aren't you?
Not bad. Does it belong to a doctor or a lawyer?
Where are you going. miss?
Let's go
Real leather!
Stop it...
What a cheap ass.
Your turn!
You're playing dirty tricks,
We gotta go! - Sir. I rented this booth to work
I don't want to bother you. he was hitting me first
Hey! I really don't know you
Don't know huh?
I don't k now you two either
I'll kick  your head
Knee?!
Damn you!
Look out
So you're sk illed in combat too
This is frustrating They are expensive
Everything is gone
Hey. punk! Why didn't you borrow it to me?
It's all gone!
Gotta pick up as much as I can
That's enough for you!
I'll retaliate if you insist to continue
You're hitting my face -I told you to stop
Just a second
My stuff was all broken. Who's gonna pay me back?
Honestly. the loser pays. right?
Again?!
You're pretty strong.
I'll going. He is rich
You're rich! Pay for it, now! I have nothing!
Nothing eh?
He hit me!
Marvelous!
I never k new you before
What are you doing?
From this moment onwards, I'll really get to know you
I think so. What do you want?
Stop making jokes!
Stop making jokes? Let's make something else
What's your name. missy?
Barbara
You've ask ed me that 1 0 times already, Die-Hard!
I'm not Die-Hard. I'm Yau Ma!
Missy, where can I tak e you to?
To see Tarzen!
Tarzen? You wanna watch that movie?
Well. you did say we'll visit him
I did?
It's a waste of talent if you're not an actor
Right, I took opera in university.
You sing opera?!
Sure, I do!
Very good, not bad at all
You know that too?
Sure, I do!
I got my 9th grade in piano when I was 8,
When I was 12. I got into the R oyal Music Conservatory
Got the Beethoven Conducting Award when I was 20
I k now, and you're rich too!
Well!
Yeah. So you must have returned from studying abroad in another country
How did you know?
Oh, of course
So you have a very keen interest in music, right?
My father was a piano teacher in Mainland China
You know. the situation wasn't all that great several decades ago
He didn't leave me much
He only left him his knowledge to me so I can make a living
Too bad he passed away before I made his dreams come true
You'll have the chance
Its so big!
Hey. you made me so comfortable last time
Can you do it for me again?
I'm good at repairing cars and nothing else
I'll wait for you in bed
This joke has gotten really big
I can probably do that too. I'll try it out on her
What about it? Beethoven!
You wanna listen to some Beethoven?
Stop!
What's wrong?
Keep going!
Nothing, next song
Ok ay
Give it a try. C'mon!
Me?! No... Don't!
C'mon.
Close your eyes
Imagine it's your recital
Can achievements bring you to a determined rank?
Can money and reputation mak e you a better person
Success and failure might not determine victory and loss
Its difficult to differentiate between pretty and ugly. good and evil
Can the importance of a lover be measured
Although, everything can't be clearly identified
If you love him so deeply. you don't need to ask
Love remains in our dreams
Heart-to-heart with no regrets
Each day, we meet and share our lives together
Our hearts come close for eternity
Nothing to consider and regardless of the situation
What's wrong? I'm waiting for you. Hurry up!
Damn you!
Can destiny give results to love?
Can an oath guarantee that love is real
Spending time apart doesn't mean it's either good or bad
Love is blind, and hard to distinguish
Can the importance of love be measured?
You drink  and smoke?
I get drunk several times each night.
What were we doing just now?
You asked me to get on bed!
It wasn't lik e that last time
Haven't I had sex with you before?
What kind of person did you think  I am?
I didn't tak e you as a whore, Don't tak e me as a gigolo either!
Whore? Gigolo?
Go grab the phone
You thought we're shopping in a red light district?
What music recital were you talk ing about just now?
That's what I'm here for
What? When are you going to stop k idding around?
Hey! My boss is off to Japan
So don't give me any threats
You're so rude! What's your name?
Security!
Die-Hard. stop playing around
Kick him out!
Sir... - What's the matter?
It's nothing. He's just causing a ruck us here. I want to
Mr, Ma - Yes!
You understand that your boss has been sent to Japan
This happened because of his attitude towards the guests
In fact l  -Apologize right away
Sorry!
Go back  to your work  It's alright!
Nice meeting you. Mr, Ma
Alright  enough, It's ok,
I am sorry!
I'm heading back  to my room
Mr, Ma, your concert at 2pm is about to begin
Right, I almost forgot
I think you should tak e a rest
We'll keep it a secret
Enjoy!
Your last name's Ma? - Yes!
Artists need love too
Why did you dress me like that
Honestly. one night stand is nothing
You think  you can do whatever to me? - What are you talk ing about?
Come, let's have a k iss
Behave! Thousands of people are waiting for your performance
You're kidding me! Me and you?
Zip it up! -Hey! Tak e it easy,
Elevator's here, hurry up...
Where are we going to?
How much did you pay for the show?
The rent's $2000 per day
$2000?
U.S, dollars
This little game is really pricy
Here comes trouble
Run quick! - For what?
Stop fooling around
I'm not fooling around - Who is he?
I don't k now
Master - What?
Please take me as your student, Master!
I beg you to tak e me in
I want to learn from you
Learn from me? - Yes!
Please take me and teach me
What grade were you in?
8th grade K,arate and 9th grade T aekwondo
You wanna learn from him with this kind of qualification?
Please take me
I guess there's misunderstanding
I'm a musician
I k now Do-Re-Me but not Ka-ra-te
I don't lik e fighting either
Y ea, he doesn't like fighting
But he has supernatural powers
Supernatural powers?
Master. I also don't lik e to fight
I'm a changed man
Look. it was you who gave me these bruises
Everyone one of them.
Represent my determination to become your disciple
Did you really beat him up lik e that?
You've got it wrong.
He didn't beat me It was a lesson brought upon by Master
Even looks convincing too
Please. master. Take me as your disciple! No
I beg you
I'll tak e you
Great... this is so great.
Master. when will I begin my lessons with you?
Right away
Go buy a piano and play it daily for 6 hours
Piano?
What is that for?
To practice your fingers
Oh right. for strength on my fingers
I understand. master
When shall I begin the practice?
Right away. Now say goodbye
Goodbye. master
Is that your wife?
Byebye.... -Nonsense
Let's leave it as it is
Take care. Master! -Bye
This bulk y guy that you hired definitely has terrible acting
Who'd be convinced of you?
I don't even believe it myself
Crap! I have to get to the press conference
What? A press conference?
Let's go
You really look lik e a musician
What? I am one
You thought I was lying all along?
Obviously
But I'm falling for it
I have no idea where she's taking me to
When would this end?
I'm going to the washroom first
Again?
What's wrong with Barbara?
She keeps following me
Ghost!
Why do you look exactly the same as I do?
Even the clothes look the same
Y eah!
Are you human or ghost? Why are we exactly the same?
Right, I'm glad I ran into you here
It'd cause a scene if others see it
Oh, that short hair girl must have thought I was you.
That's why she dressed me like this
Damn you
That long hair girl thought I was you!
That's why she thought I was lying about the concert
Concert? You're the street performer!
So?
It's nothing. Hey. do you get it now?
I got it, R emember to return my clothes to me
I don't want to cause another ruckus
Alright, You also shouldn't mention to the girl...
that I disguised myself as you, ok ay?
You know Barbara?
What? You've seen Barbara?
I'm not sure if it was her
She just jumped into my car
And kept saying to see Tarzen
So I just bought her the movie
Hey. why do we sneeze at the same time?
That's right!
Have you been on a boat lately?
Yeah!
My God! No wonder I felt seasick
Did you react when I came looking for a prostitute?
So. did you really do it?
Why should I tell you?
I hope that was not his reaction
Hey!...
I don't lik e people patting my shoulder
You forgot your cell!
Thank... You
Damn street performer!
What took you so long?
Mr, Ma, this way please.
Done with the washroom?
Barbara, what are you doing here?
You alright?
You brought me here! Your room's really nice!
Since when have we been this close?
Today! In the room!
In the room?
Did you went up with me?
What's wrong with you? You forgot about it already?
What did I do?
What did he do?
He...
You don't know what you've done?
Do I have to k eep reminding you?
If he did it. I did it too
I'll see if you remember it!
Didn't you say you were going to buy me a Tarzan movie on VHS?
When did Tarzan make a movie?
Stop that
Hey
Hey. Die-Hard
Die-Hard?
I've been look ing for you. You got to show up
I'm not Die-Hard. You've got the wrong number
I grabbed the wrong cell phone
The phone belongs to him -Liar
Damn street performer
He must have done similar things I've done
I'll check up later
Hey. Die-Hard
I'm inside. Where are you?
I'm outside right now
Come on in! I have to protect Barbara
This place is so dangerous
I can't come in yet
Come out and explain in for me. okay?
I would have done it if I could
I'm...
Hello...
Damn it. Out of batteries at this time!
Wait here for me, I'll go grab my phone
You're late
I won't be long
Wai's here for me, Stay there
Mr, Ma, this way please
Done? I've been waiting
Why is Wai waiting for me in the car?
Time's up
Stop fooling around
Let's go
Ok ay!
Where are we going to?
The concert!
Don't tell me he just left on that car
You saw it
You think  I'm seeing things?
God When did you get off the car?
What's going on?
Nice, I gotta explain one thing to you
Don't touch me
You act as if you don't know us
I really don't
Tarzan's on our hands, So. don't you play tricks on me!
You guys like watching Tarzan too?
Just keep in mind that we have Tarzan
Mak e it clear, I'm confused
Barbara
I k new what happened when I was in the washroom
You knew? You just got out from there
And keep asking me what happened
What did I tell you then?
Do you wanna ask  me again. what have you done?
No, but I'd be better if you tell me again.
take them both
Take them
Who are you people?
Hey. I don't k now the place. What do you want me to do?
Want you to save someone!
How great! Who do you want to rescue?
Our boss will be transferred to another prison today He's right in that car
Are you kidding? Carjack ing a patrol wagon is a serious offense
With your skills. it's time you should show us what you got
If you fail. you can say goodbye to Tarzan and Barbara
Calm down!
Relax
You look  more nervous than I am
This is your concert
I didn't wanna come, You dragged me over here!
Don't fool around
Unless you say you're not Yau Ma
I'm really not Yau Ma. I'm Die-Hard
Don't joke with your future, Now go!
I hate people making fun of one's future
If you walk away, that's it for Yau Ma
Why don't you go out?
Got no guts?
I've got guts. but you're tak ing the consequence
I k now what the consequences are
So many people!
What are you doing?
How can I handle the crowd
Right, the baton
Isn't it a baseball bat?
We'll use a baseball bat next time
Damn you!
Take action!
Their firepower is so much stronger than ours
Contact headquarters
Back off, back  off.
Don't be afraid, boss, I'm here to save you
Is that possible?
Take it easy! Don't be afraid  -Stop grabbing my hand
Wait for me here, relax,
You two. off the car - Yes!
What the hell? It won't budge!
The safety switch! Don't panic.
Calm down!
What?
Isn't that good enough for a porno?
Alright, cut that dialogue scene and
replace it with some scenes of bestiality
C'mon. be quick!
Look for something like two bulls with a girl, no...
Two pigs to be exact!
Bulls or pigs? Make your choice and call him back
Hello - Who are you?
Die-Hard! Where are you? Come and save me
Bro. come help me too
I'm performing for you at your concert
The conducting is a complete mess, brother!
It's worse than the Persian Gulf over here. Come and help me out here!
What's with Persian Gulf,
The Persian Gulf War! It's a battlefield out here
Listen if you don't believe me
What am I going to do now?
Scoundrel's motto, if you don't realize the situation,
Do not reveal yourself
Normally under these circumstances
we should stay on the ground as much as possible
Did you hear me?
You are now tak ing my spot
Just do what you think I'd do with the situation
You're tak ing my spot as well.
Just do whatever you think  I might do
Einstein once said
A good orchestra needs a conductor
A lousy one has an agitator
Get out!
Best of luck
Get out, go and open that patrol wagon -Let me cover my face first
You got a light?
Y es!
Damn you! I'll just do it!
It's started already
Start the car
This idiot still can't get it open
Who's that? He look s scary!
He's the boss of my boss
The biggest one?
If you don't start driving quickly you will have the biggest trouble
Start the car... Hurry up.
Feelings! ,
Start it up! What feelings?
Shut up!
Are you riding on a horse or starting up a car?
Run over him! Run over that bastard!
No way! That's illegal!
Don't run over him!
Are you alright. boss?!
I'll be going!
Start the car or I'll k ill you
Start it!
Brother Wai, they're here!
Step on the brakes. Step on it.... - You can do it!
What is that?
The brak e
What?
It's on fire!
Pull the hand-brak e!
You pull it. bro
Go rescues the boss!
Welcome, Mr. Ma!
I heard your concert was a success
We've prepared you some champagne for celebration
Mr, Ma is back!
Hello, welcome!
Is the VlP function room ready? I'm pleased!
It's all ready
May I know who are you?
Yau Ma
Then who was that other guy?
Is he back  yet?
Who's back? - Yau Ma
People are all waiting for you
I'll go tak e a shower first, I'll be right there
Shower?
Come on in
You damned band boy! You got me in a huge mess
I almost died!
Whatever. we're going back to ourselves
You're Die-Hard and I'm Yau Ma, ok ay?
Hey. is there anything between you and Barbara?
No, of course not
This is my room
It's Tong Sum
Just hide upstairs for now
Alright, I'll leave you alone then
Thanks
Didn't you say you'll wait for me downstairs?
You haven't showered yet?
Everyone's waiting for you -Got it!
You go first, I'll be right there
What?
Gimme a kiss
Dude!
I'll be downstairs. waiting for you
Where's my purse?
Hey. are you alright? What are you doing?
Getting ready for shower? What else do you think it is?
It's getting complicated
What should we do now?
Tong Sum thought you were me
And Barbara thought I was you
I have no ideas what to do
Honestly. is Tong Sum your girl?
Come to think of it
I think I prefer Barbara
Barbara is Tarzan's girl
Don't even think  about that
Think about what? I don't even know this Tarzan
What?
Touching my good friend's girl is lik e touching my girl
You're like touching my girl, get it?
You touched my girl too
I didn't know she's your girl
I don't even care whose girlfriend she is
It's none of your business which girl I'm with
Say it again!
I can say whatever I want to say
What are you saying?
You are so rude
Yau Ma!
Are you alright
I'm fine
She's asking me, not you!
She tak es me as you. so I answered her
Who are you talk ing to?
What? She's my girlfriend
She thought she likes Yau Ma,
not Die-Hard!
Not necessarily, besides. we've already...
So you want her to k now that
she's been tricked by a fak e Yau Ma?
Open the door.
or I'll ask  someone to break  in
Coming  hide yourself, quick!
Just to mak e sure
Don't tak e advantage of her
Who's tak ing advantage of her right now?
If I do it, you do it too
What? -Use your brain to think
Intellectual!
What were you doing?
Are you alright?
I'm fine
Who were you talk ing to?
Did I trick  you?
No one's around, I was talking to myself
I'm done. Let's go
What are you doing?
You got me all wet, I need a shower too
Shower?
Excuse me. I'd lik e to tak e another one
it's ok ay, we'll tak e it together
I'm fine now
We did it last time
Did we?
Not only once, remember what you did
We'll have to do it again afterwards
That bastard
Didn't you say no
Why are you taking off your clothes?
I changed my mind according to the circumstance
You weirdo
Now you're putting your clothes back on?
Me? I've never taken anything off
No?
Was that a daju vu?
What?
Set up the water!
The water's clean
Didn't you shower just now?
Y ea I did. but...
I usually like to fill it up again
A habit,
I've got to get accustomed to this little habit of yours
I don't k now what to do
It's alright, I'm already all yours
You better not to tak e the bath
Otherwise we'll never finish
What is that?
Come here! We'll shower like we did back  then
Oh behave!
Stop fooling around
People are waiting
Stop it. No -it's okay
What's wrong? Why are you yelling at a mirror?
A mirror?!
Really?
You scared me
Yeah!
Where are you?
It's not a mirror. Yau, enough with the games
Stop fooling around
Hurry up!
We're late, People are waiting for us
I'll clean it up for you, Come out soon
Hurry up!
Disgusting!
Crap
Operator... nothing. I wanna call a cab
What's wrong with you?
I just cleaned it up for you
You're naughty, c'mon. They're all waiting
Damn you!
What took you so long?
Who are you looking for?
I'm here for Die-Hard
What are you talk ing about. miss?
I think you've got the wrong room
I've been to this room before
He brought me in there today
Barbara!
Would you go check  if you've got the right room number?
Die-Hard
Go and hide
Too shameful to see me?
I don't care who you're fooling around with
What?
Crazy Keung said you have to bring the briefcase
and see him at the Yau Lun Dock yard in an hour
Or else. Tarzan's dead
What's wrong with you?
You weren't like that just now
Why did you change all of a sudden
No wonder you can pay for this room
You must have been a gigolo
Hey. what are you trying to say?
Who is she?
Barbara!
Is she your client?
No!
I'm Tong Sum. he's my fiance
Fiance?
Barbara
Don't irritate me
Remember what you've promised me?
I promised
People always had to give him reminders, how can he forget?
Why do you care so much about her?
Ok ay, this is crazy. I'm not sure if you two can tak e it
Die-Hard. Come out
Right now, Stop hiding.
He's afraid he might scare you.
Stop hiding! This is our only chance to explain ourselves
He has nowhere to go
We can find him for sure
Die-Hard. come out!
Not here!
Do I have schizophrenia?
It's all an illusion, There's no such person
The drawer
Illusion?
Come out!
Really?
Tarzan's in trouble, you have to meet up with Crazy K,eung
Did she tell you where's Crazy Keung?
Yau Lun Dock yard... I guess
and bring him the briefcase
Look after them
Are you coming back?
I'll be back  if nothing happens to me
Is it that serious?
Whoever wants to take pictures, please proceed to the Function R oom.
Thank you for your cooperation...
Manager Chan!
Mr, Ma!
This way please
Die-Hard! - Mr, Ma!
Die-Hard
Since we look so much alike, we gotta be brothers
Life is not fair
But I'll tak e it
If I had your good background
I guess, I could have done just as well
You can die for Tarzan
I wish I have a brother lik e you
We'll go together
At least one of us can call for help
We'll have to dress the same
We've been waiting for you
May I know...
Be tough. this is no social gathering
Go!
So crowded!
Pass the briefcase over
Bring it over!
Don't move, Stay there
Pass the briefcase over -It's dynamite!
You wanna bet? It'll explode when I throw it
Or why do you think  I dared to come alone
I'm taking a piss
Go
Are the fish swimming? Breaststroke or backstrok e?
Where's Tarzan?
Close to the heaven!
Help, Die-Hard! Save me
I'm stuck to a big magnet
Help!
Don't move, I'm scared. I'm so scared,
Are you Tarzan?
Help me, Die-Hard
You hung him up so high
How can I be so sure that is Tarzan?
Let him down and you'll know
Is that clear enough for you?
When is Die-Hard going to arrive?
Does Ma Y au k now how to delay time?
Say something to prove you're T arzan
You bastard. you never lock  the door when you pee
Your farts reek more than anybody
Even the dog that belongs to the fat lady next door would faint
You pick  nose regardless And you  -Ok ay ok ay
Am I really like this?
Alright, say something nice
Nice your ass, you sissy
Pass the briefcase over. or I'm dropping him
Don't move
Bro. someone sneaked in
Which one should I pick? I'll take a wild guess!
Help!
The negotiation is still going on Leave me alone. Help!
Trying to trick me?
Tarzan!
Oh! Thank  heavens
Explosion?!
Come closer and it'll explode
Screw you! Beat him up!
Stand aside
Don't be mad. bro
That's all I have
Bro. behind you!
None of my damned business!
Let's check it out
Get up there
Fire! Help
Don't run, stay there!
Don't let go, kill him!
Go!
Watch out on me
Help!
That's alotta trouble
Tarzan! Go first
Got up so fast?
Hurry it up, will you?
I wanna hurry too
C'mon!
You have some supernatural power?
How did you get down already?
What are you talk ing about?
I can't move. Gimme a hand
He's up there. Go block them!
He's there. get him!
He's got nowhere to run
Damn it. Gotta give it a try
Be quick!
Freeze!
Seems like it's over here. Go search around
Ok ay
Go check it out up there
Over there as well
Are they on your side?
Nope
Eight
Nine
Hurry up
Someone's here
Your turn
Ten
Someone's there
Hey
Keep on going
Someone's here for sure
I'm not lying, -I don't trust you
Look
They're here! -I don't trust you,
With guns as well
Don't move!
Get down
Stop checking out others cards!
Run
Tarzan? Tarzan?
It's hot!
Die...
Shut the gates! - Yes. sir
Go after them!
Tarzan? Tarzan?
I'm right over here, Die-Hard, Come over quick!
Jump in!
What are you doing in there?
We'll rush out together
The car's block ed, how can we get out?
Look around!
Y es!
It's so foggy I can't see!
Just shut up and look  around
Found it?
No, cant find anything!
What?
Excuse me. sorry!
This is no good!
What are you doing out here?
We gotta run!
Stay there!
Are you there? Die-Hard!
Understood, come here...
You're playing trick s on me?
I dare you to come over
Beat him up...
Come over here!
Get him!
Get him. Die-Hard! Q.uickly!
Nice one. good pose!
I told you to beat him up
Get him!
I'm not telling you to let him get to you!
Hot  I'm burning here!
Why did you get merciful?
No!
Are you that useless?
I told you to go get him
Don't hit me
Hit you?!
Hit yourself
No!
I'm gonna faint.
Only you?
Tarzan's in danger, Go help him
Help!
Go to hell!
No
I didn't know I can kick  this well
I'll kick  you to death
K,ick you hard...
No!
Wai, fight me if you got what it tak es
Don't bully the weak  and meager
Haven't get enough yet?
Wow. nice. Powerful!
It's so hot!
I don't get it,
Why didn't you fight back until he beat you up so badly?
You must be k idding me Would I let him beat me to a bloody pulp?
Ok, I'll turn off the stove for you
Take your time to get him
Why did it go down. Damn
Sorry, I got it wrong
What the hell, it's getting lower and lower
What are you doing? It's so hot!
Y es, it's so hot
I'll go next door to cool down
Nice!
You're here so soon!
You'd better go!
This one is easy to knock down
I'm easy to knock down?
You must have never tried my kick s
Die-Hard!
Run!
Here you go again
Don't worry! Hand this one over to me
Really?
It's show time!
Tarzan!
Don't hit me!
Die-Hard!
That was fast
Don't look, R un!
Supernatural power?!
Hurry up!
Tarzan! Why are you going that way?
Not that way, this way!
Hurry up!
Tarzan. why are you going that way. this way!
Be quick
That's so fast!
Hey. why are you coming back  and forth?
You're driving me nuts. I'm not playing
Hurry up!
Freeze!
Are you scared?!
Die-Hard...
Just find a place to hide and stop trying to be the hero
There he is!
Get him down!
Go to hell!
I'll keep that in mind!
Hurry up!
Don't run!
Shit, where's the phone?
Crap! See? I told you that it's safest to stay in the car
Go!
What a big crowd. Guaranteed victory here!
Over there,
Run! Chase after 'em!
Go!
Hurry up!
Yes!
Over there! Go...
I'll go first,
I'll go first
You're going?! The hell with you!
Go!
He can fly?
Tarzan?
Go or we're dead,
Run. Die-Hard!
Tarzan!
Tarzan... Tarzan...
100km per hour
Seat belts on and the passenger shall be fine
Are you alright?
I've got my seat belt on  I'm fine!
You and I are going to fight and see who's better
I can't. Wai, you go and fight him,
Do you really need to go this far?
Go!
Weapons?
Just run! I'll see just how far you can run
Die-Hard. where are you?
It's block ed
There's two of them
One can fight. one can't
This one can fight or not? - What do you think?
He's a fighter
Wai, he's not Die-Hard, He's someone else
Dare to fight me?
Wai, fight me if you have guts,
Dodge!
The feeling's here, Get him
Hit him, turn around and hit him hard
Kick.. Kick him...
Kick, not that side, the other side
Like this
Get him down!
Not me!
They're both fighters
Hey. open the door
Can you tell me who I am?
You're Y au Ma. who else do you think  you are?
I'm Yau Ma? But how come I can fight?
Just shut up and open the door. Open the door!
Where's Tarzan?
Should be in the car
Freeze!
Two of them? - One
One?! - You've got blurred vision!
Blurred?
Really? Squat down!
There's two of them!
Yau Ma!
Where? Where's the seat belt?
300km per hour
passengers don't have their seat belts on
Sorry! You're sure to die!
The flower's so fine -Thank you
What is tak ing him so long to arrive?
I'm longing to see the resemblance of Yau
I wish he's our son
Yes, I wish that too
But you should remain calm and avoid fainting
Got it!
Dad. Mom still haven't seen Die-Hard
I wonder where he's gone to
Mr, Ma, this is a letter for you.
Congratulations, Mr. And Mrs, Ma
Thanks so much
You two should take a rest
I'll be right over -Sure...
Die-Hard wrote this letter and left it for me
I'd never thought I'll have my family this soon
This is way too challenging for me
So I'm gonna hold it up for a bit
Take care of those two girls
I'm handing them over to you
See you later!
Dad and Mom
I think we have to cancel the wedding
Cancel?!
I'm going to go look for Die-Hard
Yau Ma!
Over there
Yau - Mr. Ma...
Yau Ma!
Die-Hard
Where are you going?
You've brought a lot of people out here
Big twin, little twin
Don't faint!
Dad! Dad!
Now what?
Of course, we run!
They're gone,
Die-Hard!
Yau Ma!
Don't run! Come back!
They're completely identical
You're Die-Hard? You're Yau Ma?
Who is who?
It's you!
What should we do now?
Just grab one
Sure!
That'll do?