The Jiawu Year autumn auction of...
Bat Island begins now. Lights off, please
Mr. Bat. Please...
The auction begins now.
The first transaction is from room no. 4
The client is a monk from Japan.
What would you like to buy?
I want the head of Chu Liu-hsiang.
I never realized it'd take 3 more days...
from Holy Water Palace to the mainland.
The fog has been quite heavy today
What's this place?
I've no idea.
A house over there. Let's check it out.
Looks like there's a big banquet here.
Where're the people?
These people from shaolin, Beggars'...
Gang and Mount Zhongnan,
are all famous in boxers' world.
Why did they all die here?
This monk looks weird.
Why's he in such a colorful attire?!
One of his arm and leg were broken.
Hey look
Who are you?
No, first tell me who you are!
Who am I?
Don't you know who you are?
I can't recall
I don't know who I am
Frankly I can't remember
strange. Who the hell am I?
Why did I come here?
Right. I need to go to the Bat Island.
I need to go to Bat Island.
Bat Island is a mysterious place.
I've heard of it before.
How about you, Chu Liu-hsiang?
Heard of it?
Bat Island! It does sound familiar
At simin villa, didn't we...
see a monk in colorful clothes?
Right!
Was he already dead?
Please have a seat.
Master, did you die already?
Why do you ask me such a question?
Because I did see your dead body.
What are you doing?
Tell me where did I die?
Who killed me?
What the hell is this?
If you were killed,
you should have seen the killer.
The fact is...
he has a twin brother.
They look and dress the same.
Both are handicapped too, but one...
on the left and other on the right.
They're known as the Ruin Brothers.
The younger one was recently killed.
He is looking for the murderer.
His younger brother was killed,
but we didn't kill him.
Why would I trust you?
Who are you?
I don't seek your trust.
But standing right in front of you...
is the world famous Chu Liu-hsiang.
Chu Liu-hsiang?
You're Master Hsiang!
Nice to meet you.
You're...
I'm Li Yuhan, my wife Liu Wumin.
The whole thing was just a
misunderstanding
Honey, look...
Excuse me. I've to leave now.
Look...
Who is she?
Master Fumei
Did you get it wrong?
No, I didn't.
Let's rent a boat to check it out.
Strange... I heard
he withdrew from the boxers' world.
Why does he show up again?
Look at the boat he just took.
Get us over there quick.
Why was the boat all burnt up?
Looks like we're late.
Do you think what happened was strange?
12 people were killed at simin villa.
The skillful boxer in white clothes...
couldn't recall his identity and...
the mysterious youngster in white hair!
Most important of all, Master Fumei...
appeared and now suddenly vanishes!
Something must've happened
in boxers' world.
I share the same view.
Help!
Wumin, hold on.
It's very painful!
Waiter, get me some wine.
Okay.
It's you, Li. What's the matter?
My wife just isn't feeling good
all of a sudden
It occurs frequently and causes much pain
I want some wine to mix medicine for her
sir, the wine is here.
Thanks.
Excuse me...
The dinner and drinks are all served
strange. I mean, they both staying here!
Who cares? I've touched the red clothes,
black and white clothes.
2 more green clothes is no big deal.
Come on, try it.
Hold it
Do you pour wine with your right hand?
Yes, I do.
When we came back...
the wine pot was placed like this.
But when you pour wine,
the pot becomes in this position
Then...
After we left for a while,
someone had moved the pot.
Right.
Don't drink it.
I've already had a sip
Master Hsiang.
Who are you?
Your skill is remarkable...
as very few can resist 10 attacks from me
But I feel strange.
You're not going to kill me,
but just to keep me here.
Your real purpose is to kill Master Hsiang
After all you're not stupid, huh
But it's too late to realize it.
What? You're still alive?
I knew the wine pot was wrongly placed
When I drank,
I had poured the wine here.
Why did you kill him?
He fought with you two.
I think he mustn't be a good man.
It's because of this,
I've many questions to ask him.
What?
Someone wants to assassinate Master Hsiang.
So I've killed him.
What? How would he dare to kill Hsiang?
He must be crazy.
Li, is this precious sword...
the ancient, long-Iost Cangshan sword?
This sword was lost for years.
How did you get it?
Have you heard of the Jade villa?
Yes, of course.
Jade villa is where the no. 1 swordsman...
Li Guanyu keeps his precious swords.
Li Guanyu is my father.
If you're interested,
please come and visit my place.
We've collected many precious swords.
Appreciating precious swords...
always gives me immense pleasure.
Yi Tien-hung, will you join me?
I'm tired of dealing with swords.
Besides, I've things to do
Please excuse me.
From here,
it's already the domain of Jade villa
Brilliant
If it interests you,
you may take a look wherever you please
We'd have to leave to arrange for the meals
okay...
over there is our home
Please...
Master Hsiang, here you are
This place is beautiful.
This is where my father tested the swords.
Mr. Li was really a swords lover.
He deserved being the no. 1 swordsman.
My father valued the swords a great deal.
He took interest in everything
related to swords
But before he died,
he had an unfulfilled wish.
What's the wish?
My father studied...
every kind of sword fight
He had not invented an invincible
sword troop.
He devoted his life for swords...
and invented Wuhan sword array.
But still it hasn't been proved...
if it's invincible.
How come?
Because no one tried this sword formation
The person must be the best fighter.
Also he has to be quite reknown
Then the result will become outstanding
Master Hsiang
is the only qualified boxer...
in the world.
So you and your wife tried your best...
to ensure bringing me here
This is your sword.
Seems like I don't have a choice today
Please...
I think Mr. Li's wish wasn't to do a test...
but to kill me.
Why do you say so?
If there's no defeat in the sword troop,
I'd die here immediately
Even if there's a defeat,
with 5 skillful swordsmen attacking me,
I'll be surely dead.
At the Liufu Inn,
it already felt strange, as to...
why'd someone kill the man in black!
Li Yuhan, what's wrong?
Don't ask anymore.
We just want to kill you.
Your father's sword troop is really good
Looks like Chu Liu-hsiang can't...
defeat the sword troop.
Don't move.
For 15 years I've been admiring the...
greatness of your Yuanyang swords.
My pleasure fighting against you today.
How did you recognize me?
When playing with 2 swords,
a person uses: : :
Only one; the other hand always
forms a fist.
For someone using just a single sword,
the fingers of his other hand are
usually out.
This is your habit I'm employing, sir...
Handing you a sword all of a sudden
I think you will understand.
This sword array can't have
one sword less...
and of course can't have one more.
Chu Liu-hsiang is really good.
Priest Tieshan, Gentlemen sword and
Bamboo sword, all of you...
are top swordsmen from righteous schools
No wonder you all cover face with a mask
What actually have I done to offend you?
Why did you have to kill me?
We didn't intend to kill you,
but to pay our debts. Li's family...
has only one son for 3 generations
Mrs. Li was pregnant,
but she has a special disease, which can...
only be cured by the poppy from India
But the poppy seller asked for your life
save the only son of an old friend...
Hold it.
Li, Master Hsiang defeated the formation...
and didn't try to kill us.
Now you repay his goodness.
We can't do these kind of immoral things.
Lacking filial devotion is a great sin.
You see, I can't afford caring too much.
Why are you blocking me, sir?
Priest Tieshan, can you bear...
watching Li's family terminated?
Where's the justice if I let you go?
Hereafter how can I face
my Wutang students?
But you can't refuse to pay
my father's debt
okay.
Priest...
Chu Liu-hsiang
I'm not able to save with my broken arm.
Owing to such a person like Priest Tieshan,
the word 'justice' still lives on
What are you waiting for?
Thank you, sir.
Wumin, what are you doing?
Yuhan, forget it.
What Priest Tieshan said is right.
The Li family can't do wrong things.
But your illness...
I'm a nobody in the boxers' world.
Nothing to compare with hsiang's life.
After my death, I request you to re-marry
Please forgive him, master hsiang.
What he did was because of me.
What we owed you,
we'd pay you back in next life.
You saved my life.
How can I...
let you die for nothing?
Tell me...
where can I buy the poppy from India?
Bat Island.
Bat Island is a recent...
uprising triad organisation
It's known that if you've money,
you can buy drugs, life or...
even the secrets of the boxers' world.
Who heads that gang?
Someone called Mr. Bat.
He's an extremely good fighter.
But no one knows who he is
Why?
When they conduct a deal, no lights are on.
So, no one ever sees...
his real face.
How can I go to the Bat Island?
I don't know.
Why doesn't anyone ever ask us?
What? Aren't we people?
You didn't ask us.
My dearest Miss song and Miss Li,
I, Chu Liu-hsiang,
ask you how I can reach the island.
The Queen lost a pearl waist-belt lately
The Invisible Thief Zhu Tong has stolen it
He can sell the things stolen from...
the King at Bat Island.
Say, If I had to go to Bat Island,
I'd rather find the Invisible Thief first.
Right.
I know whoever goes there needs a mark.
Li Yuhan has given me the mark.
But I don't know how...
I can get in touch with the people there.
I know the one who stole the belt...
has arrived at the Qinhuai River.
What kind of a person is he?
Simple. He must look like a thief.
Please come in...
Please be seated
The Invisible Thief...
does indeed look like a thief!
Come on.
Brother, I'm not a bad guy.
I just want to ask you a few questions.
Mute buddy, come in quick.
Strange... why does this house...
float to the middle of the sea?
Why is there a big house here?
How can it move?
Why does my house move towards it?
What is this place?
You don't need to know.
I don't know you.
Why did you try to kill me?
That's the reason I have to kill you.
Before you kill me, can you tell me why...
this small house is drawn
toward the big one?
Because under the house,
there's a long rope pulling it.
I see.
Who's the master of the big house?
Mr. Bat of Bat Island.
So they go to Bat Island from here.
None of your business.
You've not told me who you are
In case you kill me later,
I can at least tell...
the Hell Master who sent me there.
You know,
it'll be so embarrassing if I can't
You're a funny man. I'm Xiang Feitian,
keeper of the 78th branch of the Island
Everyone going to the Island...
will be taken care of by me.
Take care of what?
If you're a guest, I'll escort you through
If not, I'll kill you.
How do you know I'm not a guest?
Because I haven't seen you before.
But you did meet my master.
Who might he be?
Li Yuhan of Jade villa.
In which category is he registered?
Yu category.
- What does he want to buy?
- Poppy.
Proof?
You are our guest.
Guests from the 3rd stop have arrived
Which category you registered at 3rd stop?
Di category.
Gongsun Jiemin...
Yes, it's me
Guests from 5th stop arrived.
Mr. Long registered with Xuan.
Here's the proof
Mr. Long Wu, what's the matter?
You brought along 2 servants.
Yes. They've been taking care of me...
since my birth
But the boat fee is very expensive.
The money is here.
Okay, let's go.
Please...
- Please
- Please...
What do you want?
I'm trying to help you.
Thanks.
Please...
Boatsman, please.
Everyone is here.
All are here.
Take them inside first.
Let them check in their rooms.
Please...
This way.
Lady, please.
Please...
Yi Tien-hung.
Why are you here?
I'm on business.
I've someone to kill.
After you had gone, I got a letter...
saying I'd get 1 million taels of gold...
to kill someone.
So I followed the address to meet a man.
The man brought me here and
told me that...
the man I need to kill is on the Island
What? Kill someone on the Island? Who?
No idea. What I do know is just that...
the man has a very special thing.
According to the pigeon's note,
boats from the 24 branches were gone.
The guests going to Bat Island this time
Guests on our boat...
were all checked.
All were checked.
There's a filial lady in Tian room.
She's on her way to the Island...
because she wants to buy her father back
she said he was confined on the island.
The dumb man is her loyal servant,
staying by her side forever.
The guest at Di room...
is a wealthy boxer.
He goes to the Island...
to buy something precious.
The guest at Xuan room...
Iooks like a man from a wealthy family.
But I know he's a royal guard.
Maybe he's investigating...
the case of the Queen's lost pearl.
The guest at Wang room;
um... he's kind of mysterious!
He didn't say a word.
He just gave me 10 pearls and asked...
to hide on the Island for a few years
Looks like he could be the one...
who stole the Queen's pearl.
A letter from headquarters is here.
This isn't right.
The letter says there's a spy on the boat
Mr. Bat asked us to bring his body back
6 will be enough.
The same old way...
Kill everyone the headquarter wants.
Do it tomorrow.
Who?
It's me.
You...
Why are you looking for me stealthily?
Follow me.
Yesterday night...
I heard they said...
they'd kill all of us.
Who are you?
I'm Jin Linzhi.
My dad specializes in building houses.
5 years ago, my dad was given a contract
After that, he didn't came back.
I found out he's captured at the Island
so I'm going along with my servant...
to the bat island.
I have to save my dad
Master Hsiang, I must go to the Island.
I can't let them kill me.
Quiet... Miss Jin.
First, you don't know who they will kill
second, you don't know when...
they will do it.
I know. They said this morning.
Maybe someone has been killed already
I never thought he'd be killed first.
The one hiding behind the door
is the keeper of this boat.
I want to know who's the officious one.
This morning I found the boatsman...
lying dead on the bed.
Someone broke his artery last night.
Even though he was a good boxer...
he's killed by someone.
Why not?
Or else why did he die?
I think there'll be more people here...
Help...
Who killed them?
I don't know.
When I brought them meals,
they're already dead on the ground.
And 2 of them are standing there.
We heard the sound of fighting...
and came over.
Did you see anyone going there?
No.
Why do you want to kill me?
To keep your mouth shut as you're the...
only one who knows I killed the guard.
You're wrong.
When I came in this morning...
and saw you standing there,
I just suspected.
Not until now did I realize
you're the killer.
What's the matter?
He wants to kill me.
Why?
You'd better ask him.
What's going on?
He killed someone.
Strange.
We just came up here from the cabin.
Who killed him?
Sir, are you still...
going to kill to keep the secret?
Why do you want to keep the secret?
You're afraid he'd arrest you.
Since the one who was killed...
is a royal guard,
and you're the well-known
Invisible Thief...
who stole the Queen's pearl.
What? One more person has been killed?
Ought to be 1 more person here. But where?
One more people? Who?
The one who has killed the one in white...
and kills the old man now.
Besides that person is a very good boxer.
Where's he?
Look...
I know he's a very good boxer.
He killed. No one could resist him.
What? The boat owner wasn't dead yet.
Not only that, but...
the two men were killed by him.
Right.
By doing so, you'd overlook him...
and it'd be the best way to kill.
Why did he try to kill us?
Headquarter mentioned there're spies
on the boat
Because the King has ordered...
the best royal guard to
arrest Mr. Bat.
The officious Master Hsiang...
is also on the boat.
So the owner planned to kill...
all people on the boat.
Where's the boat owner now?
As you guys found out the fact, he'd
gone back to the Island on another boat.
Bullshit.
Xiang Feitian, you're wrong.
How could you kill us all?
Mr. Bat never...
does things in a wrong way.
Don't you see the candle?
What's wrong with it?
When it's gone,
the boat will be blown off...
and you'll be dead in the sea.
Holy...!
The dynamite must be under the candle.
Hurry up. Go inside and help.
Go inside quick.
Hurry up.
I never thought sitting and floating in...
a coffin would be
more relaxing than on a boat
Yi Tien-hung,
we're in the middle of the sea
The shore is out of sight. What'd we do?
Did they prepare the coffin for you?
The night sea breeze is really cool.
There is a boat over there
Why are the people drifting in the sea?
Sir, there're many people drifting...
in coffins.
Then save them immediately.
Put the rope down.
Please...
Please
Please forgive my ignorance.
Not at all. Thanks for saving us.
We'll feel embarrassed...
if you still blame yourself.
It's my honor...
to be of little help to you.
Please make yourself comfortable.
Sir, the meal is served
Please be seated
Young master became blind
when he was small
Do forgive us for any mistake
due to oversight
Ladies and gentlemen, I'd like to...
drink first to show my respects
Please...
I know Master Hsiang is a wine conossieur
Is the wine good enough for you?
How do you know he's Chu Liu-hsiang?
I was informed of 5 people
getting off the boat.
But I only heard footsteps of four
In the boxers' world, only Master Hsiang...
can land without making a sound.
To kill with ease...
Yi Tien-hung
I raise a toast to you.
How do you know he's Yi Tien-hung?
The 2 heroes busting the Holy Water Palace
Can anyone not be shocked by it?
To walk and sit side by side with Hsiang
It must be the Hero Yi Tien-hung.
Please
Though your eye-sight isn't very good,
you do see much better than many of us.
Thanks. The others are...
- I'm Jin Linzhi.
- I'm Gou Zicheng.
Mr. Gou and Miss Jin, please...
Please...
Why did you drift in the sea?
A long story...
our boat had an accident.
Right. I'd have asked...
how I should address you.
I'm Yuan suiyun.
Your surname isn't a common one.
Where's your hometown?
I come from Guanzhong.
It's a famous boxer's family.
Wuzheng villa is also the biggest villa.
I wonder if Master Yuan...
is from your family?
He's my father.
He's not only a very rich man, but also...
a reputed man in the boxers' world.
The title of his villa was given...
by other famous boxers
It meant among the boxers,
no one can compare to him.
Is he really skillful at fighting?
But he passed away 3 years ago.
I heard this young master...
has been a genius since he's a child.
He's good at fighting and also at academics
And he's of a generous character.
The boxers' world said...
Master Fumei of Huashan school is a hermit
But she and Mr. Yuan of Wuzheng villa...
had two sons.
Right. Master Fumei...
and Mr. Yuan are proud parents of 2 boys.
Fumei took away the elder son.
The younger one was left to Yuan.
What's the trouble between them?
Women are always unreasonable.
Come in
My lord invites you
to partake refreshments...
on the deck.
Thanks.
Please...
The meal is here.
Thanks
Master Fumei...
strange. Didn't they...
drown at the Qinhuai River?
How come they are here?
As such this already is a strange boat
Let's have the meals first.
The guests I serve give me trouble.
They've several meals a day.
Mine too. She takes medicine very often.
I know the poppy is very expensive.
It's only from India.
Yes.
Here's your medicine.
Thanks.
Let's have the meal first.
Come on.
Was he the man in white who...
Iost his memory at the simin villa?
Strange. Why is he here?
Don't move and make no sound.
It's you. Did you see that?
Follow me.
Mr. And Mrs. Li, Master Fumei,
the Man in White and Dingfeng.
What are they doing on the boat?
Didn't you think...
they're going to Bat Island on this boat?
Is this boat going to Bat Island?
How can it?
Wucheng villa is a reputed family.
What are they doing at Bat Island?
The young master Yuan...
was threatened by the one in white hair
The boat will go to Bat Island definitely
The boat is heading towards Carp Island.
Strange. Who the hell are you?
Why do you know each & every detail...
of everything?
I'm me, a person heading for Bat Island.
Look like, at last...
we'll be going to Bat Island
since we can only find the answers
for our questions there.
But this boat will go to Carp Island first
sir, we find the golden carps here.
Then get it up now.
Yes.
It can be only found near Carp Island.
It tastes very good.
That's the reason I've brought my boat here
The fish is coming.
Hurry up.
How come it's a man?
Sir, we fished...
4 naked women.
Dead or alive?
They don't have any breath,
but their hearts are still beating.
Maybe they've just passed out
Get them to Tian room now.
Ask Mrs. Nan to go there.
Yes
Where do they come from?
How could they get into the net?
Hurry up. Get them into the room.
Madam, their heartbeats have stopped.
Sir asked you to save them immediately.
Get out... immediately.
What the hell are they doing?
Master...
sir, big trouble!
The 4 girls killed madam.
What?
The Heart Pluck Hand!
True, Master killed them before she died.
Who are these girls?
I don't know.
Master Hsiang, do you know?
Someone ordered them to kill the master
The one must be a very good fighter,
and a powerful man.
From Bat Island?
We're heading there right now.
We must not go to bed tonight.
I need to unlock 6 body points.
Don't move. I'm here to save you.
Who asked you to come?
Your mother, Master Fumei.
How do you know I'm his son?
I happen to be her student Gao Yanan.
Follow me to the small boat over there.
Master Hsiang, something is wrong.
Our boat has stopped.
Run.
The boat is in a cave.
Hurry. Go up and look
No need. I've been there.
No one is there.
No need to go down.
No one's down there.
Mr. And Mrs. Li aren't there.
No one's in the house.
The body of Master Fumei is also gone.
Where's Mr. Yuan?
Stop. It's a friend.
Mr. Li, we're looking for you.
Why are you here?
Mr. Yuan of Wuchang villa...
invited us to the Carp Island.
But she felt sick once boarding the boat
We didn't leave the cabin at all.
You didn't know we're on the boat.
I knew many friends boarding the boat,
but I didn't know it's you.
Where is Mr. Yuan?
Have no idea
When I noticed that the boat has stopped,
he wasn't there anymore.
Did the one in red take him away?
The drug is really strong.
Even I with a stuffy nose have passed out.
What is this place?
When we woke up,
we're already hung here.
There's a Black Iron
which is the hardest thing in the world
No matter how powerful you are,
you can't break it.
Look...
Look at this valley
there's only a single door out.
Let's think of a way out of this cage.
We've a Gold sword at Jade villa.
It can break iron like paper.
I wonder if it could
break this Black Iron too
We now get into the water and swim there
Hold it.
Mr. Bat won't use only a...
cage made of Black Iron
to trap the reputed Master Hsiang
and Yi Tien-hung.
I know of a certain kind of acid...
that can melt anything.
I'm afraid this is an acid pool.
Yes, it's an acid pool.
How can I get to the exit?
There's a fire over there.
We can climb over there,
but Miss Jin mightn't be able to do it.
There's only one way out.
It'll be like hanging food one by one.
Only food could be hung on the wire!
Would the wire bear the weight of people?
I've here the Magic silk Wire,
the most pliable but strongest material
I tighten it on this precious blade...
and fling it there.
So we may climb on it to reach there.
Was this wire the ancient treasure...
used by Master Tianyi
at the last Huashan Meeting?
How could you know?
I also know that this wire belongs to...
the top royal guard now.
I presume you're not Gao Zicheng,
but the top royal guard ou Zhancheng.
How can you know all details?
Because I was paid to kill a royal...
guard who carries the Magic Wire.
Are you really a man...
who will do anything for money?
I was and I will be.
Maybe not today.
But don't forget; I'll kill you anytime.
Okay?
Okay
Is this strong enough?
Yes, but I'm afraid...
the blade didn't stick deep enough.
Master Hsiang, if I fall,
you think of another way.
Mr. Ou, let me go first.
No, the wire is mine.
Now you guys may come up here.
Mr. Li and Mrs. Li, please...
Wumin...
Miss Jin, please...
No, I'm scared.
The wire is so thin...
one on another. Very hard to keep balance
Let me help you.
Mrs. Li, please look if someone is outside.
Hold tight and give him your hand.
Yi Tien-hung. Get her.
Got it.
Be careful. No need to fear.
Be careful. Take it slowly.
Maybe not today.
But don't forget. I'll kill you anytime.
Okay. We're all over here.
You take the wire back now.
Let's go outside.
Tell me. Where are the prisoners?
This is the prison?
Yes.
Go.
Why is no one here?
Did the guard lie to us?
No. My dad usually constructs...
according to Eight Diagrams
...and constellation.
If I'm not wrong,
there'll be a trap inside.
This is the door of life
Dad? Where are you?
Linzhi...
Dad...
Lord...
something happened in the prison.
Is the safety gate on?
It's on already.
It's all right then
Let's finish them after the auction.
Yes.
Hurry up.
Don't run... It's dangerous ahead.
It's an abyss.
Don't run in disorder
How can we get out of here?
It's a cave there.
It's the only exit.
It leads to the seaside.
You get out of here yourself.
Walk slowly. Don't fall.
Kid, let's go.
Hold it, sir.
Please show me the way to...
the Bat Hall.
Why are you going there?
Because I need to catch Mr. Bat.
I've also promised my friend that I need...
to buy medicine for him.
I've never been caught by anyone.
I'm curious as to who'd want to catch me.
And you?
It is a rule of Jade villa.
If our friends are...
in danger,
we can't leave them alone.
The road is dangerous.
Why?
When I built this Bat Road,
I had looked through the place.
These caves are dangerous.
Either abysses or black oil grounds
Look at the fire.
It's burnt from the black oil.
You've to pass through these...
dead caves to the Bat Hall.
Maybe...
all of us will die and
can't make to the Hall.
Tell me the way.
I'll go there alone.
No. Let's go together.
You've saved my life.
I'm going too.
Come with me.
I never expected it to burn to the end
What is it?
The Black oils are all over the place,
especially in this cave.
When will this fire be put out?
The Black oil comes out endlessly.
It'll never be put out.
Another way to go?
No. I designed these caves.
Do you see the red rock?
I put it there.
This is the only way to Bat Hall.
Take the red rock out and climb over.
How can we pass through the broad fire?
On both sides of the cave,
there's no space to step on.
It's no use even if you can step on it.
The fire burns so fiercely...
The rock must be hot like hell.
Sir, I must go over there.
There's only one way.
Someone goes down and blocks the...
Black oil from the hole.
But the one...
Mr. Bat is the bane of the boxers' world
I created these wrong things.
It should have been me to go down.
But if I died,
no one could show you the way.
Linzhi doesn't know martial art.
She's not able to find the hole.
So it'd be wrong of me to ask you to go.
No, sir
Let me do it
No need. He brought me up.
This is my Jin family's business.
Let me do it.
Mute buddy
God bless you.
What's your name? I'll tell the King...
who will give you credit.
The cave is right under the red rock.
- Brother Mute...
- Linzhi...
I never thought it'd again be a dead-end
Why?
Do you see the 2 ice pillars there?
3 years ago, I tried to blow a hole...
to escape from here.
The day when I was going to blow it,
they caught me.
Later I thought
other prisoners had blown it.
I never imagined
they wouldn't have done it
sir...
We got no way to the Hall.
We've to make our way back.
Where's the dynamite you placed?
Good... it's still there.
The fuse is gone though
We could use our clothes.
The icy air here is humid.
Ordinary clothes can't make it.
What can I do?
Only one way. Using a person as the lead.
And we need two
I've figured it out.
There're two strength points in this cave
Look...
Right under the two ice pillars.
To blow off the cave, the 2 dynamites...
must set off at the same time.
But when it sets off, these two people...
Master Hsiang, can you get my daughter...
and me to the ice pillars?
First, you've to be well versed
in martial arts
second, to go to the Bat Hall...
is what all five of us intend to do.
Nothing to you two.
5 sticks here. 2 short and 3 long.
One who picks the long one will light fire.
Me first.
Mine is short and yours is long.
Yours is short too. Why?
Because I'm a royal guard.
To fight crimes is my duty.
I must be one of them.
But after I've died,
please do a favour for me.
Use this silk Wire to...
tie Mr. Bat up for the King.
Why me?
You know I'll do it only for money
That's why. I want to let you know...
apart from money, you've got to do...
things for other reasons as well
This is the last request of my life.
This world is so strange!
I came here because I was to kill you.
That's life.
The feelings between people change...
in accordance with different situations
But you've to promise me
use the silk Wire to tie Mr. Bat up.
Who's the other one?
Yuhan, you must stay alive.
We're not going to the Hall.
Let's head back.
Wumin...
Just now we said that...
the people of Jade villa will stay
with friends forever.
But you're the only son for 3 generations
You can't die here.
If so, it's destined...
that my family will be ended here.
Don't come over.
This concerns Jade villa.
Why do you hit my points?
Yuhan, when I was seriously sick,
did you say you'll agree with...
whatever I do?
Yes.
I'll light the fire for you.
Sir...
When we blow off the cave,
You hit them at the 5th joint of...
their backbones
and they'll be able to move again.
I know
Mrs. Li,
do you have any words for your spouse?
No
Mrs. Li, please...
Mr. Ou, please...
The people will appreciate your sacrifice
I'm going
Follow me.
Mr. Li...
The hand of Master Xinghu is the next.
The head of the governor of 8 provinces
The secret book of 5 Tigers school.
Ready?
Ready
The weapons of Chu and his friends here.
Something's wrong at the prison.
You better be careful.
While leaving the gate,
remember to dispose it off
sure
We change their clothes immediately...
and go to the Hall.
Xinghu's hand and governor's head
The secret book of 5 Tigers school.
Prepare your money for these items
Tian Zhi Hou.
Who are you?
Li Yuhan of Jade villa...
Yi Tien-hung
I'm Chu Liu-hsiang.
We're here just to take on Mr. Bat
Please leave the hall.
How could you escape from there?
As your luck is gone.
Hold it.
You're too weak...
to fight with these 3 heroes
and the guests in the 2 rooms.
May I ask who you are?
Master Fumei.
Who are you?
Brother of Wuhua,
Monk Wugan from Japan
I tried to buy your head last year.
Hsiang's reputation isn't a bluff. Bye.
Let me take care of my family matter.
Master Fumei, didn't...
Did you die on the boat?
No. I just discovered someone...
hiring a killer to get rid of me.
So I pretended to be dead first.
Suiyun, do you know who was after my life?
Suiyun
How did you know it's me?
Of course
Because I'm your mom and you're my son.
What?
20 years ago, I left your father...
with your elder brother.
I asked Mr. And Mrs. Shandong to...
bring him up and I rested secretly
in Huashan.
I thought I could avoid the trouble.
But 20 years later, I heard of the...
Bat Island jeopardizing the boxers' world
Your brother sent me a letter...
telling me that Mr. Bat could be you.
I asked him to gather righteous boxers
at simin villa, but they're all killed.
Your brother became mentally retarded
I was almost killed when showing up again
suiyun, didn't you do all of this?
Mom, how can you say such a thing?
I'm your son. How could...
I try to kill you and my brother?
Are you alright, mom?
I'm alright.
Hand over this rascal to me.
Well, what do you have to say?
You humiliated the Wuchang villa...
and the Yuan's family.
Brother, listen to me. I...
shut up. Go talk to mom.
Stop. Why?
Why did you and him have to...
meddle in my affairs?
I was separated from you for 20 years.
You didn't raise me.
Even I didn't know you
You must be really eager to know...
why I became the Mr. Bat.
Coz my family's reputation is too good.
No matter how good I'm in martial art,
I'm the only heir to Wuchang villa;
the only son of my father.
Who ever knows...
I'm the most powerful Yuan suiyun
only by doing things
completely different from you guys
can catch your attention that
there's a blind man better than you.
Only by doing so,
I can avenge...
the unfairness of my destiny.
What's unfair to you?
Why was I an abandoned son?
Why was I blind?
Who are you?
How dare you grab my sword?
If I don't dare, I'm not Yi Tien-hung
Children, put out the fire and leave.
Start the traps.
Have you heard that...
in a dark place,
the blind is the most powerful.
It's because you can't see how I attack,
but I can hear where you are.
You don't see a single thing now.
But there's a thing you can see.
That's the road to hell!
Mr. Yuan...
Now you may regret
that you're too officious.
Okay. No more kidding.
From now on,
I'll kill all of you one by one.
Let me see which one would I start with...!
Kill the officious Chu Liu-hsiang first.
Mr. Bat.
Why don't you kill me first?
Aren't you scared of me, Yi Tien-hung?
What? I afraid of you?
Okay. Lemme spare Hsiang for a while.
I'll kill Yi Tien-hung first.
These attacks are really lethal.
What? Is Yi Tien-hung dead?
How would I die?
I was just hurt in the arm.
I'm going to kill you, Mr. Bat.
One arm will be enough.
Really? But you don't know where I am
No matter how good you fight...
You are going to die.
It's hard to attack without seeing him.
Next time when you deal with me,
bring more candles.
But you wouldn't get a second chance,
would you!
How can they see my hands?
Do they hear...
the sound of pearl on my body?
So you've the most priceless treasure
the Pearl of south sea.
It's a pity that you've only one pearl.
You don't have another one.
From now on,
the next battle will take you to hell.
Mr. Li
Master Hsiang...
If you get a chance,
take my dead body back to the ice cave
so that I can stay with Wumin forever.
The most lethal attack of
Black Devil school
to kill you with your own sword.
I'll take your weapons...
and kill you with them.
Mr. Yuan...
suiyun, how are you?
Hsiang is the only one left now.
Suiyun...
What's he doing?
He promised a deceased friend that,
come what may;
he will tie Mr. Bat's body up...
to hand over to the King.