***新视界论坛制作***
制作人：Sxmyf(翻译&校对)
--------------------------
本字幕所有权益归制作人所有
纯属翻译爱好者交流学习使用
谢绝他用，否则一切后果自负
--------------------------
Mr. Lee
Crystal called you twice this morning
and asked you to return her call
Mr. Albert from London, Mr. Kay from
New York
and Mr. Short from Geneva would like
to have a conference with you
shall l call them now?
Daniel
l know, the market has slide down over
400 points
Sell all of 2137
2137?
Yes, 2137
Mr. Lee, don't forget to call Crystal
Got it
Although the South East Asian Financial
crisis
seems to be extending
l don't think it will affect Hong Kong
Shit
l've tried to reach you for three days
the stock declined over 500 points
and you're here fiddling your shoes?
What can l do?
l believe that HK won't be affected
we have a foreign exchange reserve of
90 billion US dollars
we're world's number three
Of course you are going to be
the Asian Sores
Sores
Sores?
No thanks, l'll leave that for your dad
Me? l just want to hold his daughter
You're a Nobody and you want me to
marry you?
We are World's third in terms of
foreign exchange reserve
we have over 90 billion US dollars
we have a very healthy economic
structure
moreover, we have the full backup of
the China market.
l'm worried that the drop will affect our
investments in South East Asia
l understand, Mr. Albert,
but l can guarantee that everything will
be fine
Then l have to trust you, but if/.,;'/.,;'/.,;'
Excuse me, please hold on
The morning market will be closed
in 15 minutes
but it has declined 713 points already
and with the full backup from
the China market
Clear all of 3006
Because we have 90 billion US dollars
as foreign exchange reserve
The Government won't let the market fall
any further
Let's hold on for a while
we shall be able to sell once there's
a profit margin
Buy 3005 for all of my accounts
What are you thinking? Come on! Go!
The Commissioner of Finance once
mentioned that the crash would probably
be over around Christmas
By that time, l believe the Hang Seng
lndex will re-bounce to the level of
18,000 points
We lost fifty million dollars
There's nothing to live for/.,;'/.,;'/.,;'
l agree
l wish that someone rich will take care of
this baby
Your mom must be crazy
How would someone rich adopt you?
The baby!
l'm sorry
ls he all right?
Not very good
His body temperature and blood
pressure are very low
How can you be so careless?
Adopting a child?
So you've already cleared up the mess
in the company?
Just picked up a baby back and be his
adopted father?
Wanna check your blood pressure, Miss
lt's free
Next time then
Ming, You come to see me?
Ming
Ming, l'm going to treat you and Wing
with dessert tonight
You want to take advantage of him again
What advantage?
Wing said you always take advantage
of others
But l'm making your favorite green bean
dessert
Don't you like it?
l like
So you'll bring Wing with you tonight
for dessert, OK
OK
See you then
Bye
Watch your steps
OK
Lan, didn't l tell you not to set
your stall here?
They can charge you on blocking
the road
Sir Lung, You don't go and warn those
money-making stalls at the back
but to complain about me who is doing
free social services?
The Hawker's Control Team will take
care of them
but affecting road order is my
responsibility, don't you see?
Just in case some stupid guy drives a
vehicle down and hit you
l can't bear that responsibility if anything
happens to you
You spooky mouth! Who would want
you to be responsible?
l don't mean that, just move a hit
Ming, Come and touch my mahjong for
luck
Where's Wing?
He's not back yet, just wait for a while
Want a popsicle, Ming
No, Thank you
No, thank you
Put this back for me
Go and play
ls it really so difficult for a fresh grad to
get a job now?
lt's no good to have our neighbors
seeing you.
sitting here all day doing nothing
Get a job
lt's not that difficult to get a job, sister
but it's hard to find a job which you
really enjoy
don't you understand?
What do you like to do? l'll help you
Wing is back
Let's eat
You're not finishing this round?
Thanks
Let me help you
How's your luck today?
lt's too late, my pockets are emptied
already
Take it easy, man
l'm leaving
Bye
Fatty
Wing
Lan asked us to go over to have dessert
tonight
Really? She wants to take advantage
of me again?
This is what l told her too
Did you really say that?
Done
Wing, please fix those hanging hooks
in the kitchen too
Didn't you fix them yesterday?
You did! They're so useful
So l bought three more today, thanks
This one is for Chuen, go and get your
own in the kitchen
O.K. l'll help himself
Sir Lung?
l'm sorry
but your boxes outside blocked the fire
exit
l thought these are concerns of the
Fire Department
Well, in case of any accident, it will be
too late
When l'm out on the road, you said
l'm blocking the road
when l'm home, you said l'm blocking
the fire exit
Are you picking on me
lt's nothing like that
The new Fire Ordinance
it's illegal to block the fire exit
And besides, so many elderly living at
your place
if the Fire Department discovers this
they'll charge you on illegal running an
elderly home
l'll help you to bring them in
No thanks, l'll do it myself
Want some dessert?
lt's all finished, l didn't expect you
Next time then
Jogging?
Keeping fit
Next time then
l'm teaching you this today: No problem
No, problem, low/.,;'/.,;'/.,;' paul/.,;'/.,;'/.,;' pump
What is no problem?
OK
l'll teach you another phrase: no good
Don't stay so close to the TV, it's bad
for your eyes
Come, let's sit here
Tell me what you are watching?
l hereby on behalf of the committee of
the Children's Hope Project
would like to thank the support of all
the kind donors
l'm now in Shanghai and cannot attend
this Charity show in Hong Kong
which reminds me that our organization
might have neglected a lot of friends
around us
l would like to take this opportunity
on behalf of my former husband's
organization
donate 100 million Hong Kong dollars
to help those in need in Hong Kong
We'll consider any kind of proposals
Thank you
Thank you Mrs. Leung
Dear Audience
if you do have a kind heart like
Mrs. Leung
think carefully how you would like to
help those children
Yes, and then send a proposal to us
Yes, thank you
Thank you Mrs. Leung
Thank you for joining us, good-bye
Okay
Thanks for the job well done
Thank you
Mrs. Leung, the orphanage which you
supported at Putin
will be celebrating their 2nd anniversary
next month
the children has rehearsed some
programs for you
they hope you can come and join them
Excuse me, Mrs. Lee
Mrs. Leung has a business trip to US
next month
We'll see, OK
No problem, of course work comes first
we can arrange in the future
l should leave you to rest now, good-bye
l'm sorry, bye
Welcome Mrs. Leung! Welcome
Don't
Please go out
Mrs. Leung is tired
Please go away
Please
Are you all right? Mrs. Leung?
Mrs. Leung, let's go out for dinner,
and relax/.,;'/.,;'/.,;'
l don't want to go anywhere
l just want to go back Hong Kong
tomorrow morning
You want to see Dr. Chung?
l'll arrange an appointment
Or, do you want to try other doctors?
l think l'll be scared of children for the
rest of my life
Whatever l do is useless
lt's very difficult for me to mix with kids
Don't feel so bad
Things may get better
Thank you
You go back and rest now, l'm fine
Don't stay up too late then
We can have a bigger sitting area here
if l knock down the room at the back
Knock down that room?
Wing, take this
Here?
Okay
Are you sure?
You said there's lot of stuff left from your
husband inside there
and you wanna knock the room down
if not, there won't be enough space for
the children's home
Ten and a half feet
Ten and a half times twelve feet should
be big enough
Think twice
No need
These two years, the elderly has gone
one by one
most of them have gone to 'the other side
of the world''
This neighborhood has a lot of children
wandering around
a children's home can take care of them
Over, Over! Ming forgets his clothes
Are you there? Wing?
l don't know where your clothes are
go get yourself
Wing! He's still a baby, you asked him
to get it himself?
He's four and still a baby?
Then l'm thirty something baby
How can you ask me to do so much?
Wing! Come over! Wing
Now what?
Hold this for me, l want to measure this
area
5 feet
You're not wearing your slippers again
Your feet will looks like frog's feet when
you grow up
Wing! l want to build a wall downstairs
to separate the elderly and the children's
home
Good
And here, will be the children's bathroom
Here?!
l'll get it! l'll get it
You go then
Let's move on, Lan, what else?
You're still not wearing your slippers
l know, l know
So why don't you buy me more
Hello Wing? lt's Wah
l'm Ming
Anyway
tell Wing to go to Deep Water Bay
Dockyard to work this Saturday
Saturday
Don't forget
l won't
Bye
Wah asked you to go to work this Sat
at the Deep Water Bay Dockyard
OK, Mark my appointment for me
No problem, Lan l'll write the proposal
for you
Wing, if the plan succeeded
Ming can bath at my place
OK, Ok, l get it
You'd better rest now
Wing! You must make a good proposal
Ok, l will
Ming, go to be early after your bath, bye
Say good-bye
Good-bye
Thanks, Wing
You're hurting him
l'm playing with him
You're only a four years old baby
and you're not ready for this
My usual treat! Please
Only Ming and do it
So comfy
Wing, l want to buy a popsicle
You're thirsty
Come back soon
OK
Hey, You're looking for someone?
Are you that lady on TV?
You're in the wrong place, please go!
l don't have time to play with you,
please go back
Excuse me, did you see a kid around?
This tall?
No
Thanks
Fatty
Does it hurt?
No
What's your name?
Ming, four years old
You were with your mother?
l don't have a mother
Oh! l've got to go! Bye
Hey kid! Why are you here?
Mrs. Leung, are you Ok
How can they just have these kids
wandering around
You, did you make a mess at the boat?
No
l know you won't tell me
but if you'll do this again
You'll not only hurt your hand but your
foot as well
OK! Done
What's that?
You took advantage of me again
The fish is mine
You're right! Just to remind you not to
trust people so easily
Have a bit more
You're full?
Full
Full! Ok, now wipe your mouth!
go to sleep
Go ahead, l'll still got work to do
What?
Again
OK, just two phrases
This one's better! This one
Thank you
Sir Lung
lt's raining like shit, come on over
Ming
This grumpy rain
You look busy today, running back and
forth
lf you sell umbrellas here, people will
complaint
You've been working with the Hawkers'
Control Team
l'm responsible for maintaining road
order
Just in case someone stupid drives
a vehicle down and hit you
l can't take the responsibility
OK/.,;'/.,;'/.,;'
l'm not asking you to leave, just be
careful
l will
Hey, Wing
What?
Why aren't Lan measuring people's
blood pressure these few days?
She's sick! Why don't you go and
see her?
lt's not serious, is it?
Quite
lt's just that l didn't see her around
Got to go and work
Go and see her
Send my regards to Lan
All right!
Lan is ill, you go and see her
l know, Ming, good boy
Watch the umbrellas, let's have fun/.,;'/.,;'/.,;'
Let me do it
See
Umbrellas
l thought giving my child to someone rich
he'll be happier
and then l can start all over again
but finally understand that
losing someone close is even more
painful than being poor
l've tried very hard
and l still can't find my own child
and then l got this fear
l can't get close to kids
but, it's strange
l'm not afraid of Ming
l was a bit scare at the very beginning
but then afterwards, l'm fine
maybe it's because l was helping with
his wounds, distracted
l think it's a good start
you begin to open up yourself to others
not only children, but other people
as well
l believe this is the only way that
can heal your psychological fear
l've got something for you
New medication
No
l've brought this movie for you,
a children movie
you'll watch it before you go to sleep
tonight
and you'll let me know in the morning
Whether you can sleep or not, or
nightmare? OK
Thank you
l'm leaving now
l'll see you to the door
Thanks
Thank you, Doctor Jones
Oh yes, you have been torturing yourself
for four years
Whatever you have done wrong in
the past, should more or less be justified
Take care, good-bye
Mrs. Leung, we've received eight
proposals today
This one is quite interesting, take a look
Changing a elderly home to children's
home?
Playing with fire is very dangerous
You may burn someone, yourself
or even a whole house if you're not
careful, you know that
There're many other fun things to play
with the fire
Give me the candle! Give it to me
And you, what's that in your pocket?
Cigarettes?
Give it to me
Why don't you play yo-yo when you
have one?
Give it to me
Did you steal this?
No
Let me teach you how to play this
Bring the dog out
Baby's cradle
Around the world
Here the top one, Extravaganza
Play yo-yo and not fire, OK
Go now, or l'll spat you
Watch the cars
l'm sorry, Miss,
did they hurt you?
l'm fine
May l ask you where is this Lan's
Elderly Home?
At the back, over there
Thank you!
Let me show you the way! lt's difficult
to find
Sorry about the trouble
You're from somewhere?
l came from Shanghai
You're very tall
Who are you looking for at the Lan's?
No, my uncle wants to find
an elderly home
l hope you don't mind me being nosy
the place actually can't be taken as an
elderly home, there's no facilities
Lan is a kind person
but now can she take care of so many
elderly on her own
Just taking care of their meals would
have killed her
Your uncle should go somewhere else
Excuse me, who is Lan?
Lan is a kind-hearted person, she had a
pitiable past
Her parents passed away when she was
small, she married when she just got
over twenty
but then her husband died a few years
later
Leaving her nothing but this old flat and
its rent to live on
Lan always says, she didn't take up her
responsibility as a daughter when she
was young
and now she runs this elderly home
to compensate her fault
You seem to know her very well
You're a good friend of hers?
l've been patrolling this area for a long
time, it's just something l heard
9466, 9466 roger?
9466, send
6th floor, 24 Sring Alley
an old man has fainted, go check it out
9466 will go now
lt's Lan's place
What happen? Sir?
Lan, is there somewhere quiet that l can
take the witness report with you?
Somewhere quiet? lt's a small place here
come to my room
OK
Don't touch anything
An old man goes 'home'!
Someone's dead and you're so happy?
l don't want you to feel sad
Everything is fine, l've got to work
Go back and take a rest
Play mahjong
Lan, this is Miss Wong, she's some to
see you
Miss Wong, Sir Lung has told me about
you
But l don't encourage those who don't
take care of their own elderly
The situation is, my uncle's family has
emigrated
l've got a resident here who takes care
of my elderly affairs
Why don't you have leave your name
and phone number
l'll ask him to call you back
Are you looking for Wing?
Yes, we are looking for Wing
You're so smart, Ming
Bring this lady to Wing, will you?
Sure
Really?
Smart kid
Lan, who is it this time?
The schoolmaster! This room
A bit small, but quite clean and tidy
Sir Lung, are you here to do the report
or renting a room?
The report, of course
lD please
Wong Mei Lan
What's the name of the schoolmaster?
Cheung Chi Choi
Cheung spelt as C H E U N G?
Yes
Lan
besides residents here
is there any man who would come here?
What does that have to do with this?
Someone's dead here, it's just routine
question
Wing whom lives upstairs?
Wing? He has already got a kid
What do you want to know?
Just asking
Why are you ill? What's wrong?
l'm fine, it's just flu, thanks
Are you from the northe rn region?
Yes
Do you speak Mandarin?
l was born in Hong Kong
Any other question? Done?
Almost
Lan, you've got to see a doctor when
you're ill
Try Chinese medicine
Thank you
l'll see you off
Ming, you're not taking care of your
guest
go get a popsicle for the lady
Orange Flavor?
No thanks, Ming
lt's delicious, l'll get it for you
Am l bothering you with your work?
Of course not, just daily stuff
Ming/.,;'/.,;'/.,;' is very cute
Does Wing always leave Ming behind
like this
Just let him wander around?
Actually, l think, Ming really needs a
mother
Don't you think so?
Are you a vegetarian?
Your skin looks very soft and smooth
lt's for the lady
Which lady?
Kwan
Oh yes, Lan asked Ming to bring her to
see you
She's taking advantage of me again
My name is Wong, l/.,;'/.,;'/.,;'
Daniel Lee, where are you going?
East and West Road
Great
Yours, thank you
lt's my uncle
Let's walk back while you talk
Registered mail, yours
She's pretty
Quite a good match
Too tall
lf she is changing it to children's home
l don't think she'll take in any more
elderly
l think you'd better find another place for
your uncle
Thanks anyway
Ming
Who's in 3A
l know, fatty Cheung
OK, go
Ming's mother has gone to work?
She left him behind when he's only a few
months old
Cold blooded
lf there's a children's home here
then kids like Ming would be better off
Not really
Taking care children doesn't mean only
literally taking care of them
You need to have a loving heart, time
Are you married?
Yes
Got kids?
Not yet
Well, when you have kids
come see me then, l'll teach you
l'd better go
Keep in touch, bye
Bye
Stop fussing
lt's over a thousand dollars, we don't
have the money
Let's go
What did you say just now?
You're only a 4 years old baby
who taught you to talk like that?
Look who's talking?
How dare you
Kid, don't try to behave like an adult
You'll regret when you grow up
Ming
Look at your shoestring
Come, sit down
Didn't Wing teach you how to tie your
shoestring?
For whom?
For Lan
Lan took advantage of you?
No! it's a gift for Lan
What's this?
Orchid bulbs, will grow orchid flowers!
How?
Lan knows how!
Bring this to her for me
Let's be partner
l'm making money, in the way you taught
me
You're good with foreign exchange
Piece of cake
easier than stocks
Don't be so serious! lt's just a game
You were not like that
l knew how to act then
l still have a kid to take care of
lf you come back and work
you can earn at least a hundred thousand
dollars per month
You can hire over ten Philippine maids
to look after him
lt's not like that
Fine
think carefully, call me any time
Cheers
What's up? What are you celebrating?
Wing, Wing, cheers
This suits, l wear for my company
He got a job at last
U-grade should bet a job with a suit
There's no future just sitting in shop
A man is a man
lt's a temp! For the time being!
What do you mean by temp? lt's a job
Let's eat
Wing, you've got letters
Letters?
Seems like some good news for Lan's
children's home
Yes!
And this?
Nosy body, l'm not telling you
Sir Lung, you're looking for me?
Where's Ming?
You're looking for Ming?
Seems like he's not back yet!
Mind didn't come today?
Probably not yet
Let him come back first, Ming
Ming
Sir Lung
Did you give it to Lan?
Sure! The orchid bulbs
What orchid bulbs? Those are water
lily bulbs
lt's too early for them; it's not Chinese
New Year yet
Oh? They are water lily bulbs
Bye now
Wait, wait
These flowerpot and soil, also suitable
lilies
Thank you!
Lan, the Foundation has a letter for you
They want to see you
Really?
But l'm ill/.,;'/.,;'/.,;'
OK, OK! lt's me anyway
Thanks, Wing
You'd better rest more, you're still so ill
lt's not getting better
Thanks again, Wing
Whoever loses the race will wash
the dishes
One, two, three
l know l'd promised you the beach
but l've to do something important first
l'll come back and fetch you afterwards
OK?
OK!
l'll be back soon, OK
OK
Wait for me, bye
Bye
Mr. Lee, please come in, Mrs. Leung
is expecting you
Come in, please sit down
l'm sorry about last time
l didn't explain clearly
lt's OK, you're only disguising to see
the truth
Here's the cheque
ls Lan's name correct?
lf not, l can write another one
There shouldn't be any problem
Actually, you've only see Lan once
what makes you believe in us?
When doing charity, one can't be so
calculative
l know she's sincere
Here are some documents, l need you
to fill in them
They're for lnland Revenue and Social
Welfare
No problem
Then Ming won't have to wander around
anymore?
That may not be so
you know, l travel a lot for work
and he has to follow me
Mrs. Leung, the security says that
this child was playing around downstairs
on his own
Wing
Thank you, lvy
Why are you here
That uncle brought me here
Brought you here
You brought him here and you left him
downstairs?
l didn't bring him, he follows me
Didn't l ask you to wait for me at home?
Did you promise to bring Ming to the
beach?
Wanna join us?
l don't know how to swim
We are not swimming
l want to show him something uncommon
lt's cloudy
Why were you so angry just now
Because of the sky, there're cloud
Why does that matter?
l'm not telling you
Actually, l think Ming needs another
l did whatever a mother do to a child
only except breast-feeding
To him, l'm both father and mother
Actually l don't think you are the kind of
person who does temp work
who can just let days by
l think you belong to Central
l know what you mean
l did that
Did what?
l did what you think l should do
Funds
Really?
Funds manager, the best
So, what can you say about life
But l do believe
as long as you don't give up, you'll
survive anyhow
Survive anyhow?
You heard of the crash
lt's just one afternoon, know how much
l lost?
Survive some how?
That's how you lost all your money?
Not my money, it's my clients' money
lf l'll have to pack back all the monies
a few more lifetime couldn't even be
possible
As for my money
l gave them all to my woman
Then you must love her very much
At that time, l thought she loves me more
than l do to her
She later found that
l wasn't the kind of man that she likes
Just like that
You're still young
You can start all over, anything will do
Besides, you've got Ming with you
Maybe it's because l lost someone whom
l wanna love
here comes someone who wanna me to
love
ls that right?
Right
Burn more candles
Since then
whenever l can't sleep at night, l look at
the sky
That's why l started to fall in love
watching stars
Shooting stars
Really?
They are so beautiful
Yes so short-lived
Not really
lt's because they are so short-lived
that's why you find them brilliant and
beautiful
You're pretty too
but can you guarantee that you can be as
pretty life long?
Can you forever rely on makeup?
Let me tell you
l'm angry today because it's cloudy
and we can't see the shooting stars
Really? Where?
Northeast side
Then l can make a lot of wishes
See how greedy you are
l'm not greedy
Since you like stars so much
have you ever considered studying
astrology?
Have you heard of Greenwich?
Yes
That Observatory
They offered me a job there
Really?
Congratulations
When are you going then?
l don't know yet
Their living conditions
doesn't allow me to bring anybody along
That's impossible
Actually, l can get someone to take care
of Ming
He can then grow up in a better
environment
and you can go to do what you like
Let me think about it
Thanks for offering
See, shooting stars
lt's beautiful
lt's started
Ming can you see?
lt's beautiful
What is it?
Cigarette? Show me
Superman
Where did you get this?
l just found it up there
Up there?
Don't play with fire anymore, superman
is fine
What a big mess?
Are we having a war?
Wing, how about this?
We've got lots already, and it's so dirty
Find something else
This book is much better
Sir Lung, just moved out, see if anything
suitable
Did you have the consent of the owner?
Can't be bothered! lt's not the first time
You go and take a look too
Wing, come out
What is it? Sir Lung
We never discriminate on what job a
person is doing
as long as he is earning with his own
ability
that he is not stealing from someone, right?
What do you want to say?
l hope you don't mind
l just thought whatever you do is fine
but Ming is only four years old
He has still got a long way to go
You shouldn't let him get used to
growing up amongst all these rubbish
and still feeling happy about it
Those kids, if their parents haven't been
working
they wouldn't let them to play around in
the rubbish
You should understand what l mean
Wing, you wanted feelings in things
you do
But Ming needs a future
Understand
Wing
Where did you find this?
l found it down there
So this is my company, all you can see
Good morning, Mr. Leung
You'll use this room for time being
Piece of cake
Let's go shopping after lunch, OK
Sam
Thanks
Mr. Lee, l'm Eva,
just page me if you need me
Thank you
Eva
Daniel
We can put aside some food for Wing
Come on, let's eat
Ming
Wing
You're home
Mr. Lee, l'm lvy, Mrs. Leung's assistant
l met you at the office a few days ago
l've brought the contract for Lan to sign
and she told me to show you first
Ming was alone and there was nothing
to eat
l'm sorry to have taken so much of
your time
lt's OK, l called Mrs. Leung
she asked me to stay behind
Ming's hungry, Why don't you have
dinner first
l'm leaving
Wait a minute
Ming, can you tell this lady
Have l ever ignore you
and leave you with no dinner
lgnore me, no, without dinner, yes
l just remember that l have to go back
to the office
These stuff are too heavy
Bye now
Mrs. Leung
Kwan
Oh you're back
lvy told me that Ming has been waiting
for you for a whole day
l need to work for living , Miss lvy
Money just doesn't come running into
the house itself
But still you shouldn't leave a 4 years
old child at home alone
Don't you know that it's illegal
l know you wanted to be with the child
but a child need someone who can take
care of him
why don't you consider about sending
him to boarding school?
lt's OK, thank you
We're fine
Fine?
He doesn't even know how to take care
of a kid
l don't?
l've been taking care of him for 4 years
He's very happy
Only for the time being
Taking care of children is not only
making them happy
lt's not that difficult to make a child
happy
l agree
Really?
OK, Ming
You'll bring him away for 1 or 2 days
try taking care of him
and try to make him happy
Deal, just wait and see
How is it?
Let's watch TV
Shall we sleep early so that we can get
up early tomorrow and go out to play
l can't sleep so early
Don't be so boring?
Let's watch the stars
What shall l do, Dr. Chung?
You should relax and play with him
Play what?
l've no toys here
lt doesn't matter
ask him what he wants to play
use some imagination
a child can hold a pillow and think that
it's an airplane
This is a good opportunity to deal with
your fear
Call me if you need me
Thank you
Mrs. Leung, Maybe l bring Ming back
to my place tonight
Just the two of you?
l'll bring Ming out tomorrow
Where's Ming
We were watching stars just now
l'll go check there
No, he's not here
Ming, you scared me to death
l'm sorry, shouldn't have let the kid to
run around
lt's Ok, it's usual that a kid lost his way
What is this?
Don't touch other people's thing
Come on
What is it? l wanna know
Use to talk with other uncles here
Good night! Mrs. Leung
Excuse me,
There's something l'd like to discuss with
you
Sir Lung
looking for Lan?
Can you give this to Lan for me
What's it?
lt's fertilizer, for the lilies
Wing, tell Lan to try a few more doctors
Some doctors nowadays are not so
ethical
Why don't you tell her yourself
You know why
Got to go, thanks
Bye
Wing? lt's you?
Looking for Sir Lung?
He's gone
He gave you this fertilizer
He left so soon
Can l use your phone?
You must have forgotten the bill and have
your line disconnected
Brother Wah, it's wing
Any jobs these few days?
Remember to call me. OK
Hello, Brother Cha, it's Wing
Any boat that need to scrape the shells?
l'm available if you need me
Hello, Miss May, it's Wing
The one who delivers clothes
do you need someone to deliver your
clothes?
You didn't like it here?
You come out first, l'm tired
ls Ming missing his father?
Are you?
Wing was so fierce
Has him been like that before?
No
Maybe he's unhappy
Has Ming been unhappy before?
When l'm unhappy
Wing would try to make me happy again
How did he do it?
He sang to me
That's it, Wing would sing to Ming
Would Ming sing to him too?
Wing doesn't want me to sing!
He said l sang like a pig
and scared away everyone
You don't have to sing
You can be good and listen to him
Really?
lf you listen to me, l'll be very happy too
lf l'll listen to you and be good
will you tell Wing about it?
Ming
Look, Ming, let's go on board
Wing, Ming is going to steer the ship
lf you steer like this, all the people will die
To make a child happy is really not that
difficult
l'm sorry, l've bought him too much one
time
You just want to make him happy
Actually, Ming makes me happy
These two days there were the happiest
days l ever had
There's something l want to discuss with
you
didn't you say that you want go to
Greenwich
Maybe you can let Ming stay with me
then you can go and do what you can to
do
At the president suite
l can buy a house
somewhere close to you
l'm serious
l really like Ming a lot
why don't you think about it
You'd better rest, bye
Bye
Give it to us
You wan to rob me
Come on, one, two, three
Look! They're back
Stop
lt's mine
Watch out
l've over ten years' driving experience
Tell me, who would look at the bottom
of car before driving?
What is it? What happened? Don't
quarrel
Sir Lung, you're right on time
This guy almost hit Lok
Luckily, it's just a few scratches only
Ming
Wing
Are you OK?
Wing, keep your eyes on Ming
You're not even doing the father's job
Everything is fine now
Hey, you've almost got me in trouble
Would you still dare to run around like
this
No
Would you dare not listening to me
lf ever l left you
would you dare following me?
Yes
Really?
Really
Do you know where Wing wants to go?
To the homes of the stars
Where's the home of the stars
There?
Yes
What's the name of that star?
l don't know
That is called BUULUU BUULUU star
What about that one?
That one is poo-poo star
So dirty
l'm telling you, that one over there
it's called Fartty star
What's that one?
Superman star
Wing
He may be out
l'm/.,;'/.,;'/.,;' l'm sorry
You're so early
Please come in
Let me introduce
This is the representative from the
Education Department
This one's from Social Welfare
and this lady is from the District Office
l brought them here because they can
help you to apply for the Government aid
funds
They can also find a school for Ming
Miss, what was that you just mentioned?
Daily Living Aid for single family
That's it
But you got to be co-operative
What's your name?
Lee
Yes, Lee Siu Wing
Mr. Lee, how old is your son?
Four, just about to apply for school
What's your profession?
He's just a temp worker, no steady job
nor steady income
ls it him or you who is applying?
lt's him, l'm just helping
Mr. Lee, you should fundamental be
qualified
in addition to the kid's car accident
yesterday
you have a good case to appeal
please fill in all these forms first
You've got it wrong, l don't need any
help
l've got my hands and feet
l don't need any help
Even if you don't, Ming does
l've been thinking in your shoes
lt won't get you and Ming anywhere the
way you are
Of course you've the choice to reject our
help
but since we've opened the file
You have to fill in a rejection form
for our record
Good, let me have a copy of that form
How long have you been living in HK?
Does this child have a birth certificate?
l'd like to have a look
Hey, you people are so troublesome
For the sake of Ming
it's not trouble at all
Excuse me
Chan Kai Ming
l'm here
You're up
Did you wee-wee?
Not yet
Wee-wee first, you
Chan Chi Chiu
You're not his father
Adopted father
Where's your proof that you can adopt
this kid?
Read the back, it says clearly
He just picked him back
lt's clear
lllegal adoption, we've work to do here
What do you mean by illegal adoption
Didn't you say that you are going to help
him to apply for government aid?
And find a school for the child
That's another case
We have to deal with the legal matter
first
Colleagues, please prepare a report
have one cc to my senior
and then we'll decide whether we'll
charge this Mr. Lee here
Let's bring the kid to the Children
Protection Unit
Don't do this
What did you say? Don't you touch
the kid
You can't take him away
Don't stop us from work
You may apply to adopt him
come to my office and fill in a form
Go away, to hell with your office
Mr. Lee, please understand that we have
the right and responsibility to do this
We're just doing our job
Leave alone, l just want my kid back
Please calm down, Mr. Lee
Go away
Just suppose that l didn't approach you
guys
You'd better leave, you'll regret if you
don't
You can't give him a future
Why do you hit me?
Let's go, don't scare the child
Give me back the birth certificate
lf you have guts, don't go away
l'm not going anywhere, l'll wait for you
Go away, and stop talking
Don't be scared
Wing, l just wanted to help
l understand
l really wanted to help
Go away
l'd really meant to help
Police
Come with me, there's someone
kidnapping
Don't you dare to seize an officer
Show me your lD
Dear sir,
Go upstairs, faster, go
Ming, will you listen to me?
Yes
Do what l told you to do, go down to
Lan and wait for me there
lt may take a while when these people
bring me somewhere
l can't bring you there, do you understand
Understand
Also, don't tell anyone what happened
OK
Go now, Go
Hurry up
Bye, go
Open the door
Somebody is complaining that you are
illegally keeping Ming
Mind the head
Let's find the kid first
Ming is not your son?
Sir, don't just chat, we're here to work
Hey you, Can't you see that l'm
investigating
Lee Siu Wing, where is Chan Kai Ming
now? Ming?
He's scared by them, and ran away
You have scared him away
You may search for awhile
if you can't find him, then we'll have to
leave
lt's possible, How can such a small kid
run away so fast
We'll search carefully
Sir, is this how you called investigation?
Just like this?
l don't need you to tell me what to do
Wing, if you see Ming you'll inform this
officer here
Give him your card, he needs to contact
you
Let's make things easier
Sir
Now what?
l want to charge him for hurting me
l wanted a wound examination
Seems that he really dislikes you
Would you come with me to the Police
Station?
Let's go
Bring your lD
These young people nowadays
they just don't have any manner
Ming, what's up?
Wing asked me to wait for him here
Lan is very ill
Ming, ask Wing
To bring Sir Lung to see me
Ming, be good
listen to me
ask Wing to bring Sir Lung to see
There's no proof that he illegally adopted
the kid
Beside, his family didn't approach us for
help
Even now, the kid is missing
Give me some time
l'm sure l can find his parents
l can prove that he illegally adopted the
kid
You have to detain him
l want to charge him, he hit me
Lung, you'll do a report for him
He wanted to charge the guy for hitting
him
What? lt's just casual body contacts
You know these officers, you go and talk
to him
Officer, it's just casual body contacts
You're nor hurt
Just don't make a big thing out of it,
drop it
l can't
You know this kid may continuously be
ill treated
You're a policeman
you should know that prompt action is
needed
in order to help people?
You think you can really help
Chan Kai Ming?
l may be at home quite late tonight
Can you take care of Ming for me?
l'm Shanghai now
What about Lan?
Lan is ill,telephone no respond
Did something happen?
Nothing, it's Ok
well then, Bye
Bye then
Then l'll trust you to handle the charity
matters, Chairman Cheung
See you later
Stop ahead
Mrs. Leung
Wait a minute
Do you know that child over there?
Leave me alone
What is it?
No matter what is the reason
if you leave someone who has your
same blood behind
you would regret for life
This is from my own experience, it's true
l don't know why, lvy
l'm really worried about Ming
Something must have happened
l think, l'll go back to HK tomorrow
What about your meeting with the Mayor
l'll make other arrangements
OK, let's go
Start the car
What is it? Ming?
Uncle Chan, did Wing call back?
What?
Nothing, nothing
Lan, Lan, did Wing call back?
Ming, be quiet,
Lan is sick, she needs to rest
Wing, can you hear me?
Where are you? Come back, Wing
l forgot my clothes, Wing
Wing, l forgot my clothes, can you get
them for me?
lf you need me, call me
Anytime
Keep in touch
Bye
Ming
Fartty
fartty
Far/.,;'/.,;'/.,;'
Wing
You lied, you said you'd be back soon
l tried
Are you hungry?
Starving
Let's tidy up, then we'll go eat, OK?
Ok
lt stinks, Brush your teeth
l'm going to the location now
lt's you again
Are you the only policeman in this area
What do you mean?
Who called the police?
l did, Sergeant
There's someone kidnapping upstairs
come with me
You'll stare here
Yan, call the station to inform other
colleagues
No. 24,rooftop,Spring Wind Alley, roger
Sir, hurry up
They're at the roof, Hurry
Stand still, don't run
Hurry up, hurry, hurry
Don't run
What are you doing?
Open the door
Attention, a suspect, Chinese male,
age 30 to 40, medium height
wearing a brown jacket, shorts, and
sandals
holding a 4 years old kid
last appearance, Causeway Bay
Don't say anything. Can't you see
that l'm busy?
Step aside, you're blocking my way
Go
Sir Lung, Sir Lung/.,;'/.,;'/.,;'
What is it?
You're here on time. lt's Lan
We are now waiting at the location
with ClD
we'll report with further information
Over
ls it this one?
Madam, what is it?
What happened?
Someone reported a child being
kidnapped here
Why are you here?
l've come to see a friend
May l take a look at the birth certificate
304267, 2 in bracket
Wong Mei Lan
female, 42 years old
nothing suspicious here, roger
ls it done?
Almost
OK, now let's count together
Five, four, three two one
There's nothing
What? Look carefully
Wow, a big burning cake
Which we can't eat
Here, you can eat this one
Next year, when l have money
l'll buy you a birthday cake as big as
that
which we can eat. All right?
All right
Let's have this one now
close your eyes, make a wish
Are you done? Ming?
Not yet
How many wishes have you got?
OK
Hey, what wish did you make?
Aren't you telling me?
Sir Lung
Ming, Happy Birthday
Lan has gone
Lan has gone to the other side of
the world
These few years, actually
l've been trying to find opportunities
to talk to her
but every time, we either ended up
getting nowhere, or quarreling
Such regrets
We didn't have even a chance
for hearty talk
How long have you known Lan?
We've quarreled for a few years
while l got this badge here
The first few years, l only dare watching
her from a distance
Life is so unpredictable
Let me tell you
l've applied to transfer to work
at another district
Why?
Lan is no longer here
l don't care about the order of
the area any more
What about us?
Yes, l'm selfish
For my whole life, l don't know
what l really like
and now, l don't even know
what to live for
For yourself
l don't know how to convince you
But there's always a tomorrow
after today
Think about it
lf everyone is like you
we'll have a happier world
You're right
There'll be fewer people committing
suicide
Educated person really talks differently
Of course
By the way, the whole police station
is looking for you
Why?
Do you remember, that lady?
The tall one, the one who's been
to your place?
She's the legitimate mother of Ming
Those writings behind the birth
certificate
she wrote them 4 years ago
Did she call the police?
No, it's that Welfare officer
He said he wanted to follow up the case
ln fact finding an excuse to get Ming
back to his mother
She left him behind 4 years ago
l know, l know you are very close
to Ming
Ming likes you a lot too
But when in the court
the priority is always with the mother
l don't know how to deal with these
complicated sentimental matters
Good luck
Although Ming is my own child
l don't know how to explain to him
that his mother left him behind
and didn't want him
To literally live with someone for 4 years
is not a short period
if l'm going to take Ming back now
l'm afraid that l might be hurting him
even more
l don't want to be wrong again
l've already arranged to have you
and Ming
What have you arranged?
You left him four years ago
said you had an excuse
but if you are going to leave him
again now
you are definitely inhuman
l have been living with Ming for
four years
but still , l am not his father
l think Ming will be happier to stay
with you
Much happier
You can do it
Think about it
Give me a ring then
lt's hot
lt's broken here
No, it's not. Eat
lt's broken
l thought you like sausages
l do
You're going to bring ''Short-sighted''
only?
What about ''lcy''?
''lcy'' will keep you company
Keep me company?
All right. Be careful, it's hot
Delicious?
Yes
lt's hot, did you boil it?
Listen
When you go to your mom's place
you have to be as good as you are here
l know
You really do?
Yep
Want some egg?
Want
lt's cold
l don't want it to burn you
Burn me?
Hurry up. When we finished eating
we'll go to wait for your mom, OK
Hold this
You! You just never tie your shoes
You have to learn to tie the shoestrings
properly
you're old enough to know how
Hear me?
This is the fish he likes. Call mom
Mom
My dear child
lt's getting dark, you'd better go
Ming
Keep in touch