--==本字幕由 新浪微博@纸巾老湿eric 荣誉出品==--
更多精彩字幕 请关注 新浪微博@纸巾老湿eric
Metal screams...
something hits me square in the chest...
there's no up or down...
I don't weigh a thing...
I don't remember a thing.
This doesn't look good at all,
I've gotta done something again.
Wish I could remember what.
How did I get here,
what have I done,
and why.
I must have forgotten my medicine.
I've got a condition.
It's bad to forget your medicine
when you got a condition.
Covers up with bullets,
the wound is fresh.
Maybe an hour old?
I can't remember how I got it.
And a live on me,
I can't remember.
The Projects...
ugly as ever.
What the hell am I doing here?
Put the pieces together.
Remember.
It's Saturday...
so I must have started the night at Kadie's joint.
Just another Saturday night.
Being all the other losers like me,
sucking back the sauce,
drooling like fools over Nancy.
I wasn't in the mood,
even watching Nancy couldn't cheer me up.
I get that wrath sometimes.
Empty in the gut,
hollow in that lonely place
and wishing I had an excuse to break somebody's face.
It was just another Saturday night.
I was wondering what I was gonna do with myself,
when I smelled something awful.
Burning hair.
Burning meat.
Like this poor old manos didn't have it bad enough already.
Damn frat' boys!
Damn rich spoiled brats!
Leave him be.
Crawl back into your bottle, Bernini boy!
Why did he call me "Bernie"?
At least I know they're bad guys.
Nothing wrong with killing a bunch of them.
Hell, it's practically my civic duty.
Oh, these wormy little twits.
I hate these guys.
God just kill me, please.
They made a run for it.
I did what any good citizen would do.
Go to hell!
What the hell!
That's when I get my idea.
If they got back to the university at Sacred Oaks
I'd never catch them.
I bang them around like a hockey puck,
cut them off at every turn.
I left them no choice but to head over the hill,
to The Project.
I could just turn my back
and leave them here.
My old neighbors will take care of them about good.
But hell,
why should they have all the fun!
The Projects.
I was born here.
My old neighborhood.
Damn, he's a dead man!
I'm telling you, I want beat you a good shot.
And he's a dead man!
My old neighbors.
They let me know they're watching.
I remind them who I'm.
I tell them what to do.
No, no please.
Please, I got money.
I got a trust fund, I can pay.
You'll pay.
Before you shot me, you called me "Bernie",
why did you call me "Bernie"?
Bernini, is a brand name.
That coat you're wearing,
it's a Bernini.
Thanks for clearing that up, kid.
Knife!
Bernini, huh?
That one fine coat it is.
Somebody must have spent a fortune on it.
I wonder who.
And while I'm at it,
where the heck did I get these gloves?
I can't remember for the life of me.
Poker...
savage power...
in gentleman's hands.
It's a good game!
Now,
who wants to play?
Sin City is where you go in with your eyes open
or you don't come out at all.
But the city is like a woman or a casino.
Somebody's gonna win
and it's gonna be me.
It's the kind of place your father doesn't want to talk about.
But where I come from...
father is a thing no one seems to be able to find.
I was feeling lucky.
I won money in joints all over the town.
And I finally made it to Kadie's,
where the real score is.
What happened to the show?
How's trick, stranger?
- Head or tail? - Head.
That's a trick.
That won't get you anywhere.
Follow the shiny object.
Where'd you come from, handsome?
Do me a favor, blow in this.
Does lady luck has a name?
Marcie.
Lucky man!
Every time, ma'am.
And where's the real lies?
Baby, you don't want to know.
I do want to know.
Whatever you say, boss.
Back at the bar,
it's your funeral.
He'll eat you alive back there.
I'm pretty tough to chew.
Come on.
Kiss it this time.
- Hey Marcie, - Yeah?
you want to go make some real money?
Yeah.
I'll check.
I bid a hundred.
Goodnight.
I'll play.
I'll fold.
Who is the slicker?
I busted this one for craps over Jossie once.
Play on, it's okay.
Whatever you do, kid, don't win too much.
I never lose.
What's with bringing a fair lady over here?
That's my good-luck-charm.
Besides I've had made a pretty nice dime tonight.
I gotta have someone to spend it on, right?
Silvio, let our young friend here do the honor, huh?
Cut.
New boy is good!
Nancy, Nancy, Nancy, Nancy!
Nancy, Nancy!
And the dealer will take two.
One hundred.
I'll play.
I'm out.
Yeah, me too.
- I'll fold. - I'm done.
How dumb are you feeling now, boy?
Pretty dumb.
Oh senator, I'm ready for your worst.
Boy, you don't even want to dream about my worst.
No, I don't imagine, I do.
That's why I'm gonna let you flatten your ass right now
and call it a night.
Sure, this is a fair game played by honorable man.
I'm gonna raise you 300.
Easy, kid.
You got any idea what you're up against?
Looks to me like I'm up against a man.
You're up against a Roark.
Yea, I was born here, senator.
I know who you are.
We all die here sooner or later.
I'm gonna raise you another 500.
I like this kid.
I like him a lot!
I'm gonna call you.
You won't be needing anything for cab fare, will you?
Now that's the finest hand you ever gonna have, friend.
You just keep in mind what hands are made out of this.
Will do.
Get your ass outta here, run like hell,
you might still have a chance.
No, I can't miss tomorrow night's game,
not any more than you can, officer.
Besides, I already promised Marcie I don't turn.
I can't protect you.
Then why you a cop?
Where are we going, Johnny?
Everywhere.
One of these days she'll pull the trigger
and then there's nothing I can do.
There's nothing I can do now.
All I can do is ask...
Listen, don't,
don't avenge me, Nancy.
It'll be the death of you.
And I can't help.
I can't watch.
Death is just like life in Sin City.
There's nothing you can do
and love doesn't conquer anything at all.
Good luck, Nancy.
Live well your life.
Just try, sweetheart.
We made Sin City history.
Hit every hot spot in town.
I blow thru' almost as much cash as I made at the table.
The trouble starts when I try to use my credit cards.
I'm sure there must be some mistake.
We'll be happy to extend you a line of credit.
How could all of them go bad in the same night?
It's not like you don't have cash.
That's not the point, come on.
We gotta get you home.
Something comes up behind us.
It smells all wrong.
This will slow us down.
You get to the side, Marcie.
I gotta break some bones.
What are you talking about, you silly.
You just stay right there.
Gentleman, listen. I think I know what this is about,
I want you to know you'd have no resistance from me
and that black jack you got in your hand
could split somebody's skull open.
What the hell was that all about?
You stay out of sight now,
and you'd be safe in old town.
Meet me at the 3 Sheets Hotel.
Room 166.
6...what?
Let's get this over with.
I'm enjoying it too much, wasn't I?
You made a fool of me, boy.
Right in front of the wrong people.
You took your chance like we all did and you lost!
You have any idea how easy I kill little snots like you.
Now, let's see about that winning hand.
Powerful men watched what happened at that table.
I need them to know the price of defiance.
Power is a...fragile thing.
It tolerates no threat.
Defiance must be met with an example of the wages of defiance.
You'd be smart to kill me now.
I'll do far worse than kill you, boy
What you've encountered, boy,
is power.
Everytime the wind blows cold and wet the thing
that was your hand and your two legs and throw you in agony.
Whenever it rains, you'll remember me.
You'll remember me, all the time,
my son.
Oh yeah, I know who you are.
I know you're one of mine the minute I saw you.
Family resemblance, my boy.
But I don't give a damn.
I only have one real son,
Ethan, may he rest in peace..
He could be the president.
Do you really think...
that I was going to claim you?
He beat me rogue,
but when I get back,
it'll be a whole different game.
It's another hot night.
Dry and windless,
the kind that makes people do sweaty,
secret things,
things worth money to me.
This is the last time, Sally.
This gotta be the last time.
You always say that.
I mean it this time!
She glides out of her coat
like it is a Christmas wrapping,
playing it for all it's worth
and it's worth plenty.
This is the end for us.
The end for us?
It's my wife.
She's asking all kinds of questions. She suspects something.
She'll sue and she'll get everything.
Everything!
Everything you've worked so hard for.
I worked my butt off.
I built my business up out of nothing.
Nothing.
Nobody appreciates you, do they, Joey?
Not the way you deserve.
Nobody.
Not employees would be out on the street if it wasn't for me.
Not my wife who I found on the street!
The jewels and mansion you bought her.
Wearing all those clothes that I got her!
With my money! My hard-earned money!
I think you're so strong.
You're damn right about that.
Do I get any credit?
They just take and take and take!
One of these days I'm gonna fire the whole pack of them.
I'm gonna show them who's boss!
Show me, Joey.
Show me who's boss.
Yeah, I'll show you, I'll show you.
I'll show you who's boss.
Then she's moaning.
And saying "boss" the same time with his movements.
It's all over pretty quickly.
I get everything I need.
The sad thing is some of the composition is pretty good.
You make me feel like a woman.
I know it sounds corny but it's true.
I love you, baby.
You know I love you
even when you lie to me.
My wrist hurts, Joey.
You can go get the key, it's just in my purse.
You don't have any idea how much I sacrificed.
What are you doing, Joey?
It's tearing me up how much I love you,
and what I gotta do.
But I worked too hard,
and Lori will get eveything
and I can't let that happen.
I don't have any choice. It's all her fault.
Joey, please...
I won't tell anyone, I swear.
I know you don't wanna talk.
I know that
but you're only human.
Lori is gonna find out about you,
if she doesn't know already.
And she's gonna offer you a lot of money,
my money.
She's gonna give it to you to bring me down!
- I'll go away! - Who's gonna pay for the ticket?
The ticket and God knows what else!
Then the apartment, the clothes, the car.
You're gonna suck me dry
and you'll never, ever stop!
No, please no!
Kill him! Kill him!
Nobody is killing anybody,
not while I'm around.
Then can I have a ride?
I grab the key and uncuff her.
She gives him a goodbye that
will still hurt like hell when he comes to.
I leave the slob handcuffed to the bed
for housekeeping to find.
I take her down over the hill toward old town.
Thanks for my life, man.
Sally blends into the sea of flesh that is old town.
They all come back.
The damn old town memories,
drunken mornings and sweaty sex
and stupid bloody brawls.
and that thing I did.
You can't just pick and choose.
You can't take the good without the bad,
not once you let the monster out.
I can't let it out.
Never again.
I drive 10 blocks out of my way
and stop for gas I don't need,
avoiding the worst of this job.
My employer,
the wife.
This one has got a lawyer to pay the tab, so it's easier.
Please leave by the servant's exit.
The mustang shudders,
begging to cut loose and show what it can do.
It wants to take me all the way.
I don't let it.
I think about all the ways I've screwed up
and what I'd give for one clear chance to wipe this slate clean.
I'd give anything, just to cut loose,
just to feel the fire...
one more time.
Never lose control,
not for a second.
Never let the monster out.
Remember when you did.
Remember what you did.
Yeah?
Dwight, is that you?
Ava.
I'm sorry to call.
I know I've got no right
but I need to see you,
tonight.
Please Dwight, don't hang up, please.
She keeps talking.
Like an idiot, I keep listening.
Ava.
Damn.
I should tell her to go to hell.
Instead, I show up 20 minutes early.
What the hell she wants with me now?
You can't drive 2 blocks
in Sin City without coming across a salon.
The bad kind.
Why here, Ava?
With you everything always had to be first class.
And when I couldn't foot the bill,
you sure as hell found somebody who could.
I ordered up a ginger ale and
stared at it for the better half part of an hour.
She is late,
like she always was,
and like always,
she is worth the wait..
Dwight.
How long has it been?
4 years?
Yeah, that sounds about right.
Have a seat.
So many times I wanted to call you.
I found myself thinking about you.
- Constantly. -I got places to go,
how about you tell me what you want.
Don't be cold.
I don't think I could stand that right now.
I must still mean something to you.
You came here, you must have cared.
Sure.
You called and I came running.
You still got that much of a hold on me, maybe you always will,
but I got no reason at all to be nice to you.
I guess I deserve that.
Let's not screw around.
I'm here.
I'm listening.
Just tell me what the hell it is you want?
There's only one thing I want from you,
I want it so desperately that I could scream.
I want you to forgive me.
So you got a conscience after all.
Fine.
I forgive you, you got your wish.
Now go home,
sleep tight.
You're right about me.
I'm a selfish slut who threw away the only man she ever loved.
But I was wrong.
Good one.
I was born at night but it wasn't last night.
I'm in hell, Dwight.
It's worse than you can imagine.
You made your bed, sleep in it!
- Forgive me, darling, I beg you. - No!
- I love you. - No!
No!
You do that again, I swear to hell I'll kill you.
If you can't forgive me,
then please remember me.
They say you never die as long as somebody remembers you.
What the devil are you talking about?
Mrs. Lord.
The weather is inclement, the neighbourhood is bad
and your present company...
is low.
You're due at home, Mrs. Lord.
I'd say that's up to Mrs. Lord.
This is none of your concern, sir.
Any physical contest between us
has only one outcome.
Hey buddy,
is that dickhead giving you a hard time?
You want me to break him down for you?
I got nothing going on tonight.
That would be an interesting contest.
It's not his fight.
Never mind, Dwight, it's too late.
I'll go with him.
Too late for what, Ava?
For everything.
Just remember me, my love.
Remember me.
You'll have business tonight, Mrs. Lord,
Unpleasant business.
I don't care anymore.
The night air hasn't got any colder,
it just feels that way.
Buddy, I don't mean to
poke my nose right where it don't belong but...
that there, is a dame to kill for.
Ava...damn!
Night turns to day and then it's night again
and there's no where to hide.
She isn't worth a moment's thought
and I can't get her out of my head.
What am I doing smoking?
Where did I get these cigarettes?
It's Ava making you crazy.
All over again.
Never let the monster out.
Shake her off.
Whatever she's in for, she deserves it,
but I have to know what's wrong.
It's a couple hours of drive out to Sacred Oaks.
It shouldn't take too much effort to get to the bottom of this.
Just a simple job of breaking and entering,
punishable by up to 5 years
in the slammer even if I don't kill anybody.
I wind up seeing a lot more than I bargained for.
She seems perfectly goddamn fine.
Not roughed up,
just the rich man's wife like she always intended to be.
I'm a damn fool.
Freeze! Pervert!.
Let me through, Manute.
I'm sorry, Dwight.
An atom bomb goes off between my legs.
A freight train barrows into my jaw.
I've taken a beating before but never like this.
Never like this.
The sounds go wet.
Maybe he keeps hitting me.
I don't know...
...I'm gone.
Gone to that place where there's no pain or thought.
I wake up in mid air.
The pavement rushes up to give me a big sloppy kiss.
I'll be damned.
Door to door service.
Then I spot my Mustang,
which makes no sense.
Why would they return my car?
Get out of here.
No.
Put your clothes back on and get out of here, now!
You had your chance.
You could've stay away but you came for me.
You still want me,
and I'm yours, now!
Tonight!
Get out of my life once and for all
or I'll bash your teeth in.
If you can't love me,
hate me.
If you can't forgive me,
punish me.
Make me hurt, like I've hurt you.
I called her every foul name there is.
She makes my name sound like music,
like a chant to some dark god.
She's slippery with sweat.
Before long, my hatred is spent.
But she won't let go.
She kisses me and coaxes me
and the fire grows again.
I said all the thing I swore I'd never say again.
She owns me.
Body and soul.
Tell me everything.
Manute, the man who beat you.
He's a specialist inflicting pain.
Hideous pain in all the places you just gave me joy.
That's sick, it's crazy.
Damien, my husband,
he talks and talks and watches.
It's worse each time.
It's getting closer to his final sick climax.
He says it'll be very ugly before I die.
Ava, you're not gonna die.
You're coming with me.
It's hopeless.
He lets me run away, even laughs about it.
Doesn't care where I go, what I do.
He knows Manute will always find me.
Isn't that right, Manute?
Ma'am, Mr Lord would require that you be disciplined.
No, wait, Dwight, don't fight him!
He will kill you!
He's not human.
I punch with all door, he doesn't fall down.
So I punched him again.
A wrecking ball hits me square in the chest.
Mrs. Lord, your clothes.
We have an appointment.
They can't take her away from me.
Not this time.
I know exactly what to do.
I know exactly where to go.
Now here's a girl with protection.
She maybe showing off everything she has got
and already die full of horny drunks,
but Nancy is the safest gal in the world.
Make a grab for Nancy
and you're up against 300 pounds of iron
that goes by the name of...
...Marv.
Marv.
Dwight, mighty glad to see you here.
What can I do you for?
I need your help.
It's bad and it's gonna be up against a lot of guns.
Count me in.
I could use a change of peace.
We finished off the bottle,
letting this liquid darkness fill us both.
When I'm sure he had enough
to make him good and dangerous,
I tell him about Ava
and his eyes go killer red.
I know he's willing to die for me
if that's what it takes.
So I'm using him, so what?
So he breaks the faces I want him to break
instead of somebody else's.
So he helps me get Ava back in my arms again
instead of sleeping it off in a slum house or gutter.
His life isn't worth a dime anyway.
If I don't get him killed, the world will,
one way or another.
I want you to leave that thing in the car.
Nobody's getting killed tonight.
Oh come on Dwight, why, you're no fun at all.
We split up at the gate.
It doesn't take Marv long to get their attention.
You've trespassed on hallowed ground.
You're the slug that freaked my friend out?
Shall we?
Oh, I better wrap my hand one of these days.
I'll find the truth about Ava,
and what's happening to her now.
He will tell me. I'll get it out of him.
Damien Lord.
Where's she?
What have you done with her?
Have you come to take her away from all these?
And what's all these in her present story?
I haven't the slightest notion what nonsense my wife has told you
nor do I care.
It's all lie.
Stay away from the desk.
The woman is pathological.
You have been deceived.
What did it feel like?
What?
Murdering an innocent man.
I just want to know what it felt like.
It must've been beautiful.
What are you talking about, innocence?
I knew I could count on you.
Sex always made you stupid, ready to believe anything.
You've just made me a very rich woman.
Do me one last favor, lover.
Stay still long enough for me to blow your brains out.
I'm not much of a shot
- but I'll do my best. - Ava...
I planned it and you fell for it.
This is the last time I'm gonna need anything from a man.
The last time I make my living on my back.
- Manute never hurt you... - He wouldn't dare!
- You're insane. - No, Dwight.
A crazy person would be anyone who believes me
and that would be you.
If I kiss you now, Dwight,
would you still believe it was... love?
Ava...
Damn.
Hey, I handled that big slug just like I promised.
I didn't kill him, I didn't even cripple him.
6 months in contraption, that's all, tops.
I took an eye out of him though.
Listen, before you say anything.
I know I was supposed to take this down to make my getaway
but when I saw this beauty here sitting there, you know
the key in the ignition and everything,
I couldn't pass a chance to, uh,
take a drive and get us on this tucker.
Pull over!
You know, they only made a couple of these beauties
I saw a movie about it once.
Oh, here I'm, jabbering and you're leaking all over the place.
I'll get you to a guy I know.
He's good with bullets and uh, he don't ask no questions.
Get me to old town.
Let me level with you, pal.
You ain't gonna make it to old town.
I'll make it.
I got too much I got to do to let myself die.
old town.
He left a lot of blood, Mrs. Lord.
He won't get far.
You said you knew him.
The killer's name is Dwight.
Dwight McCarthy.
You know him in what sense?
Why, a depplicable one.
I'm sorry, lieutenant. You've been so very patient with me.
You and I barely met but already...
I feel I can trust you.
You can trust me.
We were together for a while a few years ago.
It went badly.
He went insane.
He started imagining things, accusing me of things.
He followed me wherever I went.
Recently, he broke into this very property.
Did he beat you?
When he drank.
He drank a lot.
You stayed with this nutcase?
Never mind that.
You'll be surprise how much a woman can take.
You were terrified.
It was Damien who took me away.
He was so...gentle and sure.
I suppose I'm a woman who needs...protection.
He made me feel safe
but then, Dwight, he found me somehow.
He started calling me late at night, making awful threats.
And now Damien is dead
and I'm alone.
Oh please, lieutenant.
Call me Mort.
Nothing like a widow in need of confort.
I got a stiffy just watching her.
- Man, she's prime. - Just drop it, Bob.
You don't pass up a chance like that.
What's the point of being a Sin City cop
if you don't get the perks?
We're married man, Bob.
I don't care what you are.
Will you just take a look at that babe!
That's enough, Bob.
This doesn't look good.
One squad car still chases us.
Must be a rookie driving.
His buddy should've told him
the girls of old town have laws all their own,
and they don't take kind to the cops.
Oh, look that.
Oh, you're a genius, girl.
Here we are, pal.
Out of a sudden this doesn't look like the brightest idea you ever had.
You've 10 seconds to tell us
what you're doing bringing cops to old town.
Here's the problem.
I don't fight girls.
Gail!
- It's me. - Dwight.
What have they done to you?
The cork screw stamps me square in the chest
and twists.
Get Molly!
Get everybody.
It's about time.
- Hello? - Mrs. Lord.
Lieutenant...Mort. You're so kind to call.
I hope I didn't wake you.
No, I wasn't sleeping. I haven't slept at all.
I'm jumping at every sound,
just knowing he's still out there.
I guess I'm not a very strong person.
And me in the house all alone.
You shouldn't be so hard on yourself, Mrs. Lord.
You're having a very understandable reaction.
Is there any thing at all I can do for you?
I know it's a bad thing to think of you the way I do.
It's...inconvenient.
But whoever loved,
love not at first sight?
I thought about you since I saw you.
I'm thinking about you now.
Were you thinking about me?
Yes.
I hate myself for saying this but
I just don't know if I could bear to be alone tonight.
My heart beats.
I take in the rich burnt smell of coffee.
Gail! She's reason enough to open my eyes.
Can you hear me, Dwight?
The cops want you bad, Dwight.
Really bad.
Don't worry.
We'll fix you up
and when we do,
when you're all better,
I'll dag you for leaving in the first place!
I told you, you would be back.
I told you.
You belong here.
Jerk!
I thought there's another world out there.
I thought I could be a part of it.
There's only Sin City.
Molly said you're ready to leave.
No, I'm staying.
Wrong answer.
Miho.
Deadly little Miho.
If she recognizes me, she doesn't let it show.
Oh, you picked the wrong neighborhood for your hideout.
Alive or dead, you're leaving.
I'm staying.
I don't think he can feel it, Miho.
Give it a twist.
You won't give with anymore lip about staying here,
or Miho will have to...exhale.
And that heart Molly worked so hard to fix
will just pop like a grape.
He's staying.
And if you're gonna kill him,
you better kill me too,
eventhough he doesn't feel the same way about me.
He's the only man I ever loved.
They all seem to be waiting for the other shoe to drop,
Gail drops it.
It was dark in that alley, Miho.
When you were 15, you killed three of the thugs.
But the last two have a drop on you.
You were dead,
until someone appeared.
You never got a good look at the man who saved you.
Take a look now.
I get more time
and more surgery.
Listen, there's only one person
that has anything to gain for snuffimg Damien Lord
and you're too busy banging the broth
to bring her in for questioning!
You don't know her.
You don't know anything about her and
I'll be damned if I let you use that kind of language
when you talk about her.
You're in love with her!
You stupid smug!
It's one thing to poke a babe on the side,
but you can't even think straight.
Shut the hell up!
I know what I'm doing.
I guess I should've told you everything.
You're damn right you should've.
He raped me.
He almost killed me.
That son of a bitch!
I thought I could reason with him but
he was worse than ever.
His hands at my throat,
strangling me while he did what he needed to do.
He will kill me, kill me, kill me...
I have only you.
I love you, Mort.
Keep me safe.
Keep me, keep me, keep me...
Ava Lord.
For once you missed my heart.
I'm healing quickly, Ava.
I'll be coming for you soon.
You know where he is and you won't do a damn thing about it!
You don't know what you're asking.
We've to wait for old town to give him up,
it's the only way.
You're a Sin City cop.
You got a badge and a gun. You got power.
Use it!
If you ever want to have this woman again,
be a man. If you're a man...
kill him!
Don't move.
McCarthy...
You never tortured her.
You two cooked that up. You were her lover.
You were a fool.
The goddess takes no lover.
The goddess makes slave of man.
In an instant, she can see thru' the heart of you
and transformed to your deepest desire.
To Damien Lord, she was the princess bride.
To you, a damsel in distress.
She devoured all of you.
You cannot defeat the goddess.
She cannot die.
You're as crazy as she is.
If you were as rotten as her,
I would blow your brains out right now,
but I'm trying to be careful about who I kill
and all you did was pound the crap out of me.
You already paid an eye for that.
I'm letting you go with a warning.
Stay in bed.
Don't go back to work.
And don't get in my way.
No, Ava, you're no goddess.
You're a witch.
A predator.
Maybe I only got what I deserved but what about the others?
Good man driven mad.
You really lost it.
Bad enough you leave your wife for that skank.
You watch what you call her, you son of a bitch.
You throw it away your career.
Now you commit suicide, you stupid shit!
I know what I'm doing, I'm going to old town.
I'm going to nail this guy once and for all.
If I had to go it alone, I'll.
Do me a favor,
turn the car around and you go back to the station.
You gotta complain with the captain.
I'm a cop. I'm doing my job.
I'm in town for a murder.
You gotta ditch that dame!
That's enough!
You won't talk about Ava!
Somebody's gonna set you straight.
You gotta forget about that stupid whore!
Turn the car around or I'm turning you in!
I warned you.
Everyday, I warned you but you keep asking for it!
You're asking for it! Well, here it's, pal!
Mort, No!
A witch,
a predator,
destroying lives.
Sometimes for power,
sometimes for profit,
sometimes...for sport.
But now you're locked away in your mansion.
A bird of prey in a gilded cage.
Are you ready to do something stupid?
I'm so happy you chose to attend my little party, Herr Wallenquist.
Your invitation surprised me, Mrs. Lord.
Your husband had no criminal associations.
Believe me, I tried.
May I speak truthfully, Mr. Wallenquist?
Please.
old town is a thorn in your sight.
Indeed it is.
All those profits in the hands of whores.
Surely you want to put them in their place.
Make some adjustment to the balance of power.
Show them who rules Sin City.
You've limited influence on me, Mrs. Lord.
I haven't been doing so very badly.
But those two policeman, that was an embarassing blunder.
Yes, I'm out of my league.
I need a stronger, more experience hand.
I need all enterprises joined... in matrimony,
with the expertise and iron fist of a rich Wallenquist.
What you need is the corpse of Dwight Mccarthy
and a suicide note which he confesses to the murder of Damien Lord.
And you need to show those old town bitches who's boss.
Indeed, I do.
There's a specialist in Texas.
I could have him on a train tomorrow.
I'll brief him myself.
He will on your doorstep at midnight.
And I'll be yours forever.
Pray for your soul, Ava.
This won't be his last to visit Sin City.
Good evening, Mr. Kelvar.
- I'll take your bag. - Nobody touches my gear.
And I got somebody picking me up
who's one hell of a lot cuter than you.
It was our understanding that you're travelling alone.
I'm full of surprises.
Shuffle that bootie over to that shotgun side now.
I'm driving.
Follow you.
Mrs. Lord may not be please.
She's the one with the problem.
I can always get back on the train.
Wait here.
Hurry back!
You know I'll get impatient.
You know I get a little crazy when I get impatient.
Kruger, watch this woman.
Jacoby,
If this man moves, kill him.
Thought this was business.
My compliments to your surgeon, Mr. McCarthy.
Remarkable transformation...
which you still have the eyes,
the eyes of a dead man.
I hate being left alone.
When I'm alone, it makes me want to do all kinds of crazy things.
No woman should be left alone with a man like you.
Do you want me?
To do something we shouldn't?
My lips are sealed.
There's something I need in the trunk.
Bear withness.
Mrs. Lord, the specialist has arrived.
The bathing thing with her was never about bathing.
It was always theater, or maybe it was retail.
You can't make a sale without showing the goods.
It's McCarthy.
Do you mind if I say that
you're twice the man I thought you were?
You're a warrior,
a killer.
You're everything I want of a man
but I can never get the honesty out of you.
You could've been eveything that I needed.
You still could be, you're a new man!
Remember what she did. Remember what she is.
Wait for your opening.
Wait for Gail to do ber bit.
When you're immune to me, I'll let you know.
Step back, Mrs., let me kill him.
Please...
...do.
Six shots, without a single head wound.
And now it all gets down to speed and luck.
Her eyes are wet and full of love.
I never dream,
you're everything I ever wanted,
everything I need...
...you and me, forever.
It's over.
Pain has set you free.
You're not good anymore, Dwight.
You're more like me.
Be like me.
Let the old Dwight go.
Let it go, this old face.
She pulls close and I got to look.
And all I wanted is to be lost
in the sight and sound and smell of her.
- I can't think straight. - We can be free.
We can be happy, together, forever.
No...
Her kiss is a promise of paradise.
- Dwight... - The gun barks and balks in my hand.
Life leaves Ava, with a sigh.
Sirens climbing the hill, we'll take the backroads,
the old bootlegged roads,
don't ever catch us,
I'm going home.
Walk down the back alley in Sin City,
and you can find anything.
I was told I could find a man here by the name of Mr. Kroenig.
That's a doctor, Kroenig, to you.
Yes, sir.
License or no license,
these hands still got well, what it takes,
once I preped.
How much you got?
Forty bucks you got? Forty bucks worth you get!
Steady as a rock...
...once I'm prepped.
Forty bucks got you the bullet
but that hands of yours, a lot of bones need help.
I'll give you an hour, for your shoes.
Take them.
I did my best to think about winning, revenge.
The old man must have like popsicles,
he uses the sticks for splints. He licks them first.
Not so much of a goddamn thank you.
Generosity don't count for shit.
This dead age.
Quite a job he did on me, Roark.
Even my shoes.
There's nothing more you can take,
except...
Marcie, the girl.
Oh my Christ.
Marcie.
Oh, Marcie, you weren't a part of this.
You were just there to throw them off their game.
What have I dragged you into?
This has turned into one long, bad night.
The windows are not locked.
Never a good sign.
Not in Sin City.
Look who has decided to show up?
Give the man a hand.
Give the man another hand.
Ruined, penniless,
friendless and forgotten.
You really be better off dead, Johnny.
But I like you just the way you're.
I got cocky.
I got cocky and I got Marcie dead.
Damn it, Johnny.
Hate yourself only when you got the time.
Think about tonight's game.
That's all it matters now.
And all you need is money,
just one lousy buck would be enough to get you started.
Hello, ma'am.
I don't have the money to pay
but could I ask you for a glass of water?
Yeah.
Time is tough all over.
Thank you.
What's with the hand?
I beat the wrong guys at cards.
Tough break.
Thank you very much.
Just a second, you.
You don't stink of anything I don't like
and you kinda remind me of an old boyfriend, okay?
This won't take you very far.
Sweetheart, it's going to take me to the moon.
Sin City, you never know.
Don't spend it all in one place.
Hey, handsome, what are you gonna do with all that?
I'm going to kill Roark.
That Roark there, don't die that easy.
I just might surprise you.
Looks like something happened to your game hand, son.
I fold.
What's wrong, hotshot?
No good without the lady luck you brought here last time?
I'll be fine.
- I'm done. - I'm out.
I need three.
Dealer takes two.
- Check. - Check.
I bet a hundred.
Shit!
Fold.
Just not the same without your game hand, is it?
I'm ambidextrous.
Cut.
Check.
Five hundred.
I'm in.
I'll raise you...
...five hundred more.
- I fold. - I'm done.
- Here is your five more, pretty boy. - Shit!
You favored your mother,
she was a whore, not a very good one.
She was an angel.
I'm all in.
For the works.
Call.
Four aces.
See, I told you, I never lose.
I beat you,
twice, that means I'm better than you're
and everybody knows it
'cause I beat you again every time somebody tells that story,
and they will all say they won't tell it but they will.
That's the story that will be told again and again
until you're dead and long after you're dead.
I beat you forever.
And they all know what happens when you do.
Say hello to your mama.
She always was a stupid bitch.
Power is what power does.
Say I give any young man advices,
it'll be this where or whenever.
Now take out that trash, let's get back to the game!
I can't lose you, not again.
You never lose me, Nancy.
All this time, she, was right there.
Dancing in the club where you play poker.
You gotta be looking for a chance
to put this one thru' the ring, senator.
Nancy Callahan.
My son Ethen was killed because of her.
It has been 4 years now and still,
she's planting flowers at Hartigan's grave.
She's showing gratitude for the looks of it to the cop.
Gratitude to the cop,
who ripped your son to pieces.
Hartigan turned my son into a freak.
No, complete him as a freak
but I hardly blame the young lady for...
...obsession.
It's nothing more than a little fluff sorrow.
It might not be that simple.
Somehow she got her hands on Hartigan's old pistol.
She hits the ring every night just before work.
She become quite a good shot.
And I can only imagine whose face she sees on that target.
I'm listening.
She's acting kinda crazy sometimes, at work.
She's drinking, just a little past few weeks.
She never drank before.
It's all like, she's building up to something.
Maybe, building her...nerve.
That will be all, lieutenant.
This little bitch is turning me on.
This place stinks.
I never use to notice.
not when I dance.
Now I smell everything.
I see it all.
Every damn thing.
I know exactly where I'm.
I know exactly what I'm.
I don't use that stripper's logic anymore,
that they're losers and I'm not.
It was when I could shoot at him that I realize I'm dead,
that I wasn't a woman with a plan.
I was just a drunk...
I give them what they want
and I get the hell outta there.
You shot him in the gut.
It was a mishap.
Who is to pay?
...rotten town, it soots anybody who touches.
it's a rotten town but it can't corrupt its soil.
It's soil to you, John Hartigan.
Put that bottle down, Nancy. You had enough.
They made you lie to me, you're not even here right now.
- You said you never leave me. - I never left you.
I never would.
Never.
You're not even here right now. You're dead!
You blew your brains out.
You stuck a gun in your mouth and you blew your brains out.
I had my reasons, there was no way out.
I hate you!
- You swore you'll always love me. - And I always will.
No one has ever guessed what hell is.
It's watching the people you love...
...in pain.
You're the man I ever loved
and you left me alone.
You never thought I'd stand a chance
with that goddamn son of Roark.
You didn't believe in me.
You didn't think a little piece of arse like me
could take down the most powerful man in the state.
Maybe I'll prove both of you wrong.
Maybe I would go crazy.
- Crazy is sounding pretty good right now. - I love you, Nancy.
You little slut! You gonna scream before you die.
You're out of your mind...
I appreciate the obsession but you got nothing...
You could've killed me 50 times if you've the nerve,
but you don't.
You're nothing...
You'll scream, just like my boy wanted you to...
Darling, where have you been
and what have you done to your beautiful hair?
Don't worry, those bastards are getting what they want.
They always get what they want.
This is great, isn't it? What's up with you?
Something's wrong, I'm out of here.
Oh, watching my sister getting nasty,
I'm taking a hike.
Ready.
You are beautiful, Nancy.
Don't do this to yourself.
Pretty, pretty, pretty...
If a man did this to you, I'll tear him to pieces.
Lieutenant Hartigan, you just gave me a great idea.
No, babe.
Nancy...
Just give me a damn name.
Roark.
Up against a lot, we need tools.
Looks like trouble.
Looks like Christmas.
- Well, you missed last call, boys. - Bullshit!
We're ripping this place, arse hole.
Move or die!
I hope you don't mind me saying this, but...
you look hot.
There's no reason to leave anybody alive.
Nobody's innocent. We can't leave anybody able to talk.
Don't go soft on me, kid. Don't leave anybody breathing.
I won't. I'll work the perimeter and nail the guards.
Baby, you're a natural. I'll work the inside.
How would I know when you're in?
You'll have a pretty good idea.
Damn thing has fired on me.
I nearly got them all but
this piece of shit over here, he came up on me.
This piece of crap... I think I'll stuck.
Here.
Take a seat.
You're a peach.
I got this.
You clever, clever little whore.
I can't believe you made it this far.
Your Hartigan blew my son's pecker off.
So...where shall I shoot you next?
The tight little belly of yours?
I'm holding a gun on you, young lady.
The rules are, you pretend there's a chance that I won't shoot you.
I told you, you would scream before you die.
I owe it to my son.
Frankly, between you and me,
I finally accepted that...Ethen is not...presidential material.
I had a hard time buying him an election in the same asylum,
but he was my son, honey.
He was my son.
And now, he's going to hear you scream.
Scream...
This is for John Hartigan, fucker!
This rotten town has soiled everybody...