Breathe in...
...and out.
Let the wave of calm
wash over you.
Feel your stress melt away.
Let go of things
beyond your control.
Focus on your breath...
...your heartbeat.
Stay present in this moment.
Let everything else
just disappear.
Hands to heart.
Just wing it through.
And warrior.
Warrior two.
Then reach into the back
of the room, that's right.
Reaching, reaching
into the back of the room.
Reach.
Side.
Strong over your front half.
Bend.
All right. Coming through.
You can jump up or walk up.
And inhale.
Your heart is alive.
And exhale.
Come back to center.
Hands to heart.
Feel your body vibrating.
You're all one,...
...you're all here,...
...in your body
and in your power.
Thank you for joining me
this morning.
May it bring peace
to the rest of your day.
And may the merit
of our practice...
...be dedicated to all beings
everywhere.
I honor the light in you.
-Namaste.
I honor the light within you.
-That was amazing.
-All right.
Reel it in, teacher's pet.
You're just mad because you can't
even get through the flow.
Are you kidding?
I mastered a bunch of poses.
Oh, child's pose doesn't count.
So how was class?
It was perfect, as always.
I'm sure it was for you,
but I'm wondering about Charlie.
Me? Well, killed it as always.
All right, fine.
It kinda killed me.
That's right, that's why they
call it a practice, honey.
Don't worry, we'll have your body
cleansed in no time.
Thanks, mom.
All right, sweaty. Shall we?
-We shall. Thank you.
-Okay.
You're welcome.
I'll see you soon.
Another breath in...
...and out.
Let go.
It takes no effort
to simply let go.
Maybe for you.
-Thank you.
-You're home today.
-Okay, I'll see you next week.
-See you.
Yeah.
Aunt Amanda.
-Hey.
-Charlie.
-Good to see you.
-How are you?
Look at you.
I can't believe you're here.
-Hey.
-It's so good to see you.
You, too.
You, too, sis.
Autumn crocuses.
Are those for me?
Well, you're literally
the only person I know...
...who likes these.
They're beautiful.
Let me just wash up,
I've been teaching all morning.
But please, come in.
-Take a look around.
-Hey.
Wow, she's really fixed up
the place.
Yeah, you know mom,...
...everything
had to be perfect...
...for the grand reopening
this weekend.
Wanted to give the place
a rebirth.
-Her words, not mine.
-Yeah.
Well, speaking of rebirth,
you're like a new man.
Thank you.
Last time I saw you, you...
It's okay, I know.
You can say it.
I relapsed.
But I've got three years sober
next week.
-Good for you.
-Thank you.
-Oh, I'm proud of you.
-Thanks.
It really ought to do
with my mom.
Ever since I've been back,
she's been keeping an eye on me.
Well, her and Maya.
Maya?
Maya is my mom's assistant
slash star pupil...
...slash spiritual successor.
The yin to my mom's yang.
Oh, and she's my girlfriend.
It's her right there.
Wow, she certainly seems limber.
She's been taking
mom's classes for years.
Even before
she started working here.
It's actually how we met.
She's so great. Come on.
She's smart, she's funny.
She helped my mom
renovate this entire place.
Come on, I'll introduce you.
Hey, Maya. Maya.
Maya.
Charlie, oh, my gosh.
You almost gave me
a heart attack.
I couldn't help it.
It is my fault, really.
I intend to encourage
his juvenile impulses.
I'm Amanda. Lauren's sister.
Oh, my gosh.
Why didn't you say so?
Sorry. I'm just really excited.
Lauren's told me
so much about you.
Social-media consultant,
from New York, right?
Well, I have only been
in New York...
...for a few years,
but that's me, yeah.
Pretty much the polar opposite
of my tree-hugging sister.
Oh, that's okay.
I won't hold it against you.
I was just kidding. Bad joke.
Your sister is kind of my hero.
Maya's one
restraining order away...
...from being
a full-fledged stalker.
Well, I'm so glad that you
could come out for the reopening.
I know Lauren
was really hoping that you would.
I wouldn't miss it.
Good.
How long are you in town for?
Not sure.
I just finished a campaign,...
...so I was thinking of
taking a little time off...
...before my next gig.
You'd be amazed how easy it is
to sublet in Manhattan.
But it looks like you guys
have been really busy.
I mean,
I barely recognize the place.
I know. Can you believe
this is even the same building?
Your parents' health center
was an amazing foundation.
And then Lauren's vision just
helped it become fully realized.
I'm sure it's a lot to take in...
...after being away
for three years, but...
What's wrong?
-Did I say something?
-No. No, it's nothing.
It's fine, really.
Okay.
Why don't we find mom?
We'll give you
the, well, grand tour.
-Great idea.
-All right.
I didn't mean to upset her.
No, don't worry about it.
It's just...
It's a touchy subject is all.
-Okay.
-It's all good.
-All right?
Ian?
Amanda.
It's wonderful to see you.
Lauren's been talking about you
nonstop.
Welcome to our new
and growing family business.
-Hey, kids.
-Hey, pop.
Have you seen mom?
We're hoping to give Amanda
the tour.
No, but I'll get
out of your hair.
See you at the house for dinner?
Here we are. Home sweet home.
You updated the house.
Business must really be booming.
It will be. Just have to pay off
the loans first.
Don't worry, we'll more than
make up the difference.
We have big plans.
Come on.
Remember this room?
Even my old room gets a makeover.
Re-gifting my flowers already?
Oh, I thought
it was a nice touch.
Simpler times.
After you moved out,...
...we figured your bedroom
shouldn't just collect dust.
Now it's the perfect getaway
in addition to the guesthouse.
But Charlie
has officially taken that over.
And Maya
has all but moved in, too.
Look, Amanda,...
...if you ever wanted
to take a little break...
...from the East Coast
for a while...
I appreciate that.
Really, I do.
And the sound of being here
for even just a little while...
...does sound good, but...
Then what's stopping you?
You work remotely.
You don't need to be
across the country.
Come home.
I don't know
if it would be the best idea.
You're still mad at him?
After all these years?
Lauren...
...I know you never believed me.
And I know you don't wanna think
he had an affair.
I wish I was wrong.
But I know what I saw.
And...
...I'll never forgive Ian.
Think about it.
I didn't invite you back here
just for the reopening.
Come on,
I wanna show you something.
Follow me.
I've been learning about
the healing properties of plants.
Well, you've always loved
flowers.
Well, many are quite medicinal.
They're nature's pharmacy.
I miss you.
I want to give us another chance.
We were so close.
Your entire life was here.
Are we gonna throw all that away
just because of a few bad years?
I've missed you, too.
Then, please, come back home.
Let's be a family again.
Do you wanna plant the last one?
-Boo!
-Maya!
-Not cool.
-Yes.
Well, that's what you get...
...for that little gong stunt
earlier.
Oh, what's wrong?
The baby can dish it,...
-...but he can't take it?
-Okay.
Is that better?
Good.
-I have to get ready for dinner.
-What...?
What am I supposed to do?
Well, you can start
by getting dressed.
That's the opposite
of how I thought this was going.
You know,
I couldn't help but notice...
...things have been
a little bit intense...
...with Amanda being back.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know. I was kinda hoping
things between her and my dad...
...would've cooled off
by now, but...
But not quite so, I see.
Well, from what you told me,
I can't really blame her.
Is she still mad at him
for what he did?
Well, what she thinks he did.
-Yeah.
-She never did prove it.
Mom doesn't believe it.
Never did.
What about you?
I don't know.
I mean, dad's a charmer.
But cheating on mom? I mean...
...whatever Aunt Amanda
thinks he did...
...was enough
to make her leave, so,...
...I hope we can all just
put it behind us, start fresh.
Me, too.
I just don't wanna see you
get hurt again.
Or Lauren.
One thing is for certain.
-Dinner's gonna be super awkward.
-Super awkward.
So you better hurry up
and go get dressed.
All right.
I'm not gonna say no
to a lady with a bat.
Amanda, do you like the tofu?
This is tofu?
-It's great. It's very...
-Chewy?
Hey.
It's Maya's recipe.
She's been cooking for us.
In addition to everything else.
Yeah, Maya's been a real Godsend.
So, I have an announcement.
We all know that
the grand reopening...
...is just a few days away.
It's a big step
for the wellness center.
Almost a rebirth.
We're expanding a lot.
And in addition
to all the new services...
...and amenities
we'll be providing,...
...Maya and I have been working
on my brand.
Reaching more people
outside of the studio.
Expanding
my social-media presence.
Now, Amanda,
this is your area of expertise.
And since you don't currently
have a client,...
...I would like to officially
invite you...
...into the fold
as my business partner.
-Wait, what?
-Really?
That's awesome, now you can
move back, like, for good.
I know it's asking a lot.
But mom and dad
always wanted this...
...to be a family business.
They left it to the both of us.
Lauren, isn't this something...
...we should be talking about
in private?
I mean, there are other people...
...who have a vested interest
in the business,...
...people that should have a say.
Hey, no offense.
We all know
there's a lot of history here,...
...but I want to change that
to make things right.
The two of you
have nothing to worry about.
I'll still need you.
That won't change.
Yeah, I mean, it's your decision.
No, it's not. It's our decision.
Dad, come on,
this is a good thing.
Charlie, will you stay
out of this, all right?
You know what happened last time
that Amanda came here.
-Enough! Enough!
-Really?
This is my business.
I built it.
I'm the one who took over
the center...
...when no one else wanted it,...
...so the only opinions
I'm interested in...
...on the subject are mine
and my sister's.
Yeah.
It's fine.
Now, Amanda,...
...I don't expect you
to answer right away.
Take as long as you need.
But just know that you always
have a home here.
And nothing
would make me happier...
...than having you back
in our lives.
Okay.
I'll think about it.
Good.
Well, if you'll excuse me.
I just don't understand...
...how you couldn't
discuss this with me.
It's one thing for her
to come back here for a week.
But actually live here?
And to own half the business?
I am trying to make things right.
She is my sister.
-She deserves that much.
-I don't care who she is.
You never discussed it.
I knew coming back here
was a mistake.
Hey, don't say that.
-Oh, like it even matters?
-I'm glad you're here, okay?
Thanks, Charlie.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah, just walk away.
And I'm sorry
about all this, Maya.
I'm sure Charlie's told you...
...about the fallout
the family had before.
Yeah. Yeah, he did.
The way they're fighting,
it's almost like you never left.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
It's just,
Lauren and I have been...
...such a great team
the past few months.
I'm just a little hurt
she never brought it up to me.
That's all.
It's okay.
I understand.
I better get ready for bed.
It's...
...the big day tomorrow.
-So...
-Yeah.
It's a good idea.
-You ready to turn in?
-Oh, no.
No, I'm gonna stay up
for a little while.
Brew Lauren some herbal tea,
help her relax.
I know
it doesn't seem like it,...
...but she's really nervous
about the reopening tomorrow.
Thank you so much
for taking care of her.
Please.
It's the least I can do.
I'd be lost without her, so...
Goodnight.
All right.
Well, see you in a bit.
Yeah.
Everything okay?
Lauren's...
...cutting it awful close.
Her speech is in five minutes.
-Hey. Have you seen mom?
-Hey.
-What, she's not back yet?
-No.
Last time I saw her, she said...
...she was feeling
a little nauseous,...
...but that was, like,
a half hour ago.
Yeah, she said
she hasn't been feeling well...
...the last couple of days.
I think the reopening's
making her a little bit nervous.
I'm gonna go check the restroom.
-Yeah.
-I'll go with you.
I'll get another tray out
and try to stall.
-Okay.
-Thank you, Rebecca.
Oh, my gosh. Are you okay?
I'm fine. Just nerves, I guess.
Hey, you don't have to do this
if you're not feeling up to it.
No, Amanda's right.
I mean, we can postpone.
Or I could give the speech
if you want.
I mean, I basically memorized it
while I was helping you prep.
Oh, no, thank you.
I'm fine.
This is everything
that we've been working for.
I need to do this.
Trust me, I'm fine.
I've got this.
Let's go.
Good morning, everyone.
Thank you so much for coming out
to support us today.
It is my pleasure
to introduce to you...
...the woman
responsible for all of this,...
...the guru that you all know
and love.
Please put your hands together
for Dr. Lauren Birch.
Thank you, Maya.
As many of you know,...
...Maya has been my rock
in all of this.
And this would not have been
possible without her.
When my parents first opened...
...the Birch Springs
Family Health Center,...
...they had a very simple
mission in mind.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Sorry, I recently switched
from coffee to tea,...
...and my brain
has not forgiven me yet.
The mission they began
was to provide the community...
...with a center for healing.
A place of comfort,
a place of joy.
And that's a mission I've strived
to live up to my entire...
-Lauren, Lauren, you okay?
-Mom. Mom.
Lauren?
-Mom.
-Lauren!
-Lauren?
-You okay?
-Lauren!
-Lauren, you okay?
-Mom.
Lauren, Lauren?
Somebody call 911!
-Mom.
-Lauren. Lauren?
Lauren? Lauren!
We will all remember
her warmth...
...her sense of humor...
...and her caring spirit.
And her spirit will endure.
What she's built
is a testament...
...to who she was.
Her mission was to heal.
Lauren cared about the health,
personal growth of others,...
...almost more than herself.
That compassion
is what I loved about her.
That's what we all loved
about her.
She's left a hole in me.
She would want us to heal.
And right now
I'm in dire need of healing.
I think we all are.
Thank you all for coming today
to Lauren's celebration.
She would've loved that.
I'm so sorry, Amanda.
Josh? Josh Stone?
-I haven't seen you since...
-High school.
Yeah.
You doing okay?
Spent the entire past week
crying.
So I just, I feel like
I don't have any tears left.
Well...
Just in case.
It's just so bizarre.
Lauren was one of the healthiest
people I know to...
...she just collapse
like that,...
...I mean, from heart failure?
Yeah, I know.
It doesn't make sense.
When was the last time
you saw Lauren?
I'm sorry,
I don't mean to be rude.
It's just, I wasn't expecting
my high school boyfriend...
...to be at her memorial.
Lauren and I actually reconnected
a few years ago.
You did?
Yeah, someone broke
into the center,...
...vandalized the place.
She came down to the station
to give a statement,...
...and I bumped into her there.
The station? What, you're a cop?
Detective, actually.
Homicide.
I'll let you be.
I just wanted to express
my condolences.
Anything I can do to help,
even if it's just to talk...
...don't hesitate to call.
Thanks, Josh.
Oh, can you do me a favor?
Can you let Ian know
that it'll be a few days...
...before the toxicology report
comes back?
The toxicology report? What?
Yeah, the autopsy
didn't give us much info...
...beyond heart failure,...
...so the lab performed
a toxicology report.
Which, it's standard
in a case like this,...
...to help identify
the cause of death...
...and possibly identify
any contaminants in the system.
Ian was anxious
to hear the results.
Yeah, no, of course.
I'll let him know.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I'm sorry for your loss.
-Thanks.
-Of course.
-I appreciate it.
-Thanks for having me. Take care.
Thank you.
What a disaster.
Charlie making
a complete arse out of himself.
Three years sober, gone.
What do you expect?
He's a recovering addict.
And his mother just died.
Yeah, of course,
you'd defend him.
Are you kidding me? You're really
bringing this up now?
She's gone, Amanda.
We don't have to pretend
to get along anymore.
Even though I know you still
blame me for what happened.
I'm gonna go check on Charlie.
Of course, I blame you.
You cheated on her.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
Nothing happened.
It's all in your head.
Lauren understood that.
Why can't you?
I know what I saw, and so do you.
You and that girl
at the studio,...
...when you thought no one
was looking.
My gosh, would you just
let it go?
Lauren is dead.
Do you really need
to keep ruining our lives?
-You think I ruined your life?
-Of course, I do!
You nearly ended my marriage,...
...you sank our business,...
...tore our family apart...
...by pushing Charlie back
into using...
...and abandoning your sister
when things got too difficult.
So, yeah,
I think you ruined our lives.
I'm just...
...tired, Amanda.
I just lost the only person
I've ever loved,...
...and I don't have the strength
to keep fighting with you. So...
...if you need to believe
that I had an affair...
...to make me a monster...
...then go ahead.
Just...
...do it someplace else.
Our family doesn't need you
destroying it anymore.
Why are you so interested
in that toxicology report?
I ran into Josh Stone
at the memorial.
He said you were anxiously
awaiting the results.
What exactly are you implying?
I wanna know how my wife died...
...because it doesn't make
any sense.
I want answers...
...closure.
I'd expect you, of all people,
to understand that.
Oh, Charlie.
Hey, Charlie.
Okay.
I'm sorry you had
to see me like this.
It's okay.
Don't even think about it.
All right?
She would've hated me today.
No, she wouldn't have.
She would've been
worried about you,...
...but she would have loved you.
She always has and...
...she always will.
-I'm such a mess-up.
-No, don't say that.
Look, we all have
our weaknesses, okay?
And, and you've been
through a lot.
Look, we're gonna beat this.
Okay?
This, this is just
your way of showing grief.
You know?
Ian's way of showing grief
is yelling at people.
I mean...
...and which I understand,
you know?
I wish I could yell at someone.
But, but Maya?
I guess I can't expect her
to feel the sadness...
...the same way we do, but...
...she posted this strange
message on the website today...
...and then linked it
to the home page and...
...it was just so weird.
It was like she was using
Lauren's death for publicity.
I...
There we go.
Goodnight, Charlie.
We're gonna beat this, I promise.
Maya, you, you scared
the heck out of me.
Sorry about that.
I didn't wanna interrupt.
How long have you been
standing there?
Well, not long.
Amanda, I can't imagine
how hard this must be for you.
Lauren was like family to me,
but you're her sister.
And I'm so, so sorry.
Thank you.
Just know,
anything you need, I'm here.
And whatever you decide,
we'll understand.
Now that Lauren's gone,
nobody's expecting you...
...to help at the center,...
...Ian and I can take over
so that you can have your space.
Well, I appreciate that.
But I'm not gonna be leaving.
Not again.
Really?
I need to make sure
that Charlie's taken care of...
...and, I need to know the truth.
About what?
About how my sister really died.
I refuse to believe
she had heart failure.
And there's something
that just doesn't make sense.
And I'm not leaving
until I know what it is.
Well, I think that's wonderful.
And if you want to help us
carry on Lauren's work,...
...we'd love to have you.
-Okay, then.
-Okay.
-Goodnight.
-Busy morning?
-Amanda.
Maya said you might be
joining us today.
I figured since I'm here, I might
as well keep an eye on things.
It's what Lauren wanted.
I guess it doesn't matter
what anyone else wants.
Not in the slightest.
Hope I didn't ruin your day.
Amanda. Hey.
-Hey.
-You came.
Yeah.
Well, so does this mean that
you're gonna stay...
...and help us out?
I am.
Whatever you need. For Lauren.
That's so great.
I'm sure she's
smiling down on you.
Huh, pretty good
first day so far?
Better than expected.
I was worried
that closing down for a week...
...would cause us
to lose some steam, but...
People really wanted
to support Lauren.
Word must have
gotten out somehow.
Yeah, even from the afterlife
she's bringing people together.
Pretty amazing, isn't it?
You okay?
Yeah, I just...
Sorry, I...
It just feels wrong
for anything good...
...to come out of such
a tragedy, you know?
I know.
But you would have had
a good turnout regardless, right?
It's what you both
worked so hard for.
Yeah. It's not just that though,
you know?
-It's the money and...
-The money?
Yeah, you know,
Lauren's life-insurance policy.
It's gonna help
repay the loans...
...and it's gonna help expedite
further expansion,...
...or whatever, I don't know.
That's what Ian's saying, anyway.
Ian said that?
Yeah. Please don't tell him
that I told you that.
I mean, he has a hard-enough time
talking about it as it is.
I'm sorry,...
...I should not have unloaded
on you like that.
No. No, it's fine.
Really, I'm, I'm happy
to talk if you need to.
Thank you.
Well, I better go. Another class
is starting in 10 minutes.
So...
-Stone. Yeah.
-Josh?
Hey, it's Amanda.
-Amanda...
-Are you free to grab a coffee?
Okay.
In my line of work,
it's easy to jump to conclusions.
-But trust me, it doesn't help.
-Unless I'm right.
Amanda...
...this hasn't been
ruled a homicide.
It's still unclear. To...
...accuse someone
of murder at this point...
Yeah, somebody with motive.
You really think
the insurance money...
...is enough for Ian
to kill his wife?
Sure, I mean,
if he didn't really love her.
All right, look, Amanda,
Lauren told me...
...about what you thought
happened.
That you accused Ian of cheating,
that it tore the family apart.
Lauren didn't believe it.
I'm inclined to agree with her.
Which leaves Ian with no motive.
Are you okay?
It just always really hurt when
Lauren believed Ian and not me.
Now it hurts even more.
Can I get you two fresh cups?
-Yeah, please.
-Yeah, that would be great.
I'm glad you called me,
even if your motives were...
...to throw your brother-in-law
under the bus.
I'm surprised you didn't ask me
about the toxicology report.
I assumed that's why
you wanted to meet.
What do you mean?
Oh, they didn't tell you?
Oh, I dropped it off
at the center this morning.
No, nobody told me.
What did it say?
The lab found a substance
in Lauren's bloodstream.
It's possible it could've
contributed to her heart failure.
What?
Have you ever heard
of colchicine?
No.
I'm doing this
as a favor for a friend.
For Lauren.
This is not
an investigation, okay?
-Okay.
-All right.
Right.
So...
...colchicine is a natural drug.
Completely legal, mind you.
"It's often found
as a white power in tablets.
It's used to treat
inflammation, gout...
...and familial
Mediterranean fever."
Which is a real thing
according to Wikipedia.
So it's possible Lauren
was taking this medication...
...to treat some of those
symptoms,...
...got the dosage wrong.
Because if too much is taken,
it can be deadly.
Wait, those flowers,
they were Lauren's favorite.
I mean, she plants them
in her garden.
That's right.
It's also the source
of colchicine.
Which gives credence
to the theory...
...that she was
self-medicating,...
...and maybe her death
was an accident.
But Lauren wasn't reckless.
That's the only theory
we have at this point.
No, the only thing I'm hearing...
...is that somebody could have
poisoned my sister,
...and the police aren't even
considering it.
Amanda, if this is all we have,
it doesn't prove anything.
I promise you, as soon as
something suspicious arises,
I will let you know, okay?
Amanda. Come on...
Charlie?
Charl...Charlie!
Charlie!
Oh, gosh. Oh, thank gosh.
What, what's going on?
Thank gosh. I...
I came here to check on you.
And when I saw you lying here,
I thought you were...
-Oh, gosh.
-I'm fine.
No, Charlie, you're not.
What are you doing?
Relax, it's just a bit of pills.
You're not my mom.
Honey...
Hey. Do you have a minute?
Yeah.
Is everything okay?
I'm fine, thanks. What's up?
I just ran into Charlie.
Can we talk?
Sure.
I haven't seen him this bad
in a really long time.
He even had to call his sponsor.
You've seen Charlie
relapse before?
To this extent, only once,
when we first met,...
...but that was three years ago.
When I left.
It seems like whenever
I'm here, Charlie slips.
No, don't say that.
This is nobody's fault
but Charlie's.
You can't blame yourself
for his addiction.
Lauren would've said that.
I, I spoke with
Detective Stone earlier.
He said he was
by the center this morning...
...to drop off
a toxicology report?
Yeah, he did. He gave it to Ian.
Did you guys learn anything?
He said there was something
in Lauren's system.
It's a drug called colchicine.
You take it for inflammation.
But if you take too much of it,
then it can be fatal.
And he thinks
she was taking that?
That's the theory.
Apparently, it comes from
those flowers that she grows.
Somehow, she took too much.
And the evidence suggests
that it was an accident.
But you don't believe that.
It's just, Lauren was
always so careful...
...about what she put
in her system.
You know, I just, I can't see her
being that reckless.
So what does this mean?
You think somebody else
did this to her?
I don't know,
but...
...I have suspicions.
That the drugs could have
come from someone else.
You don't think that
Charlie would've...
I don't think that
he would ever do...
...anything intentionally
to hurt her.
That's not what I'm saying.
It's just...
-Yeah.
-When I saw him earlier,...
...he was, he was so out of it
and so confused and...
...you know, what if
somehow he relapsed...
...before her death
and none of us noticed?
And he just got
the drugs mixed up...
...and somehow Lauren just...
-Is this crazy?
-No. It's not.
It would explain why he relapsed
so hard this time.
I have to show you
something at the center.
Back when Charlie and I
first started dating,
I noticed him behind the front
desk computer a couple of times.
I didn't think anything about it
at the time,...
...but once
I started working here,
I figured out
what was really going on.
He was using the company account
to order drugs.
Painkillers, mostly,...
...stuff that conceivably Lauren
would have ordered.
But not all the pills
would be accounted for.
Oh, Charlie.
So it's possible that another
order was placed recently.
We can look up the order history.
So it does look like
there was an order...
...placed for some painkillers.
And...
Oh, no.
No.
Wait, but anyone could have
placed this order, right?
This doesn't necessarily mean
that it was Charlie.
Right, yeah, well, we could
check the security camera
and see if he even used
the computer.
There's a camera?
Yeah. Lauren had it installed...
...after the place was
vandalized a few years back.
Oh, that's right. Stone mentioned
something about that.
-Can we access the footage?
-Yup.
Okay, so here's the day
that the order was placed.
We can scroll
through the footage.
That doesn't look good.
Are you gonna tell the detective?
I don't know.
I mean, the last thing I wanna do
is hurt Charlie,...
...but if it's the truth, then...
I have no choice.
Yeah.
I didn't realize just how much
contempt you had for my family.
I spoke to Maya.
She shared with me your...
...concerns about Charlie.
Trust me.
The last thing I want to do
is hurt Charlie.
Trust you?
Amanda, for as long
as I've known you,...
...the only thing
I can trust you to do...
...is ruin
everything I care about.
Look, I can understand
you blaming me.
But Charlie?
Never in a million years
did I think...
...you would point the finger
at him.
Say something!
Okay.
You don't scare me.
I don't wanna blame Charlie,
but I need to know the truth.
And you ruined everything
you cared about, not me.
You listen to me, Amanda.
If you go through with this,
if you tell the detective
what you think,
it'll destroy him.
I already did.
Then whatever happens next,
that's on your conscience.
I will follow you
If you dare to fall
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Trying to save
The only thing yeah
I'm hanging on
I'm hanging by a thread
Breathe in...
...and out.
I will follow you
Another breath in...
-...and out.
-I will follow you
If you dare
Close your eyes and visualize.
Find a place
that brings you comfort...
...serenity, joy.
Do you have a clear picture?
Just stay
with whatever is happening.
I will follow you
If you dare to fall
If you dare
Keep breathing.
I will follow you...
If you dare to fall
I will follow you
If you dare
But I can't believe...
I will follow you
You...
Let calm rush over you and
let everything just disappear.
You...
Good.
Detective Stone.
What happened?
It's Charlie. He's...
He had an accident.
He...He's alive,
but it isn't good.
I know.
Oh, gosh.
Charlie.
Charlie, it's me. It's your dad.
What's wrong with him?
Why... Why isn't he responding?
He's in a coma.
The fall
and the drugs in his system...
...were just too much.
The doctors aren't sure
when or if he'll come out of it.
They said he injected a high dose
of something into his arm.
Probably morphine.
They don't know
if it was an accident or he...
Oh, dammit, Charlie.
And, what did the police say...
...about Lauren?
-Do they think that...
-I don't know.
Stone just wanted to give us
some time with Charlie, so...
I'd like to be with my son.
Alone.
No. I'm, I'm not leaving him.
Just go, Amanda.
You've done enough.
Okay, well, if you,
if you need us...
Just... Just, just go.
Charlie.
Char...
Another breath in...
...and out.
Feel your stress melt away.
Let go of things
beyond your control.
Focus on your breath...
...your heartbeat.
Stay present in this moment.
I don't understand
what that means.
Those are colchicine tablets.
The same thing
they found in Lauren.
We found it in Charlie's car,
underneath the seat.
Look at the envelope.
Yeah, that's the supplier
the center orders from,...
...which is the supplier
Charlie ordered from.
So what?
Charlie's responsible for Lauren?
Possibly,
whether directly or indirectly,
there's now a clear connection
between him and Lauren's death.
-I mean, if he wakes up...
-When he wakes up.
Sorry. When he wakes up,
I'm gonna have to question him.
He's now a person of interest.
You... you can't possibly think
that Charlie...
...is responsible
for his mother's...
-Amanda, I...
-No, Charlie is gonna wake up.
And when he does,
he's gonna have an explanation.
And you'll see
that this has all been...
...some kind of misunderstanding.
All right, I'm not trying to jump
to any conclusions.
I just needed to pursue all leads
and possibilities.
Okay.
Well, thank you.
Is there anything else
that we can do to help?
Right now you just need
to be there for each other...
...and Charlie...
...and Ian.
I know it's gonna be tough, but
Charlie's gonna need some time.
So find a way to cope. You know,
find a way to get some peace.
Thank you.
I know.
It sucks.
Today we're going to do
a meditation for letting go,
to find inner peace and calm.
Breathe in...
...and out.
Let the wave of calm
wash over you.
Feel your stress melt away.
I honor the...
Let go of things
beyond your control.
Let calm wash over you and
let everything just disappear.
Good.
Focus on your breath,
your heartbeat.
Stay present in this moment.
Let go of the things
beyond your control.
Let a wave of calm wash over you.
Let everything else
just disappear.
Maya?
You all right?
Yup.
It's just one of those days,
I guess.
Is there something
you wanna talk about?
I saw you with Ian.
Is he doing anything
inappropriate?
No.
I think we're both
just vulnerable.
And I think he got caught up
in the moment.
Are you sure?
Because if you need me
to talk to him, I will.
No, please.
He's having a hard-enough time
with everything as it is and...
Look, I know you two
don't like each other.
But Ian's a good man, okay?
You can't fault him
for just trying to find...
...some small amount of comfort
in all of this.
-Okay?
-Okay.
But if you ever need to tell me
anything, know that I'm here.
-Okay?
-I will.
Thank you.
I promise,
there's nothing to worry about.
Okay.
I'll get it.
-Oh, hey, Detective Stone.
-Hey.
-Come on in.
-Yeah.
-Hey.
Good evening, everyone,
I'm sorry to disturb your dinner.
No, it...It's fine.
To what do we owe this pleasure?
Well I had some good news...
...and I wanted to come over
and tell you in person.
Charlie's awake.
So, is he doing okay?
Well, doctors said he's stable.
He's not speaking yet,
but they're optimistic...
...he'll be able to talk soon.
That's wonderful news. Thank gad.
Can we see him?
He's still a little out of it.
But I'm told he can see people
tomorrow.
So what does this mean
as far as the case goes?
We still have to question him.
And if he's talking tomorrow,
I'll take his statement.
He's still our best lead.
Yeah. Well, I'll let you get back
to your dinner.
Thank you.
I'll walk you out.
Code blue! Cell six!
The good news is we were able
to help him in time,...
...but it was close.
No, it doesn't make any sense.
How does something like this
happen?
The odds that Charlie's
medication was tampered...
...with so drastically by mistake
are remote.
So...
...you're telling me somebody
snuck in...
...and tried to kill him
while he slept?
I know it sounds crazy.
-No.
-What...
It doesn't sound crazy to me.
Well, we have an officer
stationed outside his room.
Only authorized personnel
will get in from now on.
What about family?
I'm sorry.
I can't let you see him.
Charlie was targeted in much
the same way his mother was.
The only obvious conclusion
I can draw from that...
...is that Charlie's attacker is
responsible for Lauren's death.
This is now
a murder investigation.
Yeah, so...so,
so what happens now?
You three are
the closest people...
...in both Charlie
and Lauren's lives.
So you'll be brought in
for questioning.
What are you saying?
We're suspects?
Yes.
And you're the only ones
we've got.
But before we do all that,...
...I'm gonna go check on Charlie.
Thank you.
Detective?
Hey.
-What happened?
-Charlie, how...
How are you feeling?
Only about as good as I look.
What happened?
Well, I was hoping
you could help me with that.
Are you okay to talk?
Yeah.
I don't know how much use
I'm gonna be, but...
Well, you've been unconscious
for almost a week.
Wait, what?
Where...where is everybody?
-Do they know I'm all right?
-Yes, they know.
Maya, Amanda, your father,...
...they've been here
every single day.
Hardly left your side.
The only reason they're not here
now is by my order.
Why?
Because I gotta ask you
a few questions.
And also...
While you were under,...
...someone broke into your room,
pumped your IV full of morphine.
Enough to kill you.
Charlie, I need you to think...
...about that night
of the accident.
Were you the only one out there?
I don't know.
I remember, I, I went to drink.
Try, please. It's important.
I remember something...
Somebody grabbed me, and then,
and then a pain in my arm.
-Is that from the drugs?
-What?
Well, doctors said they found
painkillers in your system.
No, no. I didn't use that night.
I, I wanted to
and I, I went to, but...
I couldn't find any.
Are you saying
somebody drugged you?
I don't remember anything else.
What about
the colchicine tablets, Charlie?
We found them in your car.
What the heck is colchicine?
I've seen the way
you look at her.
So you admit it.
I just wanted to feel...
...something...
...besides the grief.
But it didn't make me feel
any better.
Just made me feel more...
...guilt.
And that's all I feel anymore
is just grief and guilt.
Do you really expect me
to feel sorry for you?
She's Charlie's girlfriend.
-When Charlie finds out, he's...
-I know, okay?
I know.
And it kills me to think about
Charlie...
...laying there in the hospital
and me...
...I'm tired, Amanda.
I'm tired of all the fighting.
I'm tired about the lying.
I just want it all to be over.
You want what to be over?
You were right...
...about me all those years ago.
I cheated on Lauren.
And it was a stupid,
stupid mistake.
And I couldn't tell her.
And I regretted it
every day of my life.
And now she's...
...she's gone.
And I was too much of a coward
to tell her...
...to tell her how sorry I was...
...how it ate me up inside.
I really did love her
despite what you think.
I loved her more than anything.
I never meant to hurt her.
Where are you going?
Ian?
-This is Stone.
-Hey, Josh, it's Amanda.
-Can you talk?
-Yeah.
I was actually gonna call you.
I had a talk with Charlie
that was interesting.
Well, it'll be nothing compared
to what Ian just told me.
-He admitted to the affair.
-What?
Oh, you should've seen him...
...and heard the things
he was saying.
It was almost like...
...it was almost like
a confession.
I'm going to the wellness center.
Can you meet me there?
The center?
-Yeah, but I...
-Good.
Go now.
I can't do this anymore.
I won't be able
to live with myself.
I understand.
Did you do what we talked about?
Yeah.
I...
I told her about us...
...and how I cheated on Lauren.
Everything.
I'm really proud of you.
I know that wasn't easy,...
...but now you don't have to
carry the guilt.
And like Lauren always said,...
...Harmony starts from within.
So...
-Hey.
So, what's going on?
I need your help finding
something in Ian's office.
-What?
-I'll explain as we go.
I need a warrant to search.
But don't you own the business?
Oh, half, yeah, technically.
Do I have your permission
to search the premises?
So, what are we looking for?
Charlie said he was attacked
the night of the accident.
Normally, I'd take that
with a grain of salt,...
...but since he was also attacked
at the hospital,...
...it lends the story
some credence.
Well, how did it happen?
Well, someone drugged him
and pushed him over the ridge.
And you think his dad did it?
Well, stranger things
have happened.
When you told me
about the affair,...
...thought that sounded like
enough motive...
...to at least pursue him.
Now all we need is something
that connects him...
...to Charlie's accident.
Is that...
Looks like we found our weapon.
-Look.
-Colchicine.
I'm sorry, Amanda,
looks like you were right...
...about Ian all along.
Stone.
Got it.
Two shots fired at the house.
-Let's go.
-What?
Stay here. Lock the door.
Is anyone there?
Hello?
Maya, what are doing in there?
-It's Ian.
He...he did this to me.
We were in the cottage.
We were talking
and he pulled a gun.
-He just...
-Okay. Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
-Where is Ian now?
-I don't know.
I, I just took the bat.
I knocked him out with it...
-...and then I just ran.
-Okay.
Was that Amanda?
-Hey, are you okay?
-Hey. Yeah.
-He's inside.
-Okay.
Ian?
Is he...
No, he's still alive.
What? Take it easy.
-Take it easy.
-What...what's going on?
What's going on is,
you're under arrest.
-What?
-I have you on assault...
...with a deadly weapon,...
...attempted murder
of your son...
...and a possible murder
of your wife.
But this is insane.
Look, I don't know
what happened here,...
-...but I, I didn't hurt anyone.
-Let's go.
Maya, tell him.
I'm sorry, Ian, you need help.
Amanda?
-Please, just take him away.
-What? No.
No, you're,
you're making a mistake here.
Amanda, Maya.
It's over.
Oh, it's so good
to see you sitting upright.
It feels good, too.
I never thought I'd be so anxious
to get out of bed.
Yeah?
You still think you'll be able
to come home tomorrow?
That's what the doctor says.
Although, I'm not sure how much
it's gonna feel like home...
...after what you told me.
Charlie, I'm so sorry
for everything he did.
It's so hard to believe.
I know.
I'm still trying to wrap my brain
around it.
I mean,
why would he do that to her?
Or just for some insurance money?
That and the problems he was
having with Mom, apparently.
I still can't believe he told you
about the affair.
Me neither.
It was a long time coming.
Do you think there were others?
I don't know.
It's possible, I guess.
I never told mom this, but...
...I always believed you,
about Dad.
-You did?
-Yeah. I just...
I couldn't admit it.
Do you remember
a few years back,...
...when there was a vandalism
at the center?
-Yeah?
-I don't think it was a robbery.
I think Dad dumped a girl and
she took it out on the office.
Why are you telling me this?
Because...
...I wanted to say I'm sorry.
That maybe if I did,...
...things wouldn't have
ended up this way,...
...that maybe my mom
would've still been here.
Hey.
Don't blame yourself for this.
The only person at fault here
is Ian.
Okay?
Yeah.
All that matters now
is that you're coming home.
All right, we're gonna
get through this together.
We're family.
-Okay?
-All right.
We really haven't had a chance
to catch up...
...since the other night.
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
Here you go.
Yeah, I was fillin' out
a lot of paperwork,...
...trying to explain
what the heck happened.
I bet.
How are you holdin' up?
A little better.
But still pretty shaken up.
How about you?
How are things with Ian?
Just as belligerent.
Keeps comin' up with every excuse
to deny everything.
But he can't argue
with the evidence.
-I know.
-Hey, trust me.
He's going away for a long time.
And you can all put this
behind you.
I hear Charlie's comin' home.
He is. Yeah.
I just saw him this morning.
And they cleared him
to leave the hospital tomorrow.
-Good.
-So it'll be nice...
...to have him home.
Nice to make things
feel normal again.
Well, as normal as possible,
I guess.
How are things at the center?
Well, we closed it down
for a few days, you know,...
...while we try and figure out
what to do next.
Maya keeps saying that I should
take over instead of selling it.
And keep her on staff,...
-...I presume. Yeah.
-Yeah, I, I suppose so.
I just...
I never thought that I'd be...
...taking over Mom and Dad's
place. You know?
Well, Lauren's place.
Your place.
Well, for what it's worth,
I think you should stay.
Hello? Anybody there?
Aunt Amanda.
Hey, Charlie.
I'm sorry for calling so late.
-If you can't talk...
-No, no, it's okay,...
...the nurses have eased up on me
since it's my last day.
-Is everything okay?
-Yeah.
No, everything's great.
I just had a quick question.
Something I'm trying
to figure out.
Sure.
The day the colchicine tablets
were ordered,...
...you were on the computer.
I saw it on the security camera.
Okay.
But if you didn't order
the drugs,...
...then why were you
on the computer?
And I'm, I promise,
I'm not accusing you of anything.
I'm just trying to make sense
of it is all.
No, no, no, it's,
it's totally fine.
I, I get it. But ho...honestly,
I can't remember.
Okay, please try.
It would have been a few days
before the reopening.
Remember the night when your mom
asked me to join the business?
The order was placed
the following day.
Oh, wait.
That was the night
Mom started feeling nauseous.
Maya was looking after her,...
...so she asked me to check
the schedule on the computer.
What? Maya asked you
to use the computer?
Yeah. Why?
Hello?
Auntie Amanda?
Oh, good. You're awake.
Wha...
Maya, why are you doing this?
I didn't want this.
None of this
was supposed to happen.
Nobody was supposed to get hurt.
Nobody was supposed to die.
And then you came here
and ruined everything.
Just like you did
three years ago.
It was, it was you.
You're the one that Ian
had the affair with.
Yes, and everything was fine
and then you told Lauren.
And then Ian made it stop.
That's why you killed Lauren?
Because Ian broke it off?
No, I didn't mean to kill her!
I just started work here
to spite him.
He wanted me to leave it,
but then I fell for Charlie.
Oh, gosh.
Lauren was so nice to me.
She took me under her wing.
She trusted me,
she was grooming me,...
...relying on me.
And then you showed up.
And she...she just gives you
half the company.
That's not fair.
If you cared for Lauren so much,
why did you kill her?
I didn't mean to kill her.
I just wanted her to get sick.
I just wanted to take charge
while she recovered...
...and show her I deserve
to be here and not you.
It wasn't just Lauren.
You hurt Charlie.
And you framed Ian, too,
didn't you?
Planted the pills in his office?
You didn't give me a choice.
After everything
she did for you...
Lauren was nothing
but compassionate.
Tried to help you, but you,...
...you kill her and
you destroyed everything...
...she ever cared about.
Because of you!
You kept the detective going
and investigating.
I wasn't gonna lose
everything,...
...go to jail
for the rest of my life...
...because of one stupid mistake.
Do you understand that?
-You're a monster.
-No.
Well, unfortunately for you,...
...you're the only one
that thinks that.
No! No!
No.
For what it's worth,
I really am sorry.
Maya, please.
You don't have to do this.
Yes, I do.
But don't worry.
I'll take care of Charlie...
...and I'll carry on
Lauren's legacy.
Close your eyes and visualize.
Find a place
that brings you comfort.
Let calm wash over you and
let everything just disappear.
Good.
-Hey!
So, how's the new instructor?
She's good.
I mean, she's no Lauren,
but who is?
Hey, thanks for all your help...
-...around here, Charlie.
-Yeah.
I wouldn't be able to
run the place without you.
I'm really enjoying it.
And the view
ain't so bad, either.
You...you just work on
your inner peace, okay?
Hey.
I just wanted to say I'm sorry
for how I treated you...
...and for what I did.
I'm, I'm sorry, too,...
...for thinking
you could have done it.
I, I just wanna move forward.
I'm still working on
forgiving you...
...for everything with Maya,...
...but...
...I'm, I'm tired of being angry.
Yeah, me, too.
I'd like to give it a shot.
Me, too.
Hey, buddy.
So are you gonna tell
Ian and Maya?
Nah.
I've done that once before...
...and all I did was
tear the family apart.
He never had a chance
to ask Lauren for forgiveness.
So now's his chance with Charlie.
So...
...you decide if you're stayin'?
It looks that way.
I'm gonna run the center
with Ian and Charlie.
And just a fresh new start.
I think Lauren would be proud.
Yeah.
Feel the calm.
Feel the air around you.
Let go of your past.
The future is not here yet.
Just be in the present
with your breath and your calm.
Let go of your surroundings.
Let go of all material things.
Allow yourself peace and calm.
Let the past retreat.
Be here in the moment.
Good.