All these years.
I've written so many books
with fantastic themes.
Everyone that sees me will ask.
how can you come out all these?
Is it real story?
This is a stupid question
Everyone, in everyday.
there are a lot happen around you.
Every tiny little thing.
if you wish you dig up.
it may come out with a fantastic story
If you hang out with your friends.
you may find out many interesting stories
thru their talk.
Tonight, for instance.
two of my friends are here.
Wesley
Mr, Ngai
Hello, where's Yuan Chen?
He's over there.
You've got nice glasses
Mr, Ngai
Congratulations on winning
the titles of Miss Asia.
Thanks
Cheers.
Yuan Chen, you had a daring adventure
with Wesley, didn't you?
Really? Tell us about it
Mr, Ngai is a good story teller.
Let him tell it
A good story, starts from
a good glass of wine.
Hound calling Thunderbird
Are all units ready?
I'm Thunderbird There are 6 bandits.
One of them is a sharpshooter
They all carry heavy weapons.
Tell everyone to be alert.
What's up there, Hound?
Hound, how are you, Hound?
Stop fire!
You all listen.
you gunned down a hostage!
He's having a serious heart attack.
If the doctor doesn't come, he'll be dead!
The doctor is on his way
You have been surrounded
You stand no chance of escape, Give up!
What is it?
Miss.
I'm the reporter of Western Daily.
We know But it's dangerous
so you can't get in
Please, I just wanna take a picture.
No way!
What now, Wonder Woman?
They don't let me in
I'm Doctor Yuan Are you Captain Ho?
The hostage is inside, He has heart attack
Why have to be me?
Well.
We have heard
a lot your bravery
We hope you can go in to plant a bomb
to help us save the hostage
I don't know what to do.
Inspector Kong
Yes, sir.
Dr,Yuan, I'll be the nurse to follow you in.
I'll defuse it
Go and prepare everything
Yes!
The bomb is in a layer of the first aid kit.
How is everything? OK?
Dr, Yuan, remember, it's 1 2 o'clock sharp.
We'll break in at that time
The doctor's here, Don't open fire
Scatter!
Freeze!
Bitch, don't move
I'm a woman, bitch.
Go!
Don't play tricks, kid
Where's the patient?
Get up, go!
Gimme the stethoscope
Calm down, I'm a doctor
The heart-stimulant injection
What are you doing?
Brother, a gun!
Bloody kid, you dare to fool me?
Start!
Stop!
Who are you?
I'm a reporter
Don't you know that you nearly ruined us?
I'm sorry
Where's my camer?
I wanna take some pictures.
You still wanna take pictures?
Thank you, Dr, Yuan
We are now in control.
Good, I gotta go now.
OK, retreat
Yes!
Are you gonna arrest me?
I've seen many pretty girls.
None is crazy like you
Don't you know that you may get in jail?
That
Go now
Thank you
Dr, Yuan, thank you
Not a problem.
Captain Ho.
We have to thank
lnspector Kong for just now
Captain Ho!
Ain't you that sexology writer Dr, Chor?
Danny Wong?
I've heard that you have
been writing an essay
on the climate's effect
on male sex potential?
This is merely a ratio in Mathematics.
The temperature and time constitute a ratio.
The length is one hour in tropical South
Half an hour in the central part
About 2-3 minutes in
the low-temperature North.
I remember you come from
the South Sea lsland.
According to your theory.
I should have come from North Pole.
Really?
There are some pretty chicks there
Dr, Chor, take the wine.
Leave me the girl.
Is it fun?
It's funny
Do you believe in constellation?
I can readily see you must be a Virgo.
Well, take your time.
Annie, let's sit over there
A Virgo girl's best mate is a Taurus guy.
just like me You must be Cancer.
I have quite a lotta collections.
A human head made by the New Guinea tribe.
It was shrunk to the size of a monkey head
It sounds horrible
And, there are some toes
chopped down by alien
so nasty, what else?
And me, Yuan Chan.
I have something important to talk to you
What the heck are you doing?
Miss, don't be fooled by him.
Lemme be honest to you, he's married.
What are you talking about?
Please excuse me a while.
Bye.
Annie!
You stay.
What on earth do you exactly want?
Sorry, I know I have screwed up your plan
But I need you on something important.
Shoot!
I'd like to feature you in Western Daily
to introduce your heroic deeds.
I'll take a naked photo of you
I promise you that it will
have a sense of beauty
My technique is not bad, Trust me
Sorry, it's not my fault It's that guy,,.
Idiot!
Stop!
Sayonara!
Hi.
Idiot, I thought I couldn't catcha
You such a bloody nasty bastard!
I'm sorry
You really hurt me
How did you get in? Where's Maria?
I gave her $1 000 and said
you let her have a day off.
Oh, I see
I've fooled by woman all night.
Yuan Chan!
Who are you?
You have to follow me back to Thailand
You have to help yourself and Betsy
What are you talking about?
Your blood spell has reached one year
You will soon relapse
Betsy got a ghost spell as well
We need your help.
I don't understand what
you are talking about
Stop acting, This is my address in Thailand.
I'll wait for you three days
Don't go away
What's your name?
My name is Black Dragon
Listen, keep away from sex
Or you may have a quick relapse
Who's that guy? I'm so scared
That's alright, No problem.
Mr, Wai, you're my best friend and master
I think only you can help me.
Have you ever been to North Thailand?
So, bring us two cups of coffee, please.
Sure.
Apparently you have been under blood spell.
Lemme know the detail.
It was like this
About a year ago.
I followed a medical team to North Thailand.
to seek a kind of herbs for treating AlDS
Morning.
Good morning.
Professor, I'd like to take
a walk about the lake.
Be careful Here's quite near
to Yunnan, Chinese Miao tribe.
They say a kind of worm
tribe specialize in witchcraft
I only believe in science.
Sorry for breaking your gem
Never mind I still have spare, Keep this.
Really?
Yes
I have to go.
You should get close to that girl.
Their tribe's cruel
and knows witchcraft
Professor, if they cast a spell
to anyone who talks to.
they must be damn busy
Anyways, I'm the team leader
It's my responsibility to protect you guys.
Sounds of the drum?
It comes from the worm
tribe and signal offerings
They are offering to god, eh?
Don't ever go and see it.
We won't!
What a big procession!
Go over there.
It's her
Who?
The girl I saw this afternoon
Which one?
I don't know either
Have you made up your mind?
I won't say YES.
Probably you have been chosen for offering
When Old Ancestor wakes up, you'll die
You deliberately sent
Black Dragon away and picked me
I only love him.
I won't submit.
My guys.
As a previous years.
when Old Ancestor wakes up.
someone honored by God will be chosen.
Betsy is the daughter of the ex-chief.
please don't offer her to God
This is the will of God.
But we have never tried
Anyone else refusing to do this?
Send them to the grave.
I have to rescue her
You kidding?
Are you crazy? You may be killed!
I'll play to the score.
You guys go get the weapon
No
Don't go
What now?
What shall we do now?
Run!
He's our Old Ancestor. He won't die.
Run! Leave me!
I told you to run Just leave me!
Help me!
Hurry up!
Intruders! Go and see!
Yes!
Drum sound?
He's pursuing you for your intrusion
Run!
Professor!
You brought the mess because
you didn't listen to me
Go back to the camp and pack up at once.
Go, quickly.
Besty, Besty!
Get in the car!
You two destroyed the sacrifice
and blasphemed Old Ancestor
I'll punish you behalf of God
Professor, you...
Yuan Chan, help me!
These worms are highly prolific
Don't worry.
I won't use them on you
I'm sorry for you guys
Run, quickly!
Don't let them get hold of you Run!
This is my talismanic worm.
I'm using it to help you, but
When I woke up, Betsy was gone.
The 7 bloodstains on my body were gone.
So I left alone.
I've been back to HK a year
and nothing happened
But now,,.
Black Dragon warned you
Why don't you trust him?
I don't even know him
How do I know what he wants me?
That's right
You guys
What's wrong, Chan?
So, go get the first aid kit.
The 2nd blood curst has burst
When did the first burst occur?
More or less the same time.
It means one burst every 24 hour.
When it spreads to the heart.
you'll die in 5 days
Mr. Wai, you know witchcraft well.
Is there any chance of survival for me?
Blood curse is the most mysterious.
and complex of its kind in witchcraft.
Betsy used a spell to save you
But it worked for one year only
There must be a reason Black Dragon
wants you go to go Thailand.
You want me to go to Thailand?
Chan,only the doer can undo a damage done.
Ok, I'll go see him tomorrow
Such an exciting thing.
You gotta gimme the scoop on this
You again?
Cousin, you know much about him?
Mr. Wai?
Chan, Rainbow is Wai's spoiled cousin
Don't be mad
You wanna screw up everything
I know him well
Fine, I don't wanna take your naked photo
Lemme go with you to Thailand, OK?
You think I'm going traveling?
Rainbow, it's serious, You can't go.
You mean I'm not qualified?
I went through fire and water with Dr Yuan.
You agree so?
I won't let you go with me.
Chan, I have something to do tomorrow.
I'll meet you up the day after.
Call the Thai police if anything happens.
I'll keep in touch with them.
Thank you
No problem
Cousin, you don't wanna help me?
A reporter shouldn't go too far in coverage.
This is a matter of life and death.
You are only in for kicks, Stay out of it.
Mr. Yuan Chan?
I am.
Please follow me.
You are?
My boss sends me to pick you up
You'll know when you see
Where's your boss?
Mr, Yuan, please take a rest
Thanks
Idiot
You again?
I came on earlier flight
Why there are so many weapons?
We're going to a primitive jungle
It's unsafe without them.
This is the latest laser-guided gun.
Can you afford it?
My dad is Tung Tai Ping.
Property magnate Tung Tai Ping?
I couldn't care less
As long as I have a Gold
card for an unlimited sum
Pretty, nescience, young, hell-bent,,.
and rich.
I think you are the most troublesome
woman in the world
I always pay for into out of my own pocket
We are not going to war
These can't overcome witchcraft.
Let's talk about business
I've already made a promise to the editor
And got in touch with the United Press
If your info can be front-page
in world newspaper.
I'll split half the profit with you
I'm in no mood for your frenzied idea
I don't care, I wanna go with you.
Are you going to tie me up?
Hey, idiot, let me go.
Don't ever underrate a man
You finally come
You seem like
I was being pursued immediately returned.
Who pursued you?
The sorcerer, He knew that I found you.
He conspired with the underworld against us.
They're all of a kind
I was assaulted when I returned.
Let's leave right now.
Is this the worm tribe?
No, it's a good tribe working of farmers.
But they often attacked by the worm tribe.
Dragon, it's good to have you back
Chief, what happened?
A weird thing happened.
All kids in the village
disappeared this afternoon.
All disappear?
Yep
What happened?
All kids in our village are disappeared.
It must be the sorcerer have abducted
them for casting Little Ghost Spell
Little Ghost Spell?
Yes, it's made of 1 00 children's blood
They can fly, suck blood and kill people
The spell has to be remade
after three years.
How cruel he is!
Right, I saw the little ghost
on the offering night.
The chief wants me to bring men
to rescue the kids
OK.
I wanna go, too.
It's so quiet tonight.
Yep
Not even chirps
There must be something wrong.
Be careful!
Run quickly!
Don't run Come back!
It hurts!
I told you not to follow.
Don't you know how dangerous is it?
I've already followed you all the way
There's no way not to continue.
Don't you know that there are
many booby-traps here?
Don't worry, I have read quite
many books of Vietcong tactics
when I studied in US
That shows I can take care of myself.
Fine, we have to work
against time now, Let's go.
I'll go up and have a look, Keep quiet
Rainbow!
Where are you going?
To take pictures
Rainbow, I have to be responsible
for your safety if you're with me
It's too dangerous I can't let you go
I don't care, What a male chauvinist!
Rainbow, listen.
I've been through this It's too dangerous
Things are beyond your control.
Let go!
I'm telling you, if you touch me again.
I'll tell my cousin you hares me
Though with your reputation.
few people will believe that.
I don't care what you say
You have to listen to me
Or I'll spank you without pants
How dare you?
You nasty!
So what?
I won't care about you
I'm leaving now, I won't come back.
Up to you
I won't return even if
I were bitten by snakes.
hit by arrows or scared by men!
I won't care for you anymore Don't regret.
You're so cruel hearted
Bye-bye
She's away in a twinkle
The kids are all caged and guarded.
We'd better go and help Betsy first.
OK.
Where's Miss Rainbow?
She got pissed off and she left
Never mind her Where's Betsy?
Betsy?
Dragon.
I've brought back Dr Yuan.
I'm here, Betsy
Don't come over
I don't want anyone to see me now.
Forget it, Her looks scared me
Betsy, the 4th blood curse on me has burst.
We have to figure out how
to save you and me
My dad told me before he died.
Some holy ashes can break
any kinds of spell
I consulted the records of the tribe.
And have found the hiding place.
Where?
A large Buddha in a cave It's out of reach.
No one can climp up.
So they are unobtainable
I believe that you're
my saviour from Heaven.
So I sent Dragon to get you
We can have a try
You only have 3 days to live.
No other choice
I'll go telegram them.
Askk them to prepare everything.
Besides, the Ashes will wither in 6 hours
after you take out.
Help! What are you doing? Put me down!
I'll give you money, Release me!
Release me!
Release her.
You must be the boss here.
You're such a nice guy.
I gotta go, bye
I've got the wrong way and been trapped
Did you send by Black Dragon?
No, I'm here to collect specimens
You look handsome.
Lemem take a photo for you
Damn you!
OK, I know Fine Over!
Backup and equipment are coming soon
Rainbow's not back yet.
What takes her so long?
Where 's she been to?
There're 2 possibilities, one is dead.
and one is been caught
If she's been caught, where could she be?
She's an outsider.
must be taken to the sorcerer.
Let's save Betsy first.
Rescue Rainbow.
Good buddy!
Miss Rainbow.
How is her?
Her temperature is weird
But she's not having a fever or cold
Lemme go and see if the backup's arrived
Rainbow!
What happened?
She goes berserk and is herculean
Rainbow, what are you doing?
Catch her!
What happened?
She's caught by the Sorcerer.
Then she's like this after we found her.
I think she must have got the Black Spell.
So she's herculean and wants to kill
How can we break the spell?
Lemme help you.
Betsy?
Black is needed to break a black spell.
Mix the blood of Black sheep, oxen.
dogs, cats, snakes, eagles and lizards.
Boil it and bathe her with it.
Immerse her until she wakes up
Ghost!
What happened?
What's up?
She saw my face
It's OK.
The sorcerer persecuted her like this
She saved you.
She's fine now
Dr, Yuan, there's not much time.
Go find the Ashes?
Black Dragon
No matter if you can find it.
you have to come back
I wanna go with you
Rainbow, be good
Then,,,you have to come back!
What happened?
Mr. Wai, the 6th curse has burst.
Not much bleeding.
But when the 7th bursts.
all your blood will spill out.
Mr, Wai, tomorrow is
the last day of my life
Yuan Chan, I don't believe
in fate can contral a brave man.
I think man conquers fate.
Black Dragon.
what's the name of that sorcerer?
Sorcerer Aquala
Aquala?
The witchcraft of this clan is the most
mysterious and cruel in the South.
Did he practice Little Ghost Spell?
Yes
Get a pregnant cow at once
Slaughter it and get her placenta out.
A black dog as well and get its blood.
Yes!
Wesley, what is it for?
To break the Little Ghost Spell.
a friend of Aquala Clan taught me that
I don't know if it works
Chan, it's all up to yourself.
Old Ancestor, gimme power!
Use the blood power
to turn into blood ghosts
Go kill the guys of Yuan Chan!
Where are those two grains of ashes?
Inside the eyes
We gotta climb up.
do you have problem with it?
Ha, I have even climbed the Himalaya.
They say no one trying it has ever come out.
It all depends on us
Watch out!
Be careful!
Yuan Chan!
Masters.
we try to get them to help someone only.
Please do us a favor, masters.
Run, quick!
Duck it!
Yuan Chan!
Swallow it now to break the blood spell.
Swallow it!
We have to go back in 2 hours.
Or the other grain will become ineffective
Rainbow Betsy have been taken by them.
Go rescue them quickly!
I'll catcha you guys later.
Old Ancestor is so happy today.
To have three men and three girls for food
God will punish you.
Yuan Chan is coming to kill you
I'm waiting for them now.
We are here!
I told you he would come
Old Ancestor!
Aquala, you did many atrocties
I'll make you pay for them now.
Old Ancestor!
Let's go!
Watch out!
Rainbow!
Black Dragon!
Stay aside!
Let loose the Little Ghost!
Where's the grain?
It's here.
Damn, it's over the time.
Betsy can't restore her original looks then
Dragon, would you love me still
if I look like this all my life?
The sorcerer is dead Our tribes
can lead a new life from now on.
I can help them live better.
Isn't that a pity?
Beauty lies on one's heart.
not on one's face