Hudson,
Cheelik is wrong
about you. All wrong.
I helped raise you. I know.
Where are you going?
Unless I find out who tried to
kill me for the claim,
they will come back.
I'm going to Nome.
They will kill you.
If you fight for the cave,
and I know you will,
they will kill you.
Goodbye and good luck.
Take care of the dogs.
-CHEELIK: White man's trouble!
-Come.
Haina, take care of her.
NAKKI:
So you stole this woman?
Only to get away.
Let us stay until
the storm passes.
HUDSON: I'll take her back
when it's dark.
NAKKI: It is
too dangerous for us!
HUDSON: She's freezing.
If she stays out
she'll die.
Thank you.
The white man cannot
track you in this weather.
You may stay as long as
the storm continues.
Thank you, Nakki.
We're looking for
the white woman.
The half-breed brought her
here. We know that.
We haven't seen anyone...