[GROWL]
[SPEAKING ATHABASCAN]
[SLED DOGS BARKING]
[RIFLE BREECH
ACTION]
WHERE IS HUDSON SAANTEEK?
[SPEAKING ATHABASCAN]
YOU HAVE TO LEAVE.
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE HERE,
NOT NOW.
PLEASE.
WHOA. DON'T
BUY YOURSELF TROUBLE.
I WANT THE MAN
THAT SIGNED THE CLAIM.
NOBODY HAS A CLAIM.
THIS IS A SACRED PLACE.
ASK THEM AGAIN,
SMILEY.
JESUS. A MOUNTAIN
OF SOLID GOLD.
Smiley: SO...
WHERE IS HE?
Cheelik: JUST
LEAVE US ALONE.
THIS IS OUR GRANDFATHER.
WE'RE SAYING
OUR GOODBYES.
UHH!
THERE.
I'LL ASK YOU AGAIN.
WHERE IS HUDSON SAANTEEK?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
GET OUT!
HUDSON!
Reno: DON'T LET HIM
GET AWAY!
WHERE IS HE?
UP THERE!
COME ON!
THIS WAY!
UH!
SMOKE!
[SPEAKING ATHABASCAN]
KILL THE SON
OF A BITCH!
OVER THERE!
[GUNSHOT]
YEE-HAW!
GOT HIM.
YOU GOT HIM, HUH?
YEAH.
LET'S GET BACK
TO NOME.
I'LL BUY YOUSE ALL
A NICE, WARM HOOKER.
BJORN,
WELCOME BACK.
PAPA?
SON!
YOU'VE GROWN.
YOU'RE HOME!
Man: MORNING,
MISS SARA.
I'LL TAKE HER,
THANK YOU.
MAMA.
WHAT IS IT?
BJORN.
IT'S SO GOOD
TO SEE YOU.
HANNA.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
WHAT IS IT?
THIS WINTER, YOU WILL
HAVE A ROOM OF YOUR OWN.
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
CAN YOU FEEL HOW WARM?
IT'S GOLD.
SOLD!
THE KOSOKTOK MINE,
TO THIS LUCKY MAN,
FOR $250.
NEXT UP.
THE NORTH STAR FALLS.
FORMER OWNER:
HUDSON SAANTEEK,
DECEASED.
THE BIDDING
WILL START AT $200.
DO I HEAR $200?
$200.
$200 I AM BID.
DO I HEAR 225?
225.
225. THE MAN--
250.
300.
325.
325 I AM BID.
DO I HEAR $400?
I DON'T. NO.
$400.
425.
450.
I'M BID 450,
THE MAN AT THE BACK.
GOING ONCE.
Man: 1,000.
$1,000 IS THE BID!
GOING ONCE.
GOING TWICE.
[GAVEL SLAMS]
SOLD TO
MR. SEAN McLENNON,
NEW OWNER
OF THE NORTH STAR CLAIM.
I'M, UH, VERY SORRY
ABOUT THAT.
SEEMS I EDGED YOU OUT
BY JUST A SMIDGEN.
MR. HANSON.
BJORN, WAIT FOR US.
COME ON.
HURRY UP.
I WANT TO CLAIM A STAKE.
YOU MEAN
STAKE A CLAIM.
YES, THAT.
NAME.
BJORN SVENSON.
WHERE'S THIS CLAIM AT?
HERE.
PROOF OF CITIZENSHIP.
UH, I'M SWEDISH.
I'M SORRY,
MR., UH, SVENSON.
UNLESS YOU'RE
AN AMERICAN CITIZEN,
I HAVE TO DENY
YOUR CLAIM.
WHAT?
I--I DON'T--
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
ACCORDING TO THE MINERS
ASSOCIATION,
FOREIGNERS CAN
NO LONGER STAKE CLAIMS
ON AMERICAN LAND.
BUT IT'S MY CLAIM.
I-I'VE BEEN DIGGING
FOR 8 MONTHS.
THAT'S WHY I CAME HERE.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S NOT MY RULE.
GIVE ME MY MAP.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S NOW THE PROPERTY
OF THE NORTH AMERICAN
MINERS ASSOCIATION.
GIVE ME MY MAP!
MR. SVENSON.
DON'T YOU JUMP MY CLAIM,
YOU BANDIT!
HEY. HEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
THEY SAY...
FOREIGNERS CAN'T
MAKE CLAIMS HERE.
THEY STOLE MY MAP.
WHO? WHO?
HE!
THAT'S AGAINST THE LAW.
WE'RE ONLY FOLLOWING
MINERS ASSOCIATION RULES,
LINDBERG.
IF YOU WANT TO COMPLAIN,
YOU KNOW WHERE TO GO.
ALL RIGHT.
COME ON.
WHERE'S McLENNON?
WHO?
THE OWNER, YOUR BOSS.
OH, McLENNON.
I HAVEN'T
SEEN HIM.
WHERE'S McLENNON?
YES?
GENTLEMEN,
CAN I HELP YOU?
HOW DARE YOU
DENY THESE MEN
THEIR CLAIMS.
OH, I SEE.
YOU, UH...
YOU THINK THIS
IS A CLAIMS OFFICE.
THIS MAN WAS
DENIED HIS CLAIM
BECAUSE HE WAS
NOT A CITIZEN,
AFTER 8 MONTHS
OF DIGGING.
DO YOU THINK
THAT'S JUST?
WELL, ACCORDING TO
THE MINERS ASSOCIATION,
YES, IT IS JUST.
YOU ARE THE MINERS
ASSOCIATION.
AH.
YES, THAT'S TRUE.
I AM THE PRESIDENT,
AND, AS
THE PRESIDENT,
IT IS MY DUTY
TO INFORM YOU
THAT WE'RE ABOUT
TO HOLD A MEETING
WHICH WILL DECLARE
ALL FOREIGN CLAIMS
VOID AND ILLEGAL.
NO!
NO!YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
WITHOUT THEIR CLAIMS,
THESE MEN WILL
FREEZE TO DEATH
ON THE BEACHES.
WELL, NOBODY
ASKED THESE MEN
TO COME TO NOME.
[CROWD MURMURING]
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
A MAN FREEZE TO DEATH,
MR. McLENNON?
A FROZEN MAN
OR THE ACTUAL...
FREEZING PROCESS?
[LAUGHTER]
'CAUSE, YOU SEE,
THE ACTUAL
FREEZING PROCESS
IS QUITE
SOMETHING TO SEE.
BECAUSE THE BODY'S
NATURAL INSTINCT
IS TO FALL ASLEEP,
BUT ANYWAY,
FIRST THE JOINTS
AND THE TENDONS,
THEY CONTRACT
INTO LITTLE KNOTS,
AND THEN...
YOUR EXTREMITIES,
YOU KNOW, YOUR NOSE,
YOUR FINGERS,
YOUR...
SEX ORGANS.
[CROWD LAUGHS]
UM, THEY GET
FROSTBITTEN
AND FALL OFF.
THEN YOUR BREATHING
SHUTS OFF AND YOU
ASPHYXIATE.
IT'S TERRIBLE.
DO YOU EXPECT THESE MEN
WILL STAND BY
AND WATCH THIS HAPPEN
TO THEIR WIVES
AND CHILDREN?
DO YOU?
I EXPECT THESE MEN
TO GO HOME.
WE AIN'T GOIN' HOME.
WE ARE
A PROUD GROUP.
IN THE WORDS
OF A FELLOW SCOT--
I, UH, OF COURSE,
WAS BORN HERE--
BUT A MR. MacBETH
SAID,
WHEN OUR ACTIONS
DO NOT,
OUR FEARS DO
MAKE US TRAITORS.
AND I HAVE NO FEAR
TO TELL THE TRUTH,
WHICH IS THAT
I DON'T CARE
IF YOU PEOPLE
FREEZE TO DEATH.
BECAUSE AS FAR
AS I'M CONCERNED,
YOU'RE TRESPASSING.
[ANGRY SHOUTING]
DAMN YOU!
HOW DARE YOU!
YOU ARE STEALING
FROM THE PEOPLE
TO WHOM
THIS COUNTRY BELONGS.
SO, YOU SEE, IT'S EITHER
YOUR LIVES...OR OURS.
NOW, THAT'S NOT A VERY
HARD DECISION TO MAKE,
IS IT?
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
RENO,
SMILEY.
NO!
IF YOU'RE GOING
TO TAKE MY CLAIM,
YOU'LL HAVE TO KILL ME
LIKE ALL THE OTHERS.
AND WHY NOT DO IT NOW?
COME ON, GET THEM
OUT OF HERE.
GET THESE GUYS OUT.
GET HIM.
Smiley: HEY, YOU.
GET OUT.
COME ON.
YOU HEARD ME.
NO, I DIDN'T.
GODDAMN! GODDAMN,
I'LL KILL YOU!
GET HIM OUT!
HEY! HALT!
WHAT THE HELL'S
HAPPENING HERE?
THESE MEN ARE
STEALING
FROM US.
THEY'RE THIEVES.
[GUNSHOTS]
WELL, THAT'S BETTER.
McLENNON, WHAT'S
HAPPENING HERE?
WELL, THESE, UH...
THESE FOREIGNERS
CAME INTO MY SALOON
AND STARTED TEARING
THE PLACE APART.
LIAR! YOU
STARTED THIS.
LET'S HAVE
SOME ORDER HERE.
ORDER? YOU CALL
THIS ORDER?
HE'S--HE'S PLANNING
TO TAKE OVER
ALL OUR CLAIMS.
TAKE IT EASY.
HE'S...STARTING A WAR.
LOOK, I'LL HANDLE THIS.
YOUWILL?
HAH!
YOU MAY OWN THE TOWN,
McLENNON,
BUT YOU DON'T OWN ME.
WE'LL BE BACK, McLENNON.
Hanna:
DON'T FIGHT, BJORN.
COME ON. COME ON,
LET'S GO. GO.
McLENNON...
I'M GONNA HAVE
TO REPORT THIS
TO COLONEL JOHNSON.
A BARROOM BRAWL?
IT SEEMS LIKE
A LOCAL MATTER TO ME,
BUT, UH...IF IT'S
A LITTLE TOO BIG
FOR YOU, SHERIFF...
McLENNON, I'M NOT GOING
TO HAVE VIOLENCE HERE.
THESE FOREIGNERS
AIN'T GONNA STAND BY
AND WATCH YOU
WIPE OUT THEIR CLAIMS,
AND, BETWEEN
YOU AND ME,
CONGRESS AIN'T GONNA
APPROVE IT EITHER.
AND THERE'S TALK
ABOUT AN AUDIT
OF THE CLAIMS OFFICE.
I'M SORRY, SEAN.
I'M GONNA HAVE
TO REPORT THIS.
WELL...
SHERIFF, I GUESS YOU GOT
TO DO WHAT YOU GOT TO DO.
RENO, SMILEY, COME ON,
WE GOT WORK TO DO.
Cheelik: YOU BROUGHT
THE WHITE MAN HERE.
THEY KILLED MY GRANDFATHER
BECAUSE OF YOU.
I'M SORRY.
BUT I HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH IT.
WHY DID YOU
STEAL OUR CAVE?
I DIDN'T
STEAL ANYTHING.
WHY DO THEY SAY
IT'S YOURS THEN?
WHY?
I CLAIMED IT
TO PROTECT IT.
YOU CLAIMED IT
FOR THE GOLD.
AS LONG AS I HAVE THIS,
THE CAVE IS STILL YOURS.
WE DON'T NEED YOU
TO PROTECT WHAT'S OURS.
YOU CAN'T PROTECT
YOURSELF FROM THEM.
I KNOW THESE MEN.
THEY CRAVE GOLD.
TO THEM, IT'S JUST
ANOTHER MOUNTAIN.
SOONER OR LATER,
THEY WOULD HAVE COME
TO FIND AND DESTROY IT.
AND YOU ARE HALF
OF ONE OF THEM,
AND YOU WILL DESTROY US.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
BESIDES...
THEY THINK I'M DEAD.
GOODBYE, UNCLE.
[VOICE-OVER]
"NORMAN OLSON, DECEASED.
"NEW OWNER, SEAN McLENNON.
"DOMINIC TROPINI, DECEASED.
NEW OWNER, SEAN McLENNON."
"HUDSON SAANTEEK, DECEASED.
"NEW OWNER...
SEAN McLENNON."
[URINATING]
Smiley: WHAT THE HELL?
DAMN.
[PLAYING
CLASSICAL MUSIC]
WHAT IS IT, SMILEY?
AHEM.
WE GOT A PROBLEM.
NOT NOW.
A BIG PROBLEM.
[STOPS PLAYING]
SEAN, WHAT THE--
BIG-TIME GUNFIGHTER, HUH?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
NOTHING BUT
A BROKEN-DOWN BUM.
GET OUT.
GET OUT NOW. NOW.
HE'S DEAD, HUH?
THE GUY'S DEAD?
Smiley: HEY,
I SAW THE INDIAN.
HE'S ALIVE.
I BOUGHT THAT MINE
BECAUSE I THOUGHT YOU
COULD DO SOMETHING
BESIDES THIS.
NOW I'M IN DEEP SHIT.
DEEP SHIT.
I WANT THAT HALF-BREED DEAD.
YOU'RE A BUM.
I THOUGHT
YOU SHOT HIM.
HEY, MAYBE I MISSED.
I, UH...
SQUARE PIECE
OF GARBAGE.
MY SARA.
READ ALOUD.
"MAKE ME A WILLOW CABIN
AT YOUR GATE,
"AND CALL UPON MY SOUL
WITHIN THE HOUSE.
"WRITE ROYAL CANTONS
OF CONDEMNED LOVE
"AND SING THEM LOUD
EVEN IN THE DEAD
OF NIGHT.
TWELFTH NIGHT.
"SHOUT YOUR NAME
TO THE REVERBERATE HILLS
"AND MAKE THE BABBLING
GOSSIP OF THE AIR
"CRY OUT 'OLIVIA.'
"AND YOU SHOULD NOT REST
BETWEEN THE ELEMENTS
OF AIR AND EARTH,
BUT YOU SHOULD PITY ME."
NO WAY HE'S
STILL IN TOWN.
I'LL GO BACK
AND BURN DOWN
THE WHOLE GODDAMN
INDIAN VILLAGE.
RENO SAID TO LOOK OUT
FOR HIM ALL NIGHT.
OH, RENO.
WHILE HE STAYS IN BED.
GODDAMN!
GODDAMN. I KILLED
THAT INDIAN.
[WIND BLOWING]
[CURTAINS FLUTTERING]
YOU'VE GONE TOO FAR,
McLENNON.
YOU WANT THE CAVE?
DEAL WITH ME.
LEAVE THE INDIANS ALONE.
YOU GOT THAT?
THEY HAVE NOTHING
TO DO WITH IT.
IT'S JUST
BETWEEN YOU AND ME.
[TRIGGER COCKS]
GET AWAY
FROM HIM!
GET OUT!
Sara: RENO! QUICK!
RENO!
SOMEONE!
QUICK! HELP!
QUICK. SOMEONE'S
ATTACKED SEAN.
STAY HERE.
Sara: RENO!
SMILEY! QUICK!
HELP ME!
HELP!
Hudson: DON'T MOVE.
RENO, PLEASE!
PUT YOUR GUNS DOWN,
OR I'LL KILL HER.
RENO!
LET ME GO!
SEAN!
GET OFF ME!
YOU'RE KILLING ME!
LET ME GO!
HEY, WHAT'S
GOING ON?
HEY, LET GO
OF HER!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH MY SLED?
HELP! HELP!
STOP!
DON'T SHOOT!
HELP!
NO!
SEAN!
GET THE SLEDS READY
AND GET THE GODDAMN TRACKER!
YOU MEAN THE INDIAN?
YEAH, THE INDIAN.
[SLED DOGS BARKING]
MAKE SURE
SEAN'S SLEDS ARE READY.
YOU FORMIN'
A POSSE?
NO. GOIN' FISHIN'.
DON'T FORGET
HIS RIFLE.
OF COURSE
I'M FORMING A POSSE.
ANY MONEY IN IT?
YOU TWO HELP GET
THE GIRL BACK,
I'LL MAKE SURE YOU NEVER
LOOK AT ANOTHER MINE.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, ANNIE.
ANNIE, WE'RE
GONNA BE RICH.
STOP IT!
STAY DOWN!
LET ME GO!
WHAT'S GOING ON,
McLENNON?
YOU'RE LATE,
AREN'T YOU?
YOU KNOW, A POSSE AIN'T LEGAL
WITHOUT THE LAW BEHIND IT.
STAY AND DO YOUR JOBS.
NO!
STOP!
COME BACK!
MA'AM!
HELP!
WHERE ARE YOU RUNNING TO?
THERE'S NOWHERE TO GO.
GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
I WON'T HURT YOU.
HOLD ON TO ME.
[MOANING]
GO! GO!
[SHOUTING COMMANDS
TO DOGS]
HAH!
[FEVERED MOANING]
STOP!
HEY.
HANG ON.
PLEASE HANG ON.
I'LL TAKE YOU
TO SOMEPLACE WARM.
GO! GO!
HAH! HAH!
HYAH! HYAH!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
THE GIRL JUMPED OUT.
SHE RAN DOWN THERE.
HE BROUGHT HER BACK,
THEN CONTINUED.
I CAN'T WAIT
TO KILL THAT INDIAN.
HE'S NOT AN INDIAN.
HE'S A HALF-BREED.
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE?
LET'S GO.
[SHOUTING IN ATHABASKAN]
YEAH! YEAH!
WE DON'T WANT YOU HERE!
Hudson:
HELP ME!
Cheelik: YOU BRING
NOTHING BUT TROUBLE.
LEAVE ME ALONE!
Cheelik:
WHITE MAN'S TROUBLE!
Hudson: HELP ME!
Cheelik:
YOU BRING DEATH.
[SARA MOANING]
DON'T WORRY.
SHE'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU.
[MOANING]
[DOGS BARKING]
WHITE MEN!
[SPEAKING ATHABASKAN]
WE HAVE TO GO.
DON'T TOUCH ME.
IF YOU STAY HERE,
THEY WILL KILL EVERYONE.
LET'S GO. COME ON.
DON'T TOUCH ME!
LET'S GO.
LET ME GO!
COME ON!
NO! NO!
GO! QUICK!
[SHOUTING IN ATHABASKAN]
[SPEAKING ATHABASKAN]
HE SAYS HE DIDN'T--
I KNOW
WHAT HE SAID.
I CAN SEE IT
IN HIS LYING FACE.
GO LOOK FOR TRACKS.
I FOUND TRACKS.
WE GO WHILE
THEY'RE STILL FRESH.
HEY!
WAKE UP!
STOP!
UNH!
DON'T SLEEP!
WAKE UP!
HYAH!
YUB-LUB!
AAH!
OH!
[DOGS BARKING]
UNH!
[FOOTSTEPS]
I JUST HATE
THIS GODDAMN SNOW!
Gwill: CHRIST.
Smiley: GOD!
Smiley: YOU MEAN
ALL THIS TIME,
WE'VE BEEN CHASING
AN EMPTY SLED?!
HE'S BEEN DRAGGIN'
US ALONG BEHIND A
GODDAMN EMPTY SLED!
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN,
YOU GODDAMN INDIAN!
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO DO,
KILL US?
I'LL KILL HIM!
I'LL--
SMILEY,
TAKE IT EASY!
COME ON!
NO! I KNEW WE
SHOULDN'T TRUST HIM!
I'M GONNA KILL
THE SON OF A BITCH!
I'M GONNA SHOOT
HIS RED ASS OFF!
YOU'RE GONNA
SHOOT HIM, EH?
THE SAME WAY YOU SHOT
THE HALF-BREED.
COME ON, RENO.
HE'S JUST AN INDIAN.
GO AHEAD, HALF-WIT.
I BET HE DROPS YOU
RIGHT HERE.
[RENO CHUCKLES]
I THOUGHT WE WERE
BUSINESS PARTNERS.
FRIENDS.
FRIENDS?
YOU SHITBREATH.
[CHUCKLES]
I'LL KILL YOU FOR THAT,
RENO!
I'LL KILL YOU FOR THAT!
SO SHOOT,
GODDAMN IT!
SHOOT!
YOU KILL THE HALF-BREED,
WE WOULDN'T BE HERE.
GO AHEAD. SHOOT EVERYBODY.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD
TO HELL.
[TAUNTING LAUGHTER]
HE'S JUST AN INDIAN!
HEE HEE HEE HEE!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?!
HE'S JUST AN INDIAN!
HA HA HA HA HA!
GODDAMN IT!
GODDAMN! DAMN!
GOD!
DAMN!
HE'S CRAZY.
Smiley:
I'LL KILL THEM!
EVERYTHING!
GODDAMN SHOT...
DAMN...
AAH!
[SPITS]
NOBODY DIES
TILL I TELL 'EM TO DIE!
YOU SHOULD EAT.
PLEASE?
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO HARM ANYONE.
WELL, YOU DID.
I HAD NO CHOICE.
THEY WERE TRYING
TO KILL ME.
YOU TRIED TO KILL SEAN.
NO, I DIDN'T.
YES, YOU DID.
I TRIED TO TALK
TO HIM.
WITH A KNIFE
TO HIS THROAT?
I TOLD HIM
TO STAY AWAY
FROM THE NORTH STAR.
THE NORTH STAR.
WELL, THAT'S HIS.
IT DOESN'T
BELONG TO HIM.
YEAH, IT DOES.
HE BOUGHT IT.
BECAUSE
THE OWNER DIED?
EXACTLY.
WELL, I AM THE OWNER.
DO I LOOK DEAD TO YOU?
THE NORTH STAR
BELONGS TO THOSE INDIANS
WHO GAVE YOU
WARM CLOTHING
WHEN YOU WERE FREEZING.
I FILED THE CLAIM
TO PROTECT THEM
FROM McLENNON.
[SCRATCHING]
HO!
I'M HENRY PRUETT JOHNSON,
COLONEL OF
THE UNITED STATES ARMY,
FORT MICHAEL.
MILITARY COMMANDER
FOR THE TERRITORY OF ALASKA.
AS OF THIS MOMENT,
THE TOWN OF NOME
IS UNDER MARTIAL LAW.
[MURMURING]
Hudson: SO YOU SEE,
IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
I'M SORRY,
BUT I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
WHAT?
I MEAN,
SEAN ISN'T LIKE THAT.
HE CARES FOR ME.
HE'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
YOU HAVEN'T LISTENED
TO ANYTHING.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY I AM DOING THIS.
NO, YOU'RE RIGHT,
I DON'T.
I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE BEING HONEST.
HONEST?
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT ME?
YOU JUST THINK OF ME
AS A HALF-BREED
AND A THIEF.
NO, I DON'T.
I MEAN, WHAT ARE YOU
HOPING TO PROVE
FROM ALL THIS?
[SIGHS]
THAT CAVE IS SACRED...
LIKE A CHURCH.
AND McLENNON'S MEN
DEFILED IT.
THEY KILLED AN OLD MAN
WHO WAS LIKE A FATHER TO ME.
AND I COULD DO NOTHING
TO STOP THEM.
THAT MAN HAD MY RESPECT,
BECAUSE HE TAUGHT ME
AS A CHILD ABOUT
RIGHT AND WRONG.
AND IF I CAN SAVE
THAT CAVE...
THEN I CAN BE HONEST
WITH MYSELF
ABOUT WHO I AM.
[SIGHS]
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
LOOK, I'LL--I'LL TALK
TO SEAN--
SEAN.
HE'LL BE HERE
SOONER OR LATER...
AND DO HIS BEST TO KILL ME.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
YOU DON'T KNOW HIM.
LOOK, HE'LL--HE'LL
LISTEN TO ME.
WHY ARE YOU TRYING
TO HELP ME?
YOU COULD HAVE
LET ME DIE OUT THERE,
AND YOU DIDN'T.
WE'LL LEAVE TOMORROW...
BEFORE THEY GET HERE.
WHERE TO?
NOME.
SEAN McLENNON...
OWNS 10, NOW 11,
OF THE RICHEST STRIKES
ON ANVIL CREEK,
AND HE DIDN'T FILE
THE ORIGINAL CLAIM
ON ONE OF THEM.
NOTHING WRONG WITH
TRANSFERRING A CLAIM.
HAPPENS ALL THE TIME.
THE ORIGINAL OWNERS
OF McLENNON'S TRANSFERS
ARE ALL DEAD.
HERE.
AND HERE.
Lindberg: HERE.
THIS INDIAN.
EYEWITNESSES
SAW HIM ALIVE,
HERE IN TOWN.
THAT MAKES THINGS
A LITTLE MORE SLIPPERY,
NOW, DOESN'T IT?
I'D SAY A LOT MORE.
WELL, YOU'D BEST FIND HIM
AND THE GIRL.
WELL, THIS MATTER
REALLY SHOULDN'T--
Johnson:
SHERIFF,
TAKE 3 OF MY MEN
AND GO AFTER THAT POSSE.
INFORM THEM OF
THE MARTIAL LAW DECREE,
AND ORDER THEM
TO RETURN TO NOME
IMMEDIATELY.
[DOGS BARKING]
[WHIMPERS]
[GROWLING]
GET UP! GET UP!
HMM...WHY?
GET DRESSED.
THEY'RE HERE.
NO!
SEAN...
SEAN, LISTEN. YOU HAVE
TO LISTEN TO ME.
YOU HAVE TO--
ALL RIGHT, SEAN?
KILL HIM.
Sara: NO!
NO!
TELL THEM TO STOP,
PLEASE!
NO, SEAN, YOU CAN'T!
YOU MUSTN'T SHOOT HIM!
NO, SEAN, PLEASE!
Sara: STOP IT!
STOP! STOP SHOOTING!
PLEASE! PLEASE!
STOP IT!
OUT OF THE WAY!
BLOW HIM UP!
UHH!
SEAN, PLEASE,
HE DIDN'T MEAN ANY HARM!
HE JUST WANTS
TO TALK TO YOU...
[GUNSHOTS]
WHAT ARE YOU WEARING?
WHAT DID YOU DO WITH HIM?
YOU FUCKING WHORE!
YOU WHORE!
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT
TO ME?
[HUDSON
SPEAKING ATHABASKAN]
GWILL!
OH, NO.
JESUS CHRIST.
HE'S GETTING AWAY!
HE'S ALONE.
PUT THE DOGS ON HIM.
PLEASE...
PLEASE, PLEASE.
PLEASE. PLEASE, SEAN,
JUST TAKE ME BACK
TO NOME. PLEASE.
PLEASE, SEAN.
JUST TAKE ME BACK
TO NOME.
PLEASE, TAKE ME BACK
PLEASE.
LET ME
TAKE HER BACK.
PLEASE...
[GUNSHOT]
WHAT?
I'LL TAKE HER BACK.
SHE'LL FREEZE
OUT HERE.
I MEAN, I GOTTA TAKE
GWILL'S BODY BACK ANYWAY.
I MEAN, A POSSE
AIN'T NO PLACE
FOR A WOMAN.
HUH.
ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
YEAH, THAT'S GREAT.
WHY DON'T--
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE HER
BACK TO YOUR SLED,
AND YOU KEEP HER...
YOU KEEP HER WARM.
MAYBE YOU'D...
MAYBE YOU'D LIKE TO FUCK HER,
LIKE THAT HALF-BREED.
WOULD YOU LIKE THAT?
LET'S FINISH
WHAT WE CAME TO DO.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
RUN!
RUN OUT THERE TO DIE,
OR I'LL KILL YOU HERE!
I DIDN'T COME OUT HERE
TO KILL A WOMAN.
SHOO!
[WHIMPERING]
[GUNSHOTS]
WHOA!
Sergeant: HEY,
WHAT'S THAT OVER THERE?
Lamont: THAT'S
A HELL OF A FIRE.
Lamont: IT'S ONE
OF McLENNON'S BOYS.
SOMEBODY SHOT HIM
IN THE BACK
OF THE HEAD.
Sergeant: HOW OLD
DO YOU THINK
THIS FIRE IS?
Lamont: COUPLE OF HOURS
AT MOST.
WHOEVER DID THIS,
SERGEANT, CAN'T BE FAR.
COME ON.
WAIT!
WAIT, PLEASE!
STOP!
HYAH!
[PANTING]
YAA!
COME ON.
GO ON--COME ON!
Lamont: HO!
WE'LL LEAVE THE HORSES HERE.
FOLLOW UP ON FOOT.
THAT BASTARD.
THAT BASTARD!
[SPEAKING ATHABASKAN]
HE GOES TO THE END
OF THE CANYON.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY OUT.
LET'S GET THERE FIRST.
AHH...McLENNON?
WELL, UH, LAMONT.
WHAT A PLEASANT SURPRISE
TO FIND YOU OUT HERE
LIKE THIS
IN THE MIDDLE OF ALL
THIS NATURAL BEAUTY.
BOYS.
WHAT HAPPENED
BACK THERE...
AT THE CABIN?
AHH.
YOU FOUND OLD PETE,
HUH?
GODDAMN HALF-BREED SHOT HIM
RIGHT IN THE FACE.
THE HALF-BREED SHOT HIM
IN THE FACE.
HE, UM, HE RAN OUT,
AND OLD PETE
WENT TO GRAB HIM AND...
BANG, RIGHT--RIGHT
IN THE FACE.
WHERE'S SARA?
SARA. WELL...
WE'RE OUT LOOKING
FOR THEM NOW.
McLENNON...
NOME IS UNDER MARTIAL LAW
RIGHT NOW.
MARTIAL LAW?
IS THAT RIGHT? HA HA.
YEP.
REALLY?
WELL, WELL, WELL.
WELL, WE'LL BE
GETTING BACK THERE
AS SOON AS WE FIND THEM.
SEEIN' AS HOW YOU BOYS
WILL ALL BE THERE
SEEIN' THAT
IT'S NICE AND SAFE
AND--AND MARTIAL AND ALL.
I'M SORRY, McLENNON,
BUT I'M TAKING OVER
FROM HERE.
AND I'M ORDERING YOU
AND YOUR MEN
TO GO BACK TO NOME.
YOU JUST TELL US
WHICH DIRECTION
THE HALF-BREED WENT.
I'D RATHER NOT.
NO. I'M THE LAW
AROUND HERE, McLENNON.
NOT YOU.
[SIGHS]
YEAH, LAMONT...
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU ARE THE LAW.
[PANTING]
McLennon:
THE MAN IS RIGHT.
HE IS THE LAW.
Sergeant: LOOK OUT!
HEY, WHAT THE HELL!
[BIG TIM GROANING]
UH...PLEASE!
ALL RIGHT.
[GROANING]
LET'S GET TO THE DOGS.
UNH!
UHH!
WHAT IS IT, TONGA?
VERY GOOD.
YOU CAN
SEE THINGS...
TRACK...
COMMAND DOGS.
[SPEAKING ATHABASKAN]
SPEAK ENGLISH.
YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT I SAY.
YOU DIDN'T
NEED ME HERE.
YOU'RE
A HALF-BREED
JUST LIKE HIM,
AREN'T YOU?
WHO WAS IT,
YOUR MOTHER?
YOUR FATHER?
I WON'T TELL ANYONE.
[SIGHS]
NO, YOU WON'T.
AAH!
[PIERCING SCREAM]
[DOGS BARKING]
AFRAID OF A WOLF?
Smiley: NO...
BUT THAT HALF-BREED'S
WATCHING US.
THAT HALF-BREED
KILLED HIM.
McLennon:
THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT HALF-BREED
KILLED HIM.
SMILEY,
GET THE DOGS READY.
GET THE DOGS READY!
YOU KILLED HIM,
DIDN'T YA?
I JUST SAID
THE HALF-BREED
KILLED HIM.
YOU SAW HIM?
YEAH, SURE.
WHOA, SOMETHING'S
FUNNY IN THERE, SEAN.
WHERE'D YOU THINK
YOU WERE TAKIN' US?
WHAT, ARE YOU STARTIN'
TO QUESTION ME?
IT'S TIME
TO GO BACK.
I KNOW, BUT...
HALF THE MINE IS YOURS.
YOU CAN PUT YOUR FEET UP
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
DON'T YOU THINK
THAT'S A LITTLE LATE?
I'M GOIN' HOME.
DON'T EVER TOUCH ME
AGAIN!
I'M COMING APART.
YOU CAN'T LEAVE ME NOW,
RENO.
YOU'RE THE ONLY FRIEND
I GOT.
YOU GOTTA TRUST ME.
WE'LL GO.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
AND...
IN DECIDING THIS ISSUE,
THE MINERS ASSOCIATION
DECLARES ALL FOREIGN CLAIMS
VOID AND ILLEGAL.
YEAH!
AND...
OPEN TO RESTAKING
BY THE CITIZENS
OF THIS FRONTIER GEM
WE CALL NOME...
AMERICANS...
GOD'S CHILDREN.
AND, IN SO DOING,
WE RID OURSELVES
OF THESE SCAVENGERS...
THAT HAVE COST ME
SO VERY MUCH.
THE LIFE...
OF A WOMAN...
THAT I LOVED
VERY...DEEPLY.
KILLED BY A SAVAGE.
AND THE LIVES
OF MY TRUSTED FRIENDS...
WHO BRAVELY TRIED
TO HELP ME SAVE HER.
AND HERE...
IN NOME,
YOUR--YOUR OASIS...
AMONG YOU, R-RIGHT HERE,
THERE ARE SAVAGES.
SOME ARE RED,
SOME ARE HARDER TO SPOT,
BUT THEY ALL WANT
THE SAME THING!
AND YOU KNOW WHAT THAT IS,
DON'T YA?
WHAT DO YOU HAVE
THAT THEY WANT?
AND WHEN WILL THEY TRY
TO TAKE IT?
MAYBE TONIGHT...
MAYBE NEXT WEEK...
MAYBE NEXT MONTH...
BUT ONE NIGHT
WHEN YOU'RE SLEEPING,
THEY'LL COME AND TAKE
WHAT'S YOURS,
BECAUSE YOU'RE ALONE.
BUT FROM THIS DAY FORWARD,
YOU ARE NOT ALONE.
WEARE NOT ALONE!
MacBETH SAID,
"WHEN ACTIONS DO NOT..."
"OUR FEARS,
WE WILL FIGHT AGAINST..."
WHAT?
SEAN McLENNON,
YOU ARE UNDER ARREST
FOR THE MURDER
OF SHERIFF LAMONT,
DEPUTIES ROSS AND GRAVES,
AND 3 SOLDIERS OF
THE UNITED STATES ARMY.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WE HAVE AN EYEWITNESS.
Johnson: THE INDIANS
SAVED HER LIFE
AND BROUGHT HER HERE.
TAKE HIM AWAY.
CITIZENS OF NOME...
[RAISES VOICE]
CITIZENS OF NOME!
[CROWD MURMURING
AMONGST THEMSELVES]
[SHOUTING]
PEOPLE OF NOME!
I'M ALSO HERE TO INFORM YOU
THAT MEETINGS SUCH AS THESE,
WITH OBVIOUS INTENT
TO CAUSE DISORDER...
IT'S ALL OVER.
THANK YOU.
GET YOURSELF
SOME REST.
CONGRESS HAS DECLARED
THAT ALL CLAIMS--
PAST, PRESENT, AND FUTURE--
BY ALL MINERS,
AMERICAN AND FOREIGN,
WILL BE HONORED.
CAN I HAVE
MY OWN ROOM NOW?
OF COURSE YOU CAN!
YOU CAN HAVE
ANYTHING YOU WANT!
WHERE IS McLENNON?
HE'S IN JAIL.
I WANTED
TO SAY GOODBYE.
[SNAP]
[GASPS]
Hudson: SO DID I.
Johnson:
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
HAVEN'T YOU HEARD, MAN?
THE WHOLE BLOODY BEACH
IS COVERED WITH GOLD!
Man: TO THE BEACH!
Hudson:
MY ANCESTORS TAUGHT ME
YOU CANNOT OWN THE LAND.
YOU CAN ONLY RESPECT IT.
THIS IS WHAT I FOUGHT FOR,
AND WHAT
I WILL ALWAYS BELIEVE.