[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由TimeM生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.net
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:1
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体简体,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:04.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fe134}{\fad(500,500)}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\pos(190,292)}{\fs16} {\fn方正准圆简体}{\bord0}本字幕由{\fs24}{\fn方正综艺简体}{\fe0} {\c&H26F4FF&}YYeTs{\fe134}{\fn方正宋黑简体}{\c&HFFAE1A&}人人影视 {\fscy100}{\fe134}{\fn方正准圆简体}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\fs16}校整制作\N{\fn方正准圆简体}{\fs14}{\b0}{\bord0}{\shad0}{\c&HFFFFFF&}仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为\N{\3c&H2F2F2F&}{\4c&H000000&}{\fsp0}{\fs16} {\c&HFFFFFF&}欢迎爱好者加入我们 {\c&H26F4FF&}{\fn方正综艺简体}{\fs24}www.YYeTs.net
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:04.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}{\fad(500,500)}{\3c&H000000&}{\pos(190,290)}{\fs86}{\fscx600}{\alpha&H9F&\c&H000000&}{\bord1}{\shad0}■
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.00,0:00:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}{\pos(190,268)}{\fs16}{\c&H24EFFF&}{\fn方正准圆简体}{\bord0}字幕：{\fs18}{\c&HFFFFFF&}冰蚕　　　{\fs16}{\c&H24EFFF&}{\fn方正准圆简体}{\bord0}后期：{\fs18}{\c&HFFFFFF&}冰蚕 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.00,0:00:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}{\fad(500,500)}{\3c&H000000&}{\pos(190,278)}{\fs36}{\fscx1400}{\alpha&H9F&\c&H000000&}{\bord1}{\shad0}■
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.43,0:01:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是本市酷热警告
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.75,0:01:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全球性温室效应近日严重恶化
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.85,0:01:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界各地气温不断飙升
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.85,0:01:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是深圳天气预报
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.84,0:01:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天气温再创新高
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.57,0:01:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天气持续酷热  用电量提升
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.58,0:01:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,政府呼吁市民节约用电
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.65,0:01:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各国政府相继发出指引
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.73,0:01:34.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鼓励市民以不同方法消暑降温
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.75,0:01:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  热死啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.06,0:01:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿威  阿威
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.61,0:01:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天才修理好  今天又不冷  怎么办呀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.60,0:01:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  阿威  你听见没有呀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.99,0:01:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己抠门  还说我
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.31,0:01:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你换机  你换制冷剂
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.36,0:01:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你凉快整晚  算我厉害了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.71,0:01:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你那么多钱  你说过一定行的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.61,0:01:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不跟你说了我回去吃饭
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.66,0:02:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.25,0:02:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要碰我的收音机
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.39,0:02:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.07,0:02:10.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炒你鱿鱼呀
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.36,0:02:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在那磨蹭着了  冰箱里的东西都化了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.58,0:02:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别吵了别吵了  我在弄啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.54,0:02:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  我的钱  我的钱哪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.03,0:02:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不要烦啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.03,0:02:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近  大家有没有发觉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.61,0:02:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身边特别多人非常暴燥  常常骂人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.69,0:02:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我  给我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.34,0:02:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来  这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.46,0:02:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天气跟情绪  到底有什么关系呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.03,0:02:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这种酷暑天气下
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.83,0:02:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以怎样保持头脑清醒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.71,0:02:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美女  说个笑话给你听
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.23,0:02:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么动物两条腿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.76,0:02:53.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太阳一出来很准时叫你起床
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.78,0:02:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么容易啊  公鸡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.18,0:02:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是你妈啊  -我妈
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.55,0:02:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,租伞吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.31,0:03:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够硬了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.67,0:03:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美女  冰棒哟
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.30,0:03:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,香港今年应该是最热的一年
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.32,0:03:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很难受
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.45,0:03:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们有什么办法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.95,0:03:19.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搬到北极吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.99,0:03:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北极冰山多  够冷呀
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.73,0:03:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,香港真的好热哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.98,0:03:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去这里  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.67,0:03:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一下飞机就吃寿司
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.27,0:03:32.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家店  有那么好吃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.22,0:03:34.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天气这么热  就算鱼送来了  肯定也不新鲜
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.22,0:03:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,师傅  鱼到啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.42,0:03:39.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,劏鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.44,0:03:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来香港玩多久呀
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.00,0:03:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是来玩的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.58,0:03:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定不用再走了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.30,0:03:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么啦你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.38,0:03:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么玩意呀你  你根本就不够格
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.82,0:03:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  有了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.39,0:03:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神经病呀你  你别走  你别走  回来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.55,0:03:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收工了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.94,0:04:00.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷热警告已经正式生效超过二十四小时
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.69,0:04:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老婆呀
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.85,0:04:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天生意特别旺
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.79,0:04:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这越热呢  我就越发
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.76,0:04:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好呢  保佑一年四季都热辣辣的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.69,0:04:11.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干杯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.62,0:04:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家想知道四十二度有多热
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.83,0:04:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起来看一下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.97,0:04:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家看一看  熟了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.46,0:04:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.53,0:04:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的钢琴弹得是最好的一个
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.47,0:04:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.08,0:04:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  我不会请你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.70,0:05:01.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  我真的很需要这份工作
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.43,0:05:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都快没有钱吃饭了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.09,0:05:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫李艳  可惜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.43,0:05:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人不如其名
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.06,0:05:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我请她啦  明白吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.73,0:05:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.61,0:05:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你如果再穿得少一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.32,0:05:17.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会考虑考虑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.23,0:05:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做梦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.63,0:05:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你有没有经验啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.15,0:05:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手指上的功夫  相当有经验
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.25,0:05:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手指灵活有力  无论是在节奏上力度上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.34,0:05:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都相当到位
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.56,0:05:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,九十八号  明天上班
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.48,0:06:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.04,0:06:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉  两次婚姻都失败了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.89,0:06:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.64,0:06:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一个老婆  跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.62,0:06:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  第二个呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.55,0:06:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不肯跑
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.19,0:06:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉  自由多么好呀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.79,0:06:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干吧  非勒根绳子绑住自己
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.30,0:06:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说她
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.17,0:06:35.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你天天用眼睛看着她  不是说她在说谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.50,0:06:36.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很难追的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.90,0:06:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我要是追上了  怎么样呀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.32,0:06:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.22,0:06:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的手表
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.78,0:06:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呸  我这表从当兵那年就跟着我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.86,0:06:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别废话  赌  还是不赌
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.24,0:06:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追不上怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.27,0:06:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便你呀  我整个夏天给你白干
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.84,0:06:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一言为定
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.77,0:07:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美女  冰棒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.40,0:07:09.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.23,0:07:12.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天可是免费的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.84,0:07:17.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我还有一个问题要问
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.46,0:07:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么问题呀
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.76,0:07:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不可以当我女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.88,0:07:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.70,0:07:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我迟到是要扣钱的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.95,0:07:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  你就答应我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.18,0:07:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.89,0:07:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.83,0:07:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你有诚意的话  每天正午在那儿站着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.67,0:07:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站上一百天
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.66,0:07:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么热  你耍我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.01,0:07:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好  拉倒  好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.77,0:07:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好  一百天  我们说好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.27,0:08:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  一百天以后  你就是我女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.01,0:08:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃饭了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.84,0:08:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小琪  吃饭了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.34,0:08:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么晒的天
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.37,0:08:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站在那里热不热呀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.41,0:08:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.59,0:08:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里有个疯子在晒太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.64,0:08:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.44,0:08:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识他
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.10,0:08:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会  神经病
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.38,0:08:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃饭了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.40,0:08:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先去吧  我就来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.61,0:08:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.14,0:09:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来晒衣服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.08,0:09:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚来都是那样子的  习惯就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.47,0:09:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,九十八号  有客人找你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.52,0:09:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.84,0:09:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.46,0:09:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.05,0:10:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车子呀  引擎过热
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.70,0:10:04.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下去看看嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.64,0:10:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,号码又换了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.57,0:10:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么知道我中暑
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.81,0:10:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换什么号码
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.20,0:10:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没换号码
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.29,0:10:55.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指挥家  我只有你一个朋友在香港
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.99,0:10:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还装傻
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.01,0:11:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指挥家  什么指挥家呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.06,0:11:08.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.36,0:11:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问我是谁  我还问你是谁勒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.54,0:11:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传我的号码  问我是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.60,0:11:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.47,0:11:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  有亲人在深圳  拨错号码
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.91,0:11:31.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传错  传错  你猪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.75,0:11:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海外简讯很贵的  蠢猪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.74,0:11:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.57,0:11:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.87,0:11:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.58,0:12:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在需要人聊天
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.61,0:12:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很贵吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.93,0:12:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.33,0:12:30.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然有  你是干什么的  为什么会中暑
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.89,0:12:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是一个钢琴家
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.02,0:12:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天在户外表演
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.09,0:12:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太阳太毒了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.05,0:12:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我给晒晕了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.09,0:12:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.59,0:12:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钢琴家
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.52,0:13:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是司机
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.08,0:13:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是法拉利车手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.95,0:13:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法拉利
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.19,0:13:20.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.74,0:13:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.53,0:13:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,专家说  谈情的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.22,0:13:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果在对方右边耳朵说话  对方会很陶醉的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.34,0:13:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你现在在我左耳边啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.94,0:13:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在在你左边吗  那你嫁给我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.36,0:13:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要嫁给你的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.89,0:13:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个鱼缸只有你跟我是同种啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.68,0:13:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要挡住我啦  我要看看他们在干啥
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.88,0:14:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.79,0:14:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们一定有点鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.11,0:14:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们两个有事跟我无关  是你有事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.05,0:14:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的排卵期快到  快点嫁给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.02,0:14:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.23,0:14:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  他们kiss kiss的时候  我就嫁给你啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.24,0:14:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那个杀手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.18,0:14:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用蘸
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.87,0:14:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有毒
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.55,0:14:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鱼和饭中间放了昆布  味道很足
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.92,0:14:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.26,0:14:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酱油呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.47,0:14:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看你的脸比酱油还要黑
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.26,0:14:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是那么严肃
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.65,0:14:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酱油师傅
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.86,0:14:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有帮你取错名字吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.77,0:14:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你名字很好听吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.49,0:14:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去到外国  有没有给人笑
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.99,0:14:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然没有呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.23,0:14:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Wasabi  好记又好听
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.83,0:15:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是太辣了  我放多了芥末
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.23,0:15:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我很久没有吃到这个味道了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.87,0:15:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.26,0:15:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那本书
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.68,0:15:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完美一餐  写得怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.12,0:15:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在当老板了  我们是不是可以在一起了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.47,0:15:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是说先写好那本书
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.90,0:15:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为你说需要多一点时间想一想
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.04,0:15:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一年多了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.04,0:15:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跑遍了世界各地
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.20,0:15:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都找不到完美的一餐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.35,0:16:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一听说你开店  就马上赶回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.55,0:16:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我相信
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.40,0:16:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最完美的一餐  一定是在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.43,0:16:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在自己是老板了  不是以前的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.77,0:16:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的厨房佬了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.71,0:16:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我读到小学六年级
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.19,0:16:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再给我一点时间
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.28,0:16:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再给你一百年
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.34,0:16:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还不是一样是小学毕业
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.50,0:16:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.99,0:16:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我寄给你的明信片  还有全世界各地的食谱
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.17,0:16:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通通还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.07,0:16:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不知扔哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.58,0:16:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲她  亲她  亲她呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.82,0:16:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,功亏一篑呀
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.50,0:17:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我  给我  给我  给我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.79,0:17:28.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死的  死的  死的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.09,0:17:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来  再来  给我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.32,0:17:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对呀  来呀
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.10,0:17:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不懂Sexy是吧  你是女人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.51,0:17:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大福  大福
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.46,0:17:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是男人  我  Man Man
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.41,0:17:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要你  不要你这样  我不要你的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.70,0:17:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着我  看着我的眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.94,0:17:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来  再来  再来  再来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.80,0:17:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我  死的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.30,0:17:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不够Sexy  不够  不够  不够Sexy
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.58,0:17:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你浪费了我们大家三个小时
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.38,0:18:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  她那么好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.70,0:18:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂个屁
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.92,0:18:04.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Leslie  你消消气
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.30,0:18:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沅沅绝对是最有潜质的好模特儿
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.43,0:18:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信不到一两年之内  她一定会红遍全国
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.27,0:18:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她应该放在蜡像馆里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.67,0:18:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拍不了她  你去找别人拍  好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.26,0:18:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我错什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.42,0:18:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没错  你真的很差劲
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.61,0:18:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.41,0:18:18.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说什么  我说了多少遍
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.67,0:18:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要的是眼睛  眼睛里的东西都是空洞
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.52,0:18:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很空洞  你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.54,0:18:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞎子  是你瞎了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.83,0:18:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沅沅  放开我  咱们走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.12,0:18:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你咒我  她咒我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.91,0:18:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你告诉所有的广告商  就说我说的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.08,0:18:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我用不了她  她不适合当模特儿
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.79,0:18:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  我眼睛怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.38,0:18:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.36,0:19:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我眼睛怎么看不见了  怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.89,0:19:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的眼睛怎么会突然这样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.79,0:19:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是那个很有名的摄影师  Leslie Guan
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.16,0:19:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我  我的眼睛怎么会突然这样  医生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.93,0:19:22.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.57,0:19:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面还说  你按一下快门  喀嚓  一千块
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.38,0:19:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先告诉我  我的眼睛为什么会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.71,0:19:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在还不太清楚  我们要做一系列的化验
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.24,0:19:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是细菌感染  也许
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.55,0:19:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正有很多也许  医生  很难说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.74,0:19:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他眼睛看不见就完了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.40,0:19:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想想办法呀
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.00,0:19:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦你  机场
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.66,0:19:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐  又是你呀
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.24,0:19:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你上一次说一定不离开香港的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.58,0:19:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一次  我一定不会再回来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.04,0:19:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想打这个电话就打吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.91,0:20:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不打这个电话  一定后悔的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.46,0:20:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些事我见多了  大不了我不听
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.32,0:20:08.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说好今天送空调的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.10,0:20:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没货
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.29,0:20:14.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  你怎么做生意的  我都快热死了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.99,0:20:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  喂  喂  挂我电话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.99,0:20:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪  你在干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.11,0:20:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试车  明天比赛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.68,0:20:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃  再来一份
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.93,0:21:02.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.18,0:21:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在没空听你的电话  请留言
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.40,0:21:10.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酱油师傅
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.82,0:21:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天看到你开的新店
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.67,0:21:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很替你开心  恭喜你呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.83,0:21:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在网上  看到你的店  食物满分
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.44,0:21:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卫生满分  环境满分  服务
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.32,0:21:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一分
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.05,0:21:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道为什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.82,0:21:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人都说
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.22,0:21:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那个大师傅  从来都不笑
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.99,0:21:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本我以为
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.83,0:21:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我努力一点
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.28,0:21:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定可以帮你打开那扇门
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.71,0:21:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.15,0:21:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.44,0:22:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来只有你自己
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.75,0:22:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才可以把那扇门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.69,0:22:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.41,0:22:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威哥  买了它吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.09,0:22:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粉红色的  很难卖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.84,0:22:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明明写着二手冷气机回收
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.72,0:22:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是歧视粉红色啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.03,0:22:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是歧视  罕有而已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.84,0:22:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四百吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.55,0:22:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多给一点吧  威哥
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.56,0:22:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人会出四百块  买你那粉红色空调的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.51,0:22:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你搁下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.01,0:22:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好吧  给你啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.88,0:23:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.78,0:23:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.94,0:24:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疯子
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.97,0:24:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有病呀  你懂不懂开车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.82,0:24:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说话呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.57,0:24:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是热傻了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.66,0:24:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我看着
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.48,0:24:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了  你钥匙
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.85,0:24:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两百九十八
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.57,0:24:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.88,0:25:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游到浮台
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.69,0:25:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要两百九十八下
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.71,0:25:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神经
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.53,0:25:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的车
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.13,0:25:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威信冷气
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.98,0:25:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,配错轮胎啦  你懂不懂车呀
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.63,0:25:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来比一下
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.36,0:25:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就凭你想追到我
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.46,0:25:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我追到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.54,0:25:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎么样就怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.12,0:25:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两百九十六  两百九十七  两百九十八
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.33,0:26:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叮当姐姐  要划多少次
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.08,0:26:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游到浮台要两百九十八下
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.21,0:26:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我游泳很好的  两百九十八次  我一定可以
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.75,0:26:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪我妈怕太阳晒
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.23,0:26:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没去过沙滩的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.35,0:26:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  我好了以后  你带我去可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.27,0:26:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然好啊  我请你吃冰淇淋  好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.92,0:26:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,方哥啊  最少也得十块
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.80,0:26:57.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还挺会做生意呢你
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.52,0:26:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就两块  爱干不干
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.39,0:27:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.56,0:27:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧  去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.92,0:27:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二十五  二十六  二十七
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.91,0:27:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二十八
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.59,0:27:42.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你拉我见她干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.65,0:27:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你忘了  那天她骂你是瞎子
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.45,0:27:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你眼睛就瞎了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.99,0:27:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.52,0:27:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢点  慢点  慢点
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.32,0:27:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们找谁啊  干嘛啊这是
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.22,0:27:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  我们找那个周沅沅
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.42,0:27:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周沅沅  你们是她
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.18,0:27:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是她亲人  很亲的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.63,0:27:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.89,0:28:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她匆匆忙忙的就跑了  还欠我这个月的租金
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.42,0:28:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好你们来了  替她付了吧  五百块
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.23,0:28:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要钱呢  五百块
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.37,0:28:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你知道她去哪了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.98,0:28:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能去了深圳了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.52,0:28:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能去她的房间看看
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.18,0:28:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啊  在那边
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.41,0:28:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定帮过她一次  你眼睛就没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.80,0:28:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  看什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.64,0:28:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的那期封面杂志
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.18,0:28:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看过啦  看  看什么看
Dialogue: 0,0:28:37.47,0:28:39.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你摸摸  干嘛  神经病
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.16,0:28:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你摸摸  摸到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.22,0:28:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摸什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.13,0:28:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摸到了吗  洞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.22,0:28:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那两个洞是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.18,0:28:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你的眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.46,0:28:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说游泳能不能游到少林寺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.80,0:28:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又怎样呀
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.26,0:28:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次我一定得做和尚了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.09,0:29:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那女的再也没出现过  恐怕我这辈子  唉
Dialogue: 0,0:29:07.63,0:29:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们吃过最完美的一餐是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.66,0:29:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滑蛋牛肉饭  英记  完美
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.46,0:29:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,废话  你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.29,0:29:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双层起司汉堡
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.18,0:29:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我小时候要考到一百分  老妈才肯带我去的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.73,0:29:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难怪你们还是做学徒
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.14,0:29:22.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,师傅
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.66,0:29:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在想完美一餐啊
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.73,0:29:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家那么多天都没有开手机
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.46,0:29:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明在躲你  怎么找得着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.09,0:29:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个礼拜后  我会在这里搞一个完美一餐
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.20,0:29:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你们帮我上网  铺天盖地的宣传
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.68,0:29:36.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她一定会看到
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.38,0:29:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那如果她真的看不到呢  那我们不是白做
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.70,0:29:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会白做  你不想做可以马上走
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.17,0:29:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不做就不做
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.99,0:29:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.79,0:29:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家女孩子主动找你  你还装酷
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.49,0:29:52.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活该啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.58,0:30:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天寿司店没有生意呀
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.02,0:30:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打那么多电话来
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.21,0:30:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗个澡打了三通  一  二  三
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.02,0:30:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在换你紧张我了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.80,0:30:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  下午学校朗诵比赛  你来不来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.49,0:30:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天下午要去找工作
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.33,0:30:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.78,0:30:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,草莓  老爸要去赚钱的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.32,0:30:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一百八十次了  叫我Strawberry呀
Dialogue: 0,0:30:52.56,0:30:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  冰箱有豆浆  饭团
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.86,0:30:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得热30秒就行了  不然又搞到干水了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.16,0:30:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了  啰唆
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.32,0:31:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸啊  我说好多次  以后不再弹琴了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.17,0:31:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么鬼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.20,0:31:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在弹琴  还是在按摩呀
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.57,0:31:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.26,0:32:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.38,0:32:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事呀  你看你脸都红了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.75,0:32:24.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.08,0:32:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的没事
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.20,0:32:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事就好
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.45,0:32:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.66,0:32:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.86,0:32:41.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  等一下  等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.44,0:32:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.53,0:32:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是太热了  要不然不要站了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.92,0:32:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.08,0:32:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不会放弃的  还有
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.94,0:32:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十三天
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.33,0:32:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你记着
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.02,0:33:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天晚上干什么呀
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.24,0:33:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要去喝酒
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.83,0:33:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么  再说一次
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.37,0:33:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要去喝酒
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.34,0:33:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样  去不去呀
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.46,0:33:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想追我呀
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.68,0:33:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这么喜欢纹身  你那么喜欢被人纹
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.81,0:33:36.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛮配的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.08,0:33:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你臭美呀
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.01,0:33:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这么没礼貌
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.44,0:33:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经八年了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.31,0:33:59.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来了八年了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.65,0:34:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每年来你都纹一个圈  为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.75,0:34:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明年再见到我  我就告诉你咯
Dialogue: 0,0:34:07.70,0:34:09.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上一年你已经这么说了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.35,0:34:16.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那去不去呀
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.87,0:34:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  掰掰
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.33,0:34:20.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.02,0:34:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无敌冰沙  吸管自动消毒
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.89,0:34:31.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免费的  快来试下  Welcome
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.05,0:34:40.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免费试饮  Welcome  欢迎欢迎  来
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.44,0:34:48.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位朋友  无敌冰沙  Welcome  来  来  来
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.37,0:34:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,方哥  今天一块钱  我也站了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.41,0:34:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.52,0:35:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  五毛也行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.40,0:35:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,热死人了  今天气温又再创新高
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.84,0:35:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现时录得的室外气温是摄氏四十八度
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.54,0:35:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的天气吃雪糕  不是有钱就可以
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.11,0:35:30.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有雪糕都已变成了期贷
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.09,0:35:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,软雪糕七十块  有没有人要
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.48,0:35:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七十五  八十
Dialogue: 0,0:35:36.59,0:35:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八十五
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.70,0:35:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一百
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.14,0:35:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两百
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.17,0:35:42.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两百一次
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.91,0:35:43.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两百两次
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.91,0:35:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成交
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.52,0:35:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前喝茶吃寿司才要排队等位子
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.20,0:35:54.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在去沙滩游泳都要站在一边排队慢慢等
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.41,0:35:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七百九十五号  三位  一次
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.22,0:35:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七百九十五号  三位  两次
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.83,0:36:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我  是我
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.80,0:36:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  哈哈  又大了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.44,0:36:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呀  每天都有练啊  有弹性啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.22,0:36:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靓女
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.64,0:36:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讲个笑话给你听  好不好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.56,0:36:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又说烂笑话呀  大叔
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.39,0:36:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人呢  从二楼掉下来
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.31,0:36:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟一个人从二十楼掉下来  有什么分别呀
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.69,0:36:24.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:36:24.89,0:36:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二楼那一个呢
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.68,0:36:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砰  哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.18,0:36:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二十楼那个呢
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.55,0:36:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  呀  砰
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.89,0:36:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,油缸  马力  避震
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.91,0:36:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部要最大的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.77,0:36:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你干脆买部新的好了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.37,0:36:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.68,0:36:53.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要威信空调是全香港最快的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.59,0:36:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么弄的话  几万块吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.35,0:36:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用那么贵吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.58,0:37:02.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你修空调的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.66,0:37:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天气那么热  摆自己上网好了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.82,0:37:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几万块不难啊
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.62,0:37:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  陈先生  威信空调
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.98,0:37:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.49,0:37:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一千六呀  我现在的价是
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.26,0:37:44.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一千七
Dialogue: 0,0:37:46.33,0:37:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行呀  我马上到
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.48,0:37:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:52.27,0:37:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所谓有危就有机
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.86,0:37:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天气这么热  造就了赚大钱的人
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.34,0:37:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我身边的阿威  专帮人修理空调
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.59,0:37:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是其中的一个
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.02,0:38:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿威  为什么你会想到
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.64,0:38:02.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将自己放上网呢
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.91,0:38:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想赚钱
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.29,0:38:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以如果想修空调可以
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.11,0:38:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找威信
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.64,0:38:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不但会修空调
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.17,0:38:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且又懂市场
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.52,0:38:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是从小跟师傅学的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.87,0:38:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐牢的时候学的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.28,0:38:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  你坐过牢
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.68,0:38:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么呢  你介不介意跟我们说一说
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.88,0:38:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被老爸害的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.73,0:38:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位师傅真是厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.23,0:38:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畜牲
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.19,0:38:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连老妈都气炸了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.42,0:38:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是追上你  怎么都行呀
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.53,0:38:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着办呀
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.02,0:38:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那飙一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.39,0:38:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.50,0:39:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真快  真的很快呀
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.12,0:39:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它怎么会那么快呢
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.91,0:39:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你赢了  想怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.17,0:39:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没想到  你问它
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.80,0:39:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想快一点  有期限的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.23,0:39:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有期限的
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.30,0:40:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得去一趟深圳找周沅沅
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.16,0:40:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想一辈子都这么瞎着
Dialogue: 0,0:40:11.46,0:40:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这叫做有病乱投医
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.12,0:40:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去给我拿杯酒来
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.13,0:40:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.63,0:40:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么味  大福  什么味
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.87,0:40:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火  着火了  着火了  快  快
Dialogue: 0,0:40:35.45,0:40:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.48,0:40:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照片  我的照片
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.63,0:40:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么多照片  怎么拿呀
Dialogue: 0,0:40:38.96,0:40:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我只有一张  属于我的那一张
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.13,0:40:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪  我帮你拿
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.40,0:40:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钱包  钱包里  钱包里
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.33,0:40:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冰沙呀  免费的呀
Dialogue: 0,0:40:58.48,0:41:01.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Strawberry  那颗冰好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.29,0:41:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进去拍张照吧  拍张照吧  我好想拍呀
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.87,0:41:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要拍了  走吧  我想拍张照
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.07,0:41:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,草莓
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.90,0:41:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别动呀  动着呀
Dialogue: 0,0:41:13.07,0:41:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.48,0:41:24.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天看见我为什么要走
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.28,0:41:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是冰人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.75,0:41:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很丢脸吗
Dialogue: 0,0:41:28.15,0:41:32.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  你上班一个小时赚多少钱
Dialogue: 0,0:41:34.27,0:41:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.30,0:41:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你告诉我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:41:36.65,0:41:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是看不起老爸
Dialogue: 0,0:41:38.15,0:41:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.47,0:41:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十块  可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.70,0:41:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你可不可以给我三十块
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.45,0:41:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为你怕老爸辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.87,0:41:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来想要钱
Dialogue: 0,0:41:51.03,0:41:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.21,0:41:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.04,0:41:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  没有
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.47,0:41:56.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸呀
Dialogue: 0,0:41:58.74,0:41:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,草莓
Dialogue: 0,0:42:31.91,0:42:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  这里有五十块
Dialogue: 0,0:42:34.40,0:42:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不可以买你一个小时啊
Dialogue: 0,0:42:37.02,0:42:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天放学  我朗俑比赛  好想你来看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:42:44.73,0:42:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:42:46.65,0:42:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不可以帮我一个忙呀
Dialogue: 0,0:42:51.22,0:42:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在一小时一千七
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.73,0:42:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刷卡行不行呀
Dialogue: 0,0:42:55.90,0:42:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只收现金
Dialogue: 0,0:43:01.46,0:43:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你啦
Dialogue: 0,0:43:04.04,0:43:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都拜托我  就亏大了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.97,0:43:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点走啦
Dialogue: 0,0:43:10.92,0:43:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.29,0:43:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  好  走  走  走
Dialogue: 0,0:43:23.64,0:43:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  你干什么你
Dialogue: 0,0:43:26.72,0:43:28.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面有个妈妈  脑长了瘤
Dialogue: 0,0:43:28.79,0:43:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就快不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:29.92,0:43:31.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她好想见到她儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:43:31.88,0:43:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你帮我扮她儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:43:33.74,0:43:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  她的眼睛看不到  认不出来
Dialogue: 0,0:43:36.06,0:43:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记住  你叫阿强
Dialogue: 0,0:43:37.59,0:43:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在爱民村长大  刚刚从美国赶回来
Dialogue: 0,0:43:40.55,0:43:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不是阿强呀  你只要抱住她
Dialogue: 0,0:43:42.68,0:43:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给她最后的温暖  行不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:43:45.28,0:43:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:43:46.26,0:43:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强哥  你行的  走  走
Dialogue: 0,0:43:49.73,0:43:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说不说话
Dialogue: 0,0:43:51.27,0:43:52.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婆婆
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.08,0:43:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿强来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:43:55.94,0:43:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿强  阿强
Dialogue: 0,0:44:01.36,0:44:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿强  你好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:44:22.38,0:44:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乌龟
Dialogue: 0,0:44:27.96,0:44:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们叫什么名宇呀
Dialogue: 0,0:44:30.06,0:44:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你干嘛亲我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:44:34.75,0:44:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你人好
Dialogue: 0,0:44:37.05,0:44:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是帮人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:44:40.82,0:44:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮什么帮  都不关你的事
Dialogue: 0,0:44:43.50,0:44:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是去帮他们完成最后的心愿而已
Dialogue: 0,0:44:46.98,0:44:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次那小女孩  说没机会游到浮台
Dialogue: 0,0:44:49.97,0:44:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很想知道要游几下  所以我帮她
Dialogue: 0,0:44:52.79,0:44:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我亲你呀
Dialogue: 0,0:45:13.84,0:45:14.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:45:15.16,0:45:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是深圳交响乐团
Dialogue: 0,0:45:17.91,0:45:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前收到你寄来的求职信
Dialogue: 0,0:45:20.88,0:45:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在可以安排你明天来面试了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:24.41,0:45:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  好  我会准时到的  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:45:34.60,0:45:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于等到了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:38.40,0:45:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了  死了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:44.58,0:45:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:46:38.85,0:46:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:46:46.54,0:46:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢来  慢慢来
Dialogue: 0,0:46:49.23,0:46:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎  欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:46:53.75,0:46:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,演出成功吗
Dialogue: 0,0:47:06.34,0:47:07.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟透
Dialogue: 0,0:47:07.87,0:47:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,推什么推  干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:47:16.76,0:47:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说过莫札特一生坎坷
Dialogue: 0,0:47:19.21,0:47:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他仍然乐观
Dialogue: 0,0:47:20.40,0:47:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小小挫折
Dialogue: 0,0:47:21.90,0:47:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定能克服的  加油
Dialogue: 0,0:47:39.79,0:47:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是寿司就好了  再配酱油
Dialogue: 0,0:47:50.35,0:47:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三点半
Dialogue: 0,0:48:00.26,0:48:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  还差一个
Dialogue: 0,0:48:05.25,0:48:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  以前都是我追你  你加油呀
Dialogue: 0,0:48:08.98,0:48:10.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问  Wasabi在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:48:11.55,0:48:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是那个香港人
Dialogue: 0,0:48:13.36,0:48:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是你把迷药放在寿司里
Dialogue: 0,0:48:15.96,0:48:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我女儿弄成这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:48:17.89,0:48:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯父
Dialogue: 0,0:48:20.70,0:48:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在台湾吗
Dialogue: 0,0:48:22.69,0:48:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  她还在香港啦
Dialogue: 0,0:48:25.65,0:48:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧张她了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:48:26.83,0:48:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个不懂得爱的人  是注定要失败的
Dialogue: 0,0:48:30.13,0:48:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你放手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:48:31.08,0:48:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:48:32.61,0:48:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  一讲到这个你就板起脸来了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:40.14,0:48:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Leslie Guan真的来深圳啦
Dialogue: 0,0:48:43.51,0:48:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这模特儿很普通耶
Dialogue: 0,0:48:44.77,0:48:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比普通还要普通
Dialogue: 0,0:48:46.43,0:48:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那有更好的
Dialogue: 0,0:48:47.78,0:48:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通
Dialogue: 0,0:48:48.98,0:48:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对呀
Dialogue: 0,0:48:50.14,0:48:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你睁大眼睛仔细看看
Dialogue: 0,0:48:52.18,0:48:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这叫普通
Dialogue: 0,0:48:53.78,0:48:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很普通呀
Dialogue: 0,0:48:54.88,0:48:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂个屁
Dialogue: 0,0:48:59.05,0:49:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我拍的第一张照片
Dialogue: 0,0:49:02.07,0:49:03.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是你的女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:49:05.83,0:49:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是伤我最深的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:49:11.13,0:49:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道她在哪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:49:12.91,0:49:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在苏州
Dialogue: 0,0:49:15.32,0:49:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她已经离婚了
Dialogue: 0,0:49:17.00,0:49:17.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得
Dialogue: 0,0:49:18.76,0:49:20.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她曾经好像来找过你
Dialogue: 0,0:49:21.40,0:49:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还叫我骗她  说你不在
Dialogue: 0,0:49:23.33,0:49:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是她抛弃了我
Dialogue: 0,0:49:26.07,0:49:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想见她
Dialogue: 0,0:49:28.25,0:49:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是看着她哭着走的
Dialogue: 0,0:49:31.20,0:49:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么不能给人家一次机会呢
Dialogue: 0,0:49:42.78,0:49:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  不便宜啊  还是走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:49:47.02,0:49:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等会你天天都站着
Dialogue: 0,0:49:49.23,0:49:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是按一按吧  这钱不能省
Dialogue: 0,0:49:52.48,0:49:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两位
Dialogue: 0,0:49:55.00,0:49:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:49:55.72,0:49:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行  相信我  一定好
Dialogue: 0,0:49:58.15,0:49:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  你从早到晚跟人家传讯息
Dialogue: 0,0:50:00.20,0:50:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正都来深圳了  找她出来看看漂不漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:50:03.48,0:50:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神经病
Dialogue: 0,0:50:05.51,0:50:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以为自己是谁呀  拿盆水来照照  找人家出来
Dialogue: 0,0:50:15.12,0:50:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:50:19.41,0:50:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那个不错  跟你换
Dialogue: 0,0:50:23.74,0:50:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:50:25.34,0:50:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很喜欢你  你帮他按吧
Dialogue: 0,0:50:27.76,0:50:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:50:32.35,0:50:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生  小腿很硬  肯定很累吧
Dialogue: 0,0:50:35.77,0:50:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前我做司机
Dialogue: 0,0:50:38.37,0:50:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来去做地板
Dialogue: 0,0:50:41.85,0:50:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在
Dialogue: 0,0:50:43.48,0:50:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我天天都要站
Dialogue: 0,0:50:46.59,0:50:48.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之是苦力一样
Dialogue: 0,0:50:49.68,0:50:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是苦工呀
Dialogue: 0,0:50:53.69,0:50:55.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我用力一点
Dialogue: 0,0:51:00.52,0:51:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的手法很不一样  哪里学的
Dialogue: 0,0:51:05.61,0:51:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自创的
Dialogue: 0,0:51:06.75,0:51:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痔疮
Dialogue: 0,0:51:09.35,0:51:11.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是痔疮  是自创的
Dialogue: 0,0:51:14.25,0:51:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好啊  很棒
Dialogue: 0,0:51:15.51,0:51:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生  怎样称呼
Dialogue: 0,0:51:18.58,0:51:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我苦工吧
Dialogue: 0,0:51:20.62,0:51:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苦工先生
Dialogue: 0,0:51:22.28,0:51:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:51:24.67,0:51:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就叫我九十八号吧
Dialogue: 0,0:51:26.70,0:51:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次来  记得找我
Dialogue: 0,0:51:28.19,0:51:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定找你呀  狗十八号
Dialogue: 0,0:51:31.16,0:51:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,九十八
Dialogue: 0,0:51:45.64,0:51:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你手机  手机响
Dialogue: 0,0:51:48.67,0:51:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上班时间不可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:52:00.08,0:52:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下班之后去见老板
Dialogue: 0,0:52:04.87,0:52:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来
Dialogue: 0,0:52:09.25,0:52:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先坐下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:52:12.04,0:52:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板  你找我
Dialogue: 0,0:52:14.47,0:52:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  你放心
Dialogue: 0,0:52:16.07,0:52:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明天寄点钱回家
Dialogue: 0,0:52:19.33,0:52:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么问起我老板
Dialogue: 0,0:52:21.10,0:52:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是对我有点意思  但是
Dialogue: 0,0:52:25.16,0:52:28.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了  你的意思我懂
Dialogue: 0,0:52:29.88,0:52:33.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你放心  我会让你们过上好日子的
Dialogue: 0,0:52:52.56,0:52:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道莫札特第545首奏呜曲  有什么故事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:53:02.40,0:53:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对他真有兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:53:07.66,0:53:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为我女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:53:09.53,0:53:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结婚了  结婚了还能够传简讯
Dialogue: 0,0:53:13.68,0:53:14.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我是小蜜
Dialogue: 0,0:53:19.53,0:53:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婚姻生活愉快吗
Dialogue: 0,0:53:24.15,0:53:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她一年前跟别人走了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:27.72,0:53:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:33.52,0:53:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:53:38.79,0:53:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我女儿本来很喜欢弹琴
Dialogue: 0,0:53:40.86,0:53:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有天份
Dialogue: 0,0:53:42.49,0:53:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但从她妈妈走的那天开始  她就不再弹琴了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:50.73,0:53:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这款停产很久了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:55.77,0:53:56.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老婆忌日前
Dialogue: 0,0:53:57.13,0:53:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要配到
Dialogue: 0,0:53:58.65,0:53:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你帮帮忙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:54:00.12,0:54:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试试另外一款吧
Dialogue: 0,0:54:02.35,0:54:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行呀
Dialogue: 0,0:54:03.83,0:54:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她用惯的东西就用一辈子
Dialogue: 0,0:54:05.80,0:54:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最讨厌换来换去
Dialogue: 0,0:54:08.57,0:54:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种灯泡
Dialogue: 0,0:54:10.71,0:54:11.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陪了她十几年了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:16.03,0:54:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过对面海吧(九龙)  鸭寮街可能有
Dialogue: 0,0:54:20.68,0:54:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板  帮我多配一块吧
Dialogue: 0,0:54:23.39,0:54:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威哥  最近你可出风头了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:26.52,0:54:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你便宜点儿
Dialogue: 0,0:54:27.66,0:54:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我先看看有没有货
Dialogue: 0,0:54:29.99,0:54:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没货呀  走  走
Dialogue: 0,0:54:32.33,0:54:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卖光啦
Dialogue: 0,0:54:36.35,0:54:37.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:54:38.52,0:54:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你运气真好  最后一个
Dialogue: 0,0:54:53.51,0:54:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:54:59.38,0:55:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畜牲
Dialogue: 0,0:55:01.39,0:55:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见老爸不打招呼
Dialogue: 0,0:55:03.53,0:55:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸
Dialogue: 0,0:55:05.40,0:55:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老爸找人抓我坐牢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:55:07.60,0:55:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不是我  你已经死了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:11.50,0:55:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盗版
Dialogue: 0,0:55:13.54,0:55:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放高利贷  打架
Dialogue: 0,0:55:16.87,0:55:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再下去就被人砍死了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:18.37,0:55:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你就当我死了吧  畜牲
Dialogue: 0,0:55:48.35,0:55:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板叫我给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:55:50.02,0:55:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说  今天你生日  想请你吃顿饭
Dialogue: 0,0:55:53.47,0:55:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是还给他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:55:56.41,0:55:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿着
Dialogue: 0,0:56:02.37,0:56:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人啊  他是跟你闹着玩的
Dialogue: 0,0:56:05.09,0:56:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不要太认真嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:56:07.23,0:56:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吃顿饭
Dialogue: 0,0:56:12.19,0:56:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:56:14.00,0:56:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开车
Dialogue: 0,0:56:16.30,0:56:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小琪
Dialogue: 0,0:56:29.40,0:56:30.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你大爷
Dialogue: 0,0:56:51.92,0:56:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  做得还真像
Dialogue: 0,0:56:58.06,0:57:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜  可惜  可惜
Dialogue: 0,0:57:01.21,0:57:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜什么呀
Dialogue: 0,0:57:02.69,0:57:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是辆自行车呀
Dialogue: 0,0:57:06.60,0:57:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自行车不是车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:57:11.03,0:57:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你生日快乐  祝你生日快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:57:15.17,0:57:20.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝老爸生日快乐  祝你生日快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:57:26.09,0:57:27.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道我许什么愿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:57:27.23,0:57:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以说  说了就不灵了
Dialogue: 0,0:57:29.54,0:57:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不怕  我的愿望是可以再听到你弹琴
Dialogue: 0,0:57:34.54,0:57:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过以后不会再弹了
Dialogue: 0,0:57:36.89,0:57:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  你弹得那么好
Dialogue: 0,0:57:39.20,0:57:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不弹呀
Dialogue: 0,0:57:41.65,0:57:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  听老爸一次  你那么喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:57:44.60,0:57:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢呀
Dialogue: 0,0:57:52.36,0:57:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你要放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:57:54.52,0:57:55.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不弹呀
Dialogue: 0,0:57:58.25,0:57:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妈已经走了
Dialogue: 0,0:58:03.21,0:58:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想听呀
Dialogue: 0,0:58:05.31,0:58:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不会再回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:58:06.64,0:58:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想听呀
Dialogue: 0,0:58:19.59,0:58:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来怎么样  没有啊  就那样了
Dialogue: 0,0:58:21.99,0:58:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辉叔  今天有没有笑话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:58:25.29,0:58:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的笑话不好笑
Dialogue: 0,0:58:28.97,0:58:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板娘  给我两个  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:58:31.74,0:58:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有啦  最后一个上次让一个老伯买走了
Dialogue: 0,0:58:35.71,0:58:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他挺长情的
Dialogue: 0,0:58:37.16,0:58:40.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说要在老婆忌日前  一定要配好它
Dialogue: 0,0:58:41.72,0:58:42.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮个忙
Dialogue: 0,0:58:43.45,0:58:44.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到打电话给我
Dialogue: 0,0:58:44.73,0:58:45.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你电话
Dialogue: 0,0:58:46.41,0:58:49.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  我们今天好好庆祝一下
Dialogue: 0,0:58:49.68,0:58:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庆祝  庆祝什么
Dialogue: 0,0:58:51.76,0:58:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面对现实  我学会了面对现实
Dialogue: 0,0:58:54.83,0:58:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是说好了  要找周沅沅解咒的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:58:57.24,0:58:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大福  其实两个星期前
Dialogue: 0,0:58:59.24,0:59:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就接到医生的电话  说我这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:59:02.45,0:59:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长了个瘤子  是这个瘤子影响到视线
Dialogue: 0,0:59:07.51,0:59:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么不早跟我说
Dialogue: 0,0:59:09.55,0:59:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在这里等她
Dialogue: 0,0:59:11.11,0:59:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是想留下来看能不能补偿的
Dialogue: 0,0:59:14.57,0:59:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们尽力了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:17.45,0:59:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天就回北京
Dialogue: 0,0:59:33.03,0:59:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钢琴家
Dialogue: 0,0:59:38.58,0:59:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你女儿弹琴了没有
Dialogue: 0,0:59:40.75,0:59:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万不要让你女儿放弃钢琴
Dialogue: 0,0:59:44.94,0:59:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你问我为什么喜欢弹琴
Dialogue: 0,0:59:47.77,0:59:48.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷偷告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:59:49.49,0:59:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫札特跟我是同一天生日的
Dialogue: 0,0:59:53.79,0:59:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪  没你的消息  你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:59:57.96,0:59:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要怪自己
Dialogue: 0,0:59:59.78,1:00:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你绝对不是一个失败的父亲
Dialogue: 0,1:00:39.99,1:00:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起呀  老爸把你吵醒啦
Dialogue: 0,1:00:43.10,1:00:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会呀
Dialogue: 0,1:00:45.30,1:00:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好喜欢这个草莓闹钟
Dialogue: 0,1:00:54.39,1:00:56.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是一条鱼  我不怕热
Dialogue: 0,1:01:02.84,1:01:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在最想要的是什么东西
Dialogue: 0,1:01:09.58,1:01:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在最想要一台空调
Dialogue: 0,1:01:14.99,1:01:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我送你一部
Dialogue: 0,1:01:19.16,1:01:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,1:01:22.68,1:01:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我女儿弹琴了
Dialogue: 0,1:01:26.14,1:01:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他女儿弹琴了
Dialogue: 0,1:01:33.52,1:01:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我女儿想来看你演奏
Dialogue: 0,1:01:34.89,1:01:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们上来找你  好不好
Dialogue: 0,1:01:50.48,1:01:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦你  我想配这个水管
Dialogue: 0,1:01:52.68,1:01:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水管
Dialogue: 0,1:01:54.54,1:01:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水管
Dialogue: 0,1:01:58.85,1:01:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五块
Dialogue: 0,1:02:01.61,1:02:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有长一点的
Dialogue: 0,1:02:03.21,1:02:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长一点  长一点的水管
Dialogue: 0,1:02:07.09,1:02:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十块
Dialogue: 0,1:02:08.79,1:02:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十块  很贵呀
Dialogue: 0,1:02:10.80,1:02:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个空调多少钱呀
Dialogue: 0,1:02:15.17,1:02:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会挑呀
Dialogue: 0,1:02:16.82,1:02:19.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经典粉红色  绝种了  四百五十块
Dialogue: 0,1:02:19.99,1:02:22.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四百五  可以便宜一点吗
Dialogue: 0,1:02:22.44,1:02:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以便宜一点吗
Dialogue: 0,1:02:23.74,1:02:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  粉红色耶
Dialogue: 0,1:02:25.21,1:02:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好东西  挺粗的  粉红色
Dialogue: 0,1:02:28.42,1:02:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是歧视粉红色吧
Dialogue: 0,1:02:29.53,1:02:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我赶时间  对不起  老兄  很快
Dialogue: 0,1:02:31.42,1:02:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  我所有钱  四百多块
Dialogue: 0,1:02:35.67,1:02:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我留二十
Dialogue: 0,1:02:38.01,1:02:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你啦
Dialogue: 0,1:02:40.22,1:02:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个空调内地可以用吗
Dialogue: 0,1:02:42.03,1:02:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内地不是用风扇吗
Dialogue: 0,1:02:43.85,1:02:45.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你多久没回内地呀
Dialogue: 0,1:02:45.16,1:02:46.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全换空调了
Dialogue: 0,1:02:48.55,1:02:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关你屁事
Dialogue: 0,1:02:49.95,1:02:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送你一个插头
Dialogue: 0,1:02:51.11,1:02:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢老板  可以了  不要了
Dialogue: 0,1:02:54.88,1:02:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  几块钱生意  是大爷呀
Dialogue: 0,1:02:58.76,1:03:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢老板  不好意思
Dialogue: 0,1:03:00.34,1:03:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点儿  罕有物品
Dialogue: 0,1:03:04.76,1:03:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以后也做粉红色的
Dialogue: 0,1:03:13.18,1:03:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:03:19.03,1:03:20.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  对不起
Dialogue: 0,1:03:20.99,1:03:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跑  站住
Dialogue: 0,1:03:33.94,1:03:34.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威哥
Dialogue: 0,1:03:37.49,1:03:39.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的裤子破了  今晚去哪儿呀
Dialogue: 0,1:03:39.75,1:03:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚专程来感谢你的  行不行
Dialogue: 0,1:03:42.30,1:03:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行  不过说好了  别让我装人啊
Dialogue: 0,1:03:46.41,1:03:47.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上车啦
Dialogue: 0,1:03:53.57,1:03:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:08.87,1:04:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这
Dialogue: 0,1:04:16.28,1:04:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有病  为什么不告诉我
Dialogue: 0,1:04:17.86,1:04:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生说还有多久啊
Dialogue: 0,1:04:27.64,1:04:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这病跟了我八年
Dialogue: 0,1:04:33.13,1:04:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有准备了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:37.04,1:04:38.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有
Dialogue: 0,1:04:44.49,1:04:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事啊
Dialogue: 0,1:05:57.31,1:06:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实说过很多遍了  还要我说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,1:06:00.91,1:06:02.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我不介意任何事
Dialogue: 0,1:06:03.53,1:06:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只爱你一个
Dialogue: 0,1:06:05.56,1:06:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望回到家里的时候  有你抱着我
Dialogue: 0,1:06:09.02,1:06:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想每天早上跟你一起吃早餐
Dialogue: 0,1:06:11.42,1:06:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拖着你的手逛海滩
Dialogue: 0,1:06:13.70,1:06:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这么简单  为什么你给不了我
Dialogue: 0,1:06:17.81,1:06:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你整天想着自己的感受
Dialogue: 0,1:06:20.58,1:06:21.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有想过我
Dialogue: 0,1:06:24.96,1:06:26.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你想怎样
Dialogue: 0,1:06:27.46,1:06:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不再说了
Dialogue: 0,1:06:30.01,1:06:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想清楚再打给我吧  就这样
Dialogue: 0,1:06:42.43,1:06:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝杯热茶
Dialogue: 0,1:06:47.79,1:06:48.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,1:07:03.80,1:07:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不可以抽根烟呀
Dialogue: 0,1:07:05.65,1:07:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  这里不能抽烟
Dialogue: 0,1:07:17.17,1:07:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都没有人
Dialogue: 0,1:07:20.28,1:07:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我抽根烟嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:07:21.89,1:07:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是原则问题
Dialogue: 0,1:07:23.47,1:07:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是原则问题  我想你关门了
Dialogue: 0,1:07:25.62,1:07:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该要走啦  不好意思
Dialogue: 0,1:07:27.71,1:07:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不急  慢慢坐
Dialogue: 0,1:07:29.96,1:07:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等一会儿就没事了
Dialogue: 0,1:07:42.53,1:07:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实你这里的菜挺好吃的
Dialogue: 0,1:07:47.31,1:07:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪里学师的
Dialogue: 0,1:07:50.39,1:07:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东京  银座
Dialogue: 0,1:07:54.07,1:07:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,师傅叫  Maeda-san
Dialogue: 0,1:07:56.28,1:07:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟了他八年了
Dialogue: 0,1:07:59.36,1:08:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然有一天
Dialogue: 0,1:08:00.90,1:08:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他煮了碗热拉面给我
Dialogue: 0,1:08:03.77,1:08:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃完之后  他叫我回到香港
Dialogue: 0,1:08:05.96,1:08:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将他的厨艺  好好相传下去
Dialogue: 0,1:08:08.33,1:08:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是一碗热拉面
Dialogue: 0,1:08:11.83,1:08:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那时候去东京旅行
Dialogue: 0,1:08:14.46,1:08:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那些街边的红灯区吃拉面
Dialogue: 0,1:08:20.39,1:08:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到一对情侣
Dialogue: 0,1:08:23.11,1:08:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很可爱
Dialogue: 0,1:08:25.35,1:08:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们好像没什么  很普通的
Dialogue: 0,1:08:29.94,1:08:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我看到他们一直在桌子下
Dialogue: 0,1:08:32.71,1:08:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人手拉着手  一直没有放开
Dialogue: 0,1:08:37.36,1:08:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很温馨的眼神看着对方
Dialogue: 0,1:08:41.95,1:08:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来他们的面到了  那个师傅放下
Dialogue: 0,1:08:46.16,1:08:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男孩子就很细心的帮女孩子准备好筷子
Dialogue: 0,1:08:51.93,1:08:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还喂给她吃
Dialogue: 0,1:08:53.67,1:08:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时觉得好感动
Dialogue: 0,1:08:56.51,1:08:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我觉得就算他们两个人吃一碗面
Dialogue: 0,1:09:00.56,1:09:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都可以吃得那么开心
Dialogue: 0,1:09:04.62,1:09:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱就是这么简单
Dialogue: 0,1:09:11.38,1:09:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来这么简单
Dialogue: 0,1:09:47.56,1:09:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小丽
Dialogue: 0,1:09:49.43,1:09:50.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我跟老板说
Dialogue: 0,1:09:51.65,1:09:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能接受他的礼物
Dialogue: 0,1:09:59.77,1:10:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想人家就去找她吧
Dialogue: 0,1:10:05.48,1:10:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大人的事  小朋友别管那么多
Dialogue: 0,1:10:15.17,1:10:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钢琴家在哪里
Dialogue: 0,1:10:20.22,1:10:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,1:10:21.27,1:10:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  我是草莓呀
Dialogue: 0,1:10:24.16,1:10:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸买了一部很漂亮的空调
Dialogue: 0,1:10:28.66,1:10:32.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他放在家里很久了  他想送给你
Dialogue: 0,1:10:32.96,1:10:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以见他一次吗
Dialogue: 0,1:10:39.43,1:10:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  草莓
Dialogue: 0,1:10:41.78,1:10:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  明天三点
Dialogue: 0,1:10:44.00,1:10:45.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮你约好她了
Dialogue: 0,1:10:46.08,1:10:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的
Dialogue: 0,1:10:49.84,1:10:51.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天呀  完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,1:10:58.39,1:11:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生  是不是这个牌子的黑松露呀
Dialogue: 0,1:11:02.37,1:11:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呀  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,1:11:03.63,1:11:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Wasabi  我们有新鲜的日本芥末
Dialogue: 0,1:11:07.22,1:11:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是要这种芥末
Dialogue: 0,1:11:13.32,1:11:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么那么多天了  都还不打来呀
Dialogue: 0,1:11:17.76,1:11:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  我们是安心财务
Dialogue: 0,1:11:19.55,1:11:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问小姐要借钱吗  有没有搞错
Dialogue: 0,1:11:25.81,1:11:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打的电话暂时未能接...
Dialogue: 0,1:11:36.86,1:11:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行不行  像不像
Dialogue: 0,1:11:39.07,1:11:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸你真的好
Dialogue: 0,1:11:42.28,1:11:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帅呀
Dialogue: 0,1:11:45.54,1:11:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去吧  女生不喜欢别人迟到的  真的
Dialogue: 0,1:12:03.29,1:12:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到了  你在哪
Dialogue: 0,1:12:17.16,1:12:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,华哥
Dialogue: 0,1:12:24.43,1:12:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苦工  九十八号
Dialogue: 0,1:12:26.31,1:12:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你
Dialogue: 0,1:12:39.76,1:12:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钢琴家
Dialogue: 0,1:12:41.15,1:12:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法拉利呀
Dialogue: 0,1:12:47.29,1:12:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗子
Dialogue: 0,1:12:48.94,1:12:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是
Dialogue: 0,1:12:53.31,1:12:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁说香港人不浪漫的
Dialogue: 0,1:12:55.25,1:12:58.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天有一家寿司店  弄了个完美一餐
Dialogue: 0,1:12:58.10,1:13:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是专门为一个女孩子而设的
Dialogue: 0,1:13:00.79,1:13:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种追求方式  大家不妨也学习一下
Dialogue: 0,1:13:08.65,1:13:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大福  你先回北京吧
Dialogue: 0,1:13:11.29,1:13:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去一趟苏州
Dialogue: 0,1:13:13.29,1:13:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去苏州  去找她
Dialogue: 0,1:13:16.60,1:13:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开刀前我想去看看她
Dialogue: 0,1:13:18.50,1:13:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我陪你一起去
Dialogue: 0,1:13:19.70,1:13:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了  我自己去
Dialogue: 0,1:13:21.28,1:13:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  我在深圳等你
Dialogue: 0,1:13:25.45,1:13:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大福  我知道你一直想做一位出色优秀的摄影师
Dialogue: 0,1:13:32.76,1:13:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想告诉你的是
Dialogue: 0,1:13:34.96,1:13:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打光  化妆  服装
Dialogue: 0,1:13:38.85,1:13:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是最重要的
Dialogue: 0,1:13:41.15,1:13:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的是  你要通过他的眼睛
Dialogue: 0,1:13:43.26,1:13:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓到他的开心激动
Dialogue: 0,1:13:46.73,1:13:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孤单和孤寂冷漠
Dialogue: 0,1:13:49.55,1:13:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灵魂
Dialogue: 0,1:13:55.33,1:13:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,1:13:57.53,1:13:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找到周沅沅啦
Dialogue: 0,1:14:03.08,1:14:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又搞什么呀
Dialogue: 0,1:14:14.02,1:14:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭小子
Dialogue: 0,1:14:24.52,1:14:26.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你记不记得我还欠你一样东西
Dialogue: 0,1:14:29.83,1:14:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次赛车  你赢了
Dialogue: 0,1:14:33.80,1:14:36.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过  你想怎么样都可以
Dialogue: 0,1:14:39.29,1:14:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你好了再说吧
Dialogue: 0,1:14:42.13,1:14:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:14:48.74,1:14:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在就要知道
Dialogue: 0,1:14:56.26,1:14:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你整天帮人
Dialogue: 0,1:14:58.77,1:15:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次让我帮你
Dialogue: 0,1:15:29.81,1:15:32.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  把那个招牌收起来  不会来了
Dialogue: 0,1:15:33.12,1:15:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不收不能下班啊
Dialogue: 0,1:15:39.82,1:15:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚不做生意
Dialogue: 0,1:15:42.06,1:15:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一个可以吗
Dialogue: 0,1:15:44.52,1:15:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Wasabi Wasabi Wasabi呀  师傅
Dialogue: 0,1:15:48.03,1:15:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Wasabi都不知放哪  你自己找吧
Dialogue: 0,1:15:50.64,1:15:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你那个Wasabi呀  师傅
Dialogue: 0,1:16:01.73,1:16:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肚子有点饿  你们今天晚上不做生意吗
Dialogue: 0,1:16:10.05,1:16:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些材料不是你常用的
Dialogue: 0,1:16:12.43,1:16:14.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由左吃到右  请
Dialogue: 0,1:16:19.80,1:16:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望她喜欢吃吧
Dialogue: 0,1:16:36.97,1:16:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了  全吐出来了
Dialogue: 0,1:16:40.50,1:16:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实不是那么差
Dialogue: 0,1:16:43.33,1:16:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是  不属于你的味道
Dialogue: 0,1:16:48.14,1:16:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,始终原味是最好
Dialogue: 0,1:16:49.79,1:16:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会突然想做这些混合的菜啊
Dialogue: 0,1:16:54.18,1:16:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你寄给我的食谱
Dialogue: 0,1:16:57.14,1:16:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我全看遍了
Dialogue: 0,1:16:58.91,1:17:00.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是说都丢了吗
Dialogue: 0,1:17:03.02,1:17:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舍不得还给你
Dialogue: 0,1:17:13.88,1:17:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,1:17:15.30,1:17:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你做过最难吃的一次
Dialogue: 0,1:17:20.51,1:17:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却是我吃过最感动的一餐
Dialogue: 0,1:17:27.59,1:17:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实你装得挺像的  还弄个法拉利的帽子
Dialogue: 0,1:17:32.64,1:17:33.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这帽子是真的
Dialogue: 0,1:17:34.73,1:17:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不算骗你啦
Dialogue: 0,1:17:36.78,1:17:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的是司机
Dialogue: 0,1:17:38.50,1:17:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过不是开法拉利
Dialogue: 0,1:17:40.98,1:17:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我也算真的钢琴家
Dialogue: 0,1:17:43.63,1:17:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过没有去维也纳巡回演奏
Dialogue: 0,1:17:49.20,1:17:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你  为什么不弹了  那怎么弹
Dialogue: 0,1:17:59.47,1:18:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确定是她的话  我们就去后台找她
Dialogue: 0,1:18:01.92,1:18:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  门票  先生  门票
Dialogue: 0,1:18:03.81,1:18:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  不好意思
Dialogue: 0,1:18:14.44,1:18:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,师傅  你看
Dialogue: 0,1:18:16.07,1:18:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周沅沅
Dialogue: 0,1:18:17.49,1:18:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是主角吗
Dialogue: 0,1:18:21.93,1:18:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是主角  大福
Dialogue: 0,1:18:25.07,1:18:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是主角吗
Dialogue: 0,1:18:26.09,1:18:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她比路人甲还不如
Dialogue: 0,1:18:35.88,1:18:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  冰雹
Dialogue: 0,1:18:36.70,1:18:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冰雹呀  冰雹呀
Dialogue: 0,1:18:56.95,1:18:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,1:18:58.43,1:19:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  来  跟我来
Dialogue: 0,1:19:06.69,1:19:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周沅沅
Dialogue: 0,1:19:08.47,1:19:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们找你找得好辛苦
Dialogue: 0,1:19:12.42,1:19:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,1:19:14.20,1:19:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,始终做不到最完美的一餐给你
Dialogue: 0,1:19:18.55,1:19:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感动
Dialogue: 0,1:19:20.09,1:19:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是最完美
Dialogue: 0,1:19:24.47,1:19:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你
Dialogue: 0,1:19:26.27,1:19:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不可以不走
Dialogue: 0,1:19:35.77,1:19:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找我
Dialogue: 0,1:19:37.23,1:19:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是想来看看我有多可怜吧  非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,1:19:40.55,1:19:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我的一句话  让你成了现在这个样子
Dialogue: 0,1:19:43.91,1:19:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起啊
Dialogue: 0,1:19:45.65,1:19:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我可不可以请你做我徒弟的模特儿
Dialogue: 0,1:19:49.15,1:19:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他给你拍一组照片
Dialogue: 0,1:19:50.64,1:19:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  你没问题
Dialogue: 0,1:19:52.44,1:19:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的眼睛真的被你说中了
Dialogue: 0,1:19:54.83,1:19:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经快瞎了  我做不了摄影师了
Dialogue: 0,1:19:56.70,1:19:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老师没有骗你  是真的
Dialogue: 0,1:20:00.57,1:20:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们俩不可能大老远的从北京赶到这来耍你
Dialogue: 0,1:20:10.46,1:20:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,1:20:11.10,1:20:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以相信他
Dialogue: 0,1:20:12.45,1:20:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他完全可以把你最美丽最动人  也是我
Dialogue: 0,1:20:15.83,1:20:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最想要的那一瞬间拍到
Dialogue: 0,1:20:19.35,1:20:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗
Dialogue: 0,1:20:27.39,1:20:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你流血了
Dialogue: 0,1:20:39.74,1:20:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  好了
Dialogue: 0,1:20:41.31,1:20:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要来开机
Dialogue: 0,1:20:43.14,1:20:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开吗  你开机啦
Dialogue: 0,1:20:53.18,1:20:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的有空调了
Dialogue: 0,1:20:55.32,1:20:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的有了  真的
Dialogue: 0,1:20:57.14,1:20:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是粉红色的
Dialogue: 0,1:21:00.04,1:21:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停了  停了
Dialogue: 0,1:21:02.42,1:21:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像停了
Dialogue: 0,1:21:10.01,1:21:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好凉快呀
Dialogue: 0,1:21:18.24,1:21:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是看到宣传才回来的
Dialogue: 0,1:21:20.24,1:21:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你为什么会来
Dialogue: 0,1:21:22.31,1:21:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为Wasabi跟酱油天生注定是一对的
Dialogue: 0,1:21:32.16,1:21:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一百天  一百天了  你去看看啊
Dialogue: 0,1:21:41.90,1:21:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦
Dialogue: 0,1:21:47.40,1:21:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没来
Dialogue: 0,1:21:58.82,1:22:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小方呢  怎么不见他
Dialogue: 0,1:22:01.64,1:22:03.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他走了  说到外边去闯闯
Dialogue: 0,1:22:05.87,1:22:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他走了
Dialogue: 0,1:22:07.11,1:22:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚到火车站去了
Dialogue: 0,1:22:17.10,1:22:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不站下去
Dialogue: 0,1:22:19.19,1:22:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我还有资格吗
Dialogue: 0,1:22:25.54,1:22:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要出去闯一闯
Dialogue: 0,1:22:27.73,1:22:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等赚了钱再回来
Dialogue: 0,1:22:31.73,1:22:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻瓜  到时候她会嫁人的  那我把她抢回来
Dialogue: 0,1:22:36.68,1:22:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这小子
Dialogue: 0,1:22:41.37,1:22:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿着
Dialogue: 0,1:22:44.30,1:22:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我输了  你还没有
Dialogue: 0,1:22:48.45,1:22:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上海  硬座
Dialogue: 0,1:23:11.09,1:23:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小方
Dialogue: 0,1:23:13.39,1:23:14.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小方
Dialogue: 0,1:23:19.13,1:23:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小方
Dialogue: 0,1:23:20.30,1:23:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火车马上要开啦
Dialogue: 0,1:23:21.62,1:23:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没上车的马上上车  火车马...
Dialogue: 0,1:23:24.60,1:23:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小方  你在哪里
Dialogue: 0,1:23:28.81,1:23:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底喜不喜欢我
Dialogue: 0,1:23:34.04,1:23:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不可以告诉我
Dialogue: 0,1:23:36.92,1:23:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么第一百天  你不站下去
Dialogue: 0,1:23:42.93,1:23:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我  为什么第一百天  你不站下去
Dialogue: 0,1:23:53.52,1:23:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪里
Dialogue: 0,1:24:08.38,1:24:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小方
Dialogue: 0,1:24:23.76,1:24:24.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起来
Dialogue: 0,1:24:25.43,1:24:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛  我们走
Dialogue: 0,1:24:34.14,1:24:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你整天帮人
Dialogue: 0,1:24:36.05,1:24:37.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次让我帮你
Dialogue: 0,1:24:38.48,1:24:43.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我常常在想  可以骑着摩托车一直往前冲
Dialogue: 0,1:24:45.45,1:24:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用管红绿灯  不用停
Dialogue: 0,1:24:50.02,1:24:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远都看不到终点
Dialogue: 0,1:25:05.88,1:25:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好凉快  好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:25:07.96,1:25:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲啦  亲啦  亲啦  亲啦
Dialogue: 0,1:25:11.98,1:25:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老婆  你儿子还算有点良心
Dialogue: 0,1:25:18.05,1:25:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么呀  别闹啦
Dialogue: 0,1:25:21.84,1:25:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,1:25:23.82,1:25:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我换错了插头了
Dialogue: 0,1:25:26.96,1:25:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,1:25:29.96,1:25:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么什么都看不见了
Dialogue: 0,1:25:31.77,1:25:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到嘴的鸭子又飞了
Dialogue: 0,1:25:41.98,1:25:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记不记得
Dialogue: 0,1:25:44.06,1:25:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你问过我有没有梦想
Dialogue: 0,1:25:46.38,1:25:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的梦想就是带你去开法拉利
Dialogue: 0,1:25:50.13,1:25:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一边听莫札特  一边游车河
Dialogue: 0,1:25:55.81,1:25:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在
Dialogue: 0,1:25:58.23,1:26:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的梦想可以成真
Dialogue: 0,1:26:04.23,1:26:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  我也要系安全带
Dialogue: 0,1:26:10.41,1:26:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是没有莫札特
Dialogue: 0,1:26:14.74,1:26:15.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的
Dialogue: 0,1:26:22.67,1:26:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听到
Dialogue: 0,1:26:24.73,1:26:25.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你弹的莫札特
Dialogue: 0,1:26:39.88,1:26:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老婆  我跟儿子和好了
Dialogue: 0,1:27:39.28,1:27:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿威  这样抱着你好幸福
Dialogue: 0,1:27:44.64,1:27:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,1:27:46.65,1:27:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能认识你  是我这辈子最幸运的事
Dialogue: 0,1:27:52.56,1:27:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果要记住我  就记住今晚
Dialogue: 0,1:28:14.66,1:28:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沅沅
Dialogue: 0,1:28:16.13,1:28:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看这边  好  很好
Dialogue: 0,1:28:19.66,1:28:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,1:28:23.67,1:28:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,1:28:30.03,1:28:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  今天拍了这么久
Dialogue: 0,1:28:32.23,1:28:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好
Dialogue: 0,1:28:33.70,1:28:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要一起吃早点
Dialogue: 0,1:28:36.20,1:28:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好呀
Dialogue: 0,1:28:38.69,1:28:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都拍到六点了
Dialogue: 0,1:28:40.16,1:28:41.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的手表很酷呀
Dialogue: 0,1:28:42.42,1:28:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老爸送给我的
Dialogue: 0,1:28:43.82,1:28:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二十年前  我老爸跟他的老板打赌
Dialogue: 0,1:28:47.37,1:28:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是整个夏天都要站在外面
Dialogue: 0,1:28:50.28,1:28:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像要站一百天呢
Dialogue: 0,1:29:10.58,1:29:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸他告诉我
Dialogue: 0,1:29:12.40,1:29:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一百天代表了坚守和盼望
