INSPIRED BY A TRUE STORY,
THIS FILM IS FICTION.
CHARACTERS AND EVENTS ARE FICTIONAL.
NETFLIX PRESENTS
[metal clanging, lock opening]
-[indistinct yelling in distance]
-[keys jangling]
[keys jangling]
[door unlocking, door closing]
[guard] Last name, first name,
date of birth, please.
Grégory Cerva. C-E-R-V-A.
September 4, 1976.
-Any family?
-No.
Give me your left hand.
All four fingers.
Over there, back against the wall.
[somber music plays]
-[sirens wail]
-[Yass] TN13, BAC 26. Officers in pursuit.
We're in Corbière
chasing a stolen scooter with no plates.
8 MONTHS EARLIER
The make is a Yamaha.
The suspect isn't wearing a helmet
and refuses to pull over.
[TN13] Continue the pursuit.
Describe progress.
Pull over!
-[horns honk]
-[Yass] The suspect is going uphill!
He's still refusing to pull over!
Still refusing!
-Speed up, Greg.
-[Greg] I know. I'm trying.
[Yass] Stay on him! Stay on him!
Fuck, speed up!
-[Antoine] Hey, hey!
-Hey! Pull over!
-Pull over and we'll talk!
-[Yass] He still refuses to pull over.
Officers in pursuit.
I repeat, officers in pursuit.
[tires screech]
[Greg] Shit! Fuck!
[siren stops wailing]
[scooter engine revving]
Stop!
Hey!
Shit!
-Can't believe I didn't catch this junk.
-[Greg] Didn't run fast enough, man.
You run like my grandmother.
If it'd been me…
"Me"? Where were you?
Behind your slow ass.
If I'd run ahead, he'd be in cuffs.
-If you ran ahead. Sorry.
-Yeah, right.
I was in front, so I let you pass.
What are you laughing at, huh?
You just stayed in the car, asshole.
We'll have to do two hours of paperwork
over a piece of shit stolen scooter.
It doesn't even have plates!
We're not doing this today.
-[Yass] No.
-What?
-Forget it.
-What? Forget what? I didn't say anything.
-[Yass] But you're going to.
-Come on. Shall we get stupid?
-[Yass] Here we go.
-I'll call.
[tapping phone keys]
[outgoing call tone sounds]
-Yeah, it's me.
-[woman] Let me call back in five.
-Wait.
-What do you want?
I need some quick info. Know what block
your neighborhood dealer's on today?
No one's selling around my place today.
Go to Félix Pyat. The dealer's in Block C.
All right.
Good stuff. Go ahead. I'll follow.
-Giddy up.
-Let's do this.
-Let's go the back way!
-Hear hear.
[distant yelling]
-We're coming up on the lookout.
-[distant shouting]
[rap music plays]
Looking for that fire.
[lookout] Slide on in.
[Yass] We're in.
We're coming up on the block.
Yeah. Not yet.
Got eyes on the dealer.
[brakes squeak]
[muttering]
-[Yass] All right, Greg. Head our way.
-Copy.
[car engine starts]
[tires screech]
[tense music plays]
Got a 20 sack, please?
-Police!
-[dealer yells]
[tires screech]
[whistles] 5-0!
[man 1] Let go, you little bitch!
[yelling]
[brakes screech]
Go, go! Come on, Greg, we got him!
[gang yells in distance]
-Let's go. Move, move!
-[dealer] Let me go, motherfucker!
[gang yells indistinctly]
[Yass] Faster!
-[dealer] I ain't got shit!
-What is that?
-That's not mine!
-What's that?
[Yass] Fuck!
[indistinct yelling]
Motherfucker. This might hurt a bit.
We got this. Faster!
[smashing]
["Baby Blue" by Action Bronson
ft. Chance the Rapper plays]
♪ Why you always all on my back? ♪
♪ When I'm with you ♪
♪ Baby girl, I'm blue ♪
♪ Because you treat me like shit ♪
♪ I paid for the bed
And never even slept in it ♪
♪ I paid for that crib
I never stepped foot in ♪
♪ And now somebody else
Is eating all the pudding ♪
♪ Things change
Now my dashboard wooden ♪
♪ All black Benz
Like a young Doc Gooden ♪
♪ Dark shades, 'cause I'm stone crazy ♪
♪ Girl, we grown
Stop playing on my phone, baby ♪
-♪ Be right back ♪
-♪ Why you always all on my back? ♪
♪ Why you gotta do me like that? ♪
♪ Why you gotta act like a bitch? ♪
♪ When I'm with you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Baby girl, I'm blue ♪
Here.
Hey! Only five?
What do you mean, only five?
That was the deal.
The dealer from Félix Pyat,
that was a big deal, right?
[snickers]
-Yeah, it was a big deal.
-So break me off here, please.
-I'm trying to get paid over here.
-Why you trying to play me?
Aah! [chuckles]
[woman giggles]
Nah, I'm serious.
The price for fire is high out there.
-Ah, yeah?
-It's true.
-Your government's breaking our balls.
-Gimme a hit.
Come on. Like they don't know
who's buying all that hash?
Your face. Turn.
[exhales slowly]
[chuckling] Looks like you got rocked.
[woman chuckles]
[both chuckle]
-I took a punch, yeah.
-Yeah, you got hit with a brick.
[both chuckle]
-You should've seen the other guy.
-Oh, you're such a pussy.
[woman snickers]
-Amel.
-Fuck around, and fall in that water.
I'm the one going in?
-Stop! Stop! Quit playing!
-Ooh! Don't mess with the bull.
-Wanna get some grub? Your treat.
-Here, smoke. No, your treat.
You only gave me five sticks.
So you're buying, big timer.
Put that away.
-Relax. No one's gonna steal it.
-Put it away.
-Can you smoke, please?
-What if someone walks by? Put that away.
[Amel snickers]
[siren wails]
[distant yelling]
[Yass] How's it going?
What the hell are you doing here?
You didn't do nothing, right? [snickers]
Hey. What's up, man?
Yo, brother. What's happening?
-Is this place a zoo today or what?
-Shut your mouth!
[man] Thanks, Laurence.
All right.
We can't continue like this. Every time
he sees a vehicle, it turns into a war.
-Too much damage, Greg.
-[sighs]
Some damage, 200 grams,
and a dealer off the street isn't nothing.
The headlight, a bumper,
a rear fender, that's 3,000 euros!
-That's how we're keeping score?
-Please, Greg. Stop it.
The guys upstairs
are breaking my balls 24/7.
They're up my ass
every time you pull this bullshit. Huh?
Also, you need to stop
hanging around those fucking ghettos.
-Making dealer runs.
-[Greg] Someone has to.
No one gives a fuck about 100 euros.
You need to get this through your head.
A small-time pickpocket or big-time dealer
hits our numbers just the same.
All they want us to do is meet our quota.
That, and clean arrests.
-Clean arrests.
-[man] Yeah, clean arrests.
Try taking police reports, for example.
That's efficient.
It's never that way with dealers.
They're nothing but a headache. Look…
Drug trafficking,
Félix Pyat, plus one. You see?
Cigarettes, smuggling, plus one.
-Mugging, plus one.
-That's quality?
-That the quality you're talking about?
-It's a fucking plus one.
[sighs]
[radio] I repeat, a road accident
at the Grand Littoral store.
In the parking lot, level two.
Um, Car 14, your patrol is over.
Message received. Have a good night.
[radio buzzes]
[kids yelling playfully]
I went and saw the baby with Nora.
-And?
-Yeah.
It was in 3D. It was weird.
[radio] TV13, head for Le Merlan--
I mean, he looked kinda weird.
He looks like a little alien.
What you talking about, 3D?
I mean 3D. I don't know.
You can see the baby in 3D.
It's super weird.
You get glasses?
-Huh?
-Glasses.
No, idiot. You're such an idiot.
-The image is in 3D.
-You think that?
It lets you see all the… the baby.
Ehh, it's not actually 3D.
No, not like 3D at the movies. It's not--
-Why'd you say it's 3D like the movies?
-[sighs] Forget it.
-So, no glasses?
-No, no glasses.
OK. That's what's up.
-I swear--
-Dickhead.
Does he look like you?
-I think he has my eyes.
-[chuckles]
-As long as he doesn't have your mug.
-I know, right? [chuckles]
Fuck!
[indistinct chattering]
-How you living?
-Good, you?
Listen, chief,
that ginger friend of yours,
he straight-up
grabbed my cousin yesterday.
He stripped him,
robbed him, and beat him up.
Not cool. What can I say?
He's an asshole. It is what it is.
Could you talk to him for me?
Sure. Enough of your life story.
Got any intel for me?
No, bro. I swear, I just started my shift.
-Look, my bag is full.
-Why do you swear?
-So you believe me.
-Nothing going on?
Not right now. If I hear anything,
I'll call you. You know that.
-Look, we're just selling our cigarettes.
-OK.
-I only sell cigarettes.
-All right, enough. Give me a carton.
-All you.
-OK.
[man] Have a great day.
That's nothing. Don't worry about it.
Nothing there.
[Antoine] Hmm?
[man] Thank you. Thank you very much.
Oh, nice to see you!
-How's it going, chief?
-How's the family?
-Want three kebabs per usual?
-[Antoine] Yes, sir.
Want extra harissa,
lettuce, tomatoes, onions?
[sizzling]
[Antoine] Oh, here we go.
-Check out your boy over there.
-Who?
-The guy by the fruit.
-Which guy by the fruit?
[Antoine] The guy right there
with the hoodie.
[Yass] Yeah?
Twenty euros
he's gonna grab that old lady's wallet.
[Yass] No, that guy's too relaxed.
Hands in his pockets, not looking around.
Nah.
-Twenty bucks, you're on.
-Let's go.
Come on, big fella.
She's just a little old lady.
-You got this, get busy!
-It's not gonna happen for you.
-What's he doing?
-He's holding a melon and smelling it.
Oh no! Goodbye, ma'am.
-[chuckles]
-Oh, weak sauce.
-Hey! Where's my 20?
-I don't have any cash.
You're such a cheapskate.
You never have any money.
You probably spent it all on that haircut.
-[fake laughs]
-Ask for your money back. There's lunch!
-Ah!
-This is for you.
-[Yass] You hook it up?
-Got your extra meat.
And samurai sauce. Don't worry, I got you.
-Bon appétit, my friends.
-Mm!
There are turtle vendors over there.
Shall we get them?
-How many are there?
-[Yass] Two.
That'll get us today's quota.
Hmm?
Nah, I don't do turtles.
What does that mean?
What don't you understand?
I don't do turtles.
No, no, no. Wait.
Why don't you do turtles?
-I don't do turtles.
-You wouldn't do turtles?
-I'm not doing turtles.
-[Greg] You're gonna do turtles.
-We have to go back with something.
-Think of the animals.
-Bro, in my sauce, you serious?
-"I don't do turtles," that's bullshit.
-I don't do turtles.
-Think of the animals.
[turtle sellers mutter]
-Gentlemen.
-Hello, sir.
[clears throat]
Who do these turtles belong to?
-They're not ours.
-Not ours.
-[Greg] Oh yeah?
You know it's illegal to sell these?
-Yes, but sir--
-This species is protected.
Illegal, yeah. But they're not ours.
-Stop treating us like fools.
-We told you, they're not ours.
-Your pockets.
-[seller 1] What do you mean?
-Empty your pockets.
-Nothing in them. What's the deal?
-Empty them right now.
-Sir, there's nothing in my pockets.
-Hey! What'd you slap him for?
-Empty your pockets.
-Empty them!
-What do you think you're doing?
What's your problem?
Empty your fucking pockets.
-That's not yours?
-Empty them.
-I told you to empty them.
-[seller 2] We're good men.
Pick 'em up!
-What are you doing? It's getting away.
-[Greg] Pick 'em up.
-[Antoine] Where do you live?
-The 15th.
-So, you're from around here?
-Yeah, it's my home.
Oh, these are my colleagues.
-I gotta roll. Nice to meet you.
-They're here for turtles?
Hey, Momo. Do I owe you anything?
-OK, no problem.
-Put her on my tab too.
-Whoa, whoa. Big-time collar!
-[Greg] Shut up. Get in the car.
-Stop acting high and mighty.
-What's your problem?
[TN13] All units in the northern sector,
active car jacking in the 15th.
-A black Audi.
-TN13. BAC 26, we're on it.
-Go on, get outta here.
-[engine starts]
-[siren wails]
-[tires screech]
[whistle blowing]
[spotter] Popo!
-Popo!
-[whistle blowing]
[Greg] Fucking hell!
-Shit!
-[TN13] BAC 26, TN13, abandon pursuit.
Do not enter the ghettos.
-[Antoine] These guys are fired up.
-[Greg] Let's go.
What's the problem?
Huh? What are you doing here?
We were following a stolen car.
You see it?
-You're the only person I've seen.
-Really? Didn't see anything?
Well, then.
[TN13] BAC 26, this is TN13.
Respond to my message.
Your friend over there must be hot.
-Looks like you the one in the heat.
-I'm perfectly comfortable.
[TN13] Do not enter the ghetto.
Abandon pursuit immediately.
Well, then. They're calling you.
You should probably go.
You're the law now?
[chuckles]
I'm not the law. Me, I'm a diplomat.
Here to protect you.
But if you wanna go in, go ahead.
-You know what?
-[man 2] Hey, come on.
[man 1] They'll probably be into it.
Haven't seen cops for a while. Go for it.
[gang members jeer]
[man 1] They're inviting you in.
You don't wanna go?
[all jeer indistinctly]
This is TN13, get out immediately.
I repeat, get out immediately.
I repeat, get out immediately. I repeat--
[gang members jeer]
-[man 3] Son of a bitch!
-Easy, guys.
-[man 4] Motherfucker!
-Easy, guys. Nothing to see.
These little bitches just got
a little worked up.
About done breaking our balls.
You're about done
breaking our balls, right?
You done breaking my balls,
mark-ass bitch?
Shut your mouth
and get the fuck outta here!
You heard me, you little pussy?
[gang members jeer]
You ain't shit without your boys.
Without them, who, what would you be?
Nothing!
Who'd you be without that badge?
Without your boys, you'd be nothing!
Time's up!
Roll out, or come with.
[gang members exclaim]
[man 4] You're not nothing.
[man 5] Yo, come and get some
or get lost, pig!
-[man 6] Go home, blue!
-[man 1] Talking all that shit! [laughs]
Just to leave,
walk outta here like a little bitch!
You guys ain't shit.
Next time, bring some muscle!
-[laughter]
-[man 7] That's right, go on!
[gang members jeer]
[man 8] Come on, get gone! Go, go.
Go fuck your sisters!
[man 1] Fuck your mother.
Fuck your sister.
And fuck your dad!
-That's right, get outta here!
-Beat it, boy.
-Yeah, and don't come back!
-[man 9] Fuck you!
Yo, fuck off, pussies!
[siren wails]
Guys, I brought you some sick gifts.
Come on, Mamadou.
Hey, you here legally, at least?
[chuckles]
Greg?
[Greg] No, Jérôme. I don't need this.
Don't bust my balls.
We didn't go in the ghetto,
didn't arrest anyone.
You asked us to walk away, we did.
I don't need a lecture--
Wait. I didn't come here
to yell at you. It's fine.
Then why are you here?
I know. I know what it's like.
I've been where you are.
-No. You don't know.
-Greg, I do.
-You don't know why.
-Of course I do.
Why do you think I chose a desk job
ten years ago?
-'Cause you're smart and I'm a moron.
-Stop it, you're not a moron.
Because the field is…
'Cause it's frustrating there.
Shit. I feel you. You feel like you're…
Like you're suffocating.
Right?
[sighs] We're useless.
We're useless now.
It's over.
The more we do, the less we achieve.
I don't understand how we got here.
I don't know, maybe it's too late.
These people have lost all hope
that we're here to help them.
They're resigned to living in the shit
'cause we can't help them.
As soon as we step foot in the ghettos,
we get assaulted, spat on,
I get called a pussy every day.
Every day I get called a pussy!
But we can't make waves.
We can't break our equipment.
Just laissez-faire. So there it is.
It is what it is. Maybe we have a plan
and I just don't get it. What's the plan?
Explain it to me, please.
What are we doing?
[slurps]
-[phones ring]
-[operator] 911. What's your emergency?
Yes.
Ma'am, we're contacting
the fire department now.
911, what's your emergency?
[man] The pickpocket stealing wallets
in Grand Littoral is back.
Know where he went?
He's at the Mirabeau entrance.
He's wearing a red sweatshirt.
-May I ask you for your name, please?
-[caller hangs up]
Hello?
[outgoing call tone sounds]
-It's me.
-[Yass] Yeah, babe.
Remember the gypsy stealing wallets
at Grand Littoral?
-Yeah.
-I just got a report. He's in Mirabeau.
-Red sweatshirt.
-OK. Thanks, babe.
OK. but hurry up, OK?
I didn't transfer it to central.
[train horn honking]
[kid screams]
[community members cheering]
[man] Go on!
[Antoine] Open the door!
-[Greg] No, no. Antoine!
-Come here!
[pickpocket squeals, gasps]
What's all this paper, huh?
-Dealing now?
-[Antoine] Quit your crying!
[meat sizzles]
For real, we should've taken that cash.
Are you stupid?
What for?
The ginger helps himself.
Navaro, jump in here?
-Enough, babe.
-What you want us to say?
-He's just an idiot. That's the way it is.
-An idiot?
Just saying.
No, seriously.
Go ahead and play at being gangsters.
-Babe, drop it.
-[Nora] I'm serious.
I want Tata Escobar's life too.
I'm covered in Yass and merguez.
I want jet skis,
someone to slide lobsters into my mouth,
roll in a bimmer like Grace Kelly.
Maybe then you can buy a flat iron.
[Greg chuckles]
And you can buy real smokes.
-Enough with the gypsy cigs.
-Hey, please.
They smoke just like the real ones.
Hey, Gambinos,
help me set the table. Let's go!
Hey, hold up.
Is that any way to treat a guest?
He's talking about robbing a bank,
and you can't manage a couple of forks?
-[Antoine] Burn!
-I can't wait till your woman pops.
[Antoine] I never said rob a bank.
-This all right?
-Yeah.
-[Nora] Perfect.
-Come on.
Is this your plate?
-[Nora] Here.
-[Yass] Some chicken, Antoine?
No, I'll take a merguez.
Wow, you really burned
these sausages, Yass.
-[chuckling]
-Oh!
-They're cooked, bro.
-They're not cooked, they're burned.
-Greg?
-No.
-For once.
-Straight protein.
-[Yass laughs]
-Just try it once, for me.
I don't wanna try your tomatoes.
-Yass, this is inedible.
-[Nora laughs]
-It's delicious.
-[Greg] Inedible.
It's delicious. You said
you wanted it crunchy, I made it crunchy.
It's not crunchy, it's overcooked.
-[Yass] But it's crunchy.
-[Antoine] They are tough.
-You wanted it crunchy, it's crunchy!
-Chill, my love.
-[Antoine] Did you make the tabbouleh?
-Yes.
Really good.
-Oh, you ass-kisser.
-Well, hey.
-For real?
-Try! Try this too.
-"Did you make the tabbouleh?"
-There's mint.
-"Oh, your tabbouleh's so good!"
-[Nora laughs]
-Seriously, it's so good.
-Who cooks for you?
Well, I cook for myself.
-All by yourself?
-Not like this.
Your neighbor still a pain in your ass?
No, he's calmed down.
-Yeah?
-Broke his nose.
-Are you kidding?
-No.
He's 60.
Well, if he showed some respect.
Yeah, but you gotta stop
beating everyone up.
What's going on with you?
-Hasn't given me a problem since.
-[laughs]
See?
-[gasps]
-[liquid sloshes]
-What's that?
-Yass, you seeing this?
-[gasps]
-Shit, this is so embarrassing.
-Hey, Daddy, wake up. Come on!
-[Nora] Grab something!
-[Antoine] They gotta go?
-What do I do?
-[Antoine] So, we're going?
-Um… Uh…
-Let's go.
-Shit!
-[Yass] You OK, babe?
-Yass, come on. Hurry.
-[Yass] Got it.
-[Greg] Hurry!
-Make sure you bring the hospital bag.
-[Yass] I got everything.
[siren wails]
["The World Is Going Up In Flames"
by Charles Bradley plays]
Again.
Hey. Hey!
My brother's a daddy!
More, Mando. Again, again!
Hey, on me. Drinks are on me!
[cheering]
[Greg laughs]
I'm fucking hammered!
♪ When you ♪
♪ Never felt the pain ♪
♪ Oh, oh… ♪
[thud]
[laughter]
-Call 911. Call 911!
-[Greg laughs]
♪ Ooh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ They don't hear me cry ♪
♪ Ooh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ For what I gonna do ♪
♪ Yeah, baby ♪
♪ Oh, I ♪
♪ I can't turn my head away ♪
[man] Move!
Quit crying, you little bitch!
[man 2 sobs]
I said stop crying!
Give me your fucking hand!
[man 3] Here, film him. Film him!
-[whimpers]
-[man 3] Shut the fuck up!
-I said stop crying! Shut the fuck up!
-You rob our customers, you little thief?
-[man 1 grunting]
-[man 2 yelping]
Hey, neighbors, listen up!
Here, you can buy with peace of mind.
Here, we're the police. Believe that!
-[groaning]
-[mouse clicking]
There. Went viral, huh?
Three million views.
Prefect must be thrilled.
Ah, you know it. He's delighted.
He wants our response to be, in his words,
front page news-worthy
all across the country.
Listen, we need to go all out.
Make a big splash.
-Know where this is?
-Yeah, the big complex near the water.
Yeah…
[Jérôme] What?
You've wanted
to take these drug networks down.
Here's your ticket.
You said we couldn't go
into ghettos anymore.
Well, things change. Now you have to go.
You're sucking up to the prefect?
Greg,
this case is yours.
Voila. You run the show.
You pick your team. Whatever you say goes.
-Ah, I dunno.
-[boy] En garde!
[Greg] Whoa! [laughs]
You think you can sneak up on me?
-Let's go!
-Don't back off.
Wanna see what happens when
you mess with the bull? You get owned!
This referee's the fucking worst.
He's all short,
blowing his whistle to make up for it.
So angry 'cause he's short and bald.
-[Greg chuckles]
-Yeah, go on. Take notes, take notes.
Seriously, that coach gets on my nerves!
Always taking notes. Nose in his notebook!
What's he writing down?
We haven't done anything in 20 minutes!
What are you writing down?
[soccer commentator plays on TV]
-[Greg] By the way…
-Hmm?
-What?
-You can count me in.
[alarm clock beeps]
[beeping]
[chiming]
Do you understand what I'm asking for?
I'm not asking you for a dealer here.
We wanna take down the whole network.
You need to give us some real intel.
A distribution center, you feel me?
You must have a death wish,
asking for that.
-Your cousin's from there.
-My cousin?
What do you think you'll get
from my cousin?
-Then from you.
-You want my cousin to dig my grave?
You haven't been to that neighborhood
in ages. Don't you get what a mess it is?
It's like Baghdad.
The bosses stay high
from morning till night.
They'll kill anyone to protect their turf.
They're the law now.
There are no more cops or politicians,
that's all that's left.
For Eid celebrations, they take
the kids out and give them money.
Other than that, they're heartless.
They even fight amongst themselves
to control the network.
As soon as a dealer keeps
a stick for himself, it rains bullets.
-There are no more rules. It's a jungle.
-[whimpering]
[Amel] I'm telling you,
the whole neighborhood's gone crazy.
Amel… two kilos is your cut of the haul.
I don't want two kilos from there.
What will I do with it?
-Why?
-You know why? Have you seen this?
Here, smell.
That smell,
they're the only ones who make it.
They're the only ones
who know what to put in it.
It's one-of-a-kind hash.
That's why
I can't take anything from there.
Five kilos.
Get me five kilos from somewhere else,
I'll get you what you need.
[Jérôme] Impossible.
No, it's… That's out of the question.
Really? Who gives a fuck?
Those drugs are gonna be destroyed anyway.
We don't take drugs off of the streets
to put them back there. How can you ask?
Oh, here we go.
Are you saying this is a moral issue?
Taking drugs from the evidence room
could cause other convictions
to get tossed. You know I can't.
-We can't give the informant the haul.
-[Jérôme] You have to.
Won't work.
Using their hash is a non-starter.
What do we do?
Just do it. Figure it out.
I don't want to know.
What does that mean?
It means that you find drugs
that aren't under seal or something.
So we take all the risks
and you hide behind your desk?
-Whoa!
-[Jérôme] Those are the prefect's orders.
They want a police response.
My job is to give them a police response.
-Does that work for you?
-Give us access to the drugs under seal.
Why should I risk my career
if we aren't given what we need?
Fuck this.
Nobody gives a shit about the ghettos.
The prefect just wants positive press
in the front page.
[Jérôme] That's not true. You're wrong.
So, then what's in it for us?
Raises.
-[Yass] How much?
-I don't know.
One, possibly two.
[chuckles] Are you serious?
We're gonna do this for 50,
100 euros tops per month?
-And we're risking the blame?
-[Jérôme] What blame?
Worried a sanction could keep you
from taking your officer exam?
-It looks bad.
-[Jérôme] So what?
You want to become an officer?
Do this operation.
[Greg] Yeah. OK, we got it.
Yeah.
So, figure it out?
That's right.
["Les Princes Des Villes"
by Michel Berger plays]
-[Greg] Good evening, police.
-[woman] Evening.
[Greg] Should we grab him?
-[Yass groans]
-[Greg] Come on.
Park over there, sir.
Evening, police. Can I ask you,
what you doing here?
-[man] I came to visit a friend.
-[Greg] All right. Let's keep this simple.
Either you give me the drugs you purchased
or I take you to the station.
OK. Come on, empty your pockets.
Here, come on. Show me what you got.
Well, your friend seems cool.
-Is that all?
-[man] It's all I have.
-[Greg] OK.
-All right, let's get outta here.
-[Antoine] He fucking shit himself.
-[chuckling] He fucking shit himself.
-Did you see that?
-Oh, I actually felt sorry for him.
[Greg and Antoine chuckle]
Hey, are you gonna sulk
like that all night?
No, it's fine.
I'll take the next one. All good?
-[Antoine laughs]
-OK?
[scale beeps]
-[Greg and Antoine] Ooh!
-[Yass] Come here!
[kid] Let me go. Let me go!
[Antoine] Caught in the act.
-Will you help him already?
-[Antoine] No way, he's on him.
[Greg] Oh fuck!
Little fucker's fired up today.
-[Antoine] Got him hog-tied.
-[Greg] Are you spanking him?
-[Antoine] Give him.
-[Yass] Take this piece of shit.
[kid] Fuck you and your whore mother!
Get off me, bitch!
Shut up with your man bun.
Fucking barista bitch.
-Take it easy.
-I'll fuck your mother in the face!
Don't touch me! Fuck the BAC!
I'll fuck you up the ass.
-Shut your trap!
-Fuck all you all. You ain't shit!
-Fucking bunch of pigs. Shut up, I said.
-Shut up.
Come on, you, with your old ass in front.
-Whoa!
-Stupid-ass bitch!
-I'll fuck you up. What you gonna do?
-Watch your mouth, you!
Fucking dinosaur-looking bitch.
Throw me out, I don't give a shit.
-Don't fucking touch me, I'm a minor.
-Shut your mouth.
Let me outta here. I'm supposed to be
fucking your mom, fucking whore.
I'll fuck your sister in the shower--
-You got little dick syndrome in the back?
-Speed up, you pussy!
Yass, put some music on.
I can't deal with this.
-[kid] You're a bitch!
-[Antoine] Hurry up.
[Antoine and boy shout over each other]
-[Greg] Shut up!
-Perfect. All right.
-["La Bandite" by Jul plays]
-Hey, turn it up. Turn it up!
♪ Break yo neck… ♪
Yeah!
[kid raps odd word along with music]
Listen to this guy in the back, huh?
[kid continues rapping to music]
Watch you looking at.
Get you some, nephew.
[siren wails]
-[kid] Hurry up, driver. Go on, speed up.
-You're driving like an old man.
-[horns honking]
-[kid laughs]
-What? What?
-[Yass] Let's go!
[Greg laughs] Come on!
Can you pick a lane already?
Maybe you need to get your eyes checked.
[kid yells]
Oh, smile. You love me!
You know you love me!
[rap music continues playing]
[Yass] Get on it!
[kid] Yeah!
[all rap along with music]
-[Yass] Whoa!
-[tires screech]
[Greg laughs]
[kid] Oh yeah!
[kid yells indistinctly]
[tires screech]
Whoop, whoop,
that's the sound of the police!
Motherfucker.
-Good evening. Police.
-[man] Yeah?
What you bought back there,
give it here, please.
Uh, it's just my personal stash.
Oh, my friend. Don't start stuttering.
We saw you. Give it here.
-It's all I have.
-That's all there is?
It's all I have.
-I swear.
-OK, I'll let you off this time. Go.
[Greg] Shit, I'd really love to go there.
-Where?
-Outer space.
-You wanna go to outer space?
-Well, yeah.
Lifelong dream.
People are starting to go there.
Tourists and everything.
-Yeah, rich people.
-Oh, for sure.
Still, just imagine seeing it.
Our planet all small in the distance.
You feel me?
-Crazy, no?
-Insane.
You can see it all round.
-What's your point?
-Normally, it's flat, not round.
[snickering]
-Got ourselves a real astronomer.
-He's so stupid!
Honestly, I wish I could go to outer space
so I wouldn't have to see your faces.
Dumbass! [snickers]
[Greg] Whoa, whoa, what's he doing?
Fucking hell.
[man] What are you guys doing?
Hey, what are you doing?
-What are you talking about?
-What do you mean?
Fuck, you've been robbing my customers
for the last hour!
-We're not doing anything.
-What do you mean?
Been watching you.
Why you robbing my customers?
What's going on? Where'd you come from?
What gives you the right to come
to my place and fuck all my customers?
-We didn't know this was your place.
-You didn't know?
This is somebody's place, isn't it?
Don't talk like that.
-Yeah?
-So, you're here to screw people over?
-[Greg] No.
-You son of a bitch!
-Hey, don't talk like that.
-[man] Fucking shit, huh?
-"Don't talk like that."
-Don't get worked up.
You come here, fuck me up the ass,
and I shouldn't get worked up?
-[Greg shushes]
-Don't shush me!
-[man 2] You're a bunch of thieves.
-Shut the fuck up!
-Calm down, OK?
-You can't tell me what to do!
-Whoa. Hey.
-What are you doing, huh?
-[Greg] Whoa!
-Don't tell me to get in the car!
Put that thing away!
-You think I'm scared of you?
-Back up. Lower your weapon.
-Put it away. Lower your weapon.
-I'm not lowering my weapon. Fuck you!
-Lower your weapon.
-You're fucking dead.
-I said put that away!
-Get back in your car.
You're on my turf!
You go home, you punk bitch!
Go on. Lower your weapon.
-You think you're bad, huh?
-[Antoine] I'll fuck you up!
Your face looks familiar,
you son of a bitch.
-You and I know each other, right?
-No.
We don't? Go back to the police station,
fuck your mother, son of a bitch.
They're pigs. Come on, let's bounce.
-Crooked ass.
-Pigs.
[man 1] You're a bunch
of dirty motherfuckers!
Earn your thousand euros a week, assholes!
Slaves!
-Go on, get in your Cayenne, motherfucker.
-[man 1] I recognize you! See you soon!
Are you crazy? You piece of shit!
-What are you doing?
-What happens if they shoot?
-What happens?
-Whoa!
-What then?
-Calm down!
-Huh? What happens?
-What the fuck is wrong with you?
-Calm down from what? Fuck!
-Calm down!
-It didn't go to shit.
-Your shitty plan!
-Calm down.
-Fuck you, calm down!
Hey, I have a family.
You're acting like thugs!
-And you with your shitty plans!
-Get in the car.
[Yass] Yeah, now we're thinking straight.
-[Greg sighs]
-[car door slams]
-[Antoine] Good thing I--
-Shut your mouth!
Get in the car. We're leaving.
Get in the car.
Get in the fucking car, Antoine!
[Antoine] You get in the car!
I'm the only one with any balls here.
Bunch of clowns.
[cell phone vibrating]
-Hello?
-[Amel] You gotta get over here now.
-What the fuck are you doing?
-Hang on, calm down. What?
Yeah, I'm serious.
You gotta get the fuck over here.
-I'm freaking the fuck out.
-OK. Where are you?
I'm at the spot.
-What's the matter?
-[Amel] Are you stupid or something?
What did you do at Square des Oliviers?
You're robbing people now?
-Who told you that?
-Don't ask who told me.
-Seriously. Did you or did you not?
-That's enough. Answer me.
-Where'd you hear that?
-In my neighborhood.
People talk. Are you mental? They talk.
Are you guys crazy or something?
-I don't want to die.
-That's not your problem.
-Stop saying it's not my problem.
-It's not your problem!
-Did you see anything? No.
-What, are you psychic?
-Are we being followed?
-Yes.
I leave my place, I don't feel right.
It's fucked up.
Everywhere people look at me,
I feel like they know me.
People see us. People know us.
-What do you mean following us?
-I feel like I'm being followed.
There, Mr. Antoine, I feel like
I'm being followed when I leave my home.
-By who? Where?
-Someone from the quarter.
-Think they know about us?
-Of course.
-People in your hood don't know me.
-Stop saying that.
Are you part of the BAC, yes or no?
-Are you part of the BAC?
-Yes.
BAC south or BAC north?
-BAC north?
-Yeah.
-All right.
-So what?
And where are we now? North quarter?
People in my precinct know me,
no one in yours.
-They're only two minutes apart, right?
-[sighs]
Answer me!
You've been in my neighborhood before,
right? People know you.
Got any weed on you?
[Antoine] I'm telling you,
you're spiraling out.
-[Amel] What the fuck are you doing?
-Hey!
-Please, give it back. I'm not playing.
-Look at this.
-Give it.
-This is all you need.
-Here. You keep this.
-Oh, but you--
Ease up on the weed. You're spiraling out.
-Think I'm making it up?
-You're getting paranoid.
-Yeah. Did you smoke before coming here?
-No, I didn't smoke.
-Did you smoke before coming?
-No.
Look at me. You're high.
You're just fucking with me here.
I see you.
Hey.
What happened at the Oliviers,
it's nothing.
Nobody cares. Changes nothing.
Amel, go back home.
Lay low. Let me handle the rest.
-But…
-You got me or not?
You're not in danger.
You have my word.
Why you touching my shoulder
like that, player?
-Is this better?
-You're a flirt.
-Oh yeah?
-Mm-hmm.
[Greg] Gonna be mad at each other
like this for much longer?
Enough already. Get over it.
I dunno what you have to do to make peace.
-I'm tired of this shit.
-[Yass coughs]
Did you seriously say, "Make peace"?
What kind of stupid expression is that?
"Let's make peace,"
says the BAC philosopher
-What's so funny?
-You're the BAC philosopher now.
-Peace it is, Mahatma fucking Ghandi.
-That's funny to you too?
[Antoine and Yass laugh]
Your face makes me laugh.
[radio] Calling all available cars,
requesting immediate backup.
Priority. We're surrounded. Need backup.
[TN13] BAC17, this is TN13.
Confirm your location.
[BAC17] Square des Oliviers!
I repeat, Square des Oliviers.
Send people, shit! Hurry.
[TN13] TN13 to all available units
in the north sector.
Officers in trouble
in the Square des Oliviers area.
Respond to TN13 ASAP.
Turn off the radio.
-[Antoine] No!
-Turn it off!
[groans] No way!
-[cop] Fucking hell, where were you?
-We couldn't come.
Sorry, you had something better to do?
Shit! What kind of cop have you become?
Leaving us to take a beating
without lifting a finger.
-Don't lecture me.
-Got something you want to say to me?
Pfft. Whatever.
[Greg] Jacques…
Listen, I'm sorry. OK?
I don't give a shit if you're sorry
or about your apology.
-We almost got killed!
-Calm down.
-Hey, I apologize.
-Fuck you, you son of a bitch!
-[grunting]
-[heavy breathing]
What? What
I can explain, all right?
We've been working nights for three weeks.
We've gathered about two kilos.
[Jérôme] But, Greg, you've been outed
in the northern neighborhoods.
So you're gonna need to go downtown
together to collect the rest.
And no more trouble. I'm serious.
[Greg] OK.
["Down Man" by Brainbox plays]
[tires screech]
[grunting]
♪ A man… ♪
-Go on!
-♪ A room ♪
♪ A man alone in a room ♪
♪ Tears ♪
♪ His eyes are losing tears ♪
♪ A man who's down and out ♪
♪ He's got nothing to live for ♪
♪ He knows ♪
♪ There's no doubt ♪
♪ Emptiness… ♪
[indistinct yelling]
♪ A man who's down and out… ♪
Say you stole the bag!
♪ He's got nothing to live for ♪
♪ He knows ♪
♪ There's no doubt ♪
♪ Yeah… ♪
[yelling on screen]
-Hey! Hey, whoa!
-Whoa!
What is this shit?
-Tunisian designer.
-[laughs]
Couscous Chanel!
-["Down Man" by Brainbox plays]
-[indistinct yelling, grunting]
[Antoine] Empty your pockets!
♪ A man ♪
♪ A man alone in a room
He's down and out ♪
♪ Down and out ♪
♪ Down ♪
♪ He knows there's no doubt ♪
♪ No doubt ♪
♪ Oh, down and out ♪
♪ Whoa, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Down and out ♪
♪ A man alone ♪
[Greg] You change diapers and everything?
I looked it up online.
I couldn't figure it out in the beginning.
What do you mean you looked it up?
How to put on a diaper, man.
It's not that easy.
-What, there are tutorials?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
And you like it?
No, it smells like shit.
[chuckling]
It literally smells like shit. No lie.
-Oh yeah?
-Yeah.
It's not all diapers.
I like the rest of it.
Best part of my day.
-In any case, you make a good uncle.
-[chuckles]
He's beautiful.
He gets it all from his mother.
Thank God he looks like his mother.
In three days, there's gonna be
a big shipment coming to the ghetto.
In the apartment towers.
All the bosses will be there.
But just for one day. And then… [scoffs]
-Three days?
-Yeah.
-Which apartment tower?
-I don't know.
Which block?
What do you mean you don't know?
The only thing I can guarantee you
is that they're so paranoid
about their dope,
they're never gonna let a dealer
get caught with a full bag.
Any sign of trouble, there's a guy nearby
whose job it is to pick up the bag,
bring it to the safe house.
Normally, if you follow the sack,
it'll take you
to the apartment you're looking for.
[dog whimpers, pants]
Did you hear me?
Yeah, I heard you.
[pensive acoustic guitar music playing]
There's a yellow vehicle approaching.
A yellow vehicle is headed
toward the towers.
I repeat, yellow vehicle
headed toward the towers.
-[radio buzzes]
-Yeah, I got eyes on it.
[distant yelling]
There are two men with masks
searching the car.
[whistling, indistinct yelling]
The car is headed for block M.
I got eyes on the dealer.
Bandana covering his face, black cap.
[Yass] Some kind of drawing on his bag.
I got eyes on the dealer, M block.
I repeat, eyes on the dealer.
[indistinct chattering]
Transaction is complete.
The dealer is posted up
in front of block M.
I repeat, the dealer is posted up
All teams, standby for the ready.
A reminder, do not apprehend.
Just tail them.
We follow the bag
so we can find their stash.
We locate the stash no matter what.
OK. Roger that.
[cell phone vibrates]
-[Greg] Antoine, do you read me?
-Yeah.
OK, you're up, buddy.
-The dealer is in front of block M.
-[Antoine] OK.
[moped engine approaching]
[rap music playing]
[Antoine] You got that fire?
Go to block C over there,
in front of the dumpsters.
[man whistles]
All teams, he's en route.
Mount up.
[engine starts]
[cop] Our team has eyes on Antoine.
He's walking down the alley.
He should come into your view
any moment now.
Popo!
[spotters yell] Popo! Popo!
-[whistle blows]
-[motorcycle engine revs]
-[spotter] Popo!
-[Antoine breathes heavily]
Go, go, go, go, go. Let's go! Go!
[tires screech]
[yelling in distance]
[cop] Come on.
Go, go, go, go! Let's go! Let's go!
[spotters yell in distance]
[breathing heavily]
[moped engine approaches]
Whoa!
-[jeering]
-Whoa! Hey, what's the matter?
-Get back! I said get back!
-Hey, man.
-I said get back!
-[gang members jeer]
[man 1] Come on, man.
-Calm down! I said get back!
-[tires screech]
-[Antoine] Get back!
-[man 2] Those fuckers!
[Jacques] Get back. Get back!
[gang members jeering]
Hey, Jacques. Blue T-shirt, black mask!
Blue T-shirt, black mask.
[Jacques] Blue T-shirt, black mask.
Blue T-shirt, black mask. Get back!
[Yass] Got it. I see him!
I got eyes. I got eyes!
I'm following the bag!
Block K16! Block K16!
[Yass] I'm going in. I'm going in!
-[gang members jeering]
-Get back!
[indistinct yelling]
Stash house located. Fifth floor.
[tires screech]
[distant yelling, jeering]
Open up, you son of a bitch! Open up!
[distant yelling]
Open up!
[gang members yell indistinctly]
[man 1] Kill all these pigs!
Open the door!
[indistinct yelling]
Requesting immediate backup!
I repeat, requesting immediate backup!
We have an officer trapped in block K16!
Open the door. Open your door!
-Hey, what are you doing? Get outta here!
-Sir! Sir!
-What are you doing?
-Are you crazy or something?
-Get out!
-OK! [shushes]
-[woman] Stop!
-[shushes]
-Stay there.
-Sir!
-He's in here!
-Shut your mouth!
[kid screams] What'd we do?
Move! Sit down. Quiet!
Blocks 15 and 16 should connect
through the roofs. Let's go. Let's go!
-Come on! Yeah!
-Both of us?
Oh!
Yass! Yass! Greg, Antoine are
on their way. Stay where you are!
I'm on the sixth floor. Apartment 630.
[woman] Please, sir.
We didn't do anything.
[ominous music plays]
[distant knocking on door]
[distant yelling]
Yass, we're coming.
Apartment 630, sixth floor.
I repeat, apartment 630--
[pained yelling] Fuck!
-[Yass grunts]
-[woman screams]
[woman screams]
[distant woman screaming]
-You OK, bro?
-I'm OK.
-Hey!
[woman sobs]
Come on, let's go. Come on.
-[gang members jeer]
-God help us.
What are you doing?
Get the fuck outta here!
-Get back!
-Go ahead. Go on, shoot!
-Go on, shoot! Go on, shoot. Come on!
-[cop] Get back!
[man] Shoot!
[man laughs]
Come on!
[jeering continues]
On the right.
Is that the door, Yass?
[tense music plays]
[grunting]
Yass, cover me.
-You OK?
-Yeah.
[breathing heavily] Jacques…
We're in another apartment,
still moving on the fifth floor.
Hurry the fuck up. Hurry up!
[indistinct jeering]
[man] Get the fuck outta my neighborhood!
[Jérôme] Come on, guys. Go, go, go!
[indistinct chattering in distance]
["Jalousie" by Alonzo plays in background]
[indistinct yelling in distance]
[man 1] Get the fuck outta here. Go!
[man 1] Go! Go!
[man 2] Hey, you!
Put that down over there.
Get on it!
-[man 1] Move it. Move it!
-[man 2] Put it in the bag. Let's go!
-Move!
-[man 1] OK!
-Get the bag.
-[man 2] Let's go, let's go!
[man 1] Toss me that. Move! Move!
-[man 2] Go out there.
-[man 1] Go, go!
-[man 1] We got you.
-[man 2] Go, go!
-[man 1] Hurry up. Come on! Let's go.
-[man 2] Go!
-[man 1] Toss it.
-[man 2] Don't forget to flush!
-Right there!
-[man 1] Come on. Let's go!
We gotta get outta here.
[tense music plays]
[Yass groans]
[clears throat]
-[man 2] Move it! Move, let's go!
-The drugs are in the communal trash room.
-[man 2] Yeah. What the fuck was that?
-[smoke hisses]
-[man 2] Shit! What the fuck?
-[man 1] They're gassing us!
-[man 2] Get the fuck outta here!
-[man 1] Move!
-Come on, let's get the fuck outta here!
-[indistinct yelling, coughing]
[coughing]
[man 2] Get the fuck out!
[jeering]
[glass shattering]
[indistinct yelling]
-Let's get outta here.
-Come on, run faster!
-Get against the wall!
-[man grunts]
[indistinct yelling]
[man yells]
[man] Get back! Get back!
[gunfire]
[man groans]
[rapid gunfire]
He's out! He's out! He's out!
Don't move! Don't move!
[indistinct yelling]
Don't move!
[dealer] They're here!
-What we got here? Help me.
-[Jérôme] You're under arrest!
[cop] Don't move! Party's over, bro.
[indistinct jeering]
Get the fuck outta here!
Shoot! Shoot him!
Hey, get outta here now!
Get outta here! You, beat it!
-Get the fuck outta here!
-Beat it!
-Back up! Move it! Back the fuck up!
-Move! Move!
-[Greg] Move!
-Get back! Get back!
Beat it! You, beat it!
Back up! Back up!
[indistinct yelling, jeering continues]
[engine starts]
Go! Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
[tires screech]
-[gang member] I'm gonna kill you, Pig!
-[Antoine] Drive, drive!
Go! Oh shit! Move! Move!
[indistinct yelling]
-[Antoine] What the fuck?
-[Yass] Go! Go!
[Antoine] This is fucking crazy!
[indistinct yelling, jeering]
[Antoine] Drive, drive!
-Fuck it, just drive!
-[Yass] Go, go, go!
[Antoine] Go, go, go!
-[Yass] Oh shit!
-[Antoine] Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Yass, you OK? You OK?
-Are you OK?
-[Yass] Yeah.
Don't stop, don't stop!
Go, go, go. Don't stop!
[Yass] Holy shit!
[ethereal music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[inaudible]
[indistinct yelling]
[cheering]
[Jérôme] North BAC gets it done,
that's why!
It's because of you that
we're the best gang task force in France!
Yeah!
You're all heroes, of course,
and in your own way,
but this fucking guy went in there
with balls this big!
Yass, don't ever do that again,
you fearless bastard!
[cheering]
[whistling]
Eat, drink,
but go easy on the drugs tonight, OK?
[cheering]
Yeah. Yeah!
Thank you, Greg.
Thank you.
We couldn't have done this without you.
Come on, let's have some fun. Yes!
[Jérôme laughs]
[officers chant] North BAC! North BAC!
We're here because of you, brother.
[Yass] All you, brother.
Nobody stabbed me in the back to get here.
[kisses]
[Yass] Yeah.
Come on!
I'm tired.
But I'm happy!
[exhales sharply]
'Sup?
Let's see…
Boom!
[chuckles]
[Antoine] All good?
Put it in your trunk?
[Antoine sighs]
So it is.
What are you gonna do?
-I'll probably smoke it all myself.
-[both laugh]
Another life, I'd join you.
So this is the end of the road.
This is it, yeah.
-So you're finally getting rid of me.
-[both chuckle]
All right. [slaps Amel's hand]
Take care of yourself.
Hey…
See you around, Amel.
[sighs]
Hey, Antoine…
What?
-Never mind, it's fine.
-What?
Nothing, it's fine. Get outta here.
[both chuckle]
Don't get fresh
or you'll end up in the water!
-[Amel chuckles]
-[engine starts]
-Go on. Get out of here.
[sighs, chuckles]
TWO MONTHS LATER
[baby gurgles, babbles]
[baby laughs]
Hey, bubba. [chuckles]
Who's my little buddy? You my buddy?
We're buddies, right?
-[man] Sergeant Cerva?
-Yes.
[man] Lieutenant Vidal.
-[dog barking]
-[clattering in background]
[police dog barks]
[Nora] What's going on?
Yass?
-Where's the baby?
-Inside.
I'll call you when I'm done.
What the hell is this mess?
Are you kidding?
-You don't have to do this! Why?
-Hey, calm down.
-Where's my son?
-[officer] Take it down a notch.
Everything's fine. He's in the bedroom.
We need to check the cupboards.
Emilien, check under the TV.
Shit!
Come, my love. Huh?
-He's fine.
-Are you OK?
Please leave.
Are you OK, my love? Huh?
-[officer] Go along the closets.
-Sweetie.
-[baby gurgles]
-Hey.
Mommy's here now.
[car engine starts]
-[car tires crunch gravel]
-[siren wails]
[man] I have to inform you
that this interview
will be recorded on video
for further use in the investigation.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Lieutenant Yvon. IGPN.
Great. What the hell am I doing here?
I'd like to know.
Well, the charges are…
…racketeering…
…and organized drug trafficking.
[scoffs]
[sighs]
-Are you kidding? Is this a joke?
-[Yvon] No, I don't think it's a joke.
Well? The cannabis,
who did you steal it from?
We didn't steal it.
-[Yvon] You didn't steal it?
-No.
-We collected it.
-"Collected"?
That's a nice way of putting it.
I like it. "Collected."
Police exhibit number four.
Kept a few sticks of cannabis
for yourself,
which we found in your home, to get high?
[Antoine snickers]
I smoke cannabis, yes.
So, this is for your personal consumption?
I just said so.
Didn't you hear me?
And, uh, how do you explain the presence
of this scale?
Do you know a lot of potheads
who weigh their dope? I don't know any.
Only dealers do that.
We never sold any drugs.
-Never.
-[Yvon] You didn't sell any drugs.
No. Drugs were our bargaining chip.
Drugs in exchange for information.
-That's not what people are saying.
-Oh?
Please tell me what people are saying.
They say you confiscate drugs
then turn around and sell them.
The drugs were used
to pay the informant who told us
about the distributing apartment.
An informant whose identity
is completely unknown to you.
Only Antoine knows.
The informant wanted to remain anonymous.
It's what they do. But you know that.
[Yvon] Of course.
I'm not telling you shit.
-Zero.
-And for what reason are you refusing?
You can't be serious?
If I give you my informant,
that puts them at risk.
-I promised to keep them anonymous.
-[Yvon] Yes, of course.
You gave your word so you're keeping it.
You're not a snitch.
-Is that it?
-Exactly, that's it.
That's how thugs operate.
Go fuck yourself.
I didn't catch the informant's name.
I'm not telling you anything.
There are ethics to being a cop.
-[Yvon] Oh.
-You don't look like you have any. Huh?
Trying to take down your colleagues.
You have a child?
-Yeah.
-[Yvon] Some things are understandable.
When you have a kid, 1,800 euros a month…
-Risking your life every day.
-What are you trying to say?
I think that the drugs,
you sold them because you need help
making ends meet.
Quit talking out of your ass
with your bullshit!
Why are you bringing my son into this
with that shitty condescending tone?
-You need help making ends meet--
-Think you're better than me?
-Anyone could understand.
-You think you're better?
-You think I'm dirty, don't you?
-[Yvon] No.
If you want me not to think that,
you have to give me something.
Quit looking at me like that. OK?
You quit looking at me like that.
-I've been doing this job 20 years.
-Yeah?
OK? Think you're
on the right side of the desk?
You think you know everything,
but you don't!
-I'm doing my job.
-You don't know anything!
You don't know what we went through,
don't know the northern sector!
You've never set foot there!
You're just a fucking bureaucrat!
-You should--
-We almost died out there!
-You should calm down.
-Seen the poverty out there?
You ain't seen nothing!
Get down from that high horse.
-I'm giving you a piece of advice.
-Don't take that tone. Fuck.
-I'm giving you… Calm down!
-Shut up!
-Shut your mouth!
-Calm down.
-I ask the questions, you answer them!
-I'm done talking to you! I'm done!
-Then who will you talk to?
-You want to lock me up, huh?
That way you can meet your quota,
you puny little man!
I know this story by heart. I know it by
heart! You wanna meet your quota!
-There! I'm done talking to you.
-Calm down! Calm down.
-It's pointless. You're just an asshole!
-It's in your best interest.
Go fuck yourself!
Now I wanna talk to my superior.
I wanna talk to Jérôme!
I'm not saying another word!
You're not talking to anyone!
We already talked to your superior.
Know what? Jérôme doesn't know
anything about your informant!
-You made it up!
-Oh, he doesn't?
Hey, moron. You imbecile!
My superior is my friend!
We did this mission together!
He gave the order!
-Oh, right!
-You're fucked!
You are fucked!
-You should be careful with your friends.
-I'm done talking!
I want an audience
with the prosecutor's office, and Jérôme!
Keep going.
I'm done talking to you!
I'm done talking! Go fuck yourself!
-You better control yourself!
-Hey!
-[Yvon] Take care of him.
-You should be ashamed!
-[officer] Cuff him.
-You don't know? You know what we did?
[Yvon] You're nothing now! Nothing!
[somber music plays]
[woman] Please have a seat.
[Greg] Hello, Your Honor.
[judge] So…
We're here at the request of the accused,
Grégory Cerva.
He asked to be heard in your presence,
Mr. Jérôme Bodin,
head of the anti-criminal brigade
of the northern sector.
Mr. Bodin, while exercising
your duties as an officer,
were you aware of an operation
being carried out at night by this team,
in order to collect
various amounts of cannabis hash?
No, I was not aware.
I'll remind you that you are under oath.
-Do you confirm?
-I confirm.
-Jérôme, what are you doing?
-No, Mr. Cerva.
-What are you doing?
-[judge] Mr. Cerva! Mr. Cerva!
You'll be able
to have your say in due time.
I'll remind you that you are under oath.
-Do you confirm?
-I confirm.
[judge] You never heard
about this collecting of drugs?
Never.
[judge] Is it possible
that without your knowledge,
this collecting was used
to pay an informant for information
used in the operation
that led to the dismantling
of the drug trafficking network
in question?
It's… It's possible.
But I was not aware of it.
[judge] Mr. Cerva,
you claim that your chain of command
was aware of your actions?
Absolutely. [sniffs]
[judge] You claim that your superior,
present here, had approved your actions?
Yes.
[judge] Careful now,
is this a direct accusation?
Yes.
[judge] Do you have
any evidence to present to me?
No.
[sniffles]
[Greg taps feet]
[judge] Thank you, gentlemen.
Mr. Bodin, you may leave.
Thank you.
[door opens]
[keys jangle]
[guard] You'll be in solitary confinement
during your provisional detention.
-Until the investigation's over.
-[gate locks]
[guard] You can call your family
in one month. Not before.
No contact with other inmates.
It's for your own safety.
You don't have a lot of friends in here.
[inmates yelling indistinctly in distance]
Turn to the left.
[inmate 1] Fuck your mother!
Dirty fucking cop!
[inmate 2] Come over here,
son of a bitch! Bitch!
[inmate 3] We're gonna get you!
We're gonna get your ass!
-[inmate 4] You're dirty!
-[guard] Stop here.
[inmate 5] We're gonna get you.
We'll get you, scumbag!
[inmate 6] Fucking crook!
The only person
you'll communicate with is the guard.
The only way to call him is this.
[inmate 7] We're gonna come for you!
[inmates continue jeering]
[inmates yelling in distance]
[Greg mutters indistinctly]
[intercom buzzes]
Hello. Yes. It's just that…
-[guard] What do you want?
-It's just that I need to see you now.
[guard] Not now.
We'll deal with it tomorrow.
No, it's just
that I need to talk to my captain.
[groans]
[indistinct announcement over PA]
[man 1 on TV] It's as simple as cutting
out the backbone and roasting it flat.
[man 2 on TV] Don't bother talking to me.
You hear? That's--
[TV news jingle plays]
Good evening. In tonight's headlines,
a scandal with the Marseille police.
Three BAC employees are suspected
of corruption and extortion.
They allegedly sold drugs
that had been recovered from thugs
in exchange for services.
For several months now,
investigators had installed microphones
in their vehicles.
The recorded conversations
don't leave much room for doubt,
according to the prosecutor.
[prosecutor] This is the unit in charge
of recovering drugs from dealers
and counterfeit cigarettes
from street vendors.
I will be, as I have had the opportunity
to be in other situations,
extremely strict regarding these men.
There is no room
for those who defile the police
and the Republic.
Everyone must know
that we will take the strictest…
Guard!
…possible measures.
[reporter] Every time the north BAC
is involved in a procedure, in a case,
there will be an underlying doubt,
according to many lawyers
of the Marseille bar.
And these lawyers are not excluding
requesting release for clients
who had been brought in
by these north BAC policemen at the time,
and who are currently incarcerated.
[reporter 2] Today,
I sense great distress
amongst the population.
Minister, do you have a plan
for placing this type of unit
under stricter
and more efficient surveillance?
Having to directly fight thugs
requires that much more restraint
and a sense of republican values.
And a police officer
who doesn't respect the law
and the code of ethics of the police
defiles the uniform and has no place
in Marseille's police…
Answer me!
Hey! Answer me!
Dammit, answer me!
-Hey! Hey! [grunts]
-[man on TV] Thank you.
-That's a form of corruption.
-Hey! Answer me!
Most concerning is civil servants seem
to have lost their moral standards.
[sobs]
[reporter 3] The justice department
speaks of a broad criminal investigation
that's only just getting started.
If the facts are confirmed,
the police officers could be sentenced
to up to 20 years in prison.
-[man] You all right?
-[Antoine] Yeah.
Your family gives you money
for the commissary?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
-OK.
Listen, I know I'm your lawyer,
but I'm not a miracle worker.
So far, our defense is frail.
We don't have much.
Your problem is that everyone's
gotten involved with this business.
The prefect, the mayor,
the reporters and the minister too.
You hear the minister the other day?
If there's to be a chance
of getting you outta here,
I need the name of that informant.
No, I can't do that.
Think about it.
I can't do that.
[Greg sighs]
[cell door unlocks]
What do you want?
Ah, my hand really hurts.
I can't even move it.
-I want to go back to the infirmary.
-Not now. You were there this morning.
[sighs]
OK. Um, do you know
if my lawyer spoke with my superior?
-They were meant to meet this morning.
-You're not the only one here.
You know I got no business being in here.
-Your colleagues must've explained?
-Stop. I don't need…
-Know what I need?
-Quit talking to me.
-I need you to call my superior.
-Get some rest. Sleep.
-Call him, please.
-I said get some rest!
-I don't have time to chat.
-I know, but it's for…
Cerva, stop it!
Stop it!
[guard groans]
-[guard] No, no!
-You asshole. Get it now?
-[guard] Ow!
-Get it?
I want to see my superior, asshole!
I want to see my superior!
I want to see my superior! [grunts]
I want to talk to my superior!
I need to talk! I need to talk!
-[Greg] I need to talk!
-Hey! What are you doing? Hey, guard!
[Greg] I need to talk! I need to talk!
[Greg grunts]
I need to fucking talk!
[Greg yells]
[Greg] I need to talk!
I need to fucking talk!
I need to talk! I need to talk!
[outgoing call tone sounds]
[Nora] Hi, you've reached Yass and Nora.
We're not home. Leave us a message.
Yeah, honey, it's me.
Uh, hope that…
that you're OK.
I wanted to call you, so I…
Uh…
And Malik, uh…
[Jacques] Here.
We pitched in what we could.
I'm touched, but I don't want it.
I want help.
[Jacques] Yeah, of course. Tell us.
You guys collected drugs too.
You need to say something,
tell Internal Affairs.
It can change this.
It'll give some weight to their version.
It won't, Nora. It's just gonna put
the three of us in the slammer with them.
What do you expect from us here?
They didn't rat you out. They took it all.
They said nothing. Even Greg.
They'll jump all over us, Nora,
put us in prison.
You know that if you tell Internal Affairs
that you were there, that Jérôme knew,
if you tell them what happened
those nights--
Jérôme did his job. He saved the brigade.
The ministry's gonna save its own ass
and the police's reputation.
Greg, Antoine, and Yass
don't mean anything to them.
Same goes for us if we speak out.
Know what we're dealing with?
I'm talking five to ten years.
The lawyer told me, Jacques. He told me.
I'm begging you.
What do I tell him? What do I tell Malik?
I swear, if I could've done something,
I would've done it.
I have a daughter too.
Your son could just as well be mine.
You can't ask me to do this.
[cop] I'm sorry, Nora.
[indistinct chattering]
How are you feeling?
I'm OK.
It's kinda annoying. The Jacuzzi
broke down. Apart from that, I'm good.
It's hard in here.
You're alone with yourself.
How's my little man doing?
Good. Good. He laughs all the time.
I talk to him. They say that's important.
-I tell him stories.
-What do you say to him?
-That you're coming home.
-Of course I'm coming home.
Did you talk to the others?
Kevin, Jacques… did you talk to them?
Tell me.
[Nora sighs]
They won't speak out.
[inhales shakily] No.
-Oh.
-I'm sorry.
No, it's nothing.
It happens to me too. [chuckles]
Malik and I are here.
Even if we have to wait 112 winters,
we're here.
-I'm here too.
-[both chuckle]
I'm not going anywhere.
-I'm afraid I don't have a choice.
-[both laugh]
I fucking love you.
-[Nora] Go on.
-You're my life.
-[Nora] You too.
-Come on. We gotta go.
-Yeah, I got it, chief.
-[door closes]
-[laughs]
[Nora chuckles]
[breathes shakily]
[knocks on door]
[somber music plays]
I'M NOT DEAD
[door unlocking]
I'd like a tablet.
We've been giving you tons of tablets.
It's ridiculous.
Come on.
Come on. Try to get up.
Come on. Come on.
Hey, bro!
Hey!
-Hey!
-[guard] This way, come on. Let's go.
Greg!
Your cell! Shut up!
Now you're pissing me off!
-Come on!
-Hey!
-What the fuck? It's me!
-Move it!
-Hey, what did you do to him?
-[guard grunts]
-OK.
OK, stop.
[door unlocking]
I need to get my hair cut.
Only inmates can cut other inmates' hair.
It's the law.
I know.
[guard] I can't leave you in the hands
of just any inmate.
Yeah, I know.
-You don't think I see you coming?
-I just wanna get my hair cut.
You can't refuse me that. It's my right.
[door unlocking]
[guard] I don't wanna hear
a word out of you.
Got it, chief.
[clippers buzz]
Chief?
If you had a friend
who was losing his mind…
you'd save him, right?
I said "not one word."
I'm talking to you, not him.
-So, what would you do?
-[guard] Shut up.
-But what would you do?
You'd save him, right?
Would you save him,
or would you let him die like a dog?
Hey, I saw Greg and he's not there. Fuck!
Wake up! Wake up now!
-Do what you have to do.
-[guard] Shut up!
[Yass] Do what you have to do! Fuck!
He's dying in here!
-[guard] Careful!
-[Yass] Wake up! Wake up!
[guard] Shut up!
[clattering]
[somber suspenseful music plays]
[siren wails]
[Yvon] Is that her?
Yeah, it's her.
I didn't have a choice.
[sobs]
I'm so sorry.
[judge] After confirming
the existence of this informant,
the prosecutor has decided to drop
the charges of organized drug trafficking.
Therefore, I am going
to end your provisional detention.
You'll be getting out.
There are still charges against you.
Namely, violating the civil code
and taking illegal actions
in the performance of your duties.
You will have to submit to certain
release conditions before your trial.
Is that clear?
Where's my dog?
["The House of the Rising Sun"
by The Animals plays]
♪ There is a house ♪
♪ In New Orleans ♪
♪ They call the Rising Sun ♪
♪ And it's been the ruin ♪
♪ Of many a poor boy ♪
♪ And God, I know I'm one ♪
♪ My mother was a tailor ♪
♪ She sewed my new blue jeans ♪
♪ My father was a gambling man ♪
♪ Down in New Orleans ♪
♪ Well, I got one foot on the platform ♪
♪ The other foot on the train… ♪
YASS IS NOW WITH THE POLICE UNION.
HE DEFENDS HIS COLLEAGUES
AGAINST MANAGEMENT.
♪ To wear that ball and chain… ♪
ANTOINE TURNED HIS BADGE IN.
HE WORKS AS A PRISON NURSE
LOOKING AFTER INMATES.
♪ They call the Rising Sun ♪
♪ And it's been the ruin ♪
♪ Of many a poor boy ♪
♪ And God… ♪
GREG WAS REMOVED FROM THE POLICE FORCE.
HE IS NOW A MUNICIPAL OFFICER.
["Tears" by Giorgio Moroder plays]