1
00:01:51,620 --> 00:01:53,410
Don't tell me how well you fight,

2
00:01:53,950 --> 00:01:55,360
or how great your teacher is,

3
00:01:56,000 --> 00:01:57,830
or brag about your style.

4
00:01:58,660 --> 00:01:59,900
Kungfu -

5
00:02:00,450 --> 00:02:01,610
two words.

6
00:02:02,870 --> 00:02:04,110
Horizontal. Vertical.

7
00:02:04,750 --> 00:02:07,080
Make a mistake - horizontal.

8
00:02:08,000 --> 00:02:09,860
Stay standing and you win.

9
00:02:11,660 --> 00:02:12,950
Isn't that right?

10
00:05:35,000 --> 00:05:39,660
The Grandmaster

11
00:05:50,200 --> 00:05:51,990
We're from Foshan.

12
00:05:52,120 --> 00:05:53,410
My father ran the family business.

13
00:05:53,500 --> 00:05:56,240
He exported goods to Hong Kong.

14
00:05:57,160 --> 00:05:59,320
The Ips have a long history in Foshan.

15
00:05:59,450 --> 00:06:00,990
They named a street after us.

16
00:06:01,080 --> 00:06:02,780
That's how wealthy we were.

17
00:06:05,330 --> 00:06:07,660
Before I turned 40, life was easy.

18
00:06:08,000 --> 00:06:09,830
I lived off my family money.

19
00:06:10,910 --> 00:06:12,240
I had only one passion.

20
00:06:15,450 --> 00:06:16,660
At seven, I started learning kungfu.

21
00:06:16,790 --> 00:06:18,150
My master was Chan Wah-shun.

22
00:06:18,330 --> 00:06:20,990
Foshan's Wing Chun began with Leung Jan.

23
00:06:21,330 --> 00:06:22,820
I'm the third generation.

24
00:06:24,330 --> 00:06:26,410
When I started, my master was seventy.

25
00:06:27,040 --> 00:06:28,150
The day I became a disciple,

26
00:06:28,160 --> 00:06:29,490
he tied the sash himself.

27
00:06:30,830 --> 00:06:33,990
This sash stands for school and teacher.

28
00:06:34,580 --> 00:06:36,440
It stands for honor.

29
00:06:36,660 --> 00:06:39,780
You are now a martial artist.

30
00:06:39,910 --> 00:06:42,530
You must live your life with honor.

31
00:06:43,620 --> 00:06:45,360
One sash, an unbroken tradition.

32
00:06:45,500 --> 00:06:47,280
I lived through dynastic times,

33
00:06:47,450 --> 00:06:50,160
the early republic, warlords,

34
00:06:50,250 --> 00:06:51,910
Japanese invasion and civil war.

35
00:06:52,000 --> 00:06:53,860
Finally, I came to Hong Kong.

36
00:06:54,080 --> 00:06:55,570
What kept me going

37
00:06:55,700 --> 00:06:58,450
was the martial arts code of honor.

38
00:07:02,830 --> 00:07:04,280
My wife, Zhang Yongcheng,

39
00:07:04,870 --> 00:07:07,280
was the descendant of an Imperial Minister.

40
00:07:08,370 --> 00:07:09,530
She was a woman of few words

41
00:07:09,750 --> 00:07:11,580
because she knew their power.

42
00:07:12,330 --> 00:07:14,940
We understood each other well.

43
00:07:45,080 --> 00:07:46,360
She loved music.

44
00:07:46,700 --> 00:07:49,040
I'd take her to hear opera.

45
00:07:49,910 --> 00:07:51,570
People were so conservative back then.

46
00:07:52,000 --> 00:07:54,830
Nice women didn't visit places like this.

47
00:07:55,540 --> 00:07:56,950
But gossip didn't bother her.

48
00:08:34,160 --> 00:08:36,650
When I went out, she lit a lamp

49
00:08:37,290 --> 00:08:40,150
and left it lit till I came home.

50
00:10:22,250 --> 00:10:24,160
If life has seasons,

51
00:10:24,790 --> 00:10:27,450
my first forty years were spring.

52
00:10:30,830 --> 00:10:34,870
(1936. Foshan, Guangdong Province.)

53
00:10:36,000 --> 00:10:37,580
In 1936, Foshan

54
00:10:37,580 --> 00:10:39,070
was a prosperous city.

55
00:10:39,250 --> 00:10:40,610
Life was peaceful and good.

56
00:10:41,160 --> 00:10:44,070
Back then, men socialised in brothels.

57
00:10:44,450 --> 00:10:47,070
Such places were popular in the South.

58
00:10:47,660 --> 00:10:50,860
Foshan's finest was Republic House.

59
00:10:51,250 --> 00:10:53,030
Its walls were covered in gold,

60
00:10:53,250 --> 00:10:54,700
so we called it the Gold Pavilion.

61
00:10:55,450 --> 00:10:57,940
It was the first to have an elevator.

62
00:10:58,620 --> 00:11:00,330
Enter a prince, exit a pauper.

63
00:11:00,910 --> 00:11:02,370
You'd spend money like water.

64
00:11:03,410 --> 00:11:05,740
It was like a social club for martial artists.

65
00:11:06,120 --> 00:11:08,910
Good men can be found among rogues.

66
00:11:11,870 --> 00:11:15,240
And hidden masters too.

67
00:11:17,950 --> 00:11:19,690
People saw it as a pleasure palace.

68
00:11:20,370 --> 00:11:21,700
But to us,

69
00:11:22,660 --> 00:11:24,150
it was a battleground.

70
00:12:05,790 --> 00:12:09,480
I claim three accomplishments in life.

71
00:12:09,830 --> 00:12:12,820
First, I united Xingyi and Bagua styles.

72
00:12:14,000 --> 00:12:15,910
Second, I became the director

73
00:12:16,000 --> 00:12:18,450
of the Northern Martial Arts Union,

74
00:12:19,160 --> 00:12:23,330
bringing together Tongbei, Cannon Fist,

75
00:12:23,410 --> 00:12:25,740
Tai Chi, Yan Qing and other schools.

76
00:12:26,830 --> 00:12:32,070
Third, I took the northern masters south.

77
00:12:32,450 --> 00:12:33,910
In 1929,

78
00:12:34,200 --> 00:12:36,690
the First Southern Martial Arts Academy

79
00:12:37,200 --> 00:12:38,820
was founded under my supervision

80
00:12:39,000 --> 00:12:43,790
after talks here in the Gold Pavilion.

81
00:12:44,370 --> 00:12:45,660
I'm getting old.

82
00:12:46,000 --> 00:12:48,030
It's time for new blood.

83
00:12:48,330 --> 00:12:52,450
I held a retirement ceremony up North.

84
00:12:52,540 --> 00:12:58,030
You invited me to hold a second one here.

85
00:12:59,910 --> 00:13:06,070
It's my farewell to my southern comrades.

86
00:13:07,000 --> 00:13:09,030
Up North, the one who took part

87
00:13:10,370 --> 00:13:12,830
was my top disciple, Ma San.

88
00:13:14,200 --> 00:13:16,070
He'll be my successor.

89
00:13:19,000 --> 00:13:20,990
Please give him your support.

90
00:13:22,830 --> 00:13:26,740
I'd always wanted

91
00:13:27,250 --> 00:13:30,080
to take the southern styles north.

92
00:13:31,700 --> 00:13:33,570
Sadly, my time's up.

93
00:13:34,410 --> 00:13:39,240
I want to hold a demonstration match

94
00:13:40,660 --> 00:13:43,530
with a southern martial artist.

95
00:13:46,160 --> 00:13:48,150
Someone you all support.

96
00:13:52,000 --> 00:13:53,330
Pick one.

97
00:14:06,750 --> 00:14:09,080
Think you're good enough

98
00:14:10,040 --> 00:14:11,990
to challenge the Old Master?

99
00:14:16,500 --> 00:14:18,110
Let's keep it simple.

100
00:14:19,160 --> 00:14:20,370
I'll take you all on.

101
00:14:20,370 --> 00:14:21,950
Get him!

102
00:14:49,660 --> 00:14:52,070
that at the ceremony up North,

103
00:14:52,250 --> 00:14:53,490
I had the honor.

104
00:14:54,250 --> 00:14:57,110
To worship at the feet of the Buddha

105
00:14:58,750 --> 00:15:00,330
first pass the Guardian of the Gate.

106
00:15:02,000 --> 00:15:03,740
That's me.

107
00:15:09,790 --> 00:15:11,950
How can I represent the South?

108
00:15:12,250 --> 00:15:13,660
The southern schools

109
00:15:14,200 --> 00:15:15,990
are Hung, Lau, Choy, Lee, and Mok.

110
00:15:16,580 --> 00:15:17,660
In rank,

111
00:15:18,370 --> 00:15:20,110
you are all my seniors.

112
00:15:20,410 --> 00:15:21,950
You're the leaders and masters.

113
00:15:22,450 --> 00:15:23,820
I have no standing.

114
00:15:23,830 --> 00:15:27,400
The reputation of the South is at stake.

115
00:15:28,200 --> 00:15:29,860
We Southerners

116
00:15:29,870 --> 00:15:31,660
may be petty,

117
00:15:31,830 --> 00:15:34,410
but we don't run away from a fight.

118
00:15:34,410 --> 00:15:36,030
We're not afraid of these Northerners!

119
00:15:36,040 --> 00:15:37,620
This is a challenge.

120
00:15:37,870 --> 00:15:39,080
We will rise to it.

121
00:15:39,450 --> 00:15:40,320
Isn't that right?

122
00:15:40,330 --> 00:15:41,860
Absolutely!

123
00:15:41,870 --> 00:15:42,910
It must be you.

124
00:16:17,750 --> 00:16:19,580
I'll take the kids to my mother's.

125
00:16:19,750 --> 00:16:21,330
Less for you to worry about.

126
00:16:22,830 --> 00:16:24,410
When a man reaches forty,

127
00:16:24,660 --> 00:16:26,650
he needs to be sure of things.

128
00:16:27,830 --> 00:16:29,360
When it's all over,

129
00:16:30,160 --> 00:16:31,620
come pick us up.

130
00:16:45,500 --> 00:16:46,740
Do you know

131
00:16:48,500 --> 00:16:50,330
why a knife must have a sheath?

132
00:16:51,250 --> 00:16:54,490
Its power lies not in sharpness,

133
00:16:55,410 --> 00:16:56,740
but in concealment.

134
00:16:56,750 --> 00:16:58,660
You're too sharp a blade.

135
00:16:58,660 --> 00:17:01,030
You have to stay put.

136
00:17:01,040 --> 00:17:02,490
My sheath

137
00:17:03,700 --> 00:17:05,110
is you, Master.

138
00:17:05,120 --> 00:17:06,660
With you around,

139
00:17:06,660 --> 00:17:08,280
I'm under control.

140
00:17:08,290 --> 00:17:09,780
I can no longer control you.

141
00:17:10,870 --> 00:17:12,830
You're too anxious to make your mark.

142
00:17:13,750 --> 00:17:15,830
For now, leave Foshan.

143
00:17:15,830 --> 00:17:17,190
Miss that train,

144
00:17:17,870 --> 00:17:19,330
and I'll break your legs.

145
00:17:26,040 --> 00:17:27,400
Central News:

146
00:17:27,500 --> 00:17:29,330
Southern armies

147
00:17:29,330 --> 00:17:31,360
marched north

148
00:17:31,500 --> 00:17:35,070
claiming for autonomy.

149
00:17:35,250 --> 00:17:37,240
The Central Army blocked their advance.

150
00:17:38,000 --> 00:17:39,740
The situation is explosive.

151
00:17:54,160 --> 00:17:55,120
Halt!

152
00:17:56,750 --> 00:17:58,240
Let us pass.

153
00:17:58,330 --> 00:18:00,940
Sorry. This street is closed off.

154
00:18:01,330 --> 00:18:03,990
No one bearing arms can enter.

155
00:18:04,700 --> 00:18:06,530
Do you know who's in that rickshaw?

156
00:18:06,830 --> 00:18:09,900
Call out the Gong Family disciples!

157
00:18:13,790 --> 00:18:15,400
Miss Gong, it's good you're here.

158
00:18:15,540 --> 00:18:18,730
He must call this off. Win or lose, it's a disgrace.

159
00:18:18,750 --> 00:18:20,360
My father has never lost.

160
00:18:21,120 --> 00:18:22,360
There's no question of losing.

161
00:18:22,580 --> 00:18:25,700
And so what if he wins?

162
00:18:26,040 --> 00:18:27,820
They'll say he beat a nobody.

163
00:18:27,830 --> 00:18:28,990
Ip Man's not at his level.

164
00:18:29,000 --> 00:18:30,490
Where's my father?

165
00:18:34,500 --> 00:18:35,530
Brother.

166
00:18:40,160 --> 00:18:42,320
It's me, Baosen.

167
00:18:43,080 --> 00:18:46,490
Isn't the Northeast big enough for you?

168
00:18:47,040 --> 00:18:49,490
You had to come to Foshan? Get up.

169
00:18:52,330 --> 00:18:54,990
I'm taking you home.

170
00:18:55,000 --> 00:18:56,360
Home?

171
00:18:57,040 --> 00:18:58,280
How's that possible?

172
00:18:59,160 --> 00:19:02,650
The Japanese control the Northeast.

173
00:19:04,120 --> 00:19:05,910
The Japanese flag

174
00:19:07,500 --> 00:19:09,110
won't wave over me.

175
00:19:17,830 --> 00:19:18,990
The time's not ripe.

176
00:19:19,200 --> 00:19:20,660
Making soup like this

177
00:19:21,160 --> 00:19:22,820
is a lot of work.

178
00:19:23,870 --> 00:19:25,160
It's not soup.

179
00:19:26,250 --> 00:19:27,230
It's snake stew.

180
00:19:28,250 --> 00:19:30,080
Isn't that a winter dish?

181
00:19:30,080 --> 00:19:32,490
It's a dish from a long time ago.

182
00:19:36,620 --> 00:19:38,030
Yes, decades.

183
00:19:39,910 --> 00:19:42,150
1905

184
00:19:42,790 --> 00:19:44,320
was a Snake Year.

185
00:19:46,660 --> 00:19:50,330
You left the Northeast that year.

186
00:19:52,830 --> 00:19:56,740
The fire has to be right for stew.

187
00:19:58,160 --> 00:19:59,620
Too low -

188
00:20:00,450 --> 00:20:02,070
it'll lack taste.

189
00:20:02,830 --> 00:20:04,070
Too high -

190
00:20:05,040 --> 00:20:06,870
it'll scald.

191
00:20:07,830 --> 00:20:09,320
There's a lesson in that.

192
00:20:10,410 --> 00:20:11,620
Go.

193
00:20:18,830 --> 00:20:23,740
Wait till the fire can take this wood.

194
00:20:26,160 --> 00:20:27,370
I'll go then.

195
00:20:28,080 --> 00:20:29,610
The South may secede.

196
00:20:30,290 --> 00:20:31,700
It's no time for diplomacy.

197
00:20:33,870 --> 00:20:35,280
We're getting old.

198
00:20:35,950 --> 00:20:38,290
Don't risk your reputation.

199
00:20:40,540 --> 00:20:44,230
Ip is more than he appears to be.

200
00:20:44,870 --> 00:20:46,280
Force it,

201
00:20:47,910 --> 00:20:49,780
things could go wrong.

202
00:20:52,000 --> 00:20:54,160
I know what I'm doing.

203
00:20:55,830 --> 00:20:57,440
I'm creating opportunity.

204
00:21:00,200 --> 00:21:01,990
This fire today

205
00:21:04,750 --> 00:21:06,330
needs new wood.

206
00:21:10,790 --> 00:21:12,700
Your northern colleagues

207
00:21:13,200 --> 00:21:14,740
disapprove of this match.

208
00:21:16,250 --> 00:21:18,200
It's a huge honor.

209
00:21:19,000 --> 00:21:20,860
This Ip doesn't deserve it.

210
00:21:20,870 --> 00:21:22,200
It's not how things are done.

211
00:21:22,200 --> 00:21:24,030
Don't follow the herd.

212
00:21:25,500 --> 00:21:27,330
If the old never let go

213
00:21:28,290 --> 00:21:30,700
when will the young get their chance?

214
00:21:32,580 --> 00:21:34,240
Ip Man has talent.

215
00:21:35,160 --> 00:21:37,400
Let's see if he can prove himself.

216
00:21:38,370 --> 00:21:40,240
The Gong Family has never lost before.

217
00:21:40,700 --> 00:21:42,240
With you here,

218
00:21:43,370 --> 00:21:44,740
what right does he have?

219
00:21:49,290 --> 00:21:53,200
I once had a temper like yours:

220
00:21:53,750 --> 00:21:55,990
winning was everything.

221
00:21:56,700 --> 00:21:58,660
But life's bigger than that.

222
00:21:59,330 --> 00:22:01,030
Take a longer view.

223
00:22:02,700 --> 00:22:03,940
Past the mountains

224
00:22:05,000 --> 00:22:07,160
the world opens up.

225
00:22:08,830 --> 00:22:12,490
Not to see the good in others,

226
00:22:12,830 --> 00:22:14,410
not to admit their talent,

227
00:22:15,290 --> 00:22:17,200
is to lack generosity.

228
00:22:18,580 --> 00:22:20,790
Our high standards in martial arts

229
00:22:21,120 --> 00:22:23,160
apply to character as well.

230
00:23:00,660 --> 00:23:01,700
Father,

231
00:23:04,040 --> 00:23:08,410
why did you bring me to a brothel?

232
00:23:08,700 --> 00:23:10,660
If you don't see something,

233
00:23:13,040 --> 00:23:14,820
does it not exist?

234
00:23:16,200 --> 00:23:17,860
No harm in seeing.

235
00:23:19,330 --> 00:23:21,160
The first time I came here

236
00:23:22,790 --> 00:23:24,650
was before you were born.

237
00:23:27,250 --> 00:23:30,240
Twenty years have passed in a flash.

238
00:23:30,500 --> 00:23:32,030
In life,

239
00:23:32,040 --> 00:23:33,870
ability isn't everything.

240
00:23:35,450 --> 00:23:37,320
Some thrive in light,

241
00:23:37,830 --> 00:23:39,490
others in shadow.

242
00:23:41,160 --> 00:23:43,450
The times make us what we are.

243
00:23:44,410 --> 00:23:46,120
I asked you to come South

244
00:23:46,450 --> 00:23:48,240
to bring things full circle

245
00:23:49,330 --> 00:23:51,240
and to let you see

246
00:23:51,250 --> 00:23:53,950
how I step down.

247
00:23:54,620 --> 00:23:55,990
Since you were little,

248
00:23:56,620 --> 00:23:59,160
you've watched me fight.

249
00:24:00,250 --> 00:24:02,160
This is the last time.

250
00:24:03,700 --> 00:24:05,940
You're engaged to be married.

251
00:24:05,950 --> 00:24:07,660
The Martial World

252
00:24:08,500 --> 00:24:10,200
is no longer your world.

253
00:24:10,750 --> 00:24:12,280
Be a good doctor.

254
00:24:12,290 --> 00:24:14,150
Live a peaceful life.

255
00:24:14,160 --> 00:24:16,650
This is my greatest wish.

256
00:24:28,750 --> 00:24:29,990
Master Ip.

257
00:24:30,120 --> 00:24:33,320
We're here to celebrate.

258
00:24:33,330 --> 00:24:35,440
Your big day is coming up.

259
00:24:36,160 --> 00:24:40,330
We'd like to show you our support.

260
00:24:40,330 --> 00:24:41,940
I'm humbled, Uncle Deng.

261
00:24:42,500 --> 00:24:43,990
It's nothing at all.

262
00:24:44,000 --> 00:24:45,830
Don't mention it.

263
00:24:46,200 --> 00:24:47,440
Please.

264
00:24:57,700 --> 00:25:00,190
On behalf of the ladies

265
00:25:00,200 --> 00:25:02,910
and staff, congratulations.

266
00:25:02,910 --> 00:25:04,620
That's quite a battle formation.

267
00:25:15,750 --> 00:25:18,490
Sister San heads our Peking Opera troupe.

268
00:25:18,660 --> 00:25:20,200
She dabbles in Bagua.

269
00:25:20,200 --> 00:25:22,990
She'd like to offer a few pointers.

270
00:25:26,040 --> 00:25:27,240
Please.

271
00:25:28,830 --> 00:25:29,690
After you.

272
00:25:29,700 --> 00:25:31,660
Bagua is based on swordplay.

273
00:25:31,790 --> 00:25:33,450
Single reverse palm is a single blade.

274
00:25:34,370 --> 00:25:36,030
Double reverse palm is a double blade.

275
00:25:36,910 --> 00:25:38,900
The feet arc out and in.

276
00:25:41,660 --> 00:25:43,320
There are 64 transformations.

277
00:25:43,790 --> 00:25:46,120
Attack comes out of nowhere.

278
00:26:11,250 --> 00:26:13,660
Sister San, it's just practice.

279
00:26:14,120 --> 00:26:15,700
No need to smash the ancestral tablets.

280
00:26:18,250 --> 00:26:19,830
I've done that many times before.

281
00:26:19,830 --> 00:26:21,240
No big deal.

282
00:26:21,330 --> 00:26:24,160
Mr. Ip, Bagua is underhanded.

283
00:26:24,700 --> 00:26:25,910
Beware.

284
00:26:28,790 --> 00:26:29,820
Thank you.

285
00:26:38,540 --> 00:26:41,780
Ah, Mr. Ip.

286
00:26:41,790 --> 00:26:43,400
Today is a happy day.

287
00:26:43,410 --> 00:26:47,530
We in Accounts wish you well.

288
00:26:53,330 --> 00:26:56,780
Xingyi began with General Yue Fei.

289
00:26:59,330 --> 00:27:02,040
It uses the fist as a spear.

290
00:27:02,040 --> 00:27:03,280
Drill

291
00:27:03,290 --> 00:27:04,820
Chop

292
00:27:04,830 --> 00:27:06,070
Cross

293
00:27:07,200 --> 00:27:08,280
Blast

294
00:27:09,830 --> 00:27:11,070
Crush

295
00:27:49,000 --> 00:27:52,320
Such sensitivity - impressive!

296
00:27:52,410 --> 00:27:55,150
That Crushing Fist is quite something.

297
00:27:58,200 --> 00:27:59,360
Mr. Ip,

298
00:28:00,000 --> 00:28:03,860
each challenge leads to a higher peak.

299
00:28:03,870 --> 00:28:05,830
Xingyi is brutal.

300
00:28:06,790 --> 00:28:08,620
Don't underestimate it.

301
00:28:08,620 --> 00:28:09,990
Let's see how high the peaks get.

302
00:28:10,000 --> 00:28:12,990
Hmm. This will be fun.

303
00:28:22,620 --> 00:28:26,110
My turn now, Master Ip.

304
00:28:26,830 --> 00:28:29,740
And what have you got for me, Yong?

305
00:28:30,540 --> 00:28:32,370
A string of firecrackers.

306
00:28:57,200 --> 00:29:00,400
That move, isn't that Hung Gar?

307
00:29:01,540 --> 00:29:02,780
I'm a jack of all trades.

308
00:29:14,160 --> 00:29:15,490
You do mix it up.

309
00:29:15,500 --> 00:29:16,700
What's wrong with that?

310
00:29:16,870 --> 00:29:18,490
So long as it works.

311
00:29:19,450 --> 00:29:23,320
The 64 Hands have endless combinations.

312
00:29:23,330 --> 00:29:25,990
Your Wing Chun is a three-trick pony.

313
00:29:26,000 --> 00:29:27,950
Spade, Pin, Sheath.

314
00:29:28,500 --> 00:29:29,860
How can it compete?

315
00:29:29,870 --> 00:29:31,740
Three's enough to take care of you.

316
00:30:19,080 --> 00:30:22,700
Yong, your fireworks have fizzled.

317
00:30:24,750 --> 00:30:27,110
What of it? I'm an old man.

318
00:30:28,620 --> 00:30:29,860
Youth trumps skill.

319
00:30:30,660 --> 00:30:32,280
He might be a grandmaster,

320
00:30:32,500 --> 00:30:34,160
but don't hold back.

321
00:30:34,750 --> 00:30:36,240
You'd better win.

322
00:30:37,540 --> 00:30:38,900
This has been a real privilege.

323
00:30:39,250 --> 00:30:40,910
To victory!

324
00:30:40,910 --> 00:30:41,990
Good luck.

325
00:31:13,580 --> 00:31:15,860
Every generation produces new talent.

326
00:31:16,580 --> 00:31:19,870
Mr. Ip, we were fated to meet.

327
00:31:20,660 --> 00:31:22,820
For my final contest

328
00:31:23,200 --> 00:31:25,620
I suggest we match wits,

329
00:31:25,620 --> 00:31:27,080
not skill.

330
00:31:27,330 --> 00:31:28,320
Do you accept?

331
00:31:29,910 --> 00:31:31,700
As our guest,

332
00:31:31,700 --> 00:31:32,990
it's up to you.

333
00:31:41,410 --> 00:31:46,660
When our Union was founded 25 years ago,

334
00:31:49,330 --> 00:31:51,320
a man came from the South.

335
00:31:52,000 --> 00:31:53,280
He offered a challenge.

336
00:31:54,330 --> 00:31:56,320
He held out a flat cake

337
00:31:56,330 --> 00:31:59,120
and asked our Master to break.

338
00:32:02,250 --> 00:32:04,490
Our Master wasn't offended.

339
00:32:06,830 --> 00:32:10,150
He even named the man our first chairman.

340
00:32:10,700 --> 00:32:12,690
It wasn't because of his kungfu

341
00:32:13,000 --> 00:32:14,410
but what he said -

342
00:32:15,950 --> 00:32:17,780
Kungfu divides into North and South.

343
00:32:18,500 --> 00:32:20,240
Must the country divide as well?

344
00:32:22,830 --> 00:32:25,990
That man was also from Foshan -

345
00:32:26,000 --> 00:32:27,660
Ip Yun-biu.

346
00:32:27,790 --> 00:32:29,400
He was a great man.

347
00:32:30,700 --> 00:32:32,530
Today,

348
00:32:32,540 --> 00:32:35,400
meeting another Mr. Ip,

349
00:32:36,620 --> 00:32:39,860
I will ask that same question.

350
00:32:40,790 --> 00:32:41,820
Mr. Ip,

351
00:32:43,330 --> 00:32:48,200
can you break this cake in my hand?

352
00:33:36,580 --> 00:33:40,120
A Tai Chi master kept a bird from flying

353
00:33:40,540 --> 00:33:42,990
by giving it no perch

354
00:33:43,000 --> 00:33:44,700
from which to fly.

355
00:33:46,250 --> 00:33:48,160
The Old Master's skill is too great.

356
00:33:48,830 --> 00:33:51,490
Mr Ip is a sparrow in his palm.

357
00:33:51,500 --> 00:33:55,990
I don't think he can do it.

358
00:34:48,660 --> 00:34:50,320
The world is a big place.

359
00:34:50,830 --> 00:34:51,990
Why limit it to North and South?

360
00:34:53,330 --> 00:34:55,540
It holds you back.

361
00:34:56,500 --> 00:34:58,160
To you,

362
00:34:58,580 --> 00:35:00,360
this cake is the country.

363
00:35:01,330 --> 00:35:03,070
To me it's much more.

364
00:35:04,200 --> 00:35:05,910
Break from what you know

365
00:35:06,330 --> 00:35:08,070
and you will know more.

366
00:35:09,120 --> 00:35:10,410
If the Southern arts go far,

367
00:35:10,870 --> 00:35:13,740
what boundary is the North?

368
00:35:14,830 --> 00:35:16,190
Would you agree?

369
00:35:16,200 --> 00:35:17,660
Well said.

370
00:35:19,000 --> 00:35:20,950
All my life, I've been the victor.

371
00:35:22,000 --> 00:35:23,740
My technique has never failed me.

372
00:35:25,000 --> 00:35:26,910
I never thought I'd see

373
00:35:27,330 --> 00:35:29,790
the limits of my own vision.

374
00:35:38,950 --> 00:35:40,360
Mr. Ip,

375
00:35:41,450 --> 00:35:44,070
today I've made you famous.

376
00:35:45,500 --> 00:35:46,990
In future,

377
00:35:47,620 --> 00:35:49,950
you'll face challenges at every step.

378
00:35:51,120 --> 00:35:52,740
I hope you'll be like me.

379
00:35:53,580 --> 00:35:55,990
Pass on the torch.

380
00:35:57,160 --> 00:36:00,530
Never give up the faith.

381
00:36:01,120 --> 00:36:04,490
Keep the light burning.

382
00:36:58,040 --> 00:36:59,870
Miss Gong, you mustn't do this.

383
00:36:59,870 --> 00:37:01,830
The Gongs have never been defeated.

384
00:37:01,830 --> 00:37:05,450
I will redeem our honor.

385
00:37:07,330 --> 00:37:10,040
Give this to Ip. He'll understand.

386
00:37:12,330 --> 00:37:14,360
I have no chance

387
00:37:14,370 --> 00:37:16,780
to be as great as Father.

388
00:37:17,500 --> 00:37:18,950
It wasn't my choice.

389
00:37:20,000 --> 00:37:21,610
But I'll make my mark.

390
00:37:22,950 --> 00:37:24,190
Go.

391
00:37:30,950 --> 00:37:33,660
Tonight, following Northern custom,

392
00:37:34,290 --> 00:37:35,990
the winner will host a banquet.

393
00:37:36,000 --> 00:37:39,160
Neither Ip Man nor I will attend.

394
00:37:39,370 --> 00:37:40,990
You'll represent me.

395
00:37:41,000 --> 00:37:42,160
Don't worry.

396
00:37:42,660 --> 00:37:45,570
I'll do the right thing.

397
00:37:46,580 --> 00:37:47,820
Let's go!

398
00:38:07,620 --> 00:38:10,330
Of Master Gong's martial arts,

399
00:38:10,330 --> 00:38:12,870
Ma San inherited the steel

400
00:38:12,870 --> 00:38:16,320
and his daughter the silk.

401
00:38:16,410 --> 00:38:19,280
She is the sole heir to the 64 Hands.

402
00:38:19,410 --> 00:38:23,490
Her moves are deadly.

403
00:38:23,790 --> 00:38:27,990
In booking the whole place first,

404
00:38:28,200 --> 00:38:30,950
she forces your hand.

405
00:38:32,000 --> 00:38:33,580
Don't underrate Gong Er.

406
00:38:34,450 --> 00:38:36,410
The Martial World has four taboos:

407
00:38:37,120 --> 00:38:39,530
monks, Taoist priests, women and children.

408
00:38:40,330 --> 00:38:41,820
Grappling with them is a bad idea.

409
00:38:42,250 --> 00:38:46,240
She's gone to so much trouble -

410
00:38:46,250 --> 00:38:47,740
how could I not accept?

411
00:40:26,870 --> 00:40:28,490
Three days ago,

412
00:40:28,830 --> 00:40:30,740
my father sat here.

413
00:40:32,370 --> 00:40:33,660
Tonight,

414
00:40:34,620 --> 00:40:36,530
it's between us.

415
00:40:38,700 --> 00:40:39,410
Please.

416
00:40:39,910 --> 00:40:42,490
Pity about the lovely decor.

417
00:40:43,580 --> 00:40:45,070
Kungfu is about precision.

418
00:40:46,000 --> 00:40:47,490
If anything gets broken,

419
00:40:47,830 --> 00:40:48,910
you win.

420
00:44:07,000 --> 00:44:08,160
Mr. Ip,

421
00:44:08,950 --> 00:44:10,740
I showed you the 64 Hands

422
00:44:11,330 --> 00:44:12,820
so that you'd know

423
00:44:12,830 --> 00:44:15,870
the world is a big place.

424
00:44:16,160 --> 00:44:18,150
Kungfu isn't just charging forward.

425
00:44:18,160 --> 00:44:19,570
Look behind you as well.

426
00:44:19,910 --> 00:44:21,990
I hope that's enough of a clue.

427
00:44:22,330 --> 00:44:23,780
It went your way this time.

428
00:44:24,000 --> 00:44:25,700
Who knows what

429
00:44:25,830 --> 00:44:27,280
next time will bring.

430
00:44:28,080 --> 00:44:29,160
Come.

431
00:44:30,000 --> 00:44:31,200
I'll be waiting.

432
00:44:32,790 --> 00:44:34,070
Take care.

433
00:45:41,330 --> 00:45:45,650
(I dream of seeing the 64 Hands again in the snow.)

434
00:46:28,750 --> 00:46:32,740
(I'm waiting. What's keeping you?)

435
00:47:00,370 --> 00:47:01,700
Does it fit?

436
00:47:03,080 --> 00:47:04,690
Does Foshan get this cold?

437
00:47:10,830 --> 00:47:12,280
You look lovely.

438
00:47:12,290 --> 00:47:14,370
Let's take a family photo.

439
00:48:29,330 --> 00:48:35,150
(October 1938. Foshan fell to the Japanese.)

440
00:48:41,120 --> 00:48:42,660
In October 1938,

441
00:48:42,830 --> 00:48:43,990
the Japanese invaded Foshan.

442
00:48:44,330 --> 00:48:47,120
Their army took over our home.

443
00:48:47,830 --> 00:48:49,860
If life has four seasons,

444
00:48:49,870 --> 00:48:53,660
we went from spring straight to winter.

445
00:49:34,080 --> 00:49:36,870
I'll be back with dinner.

446
00:49:50,500 --> 00:49:51,950
Help me prosper?

447
00:49:52,950 --> 00:49:54,660
Rescue me from poverty?

448
00:49:56,870 --> 00:49:58,660
I've never been poor in my life.

449
00:49:59,540 --> 00:50:00,900
The country's in crisis

450
00:50:01,660 --> 00:50:02,740
and everyone is suffering.

451
00:50:04,000 --> 00:50:05,580
To be poor is no big deal.

452
00:50:07,700 --> 00:50:09,320
I'd rather starve

453
00:50:10,330 --> 00:50:11,690
than eat Japanese rice.

454
00:50:12,790 --> 00:50:14,240
I won't collaborate.

455
00:50:15,500 --> 00:50:18,240
I have plenty of friends.

456
00:50:18,700 --> 00:50:21,990
They'll help me through.

457
00:50:22,410 --> 00:50:23,820
Enjoy your dinner.

458
00:50:30,540 --> 00:50:32,650
You won't find those friends here,

459
00:50:33,250 --> 00:50:34,740
only collaborators.

460
00:50:34,750 --> 00:50:36,410
We had a dinner just now.

461
00:50:36,410 --> 00:50:37,900
These are the leftovers.

462
00:50:37,910 --> 00:50:39,200
If it's not beneath you,

463
00:50:39,200 --> 00:50:41,110
take them back to your family.

464
00:50:44,830 --> 00:50:46,110
How can I accept?

465
00:50:46,700 --> 00:50:48,320
Dirty money paid for it.

466
00:50:48,330 --> 00:50:51,040
No point in waste. We're old friends.

467
00:50:51,160 --> 00:50:52,700
You're most welcome.

468
00:51:48,200 --> 00:51:49,690
They're brand new.

469
00:51:50,000 --> 00:51:51,700
I was going to the Northeast.

470
00:51:52,120 --> 00:51:53,490
But that's impossible now.

471
00:51:55,000 --> 00:51:57,830
Sell them and I can feed my family.

472
00:51:58,830 --> 00:52:00,240
Why is there a button missing?

473
00:52:03,000 --> 00:52:04,450
Is there?

474
00:52:05,370 --> 00:52:06,660
Must've dropped off.

475
00:52:13,200 --> 00:52:14,820
I began studying kungfu at seven.

476
00:52:14,830 --> 00:52:16,160
Before I turned forty,

477
00:52:16,160 --> 00:52:17,570
I was never beaten.

478
00:52:17,870 --> 00:52:19,160
When that happened,

479
00:52:19,830 --> 00:52:22,190
It was life that dealt the blows.

480
00:52:22,830 --> 00:52:24,440
In eight years of war

481
00:52:24,450 --> 00:52:25,740
I lost everything.

482
00:52:26,160 --> 00:52:27,320
Money,

483
00:52:27,330 --> 00:52:28,660
friends...

484
00:52:29,040 --> 00:52:32,110
China will never die!

485
00:52:36,870 --> 00:52:38,740
Girls obey their Madam.

486
00:52:39,540 --> 00:52:41,240
Gangsters obey their boss.

487
00:52:41,950 --> 00:52:43,820
Our boss was Sun Yat-sen

488
00:52:43,830 --> 00:52:45,440
We followed his orders.

489
00:52:47,700 --> 00:52:50,190
We Southerners have fire in our bellies

490
00:52:50,580 --> 00:52:51,690
and a sense of honour.

491
00:52:53,330 --> 00:52:56,820
Only cowards fear the Japs.

492
00:52:57,160 --> 00:52:58,570
I'll kill any I see!

493
00:52:58,870 --> 00:53:02,620
(1938. Uncle Deng died in a Japanese bombardment.)

494
00:53:02,620 --> 00:53:05,690
(Collaborators took over the Gold Pavilion.)

495
00:53:06,330 --> 00:53:07,820
Finally, I lost my family.

496
00:53:41,830 --> 00:53:49,610
(Ip Man lost two daughters in the war.)

497
00:54:23,620 --> 00:54:26,330
No one move!

498
00:54:27,370 --> 00:54:29,280
Where are you going? Show your IDs!

499
00:54:30,000 --> 00:54:31,200
Hurry.

500
00:54:31,830 --> 00:54:32,990
IDs!

501
00:54:35,370 --> 00:54:38,080
Where are you going? IDs!

502
00:54:39,330 --> 00:54:42,740
Halt!

503
00:55:49,830 --> 00:55:54,490
(1939. Traveling to Northwest University to practice medicine,)

504
00:55:54,500 --> 00:55:56,830
(Gong Er meets The Razor, a Nationalist agent.)

505
00:56:24,160 --> 00:56:26,650
(1940. Ma San collaborates with the Japanese,)

506
00:56:26,660 --> 00:56:28,990
(taking an official post in the puppet government.)

507
00:56:58,750 --> 00:57:01,330
Do you remember what I taught you?

508
00:57:01,330 --> 00:57:02,360
Yes.

509
00:57:03,040 --> 00:57:05,950
Never put yourself first,

510
00:57:06,160 --> 00:57:07,990
show respect.

511
00:57:09,750 --> 00:57:12,820
There's always someone better.

512
00:57:12,830 --> 00:57:14,690
To yield is not to lose.

513
00:57:15,330 --> 00:57:18,120
Master, you have taught me

514
00:57:18,660 --> 00:57:22,080
to be modest

515
00:57:22,080 --> 00:57:23,570
and know my place.

516
00:57:23,580 --> 00:57:25,490
I took you in as an orphan.

517
00:57:27,330 --> 00:57:29,570
You brought

518
00:57:29,580 --> 00:57:32,320
credit to our school.

519
00:57:33,000 --> 00:57:34,910
Let's go over

520
00:57:35,620 --> 00:57:37,660
my supreme move.

521
00:57:40,950 --> 00:57:42,490
The Old Monkey Hangs up his Badge.

522
00:57:45,370 --> 00:57:46,580
Have you practiced it?

523
00:57:47,500 --> 00:57:48,830
Yes.

524
00:57:48,830 --> 00:57:52,120
You know the key to it?

525
00:57:52,120 --> 00:57:54,660
I was never told.

526
00:57:54,660 --> 00:57:56,490
It's looking back in reflection.

527
00:57:57,160 --> 00:57:58,650
It's not the upward move,

528
00:57:59,620 --> 00:58:00,740
but the turning back.

529
00:58:05,540 --> 00:58:07,530
Understand what I'm saying?

530
00:58:08,870 --> 00:58:11,580
A warrior molds himself to the times.

531
00:58:14,410 --> 00:58:15,820
What if

532
00:58:16,500 --> 00:58:18,160
I can't turn back?

533
00:58:22,000 --> 00:58:24,160
Then the Gong Family legacy

534
00:58:24,700 --> 00:58:27,240
cannot live on in you.

535
00:58:45,500 --> 00:58:46,610
Stay back.

536
00:58:49,330 --> 00:58:50,690
Let him go.

537
00:58:52,160 --> 00:58:54,650
Never darken my door again.

538
00:59:00,910 --> 00:59:02,240
Get lost.

539
00:59:09,330 --> 00:59:11,070
Master!

540
01:00:21,660 --> 01:00:22,740
The whole clan

541
01:00:22,870 --> 01:00:24,610
heard you were coming

542
01:00:24,700 --> 01:00:26,320
and raced in from all over.

543
01:00:26,330 --> 01:00:27,280
And Jiang?

544
01:00:27,290 --> 01:00:29,030
He's keeping them company.

545
01:00:37,370 --> 01:00:38,360
Miss Gong,

546
01:00:38,830 --> 01:00:41,320
they're awaiting your decision.

547
01:00:41,660 --> 01:00:43,320
They didn't come all this way

548
01:00:44,080 --> 01:00:45,780
to hear my decision.

549
01:00:49,870 --> 01:00:50,990
Did Father have any last words?

550
01:00:51,000 --> 01:00:52,410
Don't seek vengeance.

551
01:00:56,910 --> 01:00:58,030
Miss,

552
01:00:58,500 --> 01:01:00,330
your father forbade revenge.

553
01:01:34,660 --> 01:01:36,570
I agree Ma San deserves to die.

554
01:01:38,910 --> 01:01:40,950
It's a massive crime

555
01:01:42,500 --> 01:01:43,660
to betray one's teacher.

556
01:01:45,200 --> 01:01:47,490
Nothing is worse.

557
01:01:48,950 --> 01:01:50,160
On the other hand,

558
01:01:51,160 --> 01:01:52,780
it was your father

559
01:01:53,660 --> 01:01:56,240
who united Xingyi and Bagua.

560
01:01:57,500 --> 01:02:00,820
Ma San worked hard at Xingyi.

561
01:02:01,120 --> 01:02:02,490
And your father taught you

562
01:02:03,000 --> 01:02:05,660
the 64 Hands himself.

563
01:02:06,450 --> 01:02:09,320
The two of you are his legacy.

564
01:02:10,370 --> 01:02:11,530
If you stand together,

565
01:02:12,450 --> 01:02:15,320
the legacy remains whole.

566
01:02:16,910 --> 01:02:18,070
Besides,

567
01:02:18,080 --> 01:02:20,990
if you take action,

568
01:02:21,410 --> 01:02:24,200
whatever the outcome,

569
01:02:25,330 --> 01:02:27,320
people will laugh.

570
01:02:28,000 --> 01:02:30,530
They'll say what's this Gong school

571
01:02:30,870 --> 01:02:32,330
where the disciple kills the master,

572
01:02:33,160 --> 01:02:35,530
and the daughter kills her brother-in-arms?

573
01:02:36,250 --> 01:02:40,320
A pack of wild animals?

574
01:02:41,200 --> 01:02:43,320
Besides, as for Ma San,

575
01:02:43,660 --> 01:02:46,700
even your father couldn't finish him off.

576
01:02:46,870 --> 01:02:48,360
You think you can?

577
01:02:49,660 --> 01:02:51,030
Miss Gong,

578
01:02:52,000 --> 01:02:54,410
we're old men.

579
01:02:55,500 --> 01:02:59,410
We made the long trip here

580
01:03:00,250 --> 01:03:03,990
with your best interests in mind.

581
01:03:04,330 --> 01:03:06,820
Take our advice.

582
01:03:07,200 --> 01:03:09,660
Just get married.

583
01:03:10,500 --> 01:03:12,660
Your father's last words

584
01:03:13,910 --> 01:03:16,490
were Don't seek vengeance.

585
01:03:17,330 --> 01:03:19,660
If you kill Ma San

586
01:03:19,830 --> 01:03:22,370
won't that go against his wishes?

587
01:03:25,160 --> 01:03:26,620
My father said that

588
01:03:27,500 --> 01:03:28,660
out of love for me.

589
01:03:30,660 --> 01:03:32,450
He wants me to have a peaceful life.

590
01:03:34,160 --> 01:03:35,990
But if I don't avenge his death,

591
01:03:36,830 --> 01:03:38,360
I'll never be at peace.

592
01:03:44,500 --> 01:03:46,660
I understand what you're saying.

593
01:03:49,330 --> 01:03:50,660
With respect,

594
01:03:51,790 --> 01:03:55,080
he treated you

595
01:03:55,370 --> 01:03:57,110
all like brothers.

596
01:03:58,160 --> 01:03:59,320
After he died,

597
01:04:00,540 --> 01:04:03,150
you should've dealt with Ma San.

598
01:04:03,410 --> 01:04:04,950
Instead you come here

599
01:04:04,950 --> 01:04:07,190
as his messenger.

600
01:04:09,910 --> 01:04:12,150
After all my father did for you!

601
01:04:14,160 --> 01:04:15,570
I know

602
01:04:16,830 --> 01:04:18,440
Ma San works for the Japanese.

603
01:04:19,410 --> 01:04:20,530
He's got power.

604
01:04:22,080 --> 01:04:23,820
But I'll stand up for my family.

605
01:04:25,160 --> 01:04:26,820
Is he coming, or not?

606
01:04:32,290 --> 01:04:34,400
What does it matter?

607
01:04:35,500 --> 01:04:38,240
He comes, you go,

608
01:04:38,580 --> 01:04:40,860
and that's the end of it, right?

609
01:04:42,950 --> 01:04:47,450
It's better to let it go, Miss Gong.

610
01:04:47,830 --> 01:04:50,370
Some things are out of our hands.

611
01:04:51,160 --> 01:04:53,320
It's the Will of Heaven.

612
01:04:55,950 --> 01:04:58,040
Maybe I am the Will of Heaven.

613
01:05:22,700 --> 01:05:26,280
Oh ye gods and spirits

614
01:05:27,830 --> 01:05:31,490
guide this soul to Paradise!

615
01:06:37,500 --> 01:06:38,860
Halt!

616
01:06:40,330 --> 01:06:42,160
We mustn't stop!

617
01:06:42,910 --> 01:06:45,030
Don't block the road.

618
01:06:45,830 --> 01:06:47,490
Keep to the side.

619
01:06:47,500 --> 01:06:48,360
Move!

620
01:06:49,000 --> 01:06:50,910
Ma San ordered us

621
01:06:50,910 --> 01:06:52,400
to escort the body.

622
01:06:54,700 --> 01:06:56,240
Miss Gong,

623
01:06:56,250 --> 01:06:57,330
Ma San's men

624
01:06:57,330 --> 01:06:58,820
are blocking the road.

625
01:06:58,830 --> 01:07:00,320
The have banners of mourning.

626
01:07:00,330 --> 01:07:02,160
Troublemakers!

627
01:07:02,160 --> 01:07:03,120
Miss Gong,

628
01:07:03,120 --> 01:07:06,080
time is of the essence.

629
01:07:08,750 --> 01:07:10,080
Jiang!

630
01:07:29,950 --> 01:07:33,320
Tell Ma San he's a dead man.

631
01:07:34,950 --> 01:07:37,370
Let's go!

632
01:07:39,830 --> 01:07:43,490
Oh ye gods and spirits

633
01:07:43,830 --> 01:07:47,740
...guide this soul to Paradise!

634
01:07:57,200 --> 01:07:58,570
They're here.

635
01:07:58,580 --> 01:07:59,820
Stop her.

636
01:08:00,660 --> 01:08:01,400
Keep her back.

637
01:08:01,410 --> 01:08:02,450
Let me at her.

638
01:08:02,790 --> 01:08:03,950
Stop her.

639
01:08:05,830 --> 01:08:08,620
Stay back. We're here for Ma San.

640
01:08:16,830 --> 01:08:18,740
Since you're my senior,

641
01:08:19,160 --> 01:08:20,570
I won't force my way in.

642
01:08:21,120 --> 01:08:22,700
But know this.

643
01:08:23,000 --> 01:08:25,330
You can't hide from me forever.

644
01:08:26,330 --> 01:08:28,610
I will take back my family's legacy.

645
01:08:29,000 --> 01:08:29,980
Come out!

646
01:08:32,910 --> 01:08:36,950
Better to advance than to stop.

647
01:08:37,370 --> 01:08:40,280
The Old Master taught me this.

648
01:08:40,290 --> 01:08:42,650
It became my philosophy of life.

649
01:08:42,660 --> 01:08:43,900
It's a shame

650
01:08:43,910 --> 01:08:45,700
he couldn't follow his own advice.

651
01:08:46,580 --> 01:08:49,700
His precious teachings are mine now.

652
01:08:50,750 --> 01:08:52,030
You want them -

653
01:08:52,330 --> 01:08:54,540
send a member of the family.

654
01:08:55,830 --> 01:08:58,110
You'll be marrying out.

655
01:09:01,540 --> 01:09:02,740
You don't count.

656
01:09:25,750 --> 01:09:27,410
Don't ask after me.

657
01:09:28,910 --> 01:09:30,820
No news means I'm gone.

658
01:09:37,660 --> 01:09:39,240
Find someone else.

659
01:09:46,120 --> 01:09:47,200
Miss,

660
01:09:47,830 --> 01:09:50,370
to give up such an ideal marriage -

661
01:09:50,910 --> 01:09:52,150
is it really worth it?

662
01:09:55,290 --> 01:09:56,870
Think it over.

663
01:09:57,500 --> 01:09:58,660
If you take those vows,

664
01:09:59,200 --> 01:10:01,490
you'll never be able to marry,

665
01:10:02,790 --> 01:10:05,750
teach, or have children.

666
01:10:06,830 --> 01:10:09,190
There's no turning back.

667
01:10:16,950 --> 01:10:18,190
Father,

668
01:10:19,910 --> 01:10:22,070
can you read what's in my heart?

669
01:10:24,250 --> 01:10:25,990
If you agree with me,

670
01:10:28,160 --> 01:10:30,450
show me a flame before Buddha.

671
01:11:09,580 --> 01:11:12,820
Better to advance than to stop.

672
01:11:14,620 --> 01:11:16,330
He mocks us for having no successor.

673
01:11:31,160 --> 01:11:32,650
I can only advance.

674
01:11:34,040 --> 01:11:35,320
I can't stop.

675
01:12:25,040 --> 01:12:29,580
(1950. Hong Kong. Tai Nan Street.)

676
01:12:34,660 --> 01:12:36,070
Ever taught before, Master Ip?

677
01:12:36,580 --> 01:12:37,820
To teach for a living

678
01:12:37,830 --> 01:12:38,940
is a new experience.

679
01:12:39,330 --> 01:12:40,780
So why now?

680
01:12:41,410 --> 01:12:42,490
I'm starting a new life.

681
01:12:42,500 --> 01:12:44,200
You've got your things.

682
01:12:44,200 --> 01:12:45,610
You're confident.

683
01:12:46,080 --> 01:12:47,160
Saves running back and forth.

684
01:12:47,410 --> 01:12:49,150
In Hong Kong no one knows Wing Chun.

685
01:12:49,580 --> 01:12:50,990
Any special moves?

686
01:12:51,370 --> 01:12:52,330
Not really.

687
01:12:52,830 --> 01:12:55,490
Three basic hands - Spade, Pin, Sheath.

688
01:12:56,540 --> 01:12:57,700
How many forms?

689
01:12:59,000 --> 01:13:00,030
The Concept,

690
01:13:00,500 --> 01:13:01,330
The Bridge,

691
01:13:01,580 --> 01:13:02,570
and Darting Fingers.

692
01:13:03,500 --> 01:13:04,610
Weapons?

693
01:13:05,330 --> 01:13:06,490
Double Knives

694
01:13:06,500 --> 01:13:07,830
and the Six-and-a-half Point Pole.

695
01:13:08,410 --> 01:13:09,740
Anything else?

696
01:13:10,250 --> 01:13:11,490
That's it.

697
01:13:12,790 --> 01:13:14,030
Bone-setting,

698
01:13:14,040 --> 01:13:15,120
internal energy -

699
01:13:15,120 --> 01:13:16,330
I don't do any of that.

700
01:13:17,290 --> 01:13:18,490
Drifters,

701
01:13:18,500 --> 01:13:19,530
lion dancers -

702
01:13:20,120 --> 01:13:21,580
I don't teach those types.

703
01:13:22,120 --> 01:13:23,330
Why not?

704
01:13:25,540 --> 01:13:27,200
Kungfu isn't a sideshow.

705
01:13:27,870 --> 01:13:29,200
So I won't teach drifters.

706
01:13:30,160 --> 01:13:31,570
Lion dancers jump at firecrackers.

707
01:13:31,950 --> 01:13:33,820
They're always brawling

708
01:13:34,500 --> 01:13:35,990
and showing off,

709
01:13:36,160 --> 01:13:37,740
all for a bit of cash.

710
01:13:38,910 --> 01:13:40,150
It's crude.

711
01:13:40,290 --> 01:13:41,990
I'll ask you straight -

712
01:13:42,580 --> 01:13:43,860
ever been in a real fight?

713
01:13:45,620 --> 01:13:47,780
It's wall-to-wall kungfu schools here.

714
01:13:47,790 --> 01:13:49,280
They start fights over nothing.

715
01:13:49,450 --> 01:13:50,660
Master Ip,

716
01:13:51,870 --> 01:13:53,160
have you got what it takes?

717
01:13:53,160 --> 01:13:56,150
Try me and find out.

718
01:13:57,450 --> 01:13:58,570
Fight! Fight!

719
01:14:00,250 --> 01:14:01,830
I've had a few years of training.

720
01:14:03,700 --> 01:14:05,410
Show me your stuff, Master Ip.

721
01:14:05,410 --> 01:14:06,700
Have you had lunch?

722
01:14:06,700 --> 01:14:08,320
Barbecued pork and rice.

723
01:14:08,330 --> 01:14:09,490
I suggest you wait a bit.

724
01:14:09,500 --> 01:14:10,530
It'd be a shame to waste it.

725
01:14:10,540 --> 01:14:11,620
Waste it?

726
01:14:25,660 --> 01:14:26,650
Brother Hung,

727
01:14:26,830 --> 01:14:28,280
are you okay?

728
01:14:30,620 --> 01:14:31,830
Where's the tea?

729
01:14:31,830 --> 01:14:33,070
Tea?

730
01:14:33,330 --> 01:14:34,320
To give to your new master!

731
01:14:34,790 --> 01:14:36,900
We've put a bed here for you.

732
01:14:38,580 --> 01:14:40,190
I hope it'll do for now.

733
01:14:40,660 --> 01:14:41,820
Sorry it's a bit shabby.

734
01:14:57,330 --> 01:14:58,490
Is there a hammer?

735
01:15:16,000 --> 01:15:17,160
Master Ip,

736
01:15:17,450 --> 01:15:20,950
The boys and I want some lessons.

737
01:15:20,950 --> 01:15:21,860
Eighty cents a head.

738
01:15:21,870 --> 01:15:23,160
Cheap enough.

739
01:15:23,160 --> 01:15:24,400
But call yourself a master,

740
01:15:24,410 --> 01:15:25,490
you'd better deliver the goods.

741
01:15:25,500 --> 01:15:27,200
No snake oil.

742
01:15:27,200 --> 01:15:29,160
How good's your kungfu, anyway?

743
01:15:44,790 --> 01:15:45,740
Lock the gate.

744
01:15:48,790 --> 01:15:49,400
Hey!

745
01:15:49,410 --> 01:15:50,490
Little fucker.

746
01:15:50,500 --> 01:15:52,280
Shut the door and it's on for real.

747
01:15:52,370 --> 01:15:53,950
You've got two hands and two feet.

748
01:15:53,950 --> 01:15:55,240
How you gonna beat us all?

749
01:15:55,250 --> 01:15:56,830
You're mistaken.

750
01:15:57,830 --> 01:15:58,940
I have two hands but

751
01:15:59,870 --> 01:16:01,080
Wing Chun has eight kicks.

752
01:16:01,660 --> 01:16:02,990
Never mind your boys.

753
01:16:03,660 --> 01:16:06,240
There's more than enough for you.

754
01:16:06,250 --> 01:16:07,700
More than enough for me?

755
01:16:22,000 --> 01:16:23,330
That one's free.

756
01:16:37,750 --> 01:16:38,830
First kick.

757
01:16:59,410 --> 01:17:00,570
Fourth kick.

758
01:17:13,700 --> 01:17:14,940
One more left.

759
01:17:35,330 --> 01:17:37,990
Do you remember our oath?

760
01:17:39,660 --> 01:17:40,900
What oath?

761
01:17:42,000 --> 01:17:43,490
I vow with all my heart

762
01:17:43,500 --> 01:17:44,830
to be loyal

763
01:17:44,830 --> 01:17:46,240
and obedient

764
01:17:46,250 --> 01:17:47,740
to the Party.

765
01:17:47,750 --> 01:17:49,160
I fear neither hardship

766
01:17:49,160 --> 01:17:50,450
nor sacrifice.

767
01:17:50,830 --> 01:17:52,780
Should I forsake these vows,

768
01:17:53,160 --> 01:17:58,490
I accept the harshest punishment.

769
01:17:58,500 --> 01:17:59,780
Fuck.

770
01:18:00,370 --> 01:18:02,530
The war is over.

771
01:18:03,540 --> 01:18:05,070
This is Hong Kong.

772
01:18:05,080 --> 01:18:07,910
But we stand by our code -

773
01:18:08,620 --> 01:18:09,950
Join us alive.

774
01:18:10,080 --> 01:18:11,690
Leave us dead.

775
01:18:12,250 --> 01:18:13,700
I'm leaving now.

776
01:18:14,540 --> 01:18:15,700
Can you stop me?

777
01:18:16,660 --> 01:18:18,120
Try us and see.

778
01:20:00,660 --> 01:20:04,450
(In exile in Hong Kong,)

779
01:20:04,450 --> 01:20:09,150
(The Razor ran the White Rose Barber Shop.)

780
01:20:31,000 --> 01:20:34,990
(1950. Chinese New Year's Eve. Hong Kong.)

781
01:21:11,410 --> 01:21:14,070
You don't look like you need a doctor.

782
01:21:14,410 --> 01:21:17,980
I'd like to see the 64 Hands again.

783
01:21:18,330 --> 01:21:20,030
If you don't mind me saying -

784
01:21:20,160 --> 01:21:21,740
You lost. I won.

785
01:21:23,750 --> 01:21:24,990
Have a seat.

786
01:21:31,870 --> 01:21:33,860
If you'd said that at the door,

787
01:21:34,500 --> 01:21:38,320
I wouldn't have made it so easy

788
01:21:38,830 --> 01:21:41,110
for you to get your dumplings.

789
01:21:43,660 --> 01:21:44,740
Thank you.

790
01:21:52,910 --> 01:21:54,150
You know,

791
01:21:55,160 --> 01:21:58,610
I'd hoped to visit the Northeast in 1937.

792
01:22:00,620 --> 01:22:02,110
There was a challenge waiting for me.

793
01:22:04,790 --> 01:22:05,990
I had a warm coat made.

794
01:22:06,910 --> 01:22:10,110
But the war stopped me from going.

795
01:22:11,950 --> 01:22:13,360
I didn't keep the coat,

796
01:22:15,080 --> 01:22:16,530
but I still have one of its buttons.

797
01:22:18,750 --> 01:22:19,830
Call it a memento.

798
01:22:23,750 --> 01:22:25,830
The 64 Hands is too important a legacy.

799
01:22:28,660 --> 01:22:30,450
Why let it disappear?

800
01:22:33,910 --> 01:22:35,200
In centuries of martial arts history,

801
01:22:35,750 --> 01:22:37,360
so many things

802
01:22:38,000 --> 01:22:39,330
have vanished.

803
01:22:40,540 --> 01:22:42,320
Why should the Gong Family arts survive?

804
01:22:46,580 --> 01:22:48,410
Mr. Ip,

805
01:22:48,830 --> 01:22:50,860
no art is higher than Heaven

806
01:22:51,120 --> 01:22:52,660
no gift more solid than Earth.

807
01:22:54,200 --> 01:22:57,650
Nothing lasts forever and that's fine.

808
01:22:58,790 --> 01:23:00,490
Keep this button.

809
01:23:01,450 --> 01:23:04,530
As for what may and may not be seen,

810
01:23:06,250 --> 01:23:07,660
let's not talk about it now.

811
01:23:11,910 --> 01:23:15,910
Mr. Ip, ten years ago on New Year's eve

812
01:23:15,910 --> 01:23:17,200
do you know where I was?

813
01:23:22,080 --> 01:23:23,360
Mr. Ip,

814
01:23:24,500 --> 01:23:25,990
may I have a word?

815
01:23:28,330 --> 01:23:32,200
The Gong arts belong to the Gong family.

816
01:23:33,080 --> 01:23:35,820
The 64 Hands aren't there just for show.

817
01:23:37,500 --> 01:23:38,830
The Gong Family lives.

818
01:23:39,250 --> 01:23:40,950
I know how much talent is there.

819
01:23:41,620 --> 01:23:43,280
I'm keen to learn.

820
01:23:43,540 --> 01:23:44,950
I'll be waiting.

821
01:24:06,370 --> 01:24:11,990
People - they change with the times.

822
01:24:13,000 --> 01:24:15,330
Wear shoes that suit the crossing,

823
01:24:15,330 --> 01:24:18,070
and underpants that fit your ass.

824
01:24:19,250 --> 01:24:20,950
In Hong Kong,

825
01:24:21,080 --> 01:24:23,240
I can only afford these cigarettes.

826
01:24:24,830 --> 01:24:26,320
Back home,

827
01:24:26,540 --> 01:24:28,740
I smoked real Manchurian tobacco.

828
01:24:29,330 --> 01:24:30,660
Now that was smoking.

829
01:24:33,580 --> 01:24:36,650
Be mild, good, respectful, thrifty, deferential.

830
01:24:36,830 --> 01:24:38,570
Deferential is the key.

831
01:24:40,500 --> 01:24:42,330
Let's say I'm smoking.

832
01:24:43,250 --> 01:24:45,330
A stranger sits down.

833
01:24:45,660 --> 01:24:48,200
I defer to him: Have a smoke.

834
01:24:48,580 --> 01:24:52,320
Even if he doesn't smoke, he must accept

835
01:24:52,330 --> 01:24:54,490
or he'll make me lose face.

836
01:24:55,500 --> 01:24:56,860
Mr. Ip,

837
01:24:59,330 --> 01:25:01,110
have a smoke.

838
01:25:06,200 --> 01:25:07,320
Thank you.

839
01:25:07,330 --> 01:25:08,820
You're welcome.

840
01:25:50,500 --> 01:25:51,860
You've got the gift.

841
01:25:53,700 --> 01:25:55,820
Twenty years ago,

842
01:25:55,830 --> 01:25:57,690
we could have sparred.

843
01:25:59,000 --> 01:26:00,360
What a shame.

844
01:26:05,910 --> 01:26:08,870
Some work in the light,

845
01:26:09,120 --> 01:26:10,780
others in shadow.

846
01:26:11,580 --> 01:26:13,320
The face of a school must be spotless.

847
01:26:14,330 --> 01:26:16,570
Blood must flow only in the shadows.

848
01:26:17,660 --> 01:26:19,780
If not, if it stains the face,

849
01:26:20,160 --> 01:26:22,450
then the school itself may perish.

850
01:26:23,000 --> 01:26:25,200
The face offers the cigarettes.

851
01:26:25,700 --> 01:26:28,620
The dirty work is done in the shadows.

852
01:26:29,870 --> 01:26:33,160
Mr. Ip, you're too late.

853
01:26:33,160 --> 01:26:35,030
Forget the 64 hands -

854
01:26:35,830 --> 01:26:38,160
you'll never see even one.

855
01:26:40,750 --> 01:26:44,860
(1940. Chinese New Year's Eve. The Northeast.)

856
01:27:02,080 --> 01:27:03,990
Is it hard to kill a man?

857
01:27:05,250 --> 01:27:06,580
Miss Gong,

858
01:27:07,620 --> 01:27:09,280
it's not like in the old days.

859
01:27:10,290 --> 01:27:12,240
Murder is punishable by death.

860
01:27:13,080 --> 01:27:16,740
Is Ma San worth it?

861
01:27:21,700 --> 01:27:23,740
we make our own path in life.

862
01:27:24,910 --> 01:27:26,240
Should we go home,

863
01:27:27,160 --> 01:27:28,570
or keep waiting?

864
01:27:33,040 --> 01:27:34,650
It's New Year's Eve.

865
01:27:36,040 --> 01:27:37,490
He'll be here soon.

866
01:27:38,290 --> 01:27:39,700
We have to wait.

867
01:27:41,040 --> 01:27:42,240
All right.

868
01:27:48,160 --> 01:27:49,490
We'll wait.

869
01:31:27,620 --> 01:31:31,070
This is between Miss Gong and Ma San.

870
01:31:31,290 --> 01:31:33,740
Everyone else stay out of it.

871
01:31:34,830 --> 01:31:36,410
There you are,

872
01:31:37,660 --> 01:31:39,820
still playing with your monkey.

873
01:31:41,540 --> 01:31:42,450
Deal with him!

874
01:31:42,570 --> 01:31:43,570
Get him!

875
01:32:24,410 --> 01:32:25,950
You're worse than a debt collector,

876
01:32:27,290 --> 01:32:29,740
trying to ruin my New Year's Eve.

877
01:32:30,450 --> 01:32:32,440
The dumplings are in the pot,

878
01:32:33,160 --> 01:32:35,150
but you won't be eating them.

879
01:32:36,750 --> 01:32:38,450
I let you off before

880
01:32:39,250 --> 01:32:42,820
to avoid destroying the Gong clan.

881
01:32:44,080 --> 01:32:46,030
You should know when to give up.

882
01:32:46,830 --> 01:32:48,860
Those needing salvation burn joss.

883
01:32:49,660 --> 01:32:51,450
Those who are hungry, eat.

884
01:32:52,580 --> 01:32:53,820
What I must do,

885
01:32:54,000 --> 01:32:56,280
I will do and nothing can stop me.

886
01:32:57,160 --> 01:32:58,820
The Gong Family legacy

887
01:33:00,040 --> 01:33:02,070
must return to me tonight.

888
01:33:02,830 --> 01:33:03,820
Fine.

889
01:33:05,410 --> 01:33:08,700
It's a part of me.

890
01:33:10,160 --> 01:33:11,620
You want it -

891
01:33:14,000 --> 01:33:15,160
come and get it.

892
01:37:13,250 --> 01:37:14,660
Master!

893
01:37:14,660 --> 01:37:16,700
Keep away.

894
01:37:19,830 --> 01:37:21,160
Ma San,

895
01:37:21,160 --> 01:37:22,200
speak!

896
01:37:35,910 --> 01:37:37,320
That day,

897
01:37:39,500 --> 01:37:40,780
the Old Master

898
01:37:41,160 --> 01:37:42,780
spoke to me

899
01:37:44,500 --> 01:37:45,830
about his supreme move -

900
01:37:46,620 --> 01:37:48,610
Old Monkey Hangs up his Badge.

901
01:37:50,950 --> 01:37:52,910
He said the key to the move

902
01:37:54,450 --> 01:37:55,990
was turning back.

903
01:38:03,500 --> 01:38:04,740
At the time,

904
01:38:07,620 --> 01:38:09,080
I didn't get it.

905
01:38:13,330 --> 01:38:14,490
I thought

906
01:38:15,160 --> 01:38:16,870
he couldn't keep up with the times.

907
01:38:27,870 --> 01:38:29,700
The Gong Family legacy

908
01:38:32,000 --> 01:38:33,330
I return to you.

909
01:38:34,830 --> 01:38:36,490
Let's be clear.

910
01:38:37,700 --> 01:38:39,320
You didn't return it.

911
01:38:40,830 --> 01:38:43,160
I took it back myself.

912
01:39:44,250 --> 01:39:45,660
Miss Gong!

913
01:40:08,790 --> 01:40:10,320
Miss Gong!

914
01:40:30,580 --> 01:40:35,490
(1952. Hong Kong. White Rose Barber Shop.)

915
01:40:46,040 --> 01:40:47,370
Sorry.

916
01:40:48,700 --> 01:40:50,070
I miss my mom.

917
01:40:53,620 --> 01:40:56,360
You got my notice about the memorial?

918
01:40:56,950 --> 01:40:58,410
Yes.

919
01:41:01,200 --> 01:41:03,030
Open a business, follow the rules.

920
01:41:04,410 --> 01:41:05,620
It's the same everywhere.

921
01:41:07,450 --> 01:41:09,110
Do you know how much weight

922
01:41:10,200 --> 01:41:11,820
a summons from me carries?

923
01:41:15,160 --> 01:41:16,370
It's measured in gold.

924
01:41:18,250 --> 01:41:21,740
Brother, I've got the money.

925
01:41:22,750 --> 01:41:24,030
And I've got my life.

926
01:41:25,830 --> 01:41:27,410
Whichever is worth more,

927
01:41:28,290 --> 01:41:29,280
take it.

928
01:41:35,950 --> 01:41:37,490
I like those eyes of yours.

929
01:41:39,790 --> 01:41:41,150
They remind me of my mom's.

930
01:41:41,410 --> 01:41:43,200
Want both? Or just one?

931
01:41:43,910 --> 01:41:45,150
Not so fast.

932
01:41:47,700 --> 01:41:48,780
How about,

933
01:41:50,450 --> 01:41:52,070
you do the honors?

934
01:41:54,040 --> 01:41:55,490
Forget it.

935
01:41:57,040 --> 01:41:58,530
You're a real man.

936
01:42:01,700 --> 01:42:03,110
It's the anniversary of my mom's death.

937
01:42:04,160 --> 01:42:06,280
I'll leave you those two lamps of yours.

938
01:42:07,500 --> 01:42:09,910
As the rivers flow, we'll meet again.

939
01:42:11,080 --> 01:42:12,490
I'll take my leave.

940
01:42:14,830 --> 01:42:16,110
Want the money -

941
01:42:17,330 --> 01:42:19,320
there're rules for that too.

942
01:42:19,500 --> 01:42:21,410
What use are rules?

943
01:42:21,750 --> 01:42:23,030
Keep it simple.

944
01:42:23,040 --> 01:42:25,150
I stab you three times then you stab me.

945
01:42:25,160 --> 01:42:26,400
How common.

946
01:42:26,410 --> 01:42:28,200
Then raise the tone.

947
01:42:32,790 --> 01:42:34,400
See that chair over there?

948
01:42:35,700 --> 01:42:37,570
If I can't plant your ass there,

949
01:42:38,450 --> 01:42:41,240
keep the cash.

950
01:42:44,250 --> 01:42:46,580
You're kidding, aren't you?

951
01:43:20,660 --> 01:43:21,900
Brother,

952
01:43:23,370 --> 01:43:25,950
here's your prayer money.

953
01:43:27,330 --> 01:43:28,820
Next time you'll be joining your mom.

954
01:43:29,370 --> 01:43:30,830
Off you go.

955
01:43:32,830 --> 01:43:34,160
To tell the truth,

956
01:43:35,300 --> 01:43:38,100
your eyes like my father.

957
01:43:38,410 --> 01:43:39,650
Take me as a disciple!

958
01:43:40,200 --> 01:43:41,360
Teach you?

959
01:43:42,160 --> 01:43:43,870
It'd be a waste of my time.

960
01:43:47,660 --> 01:43:49,620
That's speaking honestly too.

961
01:44:01,500 --> 01:44:03,030
Just a few pointers?

962
01:44:24,500 --> 01:44:26,830
(That same year, The Razor began teaching.)

963
01:44:26,830 --> 01:44:30,570
(Baji kungfu came to Hong Kong.)

964
01:44:48,620 --> 01:44:52,570
In 1952, Gong Er stopped seeing patients.

965
01:44:53,370 --> 01:44:56,410
Some say her old injury drove her to opium.

966
01:44:56,830 --> 01:44:59,190
Others that she was obsessed with kungfu.

967
01:45:00,330 --> 01:45:03,320
I last saw her at a teahouse.

968
01:45:43,790 --> 01:45:45,150
Do you know this opera?

969
01:45:46,660 --> 01:45:48,570
I think I heard it before in Foshan.

970
01:45:50,160 --> 01:45:51,370
Something about a dream.

971
01:45:51,620 --> 01:45:52,990
"A Dream of Love".

972
01:45:55,790 --> 01:45:57,570
Love is just that, a dream.

973
01:45:58,830 --> 01:46:00,320
It's said

974
01:46:00,910 --> 01:46:03,950
no instrument is as lovely as a voice.

975
01:46:05,160 --> 01:46:08,650
Words always sound better sung.

976
01:46:08,660 --> 01:46:10,200
Has Miss Gong studied opera?

977
01:46:10,200 --> 01:46:11,490
Just the basics.

978
01:46:18,700 --> 01:46:24,490
Back then if I'd put my mind to it,

979
01:46:25,830 --> 01:46:27,740
I'd be an opera star.

980
01:46:28,290 --> 01:46:31,910
All those tales, happy and sad...

981
01:46:33,370 --> 01:46:35,200
If I tired of "Yang Family Women Generals",

982
01:46:36,160 --> 01:46:38,320
I'd sing "Waking from a Dream".

983
01:46:39,870 --> 01:46:40,990
Think of it -

984
01:46:43,160 --> 01:46:46,480
me on stage, you in the audience,

985
01:46:48,830 --> 01:46:50,740
meeting that way.

986
01:46:52,410 --> 01:46:53,700
Wouldn't that be something?

987
01:46:54,660 --> 01:46:56,320
But what if it was sold out?

988
01:46:57,540 --> 01:46:58,990
You flatter me.

989
01:47:00,080 --> 01:47:02,870
If you came, I'd save you a seat.

990
01:47:04,410 --> 01:47:08,330
You've performed well in the opera of life.

991
01:47:08,330 --> 01:47:10,990
You have both timing and skill.

992
01:47:11,290 --> 01:47:12,990
Unfortunately,

993
01:47:14,160 --> 01:47:15,320
you never saw beyond your role.

994
01:47:18,700 --> 01:47:20,660
I'd no idea you watched me like an opera.

995
01:47:23,700 --> 01:47:25,070
This opera of mine,

996
01:47:25,910 --> 01:47:27,740
applauded or not,

997
01:47:28,330 --> 01:47:29,940
will play on to the end.

998
01:47:33,660 --> 01:47:35,280
I asked you

999
01:47:36,040 --> 01:47:37,870
here to bring things to a close

1000
01:47:38,500 --> 01:47:39,950
and say what needs to be said.

1001
01:47:40,540 --> 01:47:41,700
Are you going somewhere?

1002
01:47:47,330 --> 01:47:49,110
We have a saying in the North -

1003
01:47:50,200 --> 01:47:53,160
a tiger never quits the mountain.

1004
01:47:54,830 --> 01:47:58,900
We've both been living on foreign soil.

1005
01:48:01,620 --> 01:48:03,240
I'm so very tired.

1006
01:48:04,450 --> 01:48:05,690
I want to go home.

1007
01:48:09,040 --> 01:48:12,110
But I wanted to return this to you first.

1008
01:48:29,790 --> 01:48:31,070
As for the 64 Hands,

1009
01:48:34,330 --> 01:48:35,990
I've already forgotten them.

1010
01:48:42,540 --> 01:48:47,860
I was lucky to meet you in my prime.

1011
01:48:52,540 --> 01:48:54,070
Sadly, my time is running out.

1012
01:48:56,450 --> 01:49:00,150
To say there are no regrets in life,

1013
01:49:01,330 --> 01:49:03,320
is just to fool yourself.

1014
01:49:05,000 --> 01:49:09,660
How boring it would be without regrets.

1015
01:49:17,500 --> 01:49:20,820
Mr. Ip, to tell you the truth,

1016
01:49:24,160 --> 01:49:26,070
I cared about you.

1017
01:49:35,160 --> 01:49:37,200
I don't mind telling you that.

1018
01:49:38,790 --> 01:49:40,240
It's not a crime to love.

1019
01:49:45,370 --> 01:49:47,450
But that's all it can ever be.

1020
01:49:52,200 --> 01:49:54,070
I never said that to anyone before.

1021
01:49:56,830 --> 01:49:58,320
Seeing you tonight,

1022
01:49:59,410 --> 01:50:01,370
I don't know why, it just came out.

1023
01:50:09,290 --> 01:50:11,150
Let's say we suspend this game

1024
01:50:11,500 --> 01:50:13,830
of chess between us.

1025
01:50:21,660 --> 01:50:23,030
Take care.

1026
01:50:34,450 --> 01:50:36,990
In life, as in chess,

1027
01:50:37,660 --> 01:50:39,530
a move once made stays on the board.

1028
01:50:43,000 --> 01:50:44,200
What we have

1029
01:50:45,750 --> 01:50:46,990
is simply fate.

1030
01:50:54,200 --> 01:50:55,570
Your father once said,

1031
01:50:57,000 --> 01:50:59,780
never give up the faith.

1032
01:51:00,500 --> 01:51:01,990
Keep the light burning.

1033
01:51:05,290 --> 01:51:06,650
I hope that one day

1034
01:51:06,910 --> 01:51:09,280
I'll see the 64 Hands once more.

1035
01:52:14,750 --> 01:52:19,690
My father said mastery had three stages -

1036
01:52:21,540 --> 01:52:22,820
being,

1037
01:52:24,000 --> 01:52:25,080
knowing,

1038
01:52:26,700 --> 01:52:28,410
doing.

1039
01:52:31,370 --> 01:52:32,990
I know myself.

1040
01:52:35,000 --> 01:52:36,450
I've seen the world.

1041
01:52:42,160 --> 01:52:43,780
Sadly, I can't pass on what I know.

1042
01:52:50,660 --> 01:52:52,320
This is a road

1043
01:52:53,370 --> 01:52:54,830
I won't see to the end.

1044
01:52:58,500 --> 01:53:00,530
I hope you will.

1045
01:53:23,540 --> 01:53:25,280
Is this street of schools

1046
01:53:26,620 --> 01:53:28,450
all the Martial World has come to be?

1047
01:55:27,250 --> 01:55:31,320
A great age offers a choice:

1048
01:55:31,910 --> 01:55:34,570
stay or move on.

1049
01:55:35,830 --> 01:55:38,410
I choose to remain in my era,

1050
01:55:39,330 --> 01:55:41,320
the times when I was happiest.

1051
01:55:42,450 --> 01:55:45,900
(In 1953, Gong Er died in Hong Kong.)

1052
01:55:45,910 --> 01:55:49,030
(She kept her vows)

1053
01:55:49,040 --> 01:55:53,280
(to the end.)

1054
01:56:06,910 --> 01:56:09,820
Tomorrow I take Miss Gong's coffin home.

1055
01:56:11,200 --> 01:56:12,660
She left this for you.

1056
01:56:15,160 --> 01:56:19,660
In imperial times I was an executioner.

1057
01:56:21,660 --> 01:56:25,700
The Republic left me out of a job.

1058
01:56:27,040 --> 01:56:29,450
Had Master Gong not taken me in,

1059
01:56:30,580 --> 01:56:32,660
I'd have landed in the gutter like a dog.

1060
01:56:35,160 --> 01:56:37,700
He never looked down on me.

1061
01:56:38,620 --> 01:56:41,280
He made me his daughter's guardian.

1062
01:56:42,200 --> 01:56:44,990
My fierceness would protect her.

1063
01:56:45,000 --> 01:56:48,440
He nicknamed me Lucky Star,

1064
01:56:51,580 --> 01:56:57,370
so fortune would shine on her always.

1065
01:57:05,830 --> 01:57:07,320
For a woman,

1066
01:57:07,700 --> 01:57:09,990
taking vows is a kind of death.

1067
01:57:14,000 --> 01:57:15,610
To avenge her father,

1068
01:57:15,910 --> 01:57:19,910
she vowed never to marry or teach,

1069
01:57:20,330 --> 01:57:22,070
to remain single her whole life.

1070
01:57:23,910 --> 01:57:25,490
She kept that vow.

1071
01:57:32,330 --> 01:57:33,820
These are the ashes

1072
01:57:34,120 --> 01:57:37,660
from when she cut and burnt her hair.

1073
01:57:40,450 --> 01:57:44,650
She said she knew you a long time,

1074
01:57:45,750 --> 01:57:47,160
But you didn't really know her,

1075
01:57:47,750 --> 01:57:48,830
nor she you.

1076
01:57:52,200 --> 01:57:53,860
Seeing these ashes,

1077
01:57:57,080 --> 01:57:58,660
you'll understand her better.

1078
01:58:04,330 --> 01:58:05,610
Mr. Ip,

1079
01:58:06,830 --> 01:58:08,490
the Gong Family is through.

1080
01:58:09,000 --> 01:58:12,940
Miss Gong belongs to you now.

1081
01:59:17,910 --> 01:59:19,370
Like her father,

1082
01:59:19,830 --> 01:59:22,410
Gong Er never lost a fight.

1083
01:59:24,660 --> 01:59:27,950
She only ever lost to herself.

1084
01:59:53,250 --> 01:59:57,320
(1953. Ip Man gets his Hong Kong ID)

1085
01:59:57,330 --> 02:00:01,570
(after the border to China is shut.)

1086
02:00:30,040 --> 02:00:31,570
The day I left Foshan,

1087
02:00:32,250 --> 02:00:33,700
I wanted to say something

1088
02:00:34,830 --> 02:00:36,280
but couldn't speak the words.

1089
02:00:38,080 --> 02:00:44,450
(My heart will carry me back to you.)

1090
02:01:16,500 --> 02:01:18,160
When I left her that time,

1091
02:01:18,410 --> 02:01:20,150
I thought I'd be able to return.

1092
02:01:20,540 --> 02:01:23,030
But it was the last time I saw her.

1093
02:01:24,500 --> 02:01:26,580
After that I only had the path ahead.

1094
02:01:26,580 --> 02:01:27,780
There was no turning back,

1095
02:01:29,660 --> 02:01:30,990
and no road home.

1096
02:01:34,160 --> 02:01:37,480
(In 1960, Zhang Yongcheng died of illness.)

1097
02:01:37,500 --> 02:01:40,110
(Ip Man never returned to Foshan.)

1098
02:02:44,160 --> 02:02:46,370
Okay, begin.

1099
02:02:49,700 --> 02:02:50,610
Left fist

1100
02:02:50,620 --> 02:02:51,610
out,

1101
02:02:51,910 --> 02:02:52,990
palm open,

1102
02:02:53,000 --> 02:02:54,330
turn the wrist,

1103
02:02:54,660 --> 02:02:55,650
pull back,

1104
02:02:55,660 --> 02:02:56,820
right fist,

1105
02:02:56,830 --> 02:02:57,820
out,

1106
02:02:57,830 --> 02:02:58,820
open,

1107
02:02:58,830 --> 02:02:59,940
twist the wrist,

1108
02:02:59,950 --> 02:03:01,320
pull back.

1109
02:03:13,160 --> 02:03:14,370
Mr. Ip,

1110
02:03:15,660 --> 02:03:17,150
all encounters in this world

1111
02:03:18,290 --> 02:03:20,030
are a kind of reunion.

1112
02:04:17,160 --> 02:04:20,480
They say I popularized Wing Chun.

1113
02:04:20,830 --> 02:04:22,360
I hope they're right.

1114
02:04:22,830 --> 02:04:24,440
I never did it for fame.

1115
02:04:24,450 --> 02:04:26,410
The martial arts belong to all.

1116
02:04:26,950 --> 02:04:28,490
We're all on the same quest.

1117
02:04:29,290 --> 02:04:31,320
It all comes down to those two words -

1118
02:04:31,700 --> 02:04:33,320
Horizontal. Vertical.

1119
02:05:50,450 --> 02:05:55,150
(Ip Man was a huge inspiration to others. Because of him,)

1120
02:05:55,160 --> 02:06:01,410
(the torch of Wing Chun has been carried around the world.)

