-Come on, Mandy, you can do it!
-Hit a homer!
Easy now!
Come on, back up, back up!
Back up, back up!
Well, fans, it's the bottom of
the ninth and bases are loaded.
And guess who
the orphans have at bat?
That's right,
it's the homerun queen herself,
the belter from the shelter,
-Miss Amanda...
-Amanda Lemmon!
-What?
-I'm gonna kill you!
Didn't I tell you not to
play ball in that dress?
Oh, come on, Diane,
I ain't gonna hurt it.
It's time for your interview.
Now drop the bat, let's go!
Just let me smash
this ball downtown, okay?
All right, you got 10 seconds.
Otherwise, the game is gonna be
called on account of bloodshed.
Come on, Frankie,
I gotta go to Staten Island.
Staten Island? What about camp?
You'll miss the bus!
I won't either.
It's just a look-see.
They're not trying to place you
with the Butkis' are they?
So what if they are?
You ever met those people?
That family collects kids.
They'll take anybody.
Even the rejects like you.
Shut up, Frankie.
At least I got an interview.
And Amanda Butkis
steps to the plate.
Come on, Amanda!
Hit me in!
Come on, relay, relay!
Over here!
-Come on, come on. Hop in.
-Man, it was a grand slam.
Hey, Diane, see if they
want a little boy.
You know, me and her,
two-for-one?
What am I, on sale? Get your own.
Staten Island, please.
You're out! We win!
Amanda never touched home base!
Yeah!
You're a dead man, Frankie!
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
Okay, so, you know,
it's not exactly Park Avenue,
but you can't always judge a book
by the cover.
Besides, you don't wanna be
an orphan forever.
So adopt me, why don't ya?
They won't let me adopt you
on my salary.
Besides that, you know what?
You deserve a mother
and a father.
So get a husband.
It's not like buying
a car, you know.
I know. It's gotta be that
can't-eat, can't-sleep,
reach-for-the-stars,
over-the-fence,
World Series kind of stuff.
Right?
Well, a girl's gotta
have her standards.
Well, I got mine and I say...
...let's blow off these people.
Gum. Hat.
Other gum.
Now look, I know
these people have a stupid name.
But they really like kids, okay?
Put on a smile.
Sell it, girl.
Why do I always
gotta wear a dress?
Because it makes you
look so pretty.
Oh, isn't she the most
precious thing?
-What a pretty little dress.
-She's a honey alright.
Look at that, Fanny,
she's got your mother's smile.
And your father's sense of humor.
-I'm sorry.
-That was very funny.
-Come on in.
-Come on, sweetie.
-Callaway, huh?
-Yeah.
Must be a real bigshot.
Oh, you'd be surprised how big.
All this for her?
Geez.
Welcome home, princess.
He forgot again, didn't he?
Oh, well, I'm afraid
your father's
been unavoidably detained.
But if it's any consolation,
I know an old butler
who's mighty glad to see you.
Oh, I'm sorry, Vincenzo.
How terribly rude of me.
I'm very glad to see you too.
Thank you, honey.
Hey, I see you've
been practicing.
Congratulations.
-What's the excuse this time?
-Your father?
Well, he's, uh...
He's preparing for your arrival
up at the summer house.
-Which one?
-On Lake Minocqua.
But that's been closed for years.
-He never goes up there.
-Well, he does now.
Oh, Vincenzo, you big fat fibber.
-What's going on?
-My lips are sealed.
You mean it's a surprise?
Oh, yeah, I suppose
you could put it that way.
It's a welcome home party for me!
Isn't it?
I knew Daddy was up to something.
Oh, well, now, Alyssa,
I didn't say...
Oh, Vincenzo, I won't tell.
I've never had a surprise party
my whole life.
Well, this will certainly
be a surprise.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, move it!
-I've got 43.
-Me too.
-Guess who's missing?
-Oh, come...
-Where's Amanda?
-She's not coming.
I'm gonna kill her.
Hey, slugger, s'up?
I'm not going to stupid camp.
Oh, yeah, I don't blame you.
Look at this place,
it's a pigsty.
Probably gonna take you the whole
week just to make your bed.
Don't joke, I'm serious.
I'm not joking.
That's why I sent the bus ahead
without us.
-Liar.
-Oh, yeah?
How much you wanna bet?
-50 bucks.
-Okay, so I didn't send the bus.
Cough it up.
But I will.
And then you and I
can just sit here
until you tell me
what's really wrong.
I'm not going to
stupid Butkis' either.
I was waiting for that one.
If they're the best I can do,
Frankie's right.
I am a reject.
You're not a reject.
It's just that most
people wanna adopt...
Babies. I know.
This orphan stuff is like
growing up in the dog pound.
Everybody wants a puppy.
Just once I'd like to
sleep in my own room.
Hey, come here a minute.
Listen to me.
You listening to me?
I'm gonna find you the best home
in the entire world.
That's a promise.
You don't make
promises, remember?
I didn't say I don't
make promises.
I said I don't make promises
I can't keep.
There's a big difference.
Now... Can we please go to camp?
Please?
-Please, please, please...
-Okay, okay, okay!
Okay, okay, okay!
But you still owe me 50 bucks.
Oh, Vincenzo, it's gorgeous!
I think this house is going to be
my favorite.
Yeah, I remember
many happy years here.
-Hey! There she is!
-Oh, Daddy!
Come over here! My little...
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
You're not Alyssa Callaway.
Alyssa Callaway's a little girl
and you're a foot
taller than she is.
-It's me, honest.
-It is?
Honey, I've missed you so much.
I'm sorry I wasn't at the airport
to meet you.
That's okay. I knew it had to be
something really important.
Like... A party, maybe?
-She knows about the party?
-I didn't say a thing.
Vincenzo didn't tell me.
I figured it out on my own.
I should've let you surprise me,
but I'm too excited.
You are?
It's still on, isn't it?
Yes, of course it's
still on, sweetheart, but...
are we talking about
the same party?
Oh, Roger! She's darling!
Alyssa, I would like you to meet
a very good friend of mine,
Clarice Kensington.
Hello, Miss Kensington,
how do you do?
What a perfect little girl.
Roger, I'm absolutely smitten!
You and I are going
to be great friends.
Are you here for my party?
Your party?
Roger, don't tell me
you haven't told her.
Told me what?
Sweetheart,
the party is not for...
Another couple of hours.
So, let's get you
settled in there, princess.
Yes, why don't you do that.
I'm sure you two have
lots to talk about.
He didn't tell her, I can't
believe he didn't tell her.
Maybe he wanted to
give her the good news in person.
I'm sorry,
did I say something to you?
Remember to bring your own bag.
Everybody off!
Yo, Carmen, you blind?
What?
Girl, when you gonna get a life?
Miss Kensington seems nice.
Does she work with you?
Not exactly.
Hey, I got something to show you.
Right up here.
You see there, across the lake?
That's Camp Callaway.
That was your mom's
favorite project.
So, is she from the camp?
Who?
Miss Kensington.
Uh, sweetheart, I gotta have
a little talk with you.
You know, Alyssa,
a lot's happened
while you were gone.
And you know I haven't been
able to come up to this house
since Mom passed away.
But there comes a time
when a person has to move on.
You're getting older and...
...and there's just so much
a father can do without help.
-We have Vincenzo, he helps us.
-That's right, he does.
And he's been
a good friend to this family
for a long time, but...
...what I think
our family really needs is a...
Excuse me.
Telephone, boss,
it's a board meeting.
Oh, let me,
let me call them back...
They said it was urgent.
I'm with my...
-Will you forgive me?
-Don't I always?
It's so good to have you home.
-It's on two? Okay.
-Yeah.
Hey, young lady.
Summer vacation, official.
Go play.
-Will you come with me?
-Oh, gee,
I wish I could, princess.
But I'm afraid
I got a lot of work to do, sorry.
Wow. Check it out!
Buckingham Palace!
That's in London, brainless.
It's the Callaway house.
Nobody's lived there for years.
It's haunted.
-It's not either.
-Ask anyone.
Every full moon,
old lady Callaway's ghost
crosses the lake
and eats one of the campers.
Yeah, right,
and Santa Claus lives
with the Tooth Fairy in Queens.
-You ever been over there?
-No.
If you're so sure
it's not haunted,
why don't you go over there
and ring the doorbell?
-Think I'm scared?
-5 bucks says you're chicken.
Cough it up, choir boy.
Show me your money.
Oh, this I gotta see.
I didn't even know they had
a caterer in the country.
Thank God.
They say the first Mrs. Callaway
was a lovely woman,
but look at this room.
No wonder the woman's dead,
she had absolutely no taste.
I can't wait to sell this house.
Now, Jules,
I want one bar set up in here
and two out in the patio...
Well hello, munchkin.
Oh, boy.
Daddy!
Honey? Honey, what's the matter?
What?
What, what? You all right?
No!
What? What happened?
She... She hates this house!
Oh... Let's not be dramatic,
darling.
She was hiding in the den
and I simply said
that we might, um...
Fix it up some day.
That is if you'll let me.
Who is she?
I guess there's no
easy way to say this.
Sweetheart... Clarice and I...
-...will be married next month.
-Wha...
You're finally gonna
have a real family.
And she's gonna be
your new mother.
Isn't that wonderful?
She does this sometimes.
-Honey. Honey, honey...
-And she gets away with it.
I'm sorry, Roger, but little
tantrums mustn't be rewarded.
Alyssa... come on, sweetheart.
Roger, you're only
making it worse.
I know what I'm talking about.
All right, people, back to work.
Let's focus on
the engagement party.
Sure hope you're right.
Trust me, I'm a woman.
Oh, look at the time.
I've got to get my face on.
How's about some
milk and cookies, huh?
I've lost my mother
and now I've lost my father.
I have no family. I'm an orphan.
And I'm running away
and don't you dare tell Daddy!
Come on, come on, we gotta hide.
-What if we get caught?
-Don't let her see ya.
-Who?
-Old lady Callaway.
There's no ghost.
Look at her.
She's nuts.
I won't go back.
I won't.
She's not the boss of me.
Vincenzo, have you seen Alyssa?
I'm under strict orders not to
tell you that she ran away.
Great, why didn't you stop her?
Well, I thought I'd give her
the benefit of a head start.
So she could reclaim
a little dignity, you know.
You'll make sure
she comes home okay?
Sure, don't worry.
Right away, boss.
Thanks, Vin.
It doesn't look haunted.
That's what
they want you to think, stupid.
Frankie, this isn't funny
anymore, let's get out of here.
Don't worry, she'll chicken out.
Go, go, go.
Well, if it isn't
a little orphan girl.
-Someone's home!
-We were just coming after you.
Look, I didn't mean nothing!
It was just a joke, you know?
Just kidding around, honest!
She didn't even scream.
Let's get you ready
for the big dinner, okay?
Big dinner? Listen, Lurch, you
don't want me, I'm too skinny.
There are other kids,
big fat ones, right outside.
Eat them.
What in the world
are you talking about?
Hey, Frankie...
...the full moon,
that's tonight, right?
Old lady Callaway's ghost?
It's her!
Guess you think
I'm pretty stupid, huh?
Nah, you're just a little
upset, that's all.
Looks like I just won 5 bucks.
So, when's this party?
Am I invited?
Your dress is upstairs on the
bed, cocktails are at 5:00.
Now, if you'll excuse me, please.
A dress? Me?
You gotta be kidding.
Nobody's even looking for me.
There you are.
I have been looking
everywhere for you.
You have?
Well, of course I have.
Let me ask you a question.
You did not come
all the way up here
to sit around
like a bump on a log, did you?
No...
I... I guess not.
Well then, come on, slugger,
they're playing football.
You're missing out
on all the fun.
Okay.
I thought, "Where is she?
What's happened to her?"
So I hear Amanda's
quite the jock.
Yeah, the kid's a natural.
Great speed.
Okay, student body left.
Everybody block for Amanda.
-On four. Ready?
-Break!
-Who's Amanda?
-Funny.
She's probably eating her liver
right now.
Do you think one camper's enough?
I mean, what if
she's still hungry?
Look!
Twenty-four, thirty-six,
hut, hut, hut, hut!
-Hey, I got it!
-Run!
You're going the wrong way.
Great speed.
Bad sense of direction.
Do you see... What I see?
I don't know what you see,
but what I see is me.
I see me too.
Does that mean
there's two of you?
Or... Or two of me?
Wow, there really is two of us.
Don't you find this odd?
No, this is weird.
This is really, really weird.
Wait a sec.
You live at the Callaway house.
And you're that girl from camp.
-They thought I was you.
Alyssa Callaway,
it's a pleasure to meet you.
Amanda, put her there.
No wonder that big penguin guy
asked me in.
Oh, that's Vincenzo,
he's our butler.
Who's the woman
with the dark, long hair?
I liked her.
Oh, that's Diane. We're buds.
She's pretty cool for a grown-up.
What the heck
were you doing over there anyway?
I... I wanted to see
what it was like to be an orphan.
What? Why?
Because it looked like fun.
Fun being an orphan?
What's the matter with you?
So why were you at my house?
I was... Just...
I was just ringing the doorbell.
What for?
Because kids think
that place is haunted.
That's stupid.
Yeah? Well then,
who's that scary blond lady?
She's absolutely horrid.
If I were you,
I'd get rid of her.
-Any suggestions?
-You're talking to a pro here.
I've driven away more possible
parents than you'll ever meet.
Don't you want a family?
Girl's gotta have her standards.
So tell me something, this party.
You really don't wanna go?
I'd rather eat dirt.
Okay, so listen.
You be me, I'll be you.
One night only.
Tomorrow at noon, we switch back.
-What do you say?
-That's wonderful.
That way,
you can scare off Clarice for me.
Only, don't be such
a goody-goody.
You know, I got
a reputation to protect.
I scored a touchdown, didn't I?
Okay, just don't talk so good.
Use lousy English, like...
"Ain't ya never gonna wanna don't
ya have to go to the bathroom?"
That sort of thing.
You ain't got nothing
to worry about.
I say, you do catch
on rather quickly.
-Stables, noon.
-Yes.
Woo... Close!
Miss Kensington says "fashionably
late" was an hour ago.
What seems to be the problem?
I'm a hairdresser,
not a zookeeper.
What in the name of God
is going on here?
Hi, Vinny. I mean, Vincenzo.
I got... Distracted.
Uh, you don't have to apologize.
Really?
Cool.
I mean, it's just that
I'm so terribly relived
that you aren't pissed.
Pissed, miss?
Uh, look. Um, why don't you...
Why don't you get
dressed, please?
And let... Let Carlo do
your hair, all right?
I liked it better
when she fainted.
This is really good!
Well, of course it is, silly.
It's your favorite.
It is?
Oh, yes, of course. The, um...
Um... big, gooey, messy burger.
Also known as a Sloppy Joe.
Sloppy Joe, right.
Your favorite?
Yes, and with dern good reason.
Did you just say "dern"?
I haven't seen you in so long.
Hello. Good evening.
-Good evening.
-How swell of you to come.
-So nice to see you.
-Nice to see you.
-Like my dress?
-Very nice.
Escargot, Miss Callaway?
Why, thank you, waiter person.
I'm starving.
I mean, I'd adore one.
This tastes like a balloon.
It's snails, miss.
Good.
Nice.
Chewy.
All this money
and these people eat slugs?
Well, look who's finally decided
to grace us with her presence.
Clarice, right?
You looked better with the mask.
I beg your pardon.
Alyssa.
Clarice has been regaling us with
your many accomplishments
at the Academy.
Might we entice you
to play something?
Of course, I'd be delighted.
Whatever did you have in mind?
Checkers, dodgeball?
No, no, dear girl.
Muffy was referring to the piano.
-But...
-Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your attention,
please?
Before we sit down to dinner,
my future step-daughter,
whom I absolutely adore,
has consented to play
one of the pieces
that won her first prize at the
Windsor Academy Youth recital.
Hold it, time out.
I can't play the piano.
But I just told everyone
that you would.
Then do me a grand favor
and un-tell them.
Look, you little...
If you embarrass me
in front of all these people,
I'll make sure that
you never play anything...
...ever again.
Have I made myself clear?
Clear as glass.
In fact, I can see
right through you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
normally I'd be tickled
to play a selection from...
...Chopin. But in honor
of my new stepmother,
whom I absolutely adore...
I decided to play
a little something of my own.
You think maybe
my daughter's asking
for a little bit of attention?
I'd say she's demanding it.
A shark! Shark!
Fin! Huckleberry Finn!
Yeah, that's it! You got it!
Oh, man, the guys are ahead of us
by eight seconds.
Okay, Amanda, it's your turn.
You're up. Go, girl.
-Me?
-You're the best.
Show them what you got.
Come on.
Amanda!
Look at her, she's nervous.
Yeah, so?
I thought Amanda
wasn't scared of nothing.
What am I supposed to do?
Ready. Set. Go!
Song!
What? What happened?
London Bridge is Falling Down!
That's it!
You may enter.
-Mind if we talk?
-What ever about?
Clarice.
Hey. Hey, hey!
None of that. She was very upset
with your performance
this evening.
Now, don't you think
you should give her a chance?
I did. And she's a big
phony-baloney if you ask me.
I've never heard you
this outspoken.
Wouldn't it be nice
to have a mother?
Yeah, and it'd be nice
to have a father too.
-But I... I mean...
-No, sweetheart,
I think the person
you're really angry at... is me.
You?
-What'd you do?
-Well, I...
I haven't been much
of a father lately.
I've been working
and I haven't seen you. And...
But you know what?
All that's gonna change.
Because Clarice is going back
to the city tomorrow.
Gee, I hope it was nothing I did.
No, no, no. She's got
a wedding to plan.
But that means you
and I are gonna
get to spend some time together.
Get to know each other again.
Is that okay?
Yeah? Good.
Let's tuck you in,
you little snuggler.
-I'll see you tomorrow.
-Okay.
Good night, honey.
Hey.
I like having a father.
Well, I like having a daughter.
Good night, sweetie.
Lights out!
Lights out, cabin three.
Come on, come on,
this I gotta see.
We're gonna get caught,
I just know it.
Come on, Frankie,
it's a full moon.
Shut up, stupid.
Zombies hear better than dogs.
It's a frog!
Amanda, scared of a frog?
She's changed all right.
Now do you believe me?
Yeah, she's one of them
vampire people.
Let's get out of here!
A frog, huh?
Well, you know what?
You should've kissed it.
It might've turned out to be
Prince Charming.
Gross.
Not for you, for me.
You've kissed a frog?
No, toads are my specialty.
Big, old, ugly suckers
with tongues like this.
-It is not.
-It is too.
How else do you think
I'm gonna catch a guy, huh?
I don't know. I don't know.
Okay.
There's that smile.
And that time I think it went
all the way up to your eyes.
You remind me of someone.
I do? Who?
Someone I've never met.
Well, how can I do that
if you've never met her?
Sometimes, when I dream,
I think I see her.
You know, you've been acting just
a little bit weirdo today, kiddo.
I think maybe
it's all this fresh air.
Don't make fun.
Sorry.
It's just that usually,
you're such a tough guy.
-Don't tell anyone, okay?
-Scout's honor.
I mean, after all, I wouldn't
want to spoil my reputation none.
None.
I've got an idea.
Let's go spy on the boys.
Safe trip, honey.
Oh my God!
How was the party?
Well, the good news is,
Clarice is gone.
You did it!
The bad news is,
she'll be back in a week.
Oh, you didn't.
So what's a cool guy
like your dad doing with
a witch like her anyway?
It's too bad he didn't
meet Diane first.
Now she's awesome.
Yeah, they'd be perfect
for each other.
You're not thinking what
I hope you're not thinking.
Wanna bet?
But he's getting
married next month.
So, all they gotta
do is meet once.
Then they'll fall in
love for sure.
How do you know?
Because Diane says when it
happens, it happens like that.
Okay, so look,
you go back to Diane
and I'll go back to your dad.
Wait, why not
the other way around?
Because you know what he likes
and I know what she likes.
They need all the help
they can get.
But how are we going to
get them together?
I can't believe I let
you talk me into this.
You're too tense. Relax.
Oh, I got 1,000 pounds
of wild animal
under my butt and
she says "Relax".
Just move with the horse
and you'll be fine.
Now when did you become an expert
all of a sudden?
Ain't you never seen a Western?
Honey, the last Western I saw
was an omelet.
Look at your form, young lady.
What happened to those
equestrian classes you took?
Are you asking me equestrian?
Come on, I'll race
you to the lake.
No, no. Slow is good.
I like to enjoy the scenery.
I've got spurs
that jingle jangle jingle
As I ride merrily along
Hey, we're doing
a good job, aren't we?
I think I'm finally
getting the hang of this.
Hey!
I'm getting the hang of this!
Oh, come on, Amanda,
my voice isn't that bad!
Oh, well.
I've been in the desert
on a horse with no name
Feels good to get out of the rain
Not only is she an excellent
rider, she's a gourmet cook.
She paints. She speaks
four languages.
You know, honey, you could
learn a lot from Clarice.
Alyssa, there's a...
Alyssa.
Alyssa?
Honey?
Come here, come here.
I'm jiggling
Where is that girl?
Did you bring it?
Whoa, bud.
Somebody, turn this thing off!
Wow.
Alyssa!
Stop this right now!
I'm telling you!
Step on it!
Help me! Somebody!
-Step on it!
-Yeah!
Oh, God! Please!
Oh, dear. Oh, my.
Help!
Help me!
Somebody help me!
Hang on.
Hang on! Hang on!
-Help me, someone!
-Hang on. Slow down, girl.
Oh, God, don't talk to me,
talk to the horse.
I was talking to the horse.
Okay. It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay
No! I'm on a killer!
They gave me a killer horse!
Relax, it's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
Okay.
You okay?
Lord Almighty, I about dropped
my transmission back there.
Ah, well,
if it's any consolation,
I used to look like
a real jerk on a horse.
How many fingers here, cowboy?
-Six.
-Close enough.
-Can you stand?
-Yeah.
I'm not sure which is more
bruised, my butt or my ego.
You should have somebody
take a look at that.
-My butt?
-No.
That cut right there.
-Sorry.
-Oh, great.
You know what? We have first
aid over at the camp.
Well, thanks,
I just live over here.
Are you Roger Callaway?
-I... I think so.
-The Roger Callaway?
From the Callaway Foundation
for Kids?
Yeah, that's me.
I'm Diane Barrows. You know,
I always wanted to meet you.
My kids just love your camp.
Oh, yeah? You... You have kids?
Well, they're not mine,
I work for the East Side
Children's Center in Manhattan
and we're here for a week.
Yeah, of course.
Well, it was very nice
to meet you, Mr. Callaway.
-Roger, please.
-Roger.
Oh, and, and thank you
for saving my life.
And you really should put
some iodine on your butt.
Cut.
-Miss Barrows.
-Diane.
Diane, uh, I was wondering
if I could offer you
some, uh, iced tea or something.
I'd love to hear more about the
camp and how it's all going.
Only if we can walk.
You took the words
right out of my mouth.
-Yes!
-Come on.
-Now lay still.
-Yeah.
You certainly are
an angel of mercy, Miss Barrows.
Oh, I see worse cuts
than this every day.
Thanks, Vincenzo.
My gang's always inventing
new ways to get hurt.
You must really love children.
Well, what's not to love?
You big baby. Come here.
Is that better?
Yeah.
I can't hear anything.
We've gotta get closer.
You know, um... you're not
at all what I expected.
Yeah. What were you expecting?
Well, blue blood, for one thing.
I sort of thought you'd be
some rich, big, old, fat geezer
who smokes cigars.
Really? No, I made my money
the old-fashioned way.
-Pure dumb luck.
-I doubt that.
Nope, I swear to God.
About 12 years ago,
a cellular phone
was just something
out of Star Trek.
But I thought it was pretty cool
so... I bought the airspace.
-Get out!
-Yeah.
Oh, my God. Uh, that... that's
like money out of thin air.
You'll notice I don't carry one.
I hate the damn things.
Excuse me, Miss Kensington, boss.
She insists.
Excuse me, it's my...
Miss Kensington.
Hi, Clarice, how you doing?
How am I doing?
Please. Honey, look, honey...
Do you have any idea
what your daughter has done?
-No, what?
-She spit...
Gum? In your hair?
-Are you sure?
-Am I sure?
Oh, my God, you should see it!
Well, I'm certain it
wasn't intentional.
Look, of course,
you've had a rough day.
No, no...
..."rough" is
a broken nail, darling.
What I've had is a train wreck!
Look, just try to calm down,
I'll speak to her...
You know what, Roger? Excuse me,
I think I'm just gonna go now.
Just one second,
one second, please.
Wait, Roger. Is there a woman
there with you, Roger?
Yes, there's sort
of a woman here,
she's from the camp
across the lake.
How delightful.
I'm in the middle of a crisis
and you're having
a bachelor party.
I'm in a meeting, that's all.
It's just a meeting.
Look, no, we're not
gonna have dinner.
There's nothing gonna go on...
Please...
I'll see you at
the end of the week.
Okay. Me too. Bye-bye.
I'm so sorry...
Sorry about that.
But she squeezed me so hard,
it just sort of popped out.
Uh-huh.
Don't think
she likes me very much.
Sweetheart, she's been looking
forward to meeting
you for months.
Do you have any idea how much
she loves children?
No. Do you?
Well... come to think of it,
you are the first kid
I've ever seen her with.
But I'm sure it's a whole bunch.
And you love her, right?
Well... yes.
Like that can't-eat, can't-sleep,
reach-for-the-stars,
over-the-fence
World Series kind of stuff?
Is that what it says
in the dictionary?
And you're marrying her
because Alyssa needs...
I mean, I, I need a mother.
Honey, I think that's
enough questions for today.
Wait. I only got one left.
Let's have it.
Who was that pretty woman
out on the patio?
The Roger Callaway?
On a white horse, no less.
So?
So, he comes riding up,
saves my life.
He's probably worth
a billion dollars.
He's totally cute.
Oh, my God, he's so cute.
And to top it all off,
he's, honest to God, a nice guy.
And I'm just stupid enough
to think he's available.
-Isn't he?
-No.
Is too!
How would you know?
Was he wearing a ring?
Look, even if he was available,
he wouldn't be interested in me.
You shouldn't put yourself down.
Guys like him like
girls with food names.
Cookie, Muffin, Candy.
They don't marry girls like me.
He did once.
What is this,
published somewhere?
Her name was Kathy and she wasn't
a food, she was a teacher.
He's even more perfect
than I thought.
I'm cheating,
give me one of those.
Give me that stick.
Vincenzo?
Do you believe in magic?
You mean like card tricks?
No. Sparks between two people.
The thing that happens
when you least expect it.
Why do you ask?
I... I no reason, just...
It's been so long
since Kathy and...
I just didn't think
it could happen to me again.
Well, that Miss Kensington
is really something.
Well, actually...
...that's not who I meant.
Yeah, I know.
Well, you're my best man.
Aren't you supposed
to come up with
some words of wisdom
right about now?
Why don't you go for a drive?
See where you end up.
Where's he going?
Hey, Vinny!
It's the home office.
The Butkis' want Amanda.
The paperwork just went through.
Well...
Hi, who the hell is this?
Oh, yeah? Well, this
is Diane Barrows.
And since when does your
department okay an adoption
without the case worker's report?
Yeah, I know
these people are nice.
Yes. Yes. Look, have you
ever met those people?
These people collect kids,
they will take anybody.
Excuse me, can you tell me
where Diane Barrows is, please?
-I think she's in the office.
-Come on, let's go!
Let me just run this by you
one more time, okay?
Just, please, just...
Just hear me out one more time.
Okay, I know I don't make that
much money and I know that...
Um, I'm a little bit single,
but I want to adopt Amanda.
No! I... Are you laughing at me?
He's laughing at me!
You... You stupid jerk!
-Diane?
-What?
It's you.
Did I come at a bad time?
A bad time for a "meeting"?
No, I'm just having a little
problem with one of my kids.
Is there anything
I can do to help?
You've already saved my life,
Mr. Callaway.
What can I do for you?
I would like to apologize
for yesterday.
It was very rude. I never
should have taken that call
and I would like to
make it up to you.
Okay, then give me your car.
Well, perhaps we could discuss it
over lunch
at a little pizza
joint I saw in town.
Oh, I'm sorry. I can't.
I understand.
Maybe some other time then.
No, it's not like that.
It's that I'm on duty today
in the mess hall.
-It's my kids' turn to serve.
-Oh, I see.
But, you know what?
If your heart's set on Italian,
you could join us.
We're having macaroni and cheese.
Still come with a peach cobbler?
Oh, yeah. All you can eat.
Muffy, darling, Craig can
meet the President on Sunday.
I need bridesmaids.
You must come.
Fabulous!
There's my other line. Gotta
go, love you, mean it, ciao.
Hello? Bernard.
Bernard, why do you keep
bothering me with numbers?
It's my wedding.
Whatever it costs, just get it!
It's a cozy little spot.
When was the last time
you were here?
It must be 10 years.
-Ten years?
-Yeah.
What'd you do, build the camp
and then never come back?
No, it was my wife's idea.
She had a very, very big heart.
Had?
She passed away
when Alyssa was born.
Sorry.
I just never could come back.
Until now, that is.
Here you go.
Hi, Carmen. Where's Amanda?
I don't know. One minute she's
behind me and the next...
Will you get her for me, please?
I want to introduce her
to someone.
Sure.
I'm having the hardest time
keeping tabs on this girl.
She keeps running off.
Tell me about it.
I got one just like her at home.
-What are you doing?
-I'm...
Uh... cleaning this window.
Look at it, it's filthy.
Diane wants to see you, come on.
But... But... I...
Hey, where you
going with my hat?
Do something, Alyssa.
Here she comes now.
My compliments to the chef.
Amanda, take that thing off.
Let her keep it on.
For all we know,
it might be the latest thing.
Excuse me, ma'am...
...did you just snort?
I suppose you think
this is funny.
Well, maybe you'll get
a little chuckle out of this.
You wouldn't dare.
Food fight!
That was great!
I couldn't have done
it better myself.
I almost had a heart attack.
I... I guess that's what they
mean by "eat and run", huh?
We need doggy bags.
Damn, look at me,
I'm covered in cobbler.
Well, you look good in peach.
Actually, leave it.
I may still be hungry.
I can't believe you hit
me with the butter.
I didn't start it.
You just talked
to that short order
cook of yours.
Oh, yeah. Where is she anyway?
Look at your head.
You know, if you wanna
get cleaned up,
there's showers right over there.
You know, I've got a better idea.
Will you excuse me?
And maybe hold some of that?
Pardon me.
-What's wrong with him?
-Beats me.
I've never seen him
act like this.
I think he's gone mental.
He's got a lot on his mind.
Didn't your mother tell you
not to swim after you eat?
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
I got a cramp!
I can't swim!
No fair. I saved you.
It's too cold.
I'm not going in there.
Come on,
I don't wanna save you right now!
All right, buster,
you better be worth it.
Roger?
You're not funny.
Roger? Oh, my God.
Roger?
Say... a guy could drown
waiting for you.
Callaway, I'm gonna kill you!
Banzai!
Roger, I am gonna kill you.
-It's working.
-Look at them.
Now that's more like it.
Roger, darling, anyone home?
Well, Miss Kensington,
what a surprise.
We weren't expecting you.
Yes, I know. Where's Roger?
Uh, Mr. Callaway is out
for the afternoon.
Oh, I see.
Well, when he returns,
will you please tell him
I wish to speak with him?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Thank you so much.
I'd like a Diet Coke, please.
One Diet Coke coming up.
With lime.
Fairly early in the day
to be looking at stars.
What do we have here?
-Just like I said.
-You know what,
you can't always be this much
fun, because it wouldn't be fair.
Trust me, I haven't done
anything like this in years.
Well, it feels good, doesn't it?
Feels better every second.
-Uh, don't move.
-Why?
-There's a thing.
-What do you mean "a thing"?
-It's a little...
-A bug? A bug?
-It's a... It's a...
-A bug? What kind of...
It's right here.
A maraschino bug.
It's highly poisonous.
And you wanted to go for pizza.
I almost didn't come over at all.
I'm glad you did.
Diane?
What was that?
-It's a sign.
-What do you mean "a sign"?
I mean, I don't know
what I mean. I...
I think I know what you mean.
It's your Miss Kensington, right?
I'm getting married next month.
Well, of course you are.
So what was this?
Just sort of a last fling?
I didn't know what this was.
I was hoping to find out.
Oh, Rog, don't worry about it.
I can help you out here.
It was nice to meet you.
And thanks for the camp.
Oh, by the way, congratulations.
Diane, please. Diane.
You know what?
This just kills me.
We might've hit this one
out of the park, you and me.
It was there. I know it. That...
...can't-eat, can't sleep,
reach-for-the-stars,
over-the-fence
World Series kind of thing.
Oh, well.
I have got to get a dictionary.
They were so close.
Grown-ups, they think too much.
I give up.
No, we mustn't!
And why mustn't we?
Because, third time's the charm.
-Right?
-Right.
Boss! Boss!
-It's Miss Kensington.
-Thanks, Vincenzo.
-I'll take it down here.
-No, no, no, no.
Not here. Up there.
-Up there?
-I'm afraid so.
-Roger, darling!
-Clarice!
Your hair. You're here!
What did you do?
Fall in the lake?
You know, it's
the funniest thing. I was...
Aren't you supposed
to be in New York?
I couldn't bear to be away
from you a moment longer.
Oh, you were just gone a day.
I know and I was positively
miserable the entire time.
Which is why I've decided we
simply mustn't wait another day.
-To what?
-To be married, silly.
Oh, next month seems
like an eternity.
And when two people
are as much in love as we,
I say what's wrong with tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Darling, you haven't said a word
about my hair.
Okay, listen to this.
"Dear Roger, you are
so totally fresh."
"Just thinking about you
drives me mental."
"Meet me at that place
we met with the horses."
"7:00 tonight. Love, Diane."
-How's that?
-Very romantic.
-Wanna hear mine?
-Yep.
"Dear Diane..."
"Dear Diane, ever since the first
time I saw you riding a horse,"
"I can't stop thinking about it."
"And I know we were
disturbed at the lake"
"when the canoes fell over,"
"but I must see you again where
I saved your life at 7:30."
"Yours truly, Roger Callaway."
Yes!
There you are,
my little gum-chewing assailant.
-You're back.
-What, no big hug hello?
You're not supposed to be here.
In a perfect world,
dear, neither are you.
Now get packed,
we're leaving for the city.
Right now? It's too soon.
Maybe I didn't make myself clear.
We're leaving tonight.
This little act of
yours is getting old.
-What act?
-Oh, please.
By the time I was your age, I'd
been through three step-mothers,
so I know all about the lengths
that little girls will go through
to keep Daddy all to themselves.
Hey, you got that
all wrong, lady.
Alyssa, don't be rude.
I am talking.
What was I saying? Oh, yes.
You have had Roger to yourself
for nine wonderful years,
but after tomorrow,
I'm the woman of the house.
And you're off to
a year-round boarding school.
Possibly in Tibet.
Did you say tomorrow?
Should I have come here?
Yes, stupid.
He's only worth about 20 billion
dollars for God's sakes.
Right, now I'm just after him
for his money.
How shallow is that?
I liked him before
I knew he was rich.
So I should've come here.
Okay, so, he's
a little bit engaged.
But...
...I've never met her,
so maybe that doesn't count.
No.
God.
Come on, ladies, perk up.
Come on, Amanda,
we're missing the fireworks!
Amanda. Amanda.
Amanda, this is Miss Van Dyke,
she's from Children's Services.
Hello there, little lady.
I believe I have some
very good news for you.
Come to mama, sweetheart.
I feel pretty
ding-dang-dong stupid.
-But my name's Amanda!
-Alyssa, stop it.
Come on, honey.
Do we have to listen to this
the whole way?
Oh, great,
now I'm gonna be roadkill.
Diane, help!
Wait a minute,
what are you doing?
Damn!
You were supposed to protect her!
You should've done something.
You could've slit their tires
or something, anything!
-They had the paperwork.
-What paperwork?
We couldn't find you!
Miss Van Dyke was here.
What did you want
us to do, lie in
front of the van for God's sake?
I would have.
I'm taking the Jeep.
-Hey, that's the camp's.
-Oh, don't you give me...
Lots of tie-ups this morning.
And it's 20 minutes for the
Lincoln, 10 for the Holland.
The BQE's backed up
for about two miles
and if you're taking the Van Wyck
better allow an extra 15.
Whatever you do,
stay out of Midtown.
It's going to be
wall-to-wall limos
as socialite Clarice Kensington
finally lands her man.
Now these little
nincompoops over here
are your new brothers
and sisters.
Now from the left you got
Bubba, Bridget, Brenda,
Bonnie, Billy, Bobby,
Ben and little Harry Jr.
-Now he's ours.
-Oh...
Oh, look here, there's
been a big mistake.
You see, my name is not Amanda.
-We know that, honey.
-You do?
Sure. And you will never
have to be Amanda again.
That's right,
because from now on,
you're gonna be
little Betty Butkis.
Huh? Now kids, scoot over and
give Betty here some Cocoa Puffs.
Oh, and after breakfast,
we're gonna go down
and see where your daddy works.
Isn't that gonna be fun?
Callaway residence.
One moment, please.
Miss Callaway, it's for you.
Hello, this is Miss Callaway.
Amanda, I can't talk long.
It's me, Alyssa.
Or should I say...
Betty Butkis.
Oh, no! I'm adopted?
Those guys scary or what?
What happened yesterday?
-Are you sitting down?
-Yeah, kind of.
Clarice moved up the wedding.
Your dad's getting married
in two hours and 12 minutes.
Oh, no. What do we do now?
I don't know, but it's gonna
have to be something major.
And quick. Amanda,
you've got to get me out of here.
These people aren't just scary.
They're...
Amanda?
Alyssa?
Alyssa!
New kids aren't allowed
to use the phone.
Butkis rules.
Hey, Vin, you've been taking
care of Alyssa all her life.
-Right?
-Oh, no, Alyssa, not again.
-Answer the question.
-Yes, from the day she was...
From the day you were born.
So you know pretty well
everything about her?
Every freckle,
every bruise, every scar?
Yeah, I supposed
you could say that.
Bet you don't remember this one,
do ya?
No, that one escapes me.
Broken bottle, sliding into home.
Or this one.
Rusty nail,
right through my shoe.
Bled for six blocks.
How about here? Ever seen this?
-When did you get that?
-Roman candle last 4th of July.
-Right in the head.
-My God!
You're not Alyssa.
Nope, name's Amanda.
Put her there.
Identical strangers?
Holy mackerel, that's amazing!
Yeah, and it's weird too.
But if you're here with us,
then Alyssa is...
-In a whole lot of trouble.
-I gotta tell Mr. Callaway.
Oh, no. Wait!
You can't tell him yet.
We've gotta get him to see Diane
one more time before the wedding.
They'll fall in love
and Clarice will be history.
Where the hell is everybody?
Vincenzo!
I sure hope you got a plan.
Vincenzo?
What, what are you doing here?
I came for Mr. Callaway's
daughter, Alyssa.
You got her, I want her back.
What are you talking about?
I don't have Roger
Callaway's daughter,
I don't even know
Roger Callaway's daughter.
Oh, oh, yes you do.
This. This is Alyssa Callaway.
No, no. You... You gotta get
your eyes checked
because this is a little girl
named Amanda.
Oh, oh, no.
No, no. This is your Amanda.
But...
Oh, my God.
Look, they're identical.
Oh, this is amazing.
Yeah, and it's weird too.
Now I understand that
through some, uh...
some simple mix-up,
that Alyssa is in the care
of Child Services.
Now, I've been
authorized to tell you
that if I get her
back right away,
there'll be no legal
entanglements.
You just say...
She's not exactly with me.
-Here.
-What?
She's been...
Well, she's adopted.
Well, then you better
un-adopt her quick.
Mr. Callaway's getting married in
90 minutes at St. Bartholomew's.
He's expecting his daughter
to be there, his real daughter.
-Ninety minutes?
-Yeah.
Well, I can't even get to Staten
Island and back in 90 minutes.
Well, can I suggest that
you go really, really fast?
Here, if you get
into any trouble,
call this number.
Ask for Lou.
Lou.
Lou who?
Well, hey. Look at this mess.
Clean it up.
-You clean it.
-Betty, put a cork in it, okay?
He's management.
My father's Roger Callaway.
And when he finds out
what you're doing here,
he's gonna buy this whole town,
and kick you out of it.
Roger Callaway, huh?
Well then, how come you
ain't at his wedding?
Oh, yeah.
Come on, Diane, you can do it.
We might have to
stall a little bit.
How?
How should I know?
You're the brains
of this operation.
I must be crazy.
I am not going in that church,
no matter what happens,
I am not going in that church.
It's only natural to be nervous.
Actually, I was thinking about
the World Series.
Baseball?
Vincenzo, did you
ever hit a homerun?
Not recently.
Well, you know the feeling
when it's bottom of the ninth,
the bases are loaded,
and you know the next one's
coming right down the middle.
And then...
You just connect.
And, for an instant,
you know it's going over
the fence and out of the park,
and further than
you could ever imagine.
Yeah, that's a great feeling.
Yeah.
Clarice hates baseball.
Come on, Seabiscuit,
don't fail me now.
Hello? Hello?
You looking for a Butkis?
-What?
-You looking for a Butkis?
Yes! Yes, I am.
Do you know where he is?
At the salvage yard, where else?
Harry works those poor kids
to the bone.
What do you mean?
Why do you think
he's got so many?
Lou, Lou. Hey, hey, buddy,
can I use your phone?
Yeah, sure. No charge.
We've been looking for you,
Your Highness.
Leave me alone.
But, Your Majesty,
we brought you something.
Yeah, something to make you
feel more at home.
I knew somebody in this church
would have a Prozac.
What is taking so long?
Relax, Clarice, enjoy the moment.
This is the happiest
day of your life.
I'm happy. Don't I look happy?
This is me happy, see?
Happy, happy, happy,
happy, happy, happy!
Let's get this show on the road!
Here's your royal throne,
Alyssa Callaway.
Hail Betty.
Queen of the scrap heap.
Hail Betty!
My name's Alyssa Callaway!
Yeah, right, and I'm Princess Di.
Attention, Harry Butkis.
We're here to pick
up Alyssa Callaway.
All you kids in the yard,
stand clear. We're coming in.
Told ya!
Alyssa Callaway,
I gotta get you to that church.
Hey, that is my kid!
Get out of my way,
you piece of junk.
I would love nothing more
than to kill you.
Before I turn you over to
Social Services.
Alyssa, go on. Hurry.
Oh, God.
Hi, how ya doing?
Good to see ya.
Hey, Granny. Nice hat.
Thanks for coming.
Get moving.
Any slower and
she'd be walking backwards.
Oh, she's... she's just
not herself today.
We'll never make it.
We only have 10 minutes.
-So, Lou?
-Yeah?
How close can you land this thing
to the church?
Central Park close enough?
Central Park? The Central Park?
That will do.
Play ball!
Who would've thought
my first little girl
would be the last to get married?
Oh, Daddy... Shut up.
Enough of this.
Okay. All right, I'm here.
Let's do it.
De... Dearly beloved, we're
gathered here in the sight of God
to join in holy matrimony
Clarice and Roger.
I'm not going in the church,
I'm not going in the church.
Oh, no.
Not another horse.
Diane, come on!
All right, here we go.
Where is the driver?
Oh, hey, buddy! You gotta
take us to St. Bart's right away.
It's an emergency!
When I close this.
I'm on my break!
I wanna thank you for
all your help, bud.
Hey! Hey!
Hey! That's... That's my horse!
Faster!
To have and to hold,
for richer or poorer,
in sickness and in health
as long as you both shall live?
I do, I do. I really do. Now him.
Hit the brakes! Hit the brakes!
Amanda, there's a black car!
Come on.
-Hang on!
-I'm hanging on.
What street's it on again?
54th and Park. Are we there yet?
-Almost.
-Signal!
And do you, Roger,
take this woman, Clarice,
to be your lawful wedded wife?
To have and to hold,
for richer or poorer,
and in sickness and in health
as long as you both shall live?
Oh, God. We made it?
Aren't you coming?
No, I think I'm just gonna
wait for Amanda out here.
Diane Barrows, get
your butt up here this instant!
Okay. Okay.
Maybe I'll just stand in the back
and take a little look-see.
I...
Oh, yes!
Roger.
I can't.
Yes!
Excuse me, what did you say?
I'm so sorry, Clarice. I can't.
I should've said
something earlier.
I'm in love with someone else.
Guess I deserved that.
This is all your fault.
Lady, if you touch that child
I'll pop you one, so help me God.
Oh, my God, there's two of them.
It's a conspiracy!
Well, at least I'll get
to hit one of you.
Hey!
Back off, Barbie.
And by the way,
you have a little tiny bit of
something here on your teeth.
I have never been more humiliated
in my life!
Wanna bet?
Daddy!
My God!
About time you showed up.
I got here as soon as we could.
Hi, Daddy.
You're...
-This is impossible.
-Nothing's impossible.
-Right, Alyssa?
-You got that right.
If... If you're... You're my...
-Who are you?
-Name's Amanda.
Put her there. I'm with her.
Well, I guess we're even.
What do you mean?
You saved my life.
I'm sorry about
spoiling the party.
I just didn't want the wrong girl
to go down the aisle.
I mean... I... I mean
the wrong flower girl.
I think you had it
right the first time.
Told you, third time's the charm.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
All of this, this was your doing?
It was, was it?
Well, ladies,
what do you have to
say for yourselves?
-So, kiss already!
Put her there...
Sister.
And it's a high fly ball...
Over the left field wall.
Excuse me. This gentleman claims
that the ladies stole his buggy.
Oh, my God, he's right. We did!
You did go out of your way.
It was her idea.
Vincenzo, I'd like you to ask
that nice gentleman if he'd sell.
I don't care what it costs.
That horse deserves
a house in the country.
I trust we can make
some kind of arrangement.
Well, girls, what do you say
we do a little sightseeing?
And then you girls can tell us
the whole story.
Driver, once around the park,
if you please.
It'll be my pleasure, boss.
Walk on, Duke.