A Hero Never Dies (1998)
English subtitle - Cantonese version
( Jack / Martin )
Slowly.
Water.
Mr. Fortune Teller,
since Mr. Fong wanted to
occupy all of our possession last year,
both of our gangs have been
fighting all the time,
and this war hasn't been stopped once.
A lot of my people were killed,
I feel really bad about it.
I told you very clearly last year.
Regardless how people has died,
don't let the fighting
go on until after July.
Now I can't do anything
to help you.
Mr. Fortune Teller,
I've already tried my best.
It's not possible.
With that many casualties,
you still haven't
destroyed Mr. Fong.
It's because you guys
are afraid to die!
If you want to be
the most powerful one,
you need to have
the strongest army.
Be able to get back
all that you've lost.
You'll lose this battle.
Your men will betray you,
and you'll die painfully.
This is gonna be your destiny.
Mr. Fortune Teller,
please save me.
Then you must follow my guidance.
Of course, of course.
How can you treat
Mr. Fortune Teller this way?!
How dare you!
Tell him to drop his gun!
Jack,
what the hell are you doing?!
Mr. Fortune Teller,
your mind can
read through the future,
you can calculate everything
that hasn't yet happened.
Can you tell whether
you'll be shot today?
Jack,
are you out of your mind?!
You dare to shot me?
Can't you?
No!
Mister.
Jack, how dare you!
Mr. Yam,
nobody in our gang
is afraid to die.
If you want to win,
we all will sacrifice our lives
for your victory.
Why do you want your life
to be decided by someone else?
God is the one that carries a gun.
Am I right,
Mr. Fortune Teller?
Mr. Yam's hand is bleeding.
Jack,
how many of our brothers do you think
can go back to Hong Kong this time?
You don't need to ask God for the answer.
As long as you know who your enemy is,
you'll know the result.
Jack, the line is busy.
Keep dialing.
Jack, it's getting through.
Michael, turn back.
Mr. Yam,
Jack told us to turn back.
Ignore him.
Are we supposed to wait and die here?
Drive faster.
Back off!
Stop him,
don't let him get away.
Mr. Yam, get off the car now!
Run them over!
Michael,
take Mr. Yam to the dock.
Mr. Yam,
get inside the car!
Get in here! Joe!
Joe!
Wong.
Martin.
Leave Jack a message for me.
Tell him I'm gonna tear down
his mother fucking ancestor's home.
If you miss one word,
I'm gonna kill you.
Martin said he was gonna...
Te...
Tear down your
mother fucking ancestor's home.
Tell Martin to stick his shit face
into his asshole.
If you miss one word,
I'm gonna kill you.
I'm gonna crack
his mother's ass with a bat.
You tell him to suck my dick.
He dared to come up here
but not dared to kill me,
tell him to go to hell,
suck my dick!
Aiming for that long
but still didn't shoot,
too chicken shit that
he knew he was gonna miss?
Please don't put me on the spot.
I...
I am old,
and my memory is not so good.
You...
you guys should get together,
and clear things out yourselves.
Martin.
Yo-yo-yo, hey!
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on.
Yeah.
♫ Japanese Folk Song (English Version): Sukiyaki ♫
♪ It's all because of you ♪
♪ I'm feeling sad and blue ♪
Let him taste my bottle of wine.
♪ You went away ♪
♪ Now my life is just a rainy day ♪
Let him taste mine.
♪ And I love you so ♪
♪ How much you'll never know ♪
♪ You've gone away and left me lonely ♪
♪ Untouchable memories ♪
♪ Seem to keep haunting me ♪
This is...
for the renovation of my home.
♪ Another love so true ♪
♪ That once turned all my gray skies blue ♪
♪ But you disappeared ♪
♪ Now my eyes are filled with tears ♪
♪ And I'm wishing you were here with me ♪
♪ Soaked with love all my thoughts of you ♪
♪ Now that you're gone ♪
♪ I don't know what to do ♪
♪ If only you were here ♪
♪ You'd wash away my tears ♪
♪ The sun would shine once again ♪
♪ You'd be mine all mine ♪
♪ But in reality ♪
♪ You and I will never be ♪
♪ You took your love away from me ♪
Yes.
♪ Soaked with love all my thoughts of you ♪
♪ Now that you're gone ♪
♪ I don't know what to do ♪
- Fiona.
- How are you, Po?
Yo Yo.
Did you really
have to take this one?
This is for our guest.
My wine...
Is the very best.
Fair enough.
Compare yours to mine...
There's a big difference.
Mine is the best.
- Po.
- Yes.
You know something about wine,
right?
Just a little.
Which one is good?
Both are good.
Which one is better?
Both are equally good.
Pick up his bottle
with your left hand.
Grab mine with your right hand.
Get back one step.
Straighten both arms.
Straighten both arms!
Drop one of them onto the floor.
Are you gonna beat me?
I'll kill you!
Jack has saved his for a long time.
Po, why don't you try this?
Store this bottle first,
we'll come back for this
in a couple of days.
We'll drink this tonight.
Put a tag on,
write the names of Jack
and Martin on it.
So, here you go.
Thank you, Fiona.
Won't you get going?
You've been with Martin
for a long time?
Before I was even eighteen.
It doesn't seem like you've
been with Jack for very long.
It's been almost a year.
But till now I still don't know
how I'm supposed to be his woman.
Can you teach me?
Wear high heels.
As a top man's wife,
you have to at least look powerful,
your voice always comes first
even before you arrive.
So when your man is screwing around
he'll hear your voice in advance.
So it'll give him more time
to think of an excuse to lie to you.
Understand?
Can't we find sometime to
get together just to chat?
It's not possible for us to be friend,
you know?
Either Jack or Martin will die
on the other's hand.
They seem like friends.
This is where they stand,
can't help it.
Men are like that,
they treat their brothers
better than their women.
I knew this since day one.
Where's Mr. Yam?
Mr. Yam is in Bangkok.
I told you to take him
over to the general.
He wanted to meet the Fortune Teller.
Didn't you hear me?
Are you the boss or Mr. Yam?
Stop the car.
Hung, airport.
Yes, Jack.
Hi.
Martin,
Mr. Fong is waiting for you in there.
How generous!
Three of them.
Mr. Fong is afraid to get bore.
Hi, Miss.
Is this real or what,
can I rub it off?
Try it.
So this is real.
What are you laughing at,
you've got something to be rubbed?
Guess where that is?
Martin, how have you been?
I haven't been too well.
I had to go around detours,
and make sure nobody was
following us before I get here.
Mr. Fong.
I've been waiting for you
for a long time,
how's out there?
It's a mess out there.
When I tried to kill Yam last time,
I failed.
Three of our guys got killed.
It adds up to eighteen already.
So,
do you need me to take charge now?
Probably not,
you should be pretty safe in here.
In addition,
Yam ran off.
Where did the asshole go?
Maybe to go see the general.
Fuck!
Now he's crying for mama,
what a useless piece of shit.
This time I have to
straighten things out with him,
I won't do general a favor anymore.
Then we all gonna die.
We made a deal last year,
we both were gonna co-operate
to control the entire Hong Kong.
That bastard kicked me out,
he even tried to kill me.
The battle went on until today,
whoever gives up first loses.
Martin,
you had helped me for more than a decade,
regardless what you have to
help me this time.
However,
you have to kill that bastard to me.
Before he finds the general.
Of course.
Take a rest.
Martin, good luck.
Go have a haircut.
Boss,
- do you want me to
find you a several girls?
- No.
What was Martin thinking?
This is a country side.
Fuck!
Mr. Fortune Teller
doesn't usually meet visitor.
You're very honored today,
what do you want to ask?
Here.
I've heard something about a person...
whom I'm looking for.
So I came over to
find out what happened.
But...
Now, it doesn't matter anymore.
Mr. Fortune Teller gives you advice...
just because you're Mr. Fong's guy.
What do you do this for?!
Thank you.
Mr. Fortune Teller,
if you can read through the future that well.
Then you should check it out,
if you're gonna get shot today?
Yes or no?
Yes!
You got it.
I curse that
you will die so painfully!
Your body will be dumped on the street,
you won't even have your own grave!
This place is really for
swimming and meeting girls.
We should be having a holiday in here.
Martin,
who do you think will win this time?
Why didn't you ask that Fortune Teller
when you just had a chance 5 minutes ago.
You only need to know who your opponent is,
then you'll know the result.
Mr. Yam,
we can't go any further on this road,
it's very dangerous.
There's a motel in the front,
let's stay there for tonight.
Don't move!
You guys must be tired by now.
Thanks for your hard work.
Jack is smart and loyal,
he had saved me a several times.
But I can feel that things are
a little chaotic this time,
do you think Jack is scared?
What hasn't Jack been through before?
Things are gonna be okay.
Then you guys are lucky to
have him as a big brother,
no worries, right?
Of course.
Need I say more?
Have a good rest first.
I'll take it as long as
they're cooked alright,
- but don't make them taste too awful.
- Okay, Jack.
You must find out whether
it's gonna rain tomorrow.
Okay.
Have a cup of tea first.
I went to see the doctor last month,
he told me to quit smoking.
I'm getting old,
can't bear with this any longer.
I shouldn't go see
the Fortune Teller.
Ask those imaginative spirits
instead of real people,
can't decide anything on my own.
I think it's about time...
I have asked you a several times,
were you gonna wage a war with Fong?
You said yes,
you were gonna fight him,
till the very end,
there's no turning back.
Our gang's spirit is very important now,
you shouldn't say things like that.
I've heard that you've seen Martin?
He has arrived in Thailand...
and went to see the Fortune Teller.
So,
are we just gonna sit here
and wait for him?
It's better to fight
against people than God.
It's very late now
and it's pouring outside,
if we go up the hill,
all of us will be taking a very high risk.
I want a gun.
You can kick me out after tonight,
but it's the best for you
to trust me now.
I can't find my gun!
Don't get out!
Stay!
Close your eyes.
General.
You guy's been fighting for a year.
A lot of people got killed.
But you let it carry on.
Now I'm here to be the witness.
All of your possession will...
remain the same as a year ago.
You can't enter this area,
please leave. Go!
I know now how to be your woman.
Please wake up.
I didn't even to see Hung's face
for the last time,
how could you cremate him
just like this.
Give me back his ashes!
Mr. Yam doesn't want you all
to worry about anything.
That is my husband!
I don't care!
I have to see Mr. Yam.
Where's Jack?
Why isn't he here?
Doesn't he want to see us?
Go find Jack for me.
Mr. Yam doesn't want anyone to mention
anything about it from now on.
Here's some money for the kids.
You too hope the children
can grow up fast.
I'm sorry,
there is nothing we can do.
If we don't amputate the infection may spread,
this could cost him his life.
Then amputate them.
( Gang leaders make peace and rule Hong Kong together )
I want the one up there.
The one up there?
Sure.
- Is it aspirin?
- Yes.
You pissed your pants again?
I'm a cripple.
I've made arrangement
with the ship company,
that bastard...
They can smuggle us
back to Hong Kong.
Why did you hand up on me?!
Martin and I are at the dock,
send someone over to pick us up!
People always win!
Yeah! Mr. Fong is the greatest!
Mr. Fong, you can stop
even the biggest rain storm.
The whole world should belong to you.
Mr. Fong,
you're the greatest.
When are you gonna
open the third nightclub?
That depends on my mood.
Mr. Fong and Mr. Yam are now partners,
who else can be more powerful.
There's only you two in the world.
Then you should come more often.
Thanks a lot.
- Of course.
- Cheers.
Chris, Martin's back.
Chris.
Fiona.
We need to see Fong.
I think it's not a good time now.
Can't you see Martin's here?
Craig, can you hear?
I'm Bob,
can anyone pick up?
Martin's back.
He's coming up.
Boss.
Boss,
Martin is downstairs.
What the fuck did you say?
How can he be back?
Boss, what's the matter?
You...
Get over here!
How can he come back?
Come here!
Dare you to move out...
Boss, what's wrong?
You go and take care of it.
Go downstairs first!
It's okay,
all go downstairs.
Come on, come on.
Drink again,
drink again, come!
- I have to see Fong!
- Fong gives you and Martin some money.
- What the fuck? You thought I came to beg?!
- He'll contact you later.
Craig, you dare to lift Martin up?!
See that?!
This is all because of
your asshole boss.
You mother fucker!
Get over here to see me!
This is how it ends up
to be your brother.
Have you ever take a look at them,
concern about them for once?
When we both were stuck in Thailand with absolutely nothing,
we called you for help,
you dared to hang up on me!
We were there for you ever since we were kids,
now this is how you're treating us!
What kind of person are you?
Craig,
do I have to get down there
and fix it myself?!
Boss, I'm taking care of it.
- I'm sorry, Fiona.
Grab her.
- Let go!
Craig, who makes you become,
who you are today,
who has been helping you all these years.
Come out! You bastard!
What a piece of shit!
- You coward!
- Louder!
You don't even dare to
take a look at your brother.
What kind of boss are you?
Fuck you!
Come out! Come out!
Go to hell!
Let's go!
You traitor!
Thank you all for your shares
and partnership.
This business is surely profitable.
The most important thing is that we all
will have good business relationship.
We will make a lot of money.
I don't have much to say,
opportunity is for everybody.
Fong, you loyaless son of a bitch!
Without Martin's help,
you'd still be parking people's cars.
You wouldn't be here today!
Aren't you gonna get another one?
Your brother is going down
while you're taking all this glory!
- Get out here if you dare!
- Fiona, please don't do this.
Are you gonna beat me?
Are you?
Whenever you dump me,
I'll come right back here,
unless you kill me.
Kill me if you dare.
Fong said he didn't want to see you.
If you go one with this fuss
he's gonna kill us all.
Did you hear that?
What kind of animal is he?
You've worked for him
for more than half of your lifetime.
Now this is how he treats you.
Wake up!
This business for me is so small,
I'll share
what I've earned with everybody.
- Fong, you betrayed Martin.
- I like this combination.
- Everyone's happy, I'm happy...
- How is it fair to those who died!
- How is it fair to Martin!
Asshole!
- Come down, you bastard!
- Boss is coming down.
Taking care of it?!
Taking care of it...
Didn't you understand
what I was telling you to do?
God damn you!
You dared to betray your brother
but afraid of me?
What a useless piece of shit!
Boss, she's our friend,
dont't do this!
Boss, no!
Let go!
Don't let me see her ever again!
( Former gangster become a beggar )
He's back. Come out.
Go talk to him.
Don't be shy!
Come on.
Go upstairs.
He lives in that room.
He's so handsome!
Have a good chat with him.
Why did you come in here?
Get out!
Get out! Go!
( I am not coming back )
Jack!
This fax doesn't have a sender's name.
But the fax number is the one which you
dialed to fax Hong Kong yesterday.
Thank you.
Over there! Up there!
Martin.
Could you treat me a drink?
Sure.
Martin.
Fong is looking for you everywhere,
I have a house in Mainland China...
I want to listen to that song.
Okay.
Hey...
stop that for a second.
Quick.
Play that song "Sukiyuki" first.
- Which song?
- It's Sukiyuki.
- That Japanese folk song.
- Sukiyuki?
What the hell!
- How can you guys make a living out of this?
- Can't recall, I don't really know.
You listen to me, look at me.
- Look at me...
- Okay.
I don't like this many people around
when I'm drinking!
Mr. Fong, Mr. Yam.
Is everything okay?
I've heard that you had kept
a very good bottle of wine here.
Sure.
Mr. Fong.
I want that one.
Brilliant!
Do you know where Jack is?
I don't know.
Boss,
I've found a fax from Thailand.
Asshole!
Such a waste of wine.
Can't you find anything else
to beat him with?
Don't worry about that
if you have money!
Get me a dozen tomorrow,
otherwise you better watch out!
This place has the
most beautiful sunset.
If you want,
I can build you a house here.
The sky will get dark
sooner or later.
If I could stay here forever,
I wish it would be
sunset time every day.
That I can't help you.
I knew that I was born pretty
ever since I was twelve.
When I grew a little older,
I was afraid one day
I would have a chubby belly.
Then I would scare
the person I love away.
Once I had a very silly thought.
I wish I would die before thirty,
then my most beautiful moment
would stay forever.
I really wish
could stay here forever,
the sunset would hang like this
in the sky every day.
Can you help me
solve this problem?
What is all these craps,
you guys are like this
all the time.
You can never get that right!
It's like that...
Okay?
Start again!
You guys just didn't get it.
God damn it.
Jack.
Po.
Martin couldn't wait for you
to come back for the wine.
He just wanted to kill Fong himself.
Wong,
this is Jack.
Martin and I are going to
find Fong and Yam.
Go tell everyone,
if we're still brothers
then they should give away.
Where did you hear that?
- Go check out that guy from Thailand.
- Was it Wong who told you this?
- Ask him if he knows the assassin has been paid.
- Go find him for me now!
Mr. Fong,
those share holders said
this is our internal business,
they won't get involved.
What a bunch of jerks!
Mr. Yam,
something happened at the nightclub.
A lot of people said
something big is gonna happen tonight.
Watch out for yourself.
Leave it you had a chance.
Wasn't Martin dead,
how can he be back?
Someone said he was dead too
when we were in Thailand.
How could this get in here?!
Who put it here?!
What were you guys doing?!
- How could you let this happen?!
- I know!
I let him put it there.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I give way.
Martin's back.
What are you looking at?
Why are you scared?
He's dead!
Not yet.
You take care of this yourself,
baldy Fong.
Not yet dead?
♪ It's all because of you ♪
♪ I'm feeling sad and blue ♪
♪ You went away ♪
♪ Now my life is just a rainy day ♪
♪ And I love you so ♪
♪ How much you'll never know ♪
♪ You've gone away and left me lonely ♪
- Scot, listen to me...
- You wait a minute.
I'm positively certain
this bottle of wine is fake.
The real one had been consumed
by Fong and Yam already.
- John, you listen to me...
- Not yet your turn...
I know this is real.
My friend's friend
is a very good friend
with the boss here.
For the sake of keeping that wine,
he swapped this with
another one for them.
So this one must be real.
You finish?
It's my turn now.
You said this is fake,
you said this is real.
♪ Now my eyes are filled with tears ♪
♪ I'm wishing you were here with me ♪
♪ Soaked with love all my thoughts of you ♪
♪ Now that you're gone ♪
♪ I don't know what to do ♪
♪ If only you were here ♪
♪ You'd wash away my tears ♪
♪ The sun would shine once again ♪
♪ You'd be mine all mine ♪
♪ But in reality ♪
♪ You and I will never be ♪
♪ You took your love away from me ♪