Over here in heaven
life feels so very dull!
Got nothing better to do
but count the floating clouds
Elder sister often sings
praises of the mortal world
Where the men farm, the women weave
I'd sure like to take a peek
But it's father's wrath that I fear so
Let me go and look for my eldest sister
Perhaps she'd offer some advice
She would have some ideas
Eldest sister...
Eldest sister, I want to...
I know what it s that you want. But...
it's against heavenly rules
to take a peek at earth
If our father finds out...
We'll get into trouble
Let's make sure he doesn't come to know
It's not a big deal
to take a peek at earth
Yes, let's take a peek
Come with me then
Seventh sister's idea is great indeed
The mortal world is much more interesting
Hey, stop talking
Our father will kill us if he finds out
Look, eldest sister...
who are those people?
Those are fishermen
Fishermen?
Let me sing something in their praise
Fishermen fishing
in the middle of the sea
Middle of the sea
Sailing on lakes and seas
Selling half of the catch for wine
...and the other half for rice
For rice
Look
A woodcutter
I'll sing in his praise too
The woodcutter sings and cuts the wood
Walking down the hill after a day's work
Selling the firewood on the main street
On the main street
To buy food and be content
Listen to this
The farmers work hard in the fields
Work hard in the fields
Sowed seeds of grains, rice and wheat
Hoping & praying for a good harvest
A good harvest and happiness
Happiness
Listen to me
The scholar studies by the window
Reciting the literature
He must learn
the Four Books and Five Classics
A man should be ambitious
Ambitious
It's such a different world
Happy couples tying the knot
Tying the knot
The bridal sedan picks up the bride
It will take her to the bridal chamber
Hey, look
Sister, why is that young man
in such a hurry?
Do you know why?
His name is Tong Yong
His father passed away;
having no money for...
the funeral, he sold himself
to work as a slave
He's heading to work now
He is a filial son
But he's all alone
Poor chap!
Let's go back to the palace
The bells are urging my sisters
to rush back home
Let me take a second look at Tong Yong
Working as a slave
to raise money for burial
Wondering if & ever
he could get back home
He seems like an honest man
I sympathize for him
He's worried on earth
I'm unhappy
He's crying
I'm grieved
I desire to go to the mortal world
But I'm afraid of my strict father
If I don't go
Then I'll be alone forever
Um... Eldest sister
Seventh sister,
I know what you're thinking about
I've gone through the same experience
But if our father finds out...
You must help me, sister
The rules are stern
I've made up my mind
I'll break the rules if I must
You're too young; I'm so worried
Eldest sister
C'mon, get up
I won't if you don't promise me
Fine
Really?
Yes, get up
But...
How about this?
Here's an incense stick
If you're in trouble, burn this
The six of us will come to your help
Thanking my sister for her goodwill
She helped and gave me the incense stick
I bid her farewell
I hope their love will last forever
Rays of sunlight
pierce through the clouds
I'm on my way to the mortal world
I don't like the life in heaven
I'd rather be an ordinary girl in love
Where's the local earth-god?
Respected fairy
Oh, please arise
What can I do for you, fairy?
Oh, this I can't... no can do
If the Jade Emperor were to find out...
I will be in serious trouble
Don't worry, earth god
If my father blames anyone
I'll take all responsibility
Yes, fairy
Watch your steps
Your dress could be a problem though
Change into something
the human beings wear
Moving forward in sorrow
I see a village girl on the path
What is she doing?
She's looking at me
But I'm in no mood for gestures
My late father used to tell me
Speaking to strange women
would spell trouble
I'll take the trail then
There she is again!
Let me go back to the main path
Why are you doing this?
Lady, I don't understand
You've blocked my way twice
What did you do that for?
There's a saying:
One can choose his own path
If you can walk around
Can't I just stand around?
Excuse me, lady
All right, please
Please
Lady, you ran into me
You have a sack and an umbrella
You were preoccupied and ran into me
Are you blaming me now?
Did I bump into her?
Fine, please
Please
Lady, are you doing this on purpose?
Let me ask you
Do you want to walk past?
I... Of course
Tell me then
Where do you live? What's your name?
Where are you heading to?
If you tell me clearly, I'll let you pass
Lady
My name is Tong Yong; living in Danyang
My parents are deceased, I have no family
I couldn't afford a proper burial
for my father
Hence I've sold myself to work as a slave
Full of sorrow
I'll work for three years as a slave
Please excuse me
See, the sun is about to set soon
Please don't cry, mister
Let me give you a word of encouragement
You're like a willow in frost
You'll bloom again in Spring
Thank you for your kind words
I've a sad story too
We're both unfortunate
Where do you live, lady?
Where are you heading to?
I was living in Penglai Village
I traveled a long way to board
with my relatives
But I can't find them anywhere
That's why I'm here all alone
Then we are both unfortunate
If you wouldn't mind
I'm willing to...
To do what?
Marry you
You should have thought this over
We hardly know each other
And I've to work as a slave
at the Fu Household
I can't let you suffer with me
Please take me along;
then I won't wander around
Lady, I can hardly support myself
I don't want you to suffer too
So you're refusing to help?
There's nothing I can do
Goodbye
Mister...
Mister
Are you hurt?
Please take me with you, mister
I...
Lady, there's nothing I can do
You just have to acquiesce
No, I...
How could you be so heartless?
Left me here wandering on my own?
No, I...
Please take me with you, mister
It's so disgraceful of you both to be...
Flirting here in the wilderness,
are you?
You've got it all wrong, mister
Me and her...
I get it
A married couple having a quarrel?
No, I'm not related to her
And we're not married
Mister, please don't make wild guesses
Then why are you...
two fighting?
Honestly
We've hardly made a proper acquaintance
I've only spoken briefly to her,
then she...
What about her?
She...
Tell me
She wants to marry me
To get married?
I think you two would make a fine match
Then you had better respond to her
You know nothing about me
I'm poor and am about
to start work as a slave
I can't let her suffer with me
Thank you for your kind suggestion
I... really am...
He doesn't want you to live a poor life
He's doing it for your sake
I think you better head back home
I live very far from here
It's an arduous journey back
If he doesn't take me along
I'm afraid I'll have to...
Please don't cry
Stop crying. I'll talk to him
Young man
She's a poor girl; she's all alone
Please promise her
Mister, all men aspire to
start a family and a career
But as for my background
You should understand why I'm doing this
I um... better take your leave
Yes
Young man, please don't be so aloof
If you insist for me to marry her...
Then it'd be on one condition
What condition?
I'll need a matchmaker
and a wedding witness
At such an old age as I am...
Would it be alright for me
to be a witness?
You are aged,
of a high family and virtuous
We're lucky to have you as our witness
But the witness can't be the matchmaker
The matchmaker can't be the witness
In that case
What should we do?
Mister, there's an Ash tree here
It can be the matchmaker
What? The tree as the matchmaker?
How can it be an intermediary?
Why not?
It can't talk
What if it can?
If it talks...
Then we'll get married
What if it can't?
Then let's end all this right here
We'll go our separate ways
Really?
Deal. But you must call for three times
All right
Please be my witness, mister
Sure
Ash tree, I want to marry this lady
Could you be our matchmaker? Please talk
Has it talked?
Second time
Ash tree, I want to marry this lady
Could you be our matchmaker? Please talk
Not yet
One more try
Ash tree, I want to marry this lady
Could you be our matchmaker? Please talk
Please talk
Tong Yong, hold on
Hold on
The Ash tree
Opens its mouth and laughs
I'll be your matchmaker
I'll indeed be your matchmaker
This is amazing
Amazing!
How could a tree talk?
Is this destiny?
It's a godsend match, don't hesitate
It's a divine match.
You shouldn't hesitate
Although it's a match
predestined by Heavens
But we should take this seriously
The lady is nice to me
But you shouldn't marry
a poor man like me
I don't have a decent house
I don't have worthy belongings
If you marry me
I worry that in the days to come
You'll starve and freeze because of me
It's all right
I know what I'm getting myself into
We get married in adversities
For eternity
My love for you won't change
Come on, you two bow to heaven and earth
So you two get married under the Ash tree
Congratulations
I wish you both to have a happy marriage
And have a child next year
I'll ask for three cups of wine
After the wedding ceremony,
the matchmaker can go
It's time for me to move on
Good bye
Let us see you off
There's no need to
Me and my wife...
Dear
Dear husband
Let's go
Please
After you
A family of benevolence will be blessed
Nicely written
Zhaogui
Yes master
Send three silver coins over
Wait...
Send two coins
Yes master
Squire
What? This doesn't count?
There're seven of us in my family
We live on the farm
You... stop nagging
It's written clearly on the debit-note
If you fail to pay me back
by the due date...
the farm will be mine. You signed this
I'm going to pay you back
I'm just asking for a few more days
No, no exception
If I do that,
everyone will be asking for extensions
Please have pity on me
Over the time I've paid a lot of interest
Are you inferring that I'm a loan-shark?
No... I dare not say that
That what did you mean?
Zhaofu, throw him out
Yes
Squire...
You're heartless
I've borrowed five taels of silver
and I've already paid you half
of that as interest
Get out...
Damn it, throw him out
You're wealthy but unkind
You won't be so lucky forever
Get out...
Hey, come on
Wait here, I'll speak to the master
Go
Come on
Squire, Tong Yong is here
Good day, squire
Bring him to the mill
Yes, master
I also have...
What?
I have an umbrella outside
Bring it
Also...
What?
A sack
Bring it
Also...
What else?
And me
Who's she?
She's my wife
She's your wife?
The contract states that you are single
And now you have a wife?
Most likely it's kidnapping!
We...
I thought you are a filial son
So you are a kidnapper
Zhaogui
Yes master
Send them to the judge
Yes, master
Wait
We have a witness to our marriage
It's not kidnapping
Do you know that on the contract...
It has his name on it?
He signed the contract before
we got married
Since we're married
It's my duty to share my husband's work
My husband sold himself as a slave here
I can'tjust take off
That's right, squire
If I didn't bring her along with me...
Then where could she go?
You brought her along
A woman can't do any work
I can'tjust support her for free
I can do other chores... like laundry
I know how to weave
You know how to weave?
Yes
Don't ruin my good silk
I'm not boasting
I'm a good weaver, and efficient too
You're very confident
If you can weave quickly...
Can you finish
10 rolls of brocades overnight?
What if I can?
And what if I can't?
It would be good if you can
If you can't...
then your husband will work here
for 6 years instead
6 years?
That's not fair
If there's punishment,
there should be a reward
If I finish on time...
Then he'll work here for 100 days instead
That's fair
There's no point, dear
You can't finish that much in ten nights
...let alone in one night
Don't worry, I know what I'm doing
Do we have your word?
Absolutely
But if you can't finish it
Then he'll work here for 6 years
If I can finish it
He'll work here for 100 days only
Of course
Take them to the weaving shed
Yes master
Follow me
Zhaogui
This way
Sure
Yes
Look, dear.
All of it is tangled up and messy
You can't finish weaving
ten rolls overnight
We can't tell yet
But there's no point to be sad
It won't help
It doesn't matter to me
3 years, 6 years, it's the same
But I don't want you to be involved
How can I calm down?
I got myself into this
If you don't blame me
Then I'm willing to take the hardship
You have no idea about the squire
What about him?
He's a miser... wealthy but unkind
Dear, I think you should run away
...now that no one's around
Don't you want me anymore?
I didn't mean that
Not at all
Then I'll stay
I want to be with you
For better or for worse
Tong Yong...
Go to work in the mill
Yes
Go
I can't blame him for worrying
He knows nothing that I'm a fairy
Let me fix all this silk first
I'm now at the mill and worrying
I suggested you to leave;
you just won't listen
We'll be slaving here for 6 years
This is giving me a headache
Then I heard the sound of the drum
With just a pair of hands
To finish weaving 10 rolls overnight
It's difficult
Remembering what my eldest sister told me
Burn the incense stick when in trouble
I hope they will be here soon
The incense smoke raises up to the sky
Our baby sister must be in trouble
Let's go to take a look
Eldest sister
Seventh sister
Second sister
How have you been?
Are you well?
Fourth sister
Where's our brother-in-law?
Where's he? Let us see him...
He's working in the mill
What? This is your wedding night
He should be here with you
That's outrageous
It's not his fault
Him... who's he?
Tell us who is he?
Tell us
Come on, seventh sister
Seventh sister
Who's he?
Come on
Eldest sister
That's enough, everyone
You summoned us here
What's the matter?
Eldest sister, the squire is mean
He's doing this on purpose
How?
How has he troubled you?
To weave ten rolls of brocade overnight
That's a piece of cake
With the seven of us
We can finish thousands
You just relax, let us all help you
We will help you
Okay... Let's begin
Come on
The shuttle of this loom is all broken
It's broken
He's terrible
He makes sure you won't be able to finish
What then?
What now?
Let me fly to the milky way
and borrow the Weaving Fairy's shuttle
That's right
You don't need to go in person
Send the crane
Come with me
Crane, where are you?
Go to the Weaving Fairy
...and borrow her shuttle
Hurry back
It's here
Look, the shuttle is here
Let's go
Watchtower strikes two; the night is deep
All the sisters are determined
to show their talents
Weave brocades from the messy silk
So that Tong Yong will work for 100 days
100 days
The stroke chimes again, it's 3 o' clock
Indicating 3 o'clock
The Weaving Fairy
has been touched by their plight
If it weren't for the milky way
The Weaving Fairy
would descend to earth again
Descend to earth again
The stroke chimes, the night is passing
Weaving away
The eldest sister weaves
a pattern of unicorn sending a son
The second sister weaves
Evergreens
A symbol for longevity
Third and fourth sisters
weave extraordinary patterns
Peonies and butterflies
Fifth and sixth sisters decided
to weave dots
and patches
They are actually clouds
Spread all across the sky
The seventh sister is in love
She weaves a pair of mandarin ducks
So impressive
Don't you agree?
I think of my wife in the weaving room
I worry that the sun will soon rise
I can mill for thousand rounds
But my dear wife,
how could you weave ten rolls?
Guess, how many have we woven?
How many, eldest sister?
Ten rolls
Three feet six inches extra
Really? That's great
For those that are extra
We won't give it to the miser
No way
Let's leave that
for our future nephew's gown
I don't want it
Pass it to her
Don't be shy
Take it
Seventh sister, take it
It's almost dawn
It's time for us to leave
We better head off
Thank you for your help
I appreciate it
We're sisters,
we'll always help each other
Take care, seventh sister
Take care
I can't see you off
Hurry and leave
Bye, seventh sister
Bye
We'll be seeing you again
Take care
Dear
Dear husband
Don't worry about the weaving
Let's just accept life
Six years will be over in a jiffy
Come with me
What is there to look?
Come on
Look
Dear, these...
Exactly what the Squire asked for
The brocades all look great
My wife is talented
The butterflies are in pair
So are the mandarin ducks
My wife is indeed very dexterous
My wife has refined craftsmanship
Are you the weaving star?
I'm not the weaving star
I learnt under a good teacher
I couldn't believe it
But it's all done now
Let's go to the Squire
Excellent
Tong Yong...
Squire
Here you go
Please take a look
You stole them?
My wife weaved them
How could you say that?
How many wives have you got?
One
How many pairs of hands does she have?
Right
One wife with her single pair of hands
How could she do it?
You stole these
Squire, you say. Stolen from whom?
Who's the owner? Got any proof?
That...
You're just disinclined to change...
the three years contract into 100 days
That's why you're doing this
Man, I don't know
the background of your wife
I'm going to the judge
For you have kidnapped
Let me tell you
We had a matchmaker and a witness
for our wedding
If you go to the judge
And the matchmaker shows up
You'll be charged with
making false accusations
Then
You'll be fined for at least 800 taels
The contract is now changed to 100 days
This fairy tale will be told
through the ages
Through the ages
They are so in love with each other
Going home within 100 days
The birds are in pairs
The lush green hills are smiling
There's no more menial work
We can go home now
You farm, and I'll weave
I will carry the water, you irrigate
Even a broken hut can give us shelter
Our love can overcome all hardships
We are like the mandarin ducks
and living happily on earth
We've been walking for a long time, dear
Let's take a break
Good idea
Hey wait
You should sit down too
Sure
Your gown is torn
Let me mend it
What's this, dear?
Are you pregnant?
Thank you, God
Take care of yourself
Let me go ahead
and hire a sedan chair for you
There's no need to waste money
I'll be fine after a break
Then I'll go get some water
Hurry back
I'll be back soon
I'm pregnant now
I'm just so thrilled about it
When I give birth to my child
I'm going to have a healthy happy child
One big happy family
Everyone says that I've good fortune
Seventh princess, good day
What are you doing here?
The Jade Emperor has ordered that
Your Highness must return by 12:45 p. M
What are you talking about?
The Jade Emperor has found out about this
His Majesty is in a rage.
Please come with us
I'm happily married
I can'tjust leave like this
If Your Highness refuses to come with us
...then we'll have to capture you
I'm not scared of anything
Leave me alone
I'll report this to the Jade Emperor
My father ordered me to go back
This is a disaster
I'd rather be a mortal than a fairy
I'm not going back
Let me burn the incense stick
Hoping that eldest sister
will come to my rescue
Because she helped me before
She's been locked up by our father
She ordered the crane to send me a letter
And told me to take this
into my own hands
Seventh princess
What are you doing here again?
We've received a second order
The Jade Emperor orders you to go back
I won't go with you
If that's the case, we will...
What?
We'll have to kill Tong Yong
At 12:45 p. M
I'll await you at the South Gate
My father has ordered twice
It's like being stabbed in my heart
I'm not afraid for myself
But I don't want anything to happen
to my husband
I'm caught in the middle
Dear
How can I tell him the truth?
It was windy all of a sudden
The whole sky turned dark
Were you scared?
I was hiding behind the tree
I'm fine
That's good
I ran into a friend
He gave me a pear and some dates
Have some
You go ahead
I got those for you
It's a bad omen
Sorry?
Pear and dates,
they signify 'we'll be split soon'
There's another interpretation
Having a child soon, and never apart
Never apart?
Never apart
Look
What are the kids doing?
Flying a kite
Why is the kite flying up?
Coz its string is broken
I have an analogy
What kind?
A blown off kite is like a wife
goes up to heaven
Interesting
Since we left the Fu Household
We've been free
Just as like going to heaven
It's done. You can wear this now
I have a wife to mend my clothes
Much better than when I was single
Now that we're going home
Everyone will be impressed with my wife
Let's go, dear
Please
My husband is walking fast leading ahead
I'm crying behind
He's so delighted
and knows nothing of my worries
He has a wife to mend his clothes
But who would have thought that
...the wife is about to leave him!
I can only hate my father
for not letting us to stay as a couple
There's no place like home
Tong Yong's heading home today
I was single before
Now I'm married
We're going home together
And we'll never be separated
I see the ash tree again
I'm so delighted
We owe it to you
...for being our matchmaker
Dear, you should pay your respects
I'm pregnant, I can't bow
Right
Have a seat
I remember one thing
When we got married
Our witness said that
If we'd have a baby next year
Then he'd have three cups of wine
Do you remember?
Yes
Although we are poor
But as for the three cups of wine
We must treat the old Sir
Tong...
It's almost noon. Let's go, dear
It's almost noon?
You're sweating
Take this fan
Thank you, dear
There're a few lines of 'sayings'
written on it
Have you read those?
Writings
Meeting a fairy underneath the Ash tree
A loving couple
hoping to spend
the rest of their lives together
Yet the mandarin ducks will be split
Do you get it?
Lts meaning...
No, I don't
Look, a pair of mandarin ducks
One's crying,
the other is about to take off
Dear, why does it have to be so?
They were a loving couple
The female is about to fly
The male is left crying
I don't believe it
I'll show you
Female mandarin duck...
Today is your day to fly
Why don't you just fly?
I can get the male mandarin duck
to fly too
Male mandarin duck...
Why don't you go with her?
You fly off...
Go ahead
Why won't he listen?
The female one is a celestial bird
That's why she can fly to heaven
The male one is but a mortal
That's why he can't fly
Dear
How come you're acting strange today?
If they are a loving couple
Then they shouldn't be split up
Please don't blame me
You know we're like the mandarin ducks
Meeting a fairy underneath the ash tree
Are you a fairy?
Dear, let me tell you the truth
I'm the seventh daughter
of the Jade Emperor
I descended down to earth to marry you
Now my father has found out
He's ordered me to go back
by 12:45 p. M today
It's such a shock
Being separated from my wife
A mortal and a fairy?
Since she's married to me
She shouldn't leave me
I must look for our witness
Do you know who he is?
No
He's the local earth-god
The local earth God
Earth god
Since you're our witness
Now that she has to leave
Why don't you show your powers?
When we got married
The ash tree was our matchmaker
We must go ask the tree
It's useless
Please, I insist
Ash tree, when we got married
You opened your mouth
Now that she's leaving
Why don't you make her stay?
Please speak
Please
Dear, it's just a piece of dumb wood
Hey dumb wood, dumb wood
Why don't you open your mouth now?
You were our matchmaker
and today... Why?
Why can't I make my wife stay?
The loving couple can't be separated
Please don't leave me
My dear
It's almost 12:45 p. M now
I won't let go
This is the Jade Emperor's order
It's 12:45 p.m.
Your Highness please come with us
No, I won't let her go
Or we'll have Tong Yong torn into pieces
My dear
Dear husband
My dear wife
Stop it, please don't hurt him
Please don't hurt him
I'll go with you
Just let me have a moment with him
All right, generals
Yes
Let's go
My husband is lying in a coma
I can do nothing but cry
We are a loving couple
I don't want you to get hurt
Look what they've done
If I don't go back
You'll be killed
Let me write down a note on the tree
So that you can read it when you wake up
Next spring
Underneath the Ash tree
My dear husband
I'll deliver my son to you
I'll be bound by no rules whatsoever
Although we can't be together
But we'll love each other forever
My dear...
Next spring
Underneath the tree
My dear husband
I'll deliver my son to you
No rules are going to stop me
Although we can't be together