This is the Foochow Road in Shanghai
In 1922 Ma Yung Chen was ambushed
at Qing Lin tower
and was mortally injured
He was surrounded by many people
who axed him to death
It's been more than 20 years
and the Foochow Road has changed
but only on the outside;
Inside it is filled with low-lives
Ma Yung Chen of Shangtung
has become a legend
A similar tragedy is about to
re-enact in this place
The hero's name has changed naturally
Our protagonist is a famous person
in this vicinity
Qiu Lian Huan
Master Qiu
Mr. Yu, is this wine alright?
Mr. Yu, this wine…
Get lost
What? Haven't decided yet?
King
Would it be a straight?
Xiao Kai likes card games
It might be a straight
Your turn to call
Marvellous
One dollar
How much do you still have?
Not less than you
You want to chicken out?
Here's 23 grand, you may give up
if you have no guts
A full house
Damn, I've lost again
Ju Fang, let's go
Xiao Kai, don't go,
you haven't lost much today
I suggest you go too
the cards are possessed by a ghost today
Hey, mind what you say
What I say is clear enough
Kid, if you can't bear to lose, don't play
It's for you to buy candy
for your girlfriend
Jin Xi Fu, bring him over
We're all here just for fun, stop
I'll come over myself
Let him go, he's not such a tough guy
Ju Fang
Who is this woman?
The famous socialite
Shen Ju Fang of Shanghai
You don't know her?
I must say
why did you fight with Xiao Kai?
His father is not a nice guy
Right
I know
Qiu Lian Huan? Who is he?
How come you sit at
the same table with his kind?
Boss, you've been away
from the scene for a while
and don't know about the new upstarts
This Qiu Lian Huan is quite well known
around Foochow road
Enough to cause me problems?
Of course not
Who in Shanghai dares do that?
Get my card and bring that
Qiu Lian Huan to see me
Yes
Go…
If you need money
get it from the treasurer
Boss, Xiao Kai has grown up
you should hand over your affairs to him
Gen Bao, we're old friends
don't pull my leg
He isn't of such calibre
Our affairs still require our own efforts
The city still unsettled
as the Japanese have just left
we can use the opportunity
to make a quick buck
Over there, the ball is over there
Well?
Forget it,
that woman is kept by Yu Xiao Kai
I haven't even stepped into the front door
Nonsense, you didn't say I want to see her
I did
The doorman said he's never heard of you
It's over there. Ask him
Give us back the ball…
You fought with them?
Right, my name is not as
popular as tycoons like
Yu Zhen Ting Zeng Gen Bao
It's still a long way off
He kicked it far away
That's why
we want to kick these people away
So we would not be over-shadowed by them
You…
Well? Are you afraid?
It's not that
it's just that no one has ever
messed with them
Someone has to sooner or later
You go back first
If anyone asks say I am at
the home of Shen Ju Fang at Yu Yuan Road
That woman has over 10 people
guarding her door
If you went there…
That's precisely why I want to go there
You will run into trouble I'm afraid
"Shen Residence"
Hey, what are you doing?
I want to see Miss Shen
Who are you?
I am Qiu Lian Huan
Damn you
You want me to charge in?
Do you know what this place is?
Shen residence
Mr. Yu is here
Save it
What ajoke, it doesn't say
'Yu Residence' on the door
I am here to see the master of the house
Alright, if you go in
I'm sure you'll come out deadl
Miss Shen, it's so difficult to see you
Get out
Ask them to get out
You get out
You're mistaken
Not at all
An upstart like you is lucky
to see me twice
Alright
"Yu Zhen Ting"
Master Yu likes to invite
Master Qiu over for dinner
As Master Qiu is not here we cannot decide
No one dares to decline
an invitation from Master Yu
I am bringing you the message,
it's just the same
That's not true
Master Qiu is with Miss Shen
you must know that place well
please make the trip again
If Yu Xiao Kai is there as well
it'd be easy to clear things up
Please go back
Let's go
If we get on Yu Zhen Ting's nerve
we'll be in trouble
I know, but we have no choice
You nincompoops
What difference does it make
even if you were there?
Alright, Qiu Lian Huan
I will teach you a lesson for this
What's the use of your anger here?
Go and speak to him
Prepare the car, I'm off to see my dad
Yes
I think this kid Qiu Lian Huan
will not give you face
I don't think so, who does he think he is?
Real good
This isn't like our old time
What's the matter?
Master Zeng
This afternoon
Qiu Lian Huan went to the girl who
was kept by Xiao Kai and caused trouble
He injured many people there
We let him escape again
Old man
We can't stay in Shanghai anymore
let's move to Mongolia
What are you shouting?
Ask our men to seek out Qiu Lian Huan
regardless of where he is
and what he's doing
bring him to me
Yes
I'll go back and ask our men to find him
We can't let him go on like this
But let's not make a big deal
or we'll exaggerate his importance
I'll go too
When I find him I'll teach him a lesson
Jin Xi Fu, come with me
Yes
I'll go too and make arrangements
Don't be nervous
remember who we are
we are used to his kind
They want to charge in
but will end up all dead
Master, I've heard things
about this Qiu Lian Huan
people say he is not afraid of death
but he can't do anything to us
But Xiao Kai is attracting
too much attention outside
You mean…
I was just guessing
Ask Xiao Kai to be more careful
I'm leaving
Master Zeng
Come here, everyone
Business is here
Go to Bai Sin Bridge again
ask a few men to come here
Yes
Let's go
Put in your efforts, everyone
We'll teach Qiu Lian Huan
a good lesson tonight
Master Qiu
Thanks
Thanks…
You…
Trying to put on airs? I must get you
You've already got me
I didn't mean you
Don't think we wouldn't hit back
That's exactly what I want you to do
Jin Xi Fu, bring him over
Where is Qiu Lian Huan? Speak
Beat him
Damn you
It doesn't matter if you don't speak
we'll wait here till he returns
Let him go
Qiu Lian Huan is back
Master Qiu
Many people came to your home
but haven't left
No, don't
Brother Qiu, you're back
Geng Sheng, don't worry
Whatever they did to you
we'll do the same to them
You messed up my place
You should say something
I'll pay…
What about my men who have been injured?
I'll get them the best doctor
Master Qiu,
you have been given enough face
let Xiao Kai go
Nonsense, you charged in this place
and still say I've been given face?
Just tell us what you want
What's the use of talking to you
I'll take you to your dad
Alright, let me go first
We'll go this way
Boss…he came too fast
and got right to Xiao Kai
l…
Enough
Get the sitting room ready
to welcome the guest
Yes
Go out all of you
He's here
How many men has he brought?
None, just him and Xiao Kai
Master Qiu, thanks for bringing him
I admire your courage to come alone
Someone like you has appeared in Shanghai
it's ajoke
we could have missed you
Xiao Kai is still young
and is backed by Master Yu
if I used too much force, please pardon me
No, someone should teach him a lesson
Don't…
What are you standing there for?
Get in
Wait, the woman you harbour
is not a proper person
If Master Qiu likes her
then you stop seeing her
No way
Have you not had enough? Get inside
Please sit
I am old now
but I too feared nothing when I was young
Please sit
Let this matter rest
Thanks for bringing him back
I'll pay for the damages
It's okay, I can afford them
Master Sua,
Xiao Kai needs to retain his credibility
he won't mention this incident,
how about you?
Don't worry
if we hadn't fought, we wouldn't have met
Master Qiu, please take care
You are too kind
My men are anxious for my return
I must go
Please
Call Master Zeng
Hello, yes
Call from the Yu Residence
Hello
Really?
Alright, I'll come…
I think Yu Zhen Ting wants me
to deal with Qiu Lian Huan
Then we…
He is too old
and should retire
but he insists on staying
I have a plan, Xiao Kai is his life
Tell Miss Shen, Master Qiu is here
Yes
I'm here
Please sit
Master Yu called me
I'm all yours
You don't seem happy to see me
What has that to do with anything?
You like me and have got me
isn't that enough?
You like Xiao Kai
Xiao Kai? I merely pity him
I can give you whatever he could give you
Right, any man can give me that
Don't take me for any man
What's the difference?
You'll know in time
Let's go
Boss, where to?
Go back
Hey, do you know how to drive?
Sorry, I lost control
Sorry is not enough
Forget it. Let's see if the car can start
don't bother with this kind of people
Yes
Attack
Master Qiu, please come with us
and you'll not suffer
Who's your boss?
It's Master Yu naturally
He wouldn't do such a lowly thing
You…
Sit aside
Why have you got into so much trouble?
To have to fight against Yu Zhen Ting
is bad enough
and now you provoke Zeng Gen Bao too
They are his men?
We either destroy others or be destroyed
Blood?
It's mine
Let's go
If we don't deal with him
I don't know what he'll do
He's ruthless enough
Don't worry, I'll take care of it
and avenge Xiao Kai
Thank you, uncle
Qiu Lian Huan is no nice guy
Boss, it's best Xiao Kai went out less
I'm not afraid of him,
I'll deliberately go outside
Then take more men with you
I'm going, contact me if you need anything
Alright
Am I getting old?
I can't even deal with such a person
Miss Shen, I'm going
Don't play tough
you're seriously wounded
If you bump into Zeng Gen Bao's men
you'll be dead
You know he established himself
by the Knife gang
they are desperados
I don't want your pity
like you pity Xiao Kai
Don't go
No one will know you are resting here
I am not pitying you, I want to help you
Is it worth it suffering for a woman?
It's not only for you
I've gone too far on this course
and will end up like this one day
I told you so
Qiu Lian Huan is no nice guy
Why don't you find out
how many men he's brought?
He has only three men
We have over ten people
we could get him back
Get him back? Where is he?
He must be wounded
Even if he's gone into hiding
we could get his whereabouts from his men
with a bit of force
Then do it now
Yes…let's go
We'll deal with Yu Xiao Kai's matter later
Yes…
Let's go
Go
Don't move
Is Master Qiu here?
No, you're…
What's the matter?
Lin Geng Sheng, someone's looking for you
Who?
Master Zeng Gen Bao
Who am I
to have such an honourl
What does he want me for?
Are you going or not?
What's to fear?
My life is cheap
it matters not even if I die
So resolute
Don't worry,
Master Zeng will treat you well
Let's go and look inside
If Master Qiu is in
please invite him to come along
Yes
Master Qiu is not here
What has happened to him?
Not that serious
He killed Master Zeng's men
He has not returned since going out
I don't know where he has gone
Tell Master Zeng by yourself
If he's injured where would he seek help?
I don't know
Qiu Lian Huan is tough
I little expect his man to be tough too
I tell you I want to find him
regardless of where he's hiding
I'll find him
Then look for him yourself
When I find him
you will have trouble
Apart from you, Master Qiu
has 54 men, right?
How do you know that?
I've bought 48 of them
but 6 refused
They have all been eliminated
You are cruel
Lin Geng Sheng,
you're of course worth more
How about ten?
Well?
My relation with Master Qiu
is not for sale
Alright, go then
See him out properly
It's okay, please return
We want to see that you die
Tell Zeng Gen Bao
even if I die today
Stuff these into his stomach
and put him in a bag
Let's go
I must call Lin Geng Sheng
so he'll not worry
Do it tomorrow
Hello, yes, Master Qiu
Nothing much, looking for Lin Geng Sheng
Looking for Lin Geng Sheng?
Master Qiu, where are you?
Who are you?
Master Qiu, I am Ah Mo
just tell me what you want
Where are you?
Right, get Lin Geng Sheng on the phone
He has gone out
What's your number? When he comes back…
No, I must go back
something must be wrong
In that case
you should all the more not go out
I'll investigate for you
Alright, but you can't say I am here
I am no fool
I've bought Qiu Lian Huan's all men
I've also filled
Lin Geng Sheng's stomach with lead
and threw him into the Wang Pao river
Qiu Lian Huan must have
fled to the village for fear
and dare not come to Shanghai
Doesn't seem like
how Qiu Lian Huan would handle things
Xiao Kai, Shen Ju Fang is yours again
The boss is getting old,
he's much too concerned
Uncle, you're right
I've won again today
Smells good
So sweet
Naughty
It looks like we miss one person today
Qiu Lian Huan is finished
Don't mention him again
His men have been bought by Master Zeng
What about his assistant Lin Geng Sheng?
His stomach has been filled with lead
and he has been drowned
Hello
Xiao Kai is really good
Sir, your telephone
Hello, alright
Wait till I've arrived,
don't beat him up yet
When I get there
I'll give him a painful time
We've found Qiu Lian Huan
Let me give him a hard time first
Where did you find him?
In the village of Pui Tung
Wait for me at home tonight
Coming, hurry
Stop running, stand still
If you want to fight, go elsewhere
We're Master Qiu's brothers, hear that?
Yes
Quickly…
You're still here
What's the matter?
Xiao Kai received a call
saying that you've been caught
It must be ajoke
I don't think so
It was a call from a friend
He left right away after he hung up
Never mind him
What news have you got?
What about it?
You're finished
How can I?
Zeng Gen Bao has bought off all your men
Each one has been well paid
What about Lin Geng Sheng?
He won't betray me
They threw Lin Geng Sheng
down into the river
You're all by yourself now,
you haven't recuperated yet
You'll kill yourself
Yes, I'd better go on hiding
Hide at a woman's home and be a coward
and dare not see people
Qiu Lian Huan, watch your mouth
I'm at your mercy, and this is your place
You can do whatever you want
after you've recuperated
Now, sit down
I've no time
I still have a lot of friends
I'll go and find them
I have a lot of friends
Don't trust those scumbags
They are my friends, they are like me
They are like Zeng Gen Bao too
Shut up
If I was afraid of you,
I wouldn't have been with you
Extra…Come for the Extra…
Give me one
"Son of Yu Zhen Ting is kidnapped"
Any news?
Yes
How much they want?
Nothing
Want me to leave Shanghai
I should have left earlier
There won't be a happy ending
for a person like me
I have already handed over
half of the business here to you
Send someone to handle the other half
I'll leave tomorrow
Brother, don't be upset
We'll think of something
when Xiao Kai comes back
Never mind
Gen Bao, you've been with me
ever since the Knife gang first started
He's my only son
Don't be too harsh on him
Boss, what do you mean?
Gen Bao, never mind
Qiu Lian Huan wouldn't put up
such conditions
At the club
he left after he received a call
from friends
Although I am old, I am not stupid
If you suspect me
I'll go with you
No need
Gen Bao, be careful
You'll be treated the same way
you treat others
When I leave tomorrow
will you go with me?
We'll stay with Master Zeng
Alright
Master Zeng has an errand for us
Master Yu, please don't blame us
Ask Gen Bao to come to me
Master Zeng went to examine goods
at some companies
You…
Xiao Kai has been caught
The one who caught Xiao Kai
claimed to be your man
I've been to the club
and they said that Yu Zhen Ting is dead
Zeng Gen Bao is taking care of his funeral
They also said that Zeng Gen Bao
has taken over
all of Yu Zhen Ting's business
I'm afraid
Xiao Kai might have been killed too
The matter is now very clear
It's Zeng Gen Bao
who is playing all the tricks
He is now more powerful
than Yu Zhen Ting used to be
No matter how powerful he is,
I've to find him
Better wait until you recuperate
Ju Fang, I made you so happy last night
how can you say that I haven't recuperated
Tonight I must go and find some help
otherwise he'll grow in power
and make it more difficult
to deal with him
You've got into big troubles
you'd better go on hiding
If you are in need of money,
I can give it to you
What I've mentioned just now…
It's not much, please don't mind
This is…
Zeng Gen Bao is looking for you
You can't stay here for long
What's wrong?
Your boss and I are sworn brothers
"Sworn brothers"
Don't worry, your troubles are mine too
Make yourself at home
Those who I called friends all deserted me
It isn't like that
I still need to go somewhere else,
we'll be in touch
Don't go
Why?
Brother, since you are here
we should have a chat
Alright, this is what good friends are for
When Zeng Gen Bao comes,
give him my regards
Geng Sheng
None of those who are with us
are human enough
Neither of us are
"Qing Lin Tower"
Newspapers…Come for a newspaper
Newspapers…
Master Qiu, you have guts
You too
Yu Zhen Ting has helped you before
how can you treat him like this?
It's a world where the fittest survive
You are right
Qiu Lian Huan,
beg for pardon and you'll be alright
I definitely won't
I am tired of this life
Sorry, please leave now
Go…
Grab the weapons
Master Zeng looks highly on me after all
You've even sent your favourite Knife gang
Qiu Lian Huan, you have two options
One is to serve me
If you do
you'll be my right hand
If not, you'll die
I'd rather die than to serve you
But even if I have to die
I'll avenge for Lin Geng Sheng first
"Hui Le Lane"
Qiu Lian Huan has just been stabbed
His stomach is cut open,
don't be afraid of him
Kill him
Qiu Lian Huan is finished
Attack
Go…hurry
"Qiu Lian Huan was killed"