[Rachel] I'm just
trying to understand why.
[Dr. Grillo, on phone] You know why.
-You didn't put in the effort.
-But... but I did, sir.
All my course papers
were handed in on time
my sources were listed,
but yet you still gave me an F.
Rachel, I don't have to
justify the grade I gave you.
So that's it?
I'll have to carry over
the course next semester?
Well, that's entirely up to you.
Meaning what?
It's unofficial.
I haven't handed in
the grades to the faculty yet.
Then, sir, you can please take
another look at my paper and reconsider.
Please.
Maybe.
Dr. Grillo, what can I--
Don't mention my name!
Why did you mention my name?
I'm sorry, sir. Please.
I can't take another semester
just because of an elective course.
Please help me.
Please.
You'll have to help me
to help you.
I... I don't understand.
Okay. No problem.
Wait, hold on, sir!
Sir? Are you there? Sir?
-Dr. Grillo?
-Stop mentioning my name.
I'm sorry, sir,
but please help me. Please.
Rachel, I don't have time for this.
No, no, no, sir,
please don't cut the call.
Are you ready to do
the needful? Yes or no?
[sighs]
What do I need to do?
The Sunrise Motel.
-I know it.
-Tomorrow.
6pm. Go and pay for a room there.
-Then call me.
-Jesus!
Really?
Otherwise I hand in
the grade as it is. Finito!
[line goes dead]
[Students ranting]
Gentlemen, wait, wait!
This is the last act
you'll do in this university.
I am a Christian.
Ahh! Apostle.
Carry him!
[crowd screaming]
Meaning you could have chosen a path
far less destructive
and consequential than
that taken by you.
This university has a
forum for airing such grievances
but you ignored that platform
to take
to the option of being the jury and...
uh, judge...
in a complaint that had not
been brought before the senate.
That arbitrary decision
has resulted in a loss of life.
That is a matter for the judiciary
outside this citadel of higher learning
to deliberate upon.
But as far as this
institution is concerned,
all three of you,
including the one that ran away,
are hereby rusticated from the university.
Your academic records are henceforth
expunged in their entirety.
That is our ruling.
[Kwesi] No, no, no.
Wait, Remi.
Hold on, look,
you're not even 21 years old yet.
[Gloria] Would you
leave the poor girl alone?
What is your problem?
Why are you hounding her?
[Pidgin] Are you the
one paying her school fees?
It's okay, Gloria.
If I had one naira for every time
someone was amazed by how young I am
I'd be a millionaire in dollars by now.
Just 20 and you're
already sitting for your Masters?
Hmm. Hmm-mm.
I was still writing my
university entrance exams in Accra...
-when I was 20.
-But that is the difference.
[Ibibio] You are a dullard.
You know what I mean?
Like a compound dullard.
That's the difference.
What does "Nton" mean?
Charlie, don't worry, it means nothing.
But you're just an amazingly,
intelligent young man.
Anyway, age is a question
of mind over matter.
-Tell him.
-If you don't mind,
it does not matter.
-Philosophy 101.
-Come on, come on.
-[sighs]
-Oh, no!
Professor Osagie!
-I hope he's not taking this course.
-Why?
Well, he lectured in Ghana
during my bachelor's degree.
The man is stingy with grades.
In my whole four years as an undergraduate
I never saw that man smile once.
Um... Good morning, class.
Good morning, sir.
Um...
For those of you who don't know me...
I do.
...I am Professor Osagie,
dean, postgraduate college.
Scholars...
we are in the presence of...
academic royalty.
He graduated...
a first-class honors degree
in social science...
from the Sorbonne University in Paris...
at a tender age of seventeen.
[students murmuring]
-At seventeen?
-He then polished off a PhD...
-Sound familiar?
-...in Humanities
at Harvard University.
Having lectured in
various higher institutions,
he was appointed...
as a special envoy in conflict zones
in Sudan
and Iraq by the United Nations.
We are therefore indeed honored
to have him in this institution
as your...
senior course supervisor...
for your master's degree programs.
Professor Lucien N'Dyare.
My, my, my!
After this type of introduction,
I feel like I should just stand here
and pose for photographs.
[students laughing]
Wow.
I think I've just met
the father of my unborn babies.
Thank you very much, Professor.
You are welcome.
The dean is somewhat... correct,
because I am from Senegal.
But my mother is from the Benin Republic
and my maternal grandmother
is from Nigeria.
-Wow.
-I guess that makes me a Nigerian.
[students laughing]
I am... looking forward...
to embarking on
this journey with all of you.
So I wish you the best of all,
the best of luck, and, um...
thank you very much for having me.
-Once again, you are welcome.
-Yes.
Thank you.
-Excuse me, sir.
-Just a minute, sir.
Please just a minute of your time.
Just one question, please.
Just one question.
-Okay.
-Prof, why is there so much controversy
surrounding the line of demarcation
between India and Pakistan?
Is China's rising dominance a sign
that communism is
indeed now a coded password?
The rise of xenophobia in South Africa,
why is it coming from the blacks
whom we freed,
rather than coming from the whites
whom we campaigned
against during apartheid?
Are you single?
[chuckles, sighs]
-No, I'm married.
-Ouch.
Your friend has no shame.
She'll soon ask the learned fellow
to guess her bra size.
Blessed with two children
who reside in Paris.
Mr. Kwesi, come on. Everyone
is impressed with his credentials.
Uh, the prof's credentials are
the last thing on Gloria's mind, trust me.
Why don't you just ask her out already?
It's pretty obvious you've been
crushing on Gloria
-since forever.
- Yeah, right.
[laughs]
I see.
but we can still, you know,
show you around.
So regarding your question,
India-Pakistan situation
is extremely complex...
What?
Look, I was only trying to see
if I could gather some,
you know, extra classes.
Sure.
Look, let's go, girl.
[whistle blows]
-[instructor calling out]
-[students replying]
Good class, everybody. One minute break.
Gather round together.
Okay, so that's how it should be...
Girl! You have to take it easy on me.
Auntie, fetch the ball.
So now this is my turn to serve.
-Serve.
-Okay, here we go.
Yes!
That's a smash.
Go get the ball.
-Hey. What's up?
-My ball?
Looking for this, huh?
My name is Koyejo.
Final year. Med school.
And over there is my brother.
He's a lecturer and he's into basketball.
[Yoruba] My elder brother.
So what's your name?
-Moremi.
-Oh, my goodness.
Bloody Jambites.
I'm not asking for your hall of residence.
I'm asking for your name.
[Yoruba] My name is Moremi.
-The ball?
-What?
[Yoruba] So you can speak Yoruba? Huh?
You are saying it like
you are speaking Egun dialect.
[laughs]
My ball.
-Where were you during freshers week?
-Moremi!
-What's going on?
-I'm coming.
Where were you? Hmm?
What were you looking for
during freshers week?
-[English] The ball?
-Okay.
[English] Somebody's got attitude.
-[Pidgin] Take.
-Thanks.
Okay.
So what does Jackie Chan want?
-Serve.
-Really, you're not going to tell me?
The social and economic
ramifications of a political process
that does not include...
the will of the citizenry...
will always conclude in a conundrum.
Leading to the breakdown
of that very political process...
that spur the extremity
in the first place.
Now, a perfect example
is the 1956 British handling
of the Suez crisis.
Yes, they brought down the government
of the Prime Minister Anthony Eden.
But at the same time,
they turned Egypt's Colonel Nasser
into a hero.
The British were simply
protecting their neo-colonial interest.
They did not take into account
the social and economic will
of a group of people
who just had enough...
of the British interference...
in their internal affairs.
That's your toaster out there.
Now...
the Suez crisis became a clarion call...
a reference point to the rest of Africa...
still under colonial rule.
I can't... [chuckles] No, no.
[French] Excuse me.
Kwesi, everybody...
I hope that you are not
just quoting me verbatim?
This is a master's degree program.
I don't want you to just lap it all up.
I want you to analyze it,
disagree with it, even.
This is not dogma.
Ehnn?
This is an intellectual discourse.
We are all learning here.
Well, the only difference is that
I am being paid.
[students laughing]
All right, now
I've divided the class into...
five tutorial groups.
One over which I will preside,
and the rest will be shared
amongst the other lecturers.
So please come up
and see what group you belong to.
-Why is she so excited about everything?
-Moremi!
Okay, I will catch up with you guys.
[sighs]
[Yoruba] Yeah, how can I help you?
First of all, hmm...
I'm legit sorry.
Okay?
I swear down.
I have been searching for you.
I have looked everywhere for you.
I went to every department,
every faculty, even every cafeteria.
And then it dawned on me.
What if this girl is not
even an undergraduate?
What if she's postgraduate?
God, as if the ground should
open up and swallow me.
I swear, I'm sorry.
No need.
I'd push you in myself.
Mister "I'm Koyejo.
Final year Med School."
She got me.
Will you ever forget that scenario?
Will you ever?
Eventually.
Hmm! Eventually?
-Eventually? Okay, that means we're cool?
-Hmm.
Do you still want me to
push you in that hole in the ground?
Please, please don't be angry.
Don't push me into it.
Can I...
have your number?
Please?
Not to worry. You'll be fine.
Remember what I said.
It's not like a court,
but a senate hearing
carries a lot of weight.
You are the complainant,
he is the respondent.
Only the panel will
be allowed to ask questions.
I cannot address the panel.
Neither can I question the respondent,
nor the...
um, witnesses.
And same goes for the representation
of the respondent.
But I will be allowed
to whisper advice to you.
It's a closed hearing.
That's why we didn't
bother to invite your parents.
How are you holding up?
Everyone on campus is staring at me.
Your story has gone viral.
I don't want to read any of it.
We need the noise.
-[sighs]
-We need the publicity.
I just want to stay in school,
continue my studies.
The Ajike Advocacy Centre
hired me to give you
the best representation at this hearing.
I promise to do that, hmm?
What happens if I lose?
Do you remember the case of Dr. Grillo?
A couple of years back?
No, you wouldn't. Your first degree
wasn't in Nigeria, was it?
Dr. Grillo was a university lecturer
whose conversation with a female student
demanding for sex
before he changed her grades
was caught on tape.
Now, instead of the female student
to hand over to the university authorities
the recorded conversation,
her boyfriend decided to lay a trap
for Dr. Grillo in a local hotel.
Suffice to say, the entire escapade
ended in a tragic death.
And all the students involved,
including the female student in question,
were expelled from this university.
And they were then jailed
by a high court for manslaughter.
So I could be rusticated too
for slandering a lecturer?
At least you didn't kill him.
Let's go.
I'd like to welcome everyone
to this committee meeting and...
first I'd like to introduce
every member of the panel
starting from Uzoamaka Chukwu,
who is representing the student body.
And on my right is Professor Osagie,
one of our highly respected deans.
To my left is our dearest
Professor Yahaya.
And Dr. Mrs. Nwosu. Thank you very much
for being part of the panel.
Obviously here is Miss Oluwa
with her legal representation,
and Professor Lucien
and his legal representation.
And I have the privilege
to chair this session.
My name is Professor Ibukun Awosika.
So I'd like everyone to know that
the entire proceeding will
be audio-recorded by the clerk
who is sitting over there,
so we'll have no dispute
about anybody's contribution.
So, Miss Oluwa, shall we proceed?
My, um...
My first one-on-one contact
with Professor N'Dyare
was after a tutorial class.
The political inclination of any nation
has the most profound impact
on the foreign policy of that country,
in terms of how it
deals with its neighbors.
Now, Senegal and Gambia
are both capitalist by nature.
Imagine that one nation
is a communist country
with leanings towards Russia.
And the other one was a capitalist economy
with leanings towards the west.
Yes?
I don't think it would make
any difference whatsoever.
Sorry, I didn't get your name?
Moremi Oluwa.
Moremi.
During my tour of the campus,
I saw a hall of residence
with the same name.
The university named a hall
after you already?
I mean you must be either
highly intelligent or highly connected.
Just a mere coincidence, sir.
All right, go on with your point.
When it comes to African countries,
culture is a strong determining factor,
so Senegal is a former French colony,
Gambia British,
yet culture trumps ideology.
It takes far more
than political inclinations
to tear neighboring countries apart.
What of Sudan and South Sudan,
always at loggerheads?
Well, that was formerly one country.
Siblings disagree all the time.
Just like North and South Korea.
All right.
Moving on...
[French] This is just impossible,
I can't drive this car.
What a mess.
Professor N'Dyare?
-Moremi?
-[French] Having issues with your car?
You speak French?
Yes, I have a French
baccalaureate qualification.
Did you take any electives
in mechanical engineering?
[laughs]
[sighs]
I must tell you...
I don't want you to make fun of me.
[English] I don't know how to drive stick.
Excuse me?
[French] I learnt how to drive in America
on an automatic gear shift.
But this university
loaned me a car with a stick gear.
You mean you don't know how
to drive a car with a manual gear?
Well... Stick.
Your car key, sir?
What do you intend doing?
Shall we?
Okay, Professor.
I'm going to teach you how to
drive a manual gear shift automobile.
Where are you heading to?
-Road 8.
-Okay.
Sir, you've got to understand...
the gear ratio when driving manual.
When driving stick.
[Lucien] I think it's just
too much information and jargon.
Automatic is much more easier.
[Moremi] But with manual, you're
in control, the one in the driver seat.
In an automatic, gear change is automated.
[Lucien] l guess you like
to be in control. [laughs]
Thank you so much.
You're very welcome, sir.
I might have to ask
the university for a driver,
or get an automatic car instead.
Just practice, it makes perfect.
If you continue to teach me,
then no problem.
Please come in. The least I can do
is offer you a drink, some refreshments?
That's okay, I was heading to
the supermarket when I ran into you.
-But it's a long way from here.
-There's a bus stop around the corner.
Ah. Okay. Well, thank you.
Goodbye.
Wow.
-Excuse me?
-Sorry.
Good.
Um... Professor N'Dyare.
In your first account
of the same encounter,
you declared that it was Miss Oluwa...
who actually said to you
that she was coming into your residence.
Is that correct?
She said she had time to kill.
And I...
I told her it would be highly
inappropriate for me to invite her in.
I thanked her for her service...
and she left.
Liar!
Okay, as things
are getting a little heated
I think it will be a good point for us
to take a break for lunch,
and when we come back from lunch
we can pick up things and continue.
Thank you very much for your time.
A penny for them?
The panel...
I saw a lot of doubt on their faces today.
Especially from my own dean,
Professor Osagie.
Should I tell you how I met my husband?
After law school,
I was a junior associate in a law firm,
and he was a senior partner
at the same firm.
He asked me out three times
before I finally agreed
to go on a date with him.
We've been married now for... 21 years,
have three adorable
but seriously troublesome children.
My point is...
He was my senior in the workplace.
Now after the third time,
would it not be considered harassment
in today's context?
There's a thin line between
wooing and oppression,
especially when one party
has power over the other.
What we must do...
is make sure that we erase the doubt
from the minds of the panel.
I have to return these calls, okay?
See you in there.
Hey.
Mr. Kwesi, you're a witness!
You're not supposed to be talking to me.
Yeah, right.
They should come and arrest me then.
So how are you doing?
Be careful you're not being used.
You've become the poster girl
for every woman
with a grudge against
a male lecturer on this campus.
Yeah. They all think they can swim,
until somebody drowns.
Remi, I...
Look, I shouldn't have left you alone
that night after the Easter party.
I should have waited.
Mr. Kwesi...
it's okay.
All right, See you.
[sobbing]
And... well, that takes us back
to the situation of the refugees.
The refugees camp,
displaced person, IDP... All over.
We are not taking any questions.
And, in any case, for those of you who...
have not yet understood,
or who are not following,
please refer to my...
page 12 and 14 of the materials.
Some of you are in possession.
I've given it out. You know how to get it.
And then...
now to the real situation
of international relations
flashpoints all over the world.
Let us... A situation
whereby a no-fly zone...
has been established in an airspace.
[Lucien] Hence, society tends to mirror
that which it reflects.
Now, if we take any group of people
and we ask them if they're happy
with the government they have,
if they say no,
chances are that they're living in
a society where freedom of speech
is enshrined in the constitution.
If they say yes, well, chance is
that it's a totalitarian society
where fear is the order of the day.
Now, in that scenario,
how does an arbitrator mediate
to the best interest of the party
that brought the grievance to the table?
-Yes, Kwesi?
-Sir,
you don't mediate to the interest
of the party that brings the grievance.
You mediate to the interest
of all parties concerned.
Hmm. What if serving all parties
inadvertently put one country
at a disadvantage?
Hmm. Well, sir, if anyone
had the answer to that brainteaser,
-there would be peace in the Middle East.
-[laughter]
Yes, Moremi?
Somebody is going to
walk away unhappy regardless.
What if hostilities are declared,
based on a failed resolution?
Resolutions that lead to an escalation
of hostilities are not resolutions.
They are proxy wars,
fought under the guise of covert
economic and political interest.
So you'd do away
with resolutions altogether?
No, sir. I just wouldn't present
a resolution as one
if it has no chance of resolving anything.
Otherwise you'd have Rwanda
all over again.
A situation in which
UN peacekeeping forces stood aside
whilst up to a million people
were brutally massacred.
That's not a resolution.
That's genocide.
All right.
Well, all I know is that jollof rice
originated from Senegal.
[students laughing]
[Kwesi] Come on!
Come on, jollof rice is from Ghana!
All right, calm down!
Calm down! Listen, Kwesi.
Nigerians will never agree with you.
All right, so now let's look at
the aspect of human rights violations
within the framework
of a failed state.
-Okay, all right.
-Yeah?
[sighs] I don't know why
it keeps stalling.
Calm down. You're pulling
your foot off the clutch too fast.
There has to be a balance
between the accelerator and the clutch.
There is no logic to this.
We have two legs. Why make three pedals?
It is ridiculous.
Listen, start the car again.
The gear needs to be in Switzerland
before you start the ignition.
Switzerland?
Neutral.
Switzerland - neutral.
-Very funny.
-Okay.
Don't forget,
ease your foot off the clutch
whilst gently pressing the accelerator.
Slowly, okay, slowly.
Perfect! Brilliant!
Very good, Professor.
Well done.
Okay, now you're going
to shift it down into gear two.
-Like this?
-Perfect, very good.
-You're really getting the hang of it.
-That works.
[laughter, indistinct chatter]
I can see that you're now an expert.
Thanks to you.
You were very patient with me.
-Thank you.
-My pleasure, sir.
I love to resolve conflicts.
Conflict?
Which conflict are we talking about?
-There's no conflict.
-Sir...
I think the gearbox of this car
would disagree with you.
[laughs]
What was it like working at the UN?
Working in UN?
It's nice, but quite stressful.
When you're working for a common goal,
people would want
to frustrate your efforts.
For as long as I can remember,
I've always dreamed of
working with the United Nations.
You?
Somehow I saw an academic in you.
Well, first of all,
my father is a retired diplomat.
Then secondly...
[Lucien] The Kevin Carter photograph.
Sudan. 1993.
-The famine.
-Mm-hmm.
A vulture waiting for
an emaciated African child to die
so that it can devour its remains.
A photojournalist who could do nothing,
but stood aside to
record the image for posterity.
I first came across that photo
when I was 11 years old.
It has haunted me ever since.
It haunted the photographer, too.
He committed suicide a year later.
I vowed from that day
to spend the rest of my life
trying to make a difference
to the world at large.
Like your namesake Moremi Ajasoro?
[chuckles]
You've read about her?
Of course, I did my research.
Infiltrated the ranks
of the Ugbo forest tribe,
discovered their weakness, and...
saved her people of Ile-Ife from invasion.
She was quite the heroine.
I can only aspire.
We all aspire, my dear.
But sometimes a prophet is without honor
only in his hometown.
Would you like to take a walk?
Yes.
You and I, we are new-age rebels.
Rebels with a cause.
-We ruffle feathers.
-We roar.
-Mansa Musa!
-Che Guevara!
-Toussaint Louverture!
-Obafemi Awolowo!
-Nelson Mandela!
-Kwame Nkrumah!
Moremi Ajasoro!
[Lucien] This absolutely beautiful.
[Moremi] It's amazing, look at this.
Well...
Um... That might be...
all for the day.
Please submit your term papers on time.
Moremi!
We were just talking about you.
Listen, sister, we just want you to know
that if there's any help you require
-we are here for you.
-Thank you.
We know what you're going through,
and we salute you for taking
a stance for all the females on campus.
That's why we've been distributing
these flyers all over campus.
These sex-for-grades scandals must stop!
I really appreciate this,
but I need to go.
Remi, we are here for you always.
We're your Ajike foot soldiers.
-Anything you need, just holler.
-Thank you! Okay.
[both]
We stand shoulder-to-shoulder with you
in the struggle against
oppression and victimization!
Bye!
Keep them! Spread the word!
Gloria!
[Gloria] Birthday girl with the sauce!
Thank you.
Hi, Gloria. Thank you.
I didn't even want to make a big deal,
but Koyejo...
-Hmm.
-Look...
if lover boy decides to make
your 21st the hit event,
what is your problem? Girl, chill.
Well, to be honest, he's growing on me.
Like I don't even know already!
I know that.
Look, all I'm asking for is,
I must be the one
to choose the uniformed color.
-I have to choose the head tie.
-Head tie?
There are a few things I need to achieve
in life before I walk down the aisle.
Okay, like what exactly? Huh?
Madam Secretary-General
for United Nations?
I already know that.
Now tell me something else.
Whatever, auntie.
Anyway, you know Mr. Kwesi
is going to be there tonight.
Mm-hmm.
And so what?
Well, Mr. Kwesi has been crushing
on a certain someone.
Please, please, please.
In case you have not noticed,
I don't have time
for all those small boys.
Wait! What small boy?
Look, babes...
let me help you with that.
You already know my stance.
I have no time for all these
small boys on campus.
As long as you are a guy
that is in this school,
you are a small boy,
and I don't have time for that, baby girl.
Wait, so Mr. Kwesi, who is 40 years old,
worked for 10 years in Ghana
after his first degree,
and then returned to school
for his PG is a small boy?
Sweetheart, let me help you with that.
But you know,
like I always told you, baby girl,
but sugar, you've always
known my preference in men.
I mean, I've never hidden it from you.
I like men like...
you know, Professor Lucien.
Excuse me?
He is my kind of man.
Honey, he's mature, he's...
He's my kind of man, and look, listen,
this man has always had eyes on you, okay?
I am not... I didn't even make the cut
for his tutorial classes,
but you made it. Baby girl, come on now.
Do it for your girl.
Hook a girl up now, girlfriend.
-Gloria!
-Hook me up!
Gloria! Respect yourself.
Okay.
But you don't like the guy.
I like him, so what's up with you?
He's married. He's our lecturer.
What does that even matter?
Okay.
I'm not even going to entertain this.
Come on, let's go.
Baby girl, come on now.
I can't even play with you. It was a joke.
Please, I don't do lecturers.
-Okay, okay, let's go.
-I don't do lecturers.
-You already know that.
-Let's go.
I was just playing with you.
You're too "extra, please."
[Koyejo] There you go.
-Close those eyes, babes.
-[Moremi] Where are we going?
Don't worry about it.
So you don't know
the meaning of surprise again, huh?
I understand surprise,
but this is too much.
It's not.
It's not too much once it's Koyejo,
and once it's for Moremi,
-it's not too much
-Aw, babes.
-Just take a step.
-Okay, okay.
-One step at a time.
And then...
-[♪ Happy Birthday To You plays]
-Oh, my God!
-My pal!
-[Seun Kuti] My brother!
-Thank you.
-How you doing?
-Thank you so much.
-Thanks for coming out.
-Happy birthday, Moremi.
-Thank you.
You shall grow old and live long.
Fine girl, thanks for coming out.
I'm such a fan.
Charlie, hope you're enjoying Nigeria?
Yetty, please bring the cake.
Oh, my God!
I bought a cake for Remi.
Have it.
-Treat her well.
-Normal.
You guys have fun tonight.
-I will see you backstage.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy.
-I hail.
I'm your fan.
Wow!
[Pidgin] It's amazing
Boo, how do you manage to do that?
I'm telling you!
So I didn't tell you
Seun and I are cousins.
Huh?
Wait, so you are related to Fela?
Uncle Fela?
Seun's mum and my mum they are sisters.
Wait! For real, for real, for real?
I'm just kidding.
And to think that I almost believed him.
You're a fool, do you know that?
-You're a fool?
-I agree.
What type of stunt, I mean...
That was superb.
Seun is my friend, anyways.
You know, I met him through a friend,
so we've been like this ever since.
But you're a big guy now. I trust you.
-You delivered.
-You know now.
Oh, my gosh.
This has been my best birthday ever.
Put it here.
Mr. Man, don't even think it.
Guys, where are we going to?
Let's go somewhere. Let's just go.
[Seun Kuti and the Egypt 80 Band playing]
Greatest Nigerian students!
Great!
Greatest, greatest Nigerian students!
Stop!
So mostly, yeah,
at the tail end of the semester
we're having this grading
in our karate listing.
So I am finally going for my...
My baby, my black belt.
Like I even know what that means.
[laughs]
Okay, let me explain it to you.
[Yoruba] You see, in karate...
-there are different stages, understand?
-Mm-hmm.
The first stage, as a beginner...
-Yes.
-..you start with white belt.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
From white you move to yellow,
from yellow you move to green,
from green to blue from blue to brown,
then finally the highest standard,
black belt.
-Black belt.
-Yeah.
Is it not all about fighting Chinese?
[laughs]
Wait, wait, wait.
Besides, how do you even reconcile
learning how to fight
and training to be a doctor?
-Really?
-Yes.
-Yes, really.
Okay, okay.
Karate is not solely about
just fighting, are you listening?
-It's more self-discipline.
-Okay.
-Do you understand? And self-defense.
Hmm. And... Um...
Let me break it down, okay?
Somebody is giving me
a stance to work with.
-Aha!
-Where?
-Let me give you a tip, yeah?
You want to learn about karate?
-Don't worry, Jackie Chan!
-Wait.
-No!
-Babe, this might come in handy now.
-Okay.
-Calm down, let me show you.
Let the master teach you
how to do this thing.
Okay, take for instance, yeah?
Imagine an assailant, yeah,
-holding on to your hand this way.
-Yes.
Your two hands and you can't
break free, you can't do nothing.
Two things you can do. First one,
either you break free by force
and run as fast as you can.
Or you close in on the attack this way.
Okay. [laughs]
I hope you're not
using style to tap current.
[chuckles] I am tapping?
-Oh, my goodness.
-Yes.
Will you be serious
with this thing please?
-Okay.
-This thing might come in handy,
and I am not joking about it. Please.
You close in.
You have to pull him in or pull her in,
or whatever the case is,
and use your knee cap.
-Yes.
-Yes, and you hit him in the scrotum.
-In the what?
-In the balls.
-Jesus!
-Mm-hm.
-Okay, okay, okay.
-You to want to try?
Yeah, let's try, let's try again.
Wait, calm down, okay?
-Go on, try it.
-Okay.
Moremi…
-Relax.
-Relax what?
-Don't damage my family planning?
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, yeah.
-Like this?
-Yeah, but a little harder.
Okay. Like this?
Babe, you're a witch. I'm not
doing this thing with you again.
-You're not even taking this serious.
-Okay, okay, okay.
-I saw you on Thursday
-Yes?
-With your lecturer. You guys drove past.
-My course supervisor, yeah.
-A lecturer?
-Yeah. Professor N'Dyare.
He's here on
a foreign exchange attachment.
He was actually at the show tonight.
Seeing you with him like that...
Are you listening?
I don't like it.
I was just teaching
him how to drive manual.
I don't like it.
Okay.
-No, you have to be careful.
-Okay, okay, okay.
And I'm serious about this.
You know how some men
see overfamiliarity as a green light.
[sighs] Okay, I've heard you.
-What is okay?
-Okay.
Before you now say that,
I am jealous, yes.
Yes, you're jealous, yes,
you're very jealous.
So I need to say it, so that you know.
[Lucien] I made her understand
that I was not in the business
of securing jobs for
students after graduation.
She was very charming, tenacious.
I had no idea there was
an undercurrent to her modus operandi.
Hence no immediate
cause for alarm at the time.
[Prof. Yahaya] Hmm.
Professor N'Dyare,
and what eventually
raised the alarm bells for you?
When Miss Oluwa...
intimated that she was
prepared to do anything...
as long as she'd get that referral.
Aha! And how did Miss Oluwa
go about doing that to you?
[whispering]
By revealing that...
she wanted to indulge me
in a sexual relationship.
Sorry, she legit told you that?
Yes.
In a one-to-one
meeting we had at my office
regards her dissertation.
[Moremi, in French] I assumed
that if I had a presupposition
I have to defend it
with research and citations.
Yeah, with original content.
I like your premise,
and your first chapter is excellent,
but for your chapter two and three
I am not so sure.
It talks more of the situation
from a third party's point of view
than it does from yours.
It's like, whose dissertation is this?
Is it yours? Or your source?
Aside from that,
let me hear your hypothesis.
Take note of my comments in red.
Okay, thank you, Professor.
Professor?
When it's just you and I together,
you can call me Lucien.
I'm not entirely sure
that would be appropriate.
But I insist.
I'd rather maintain...
the status quo.
My old supervising professor at Harvard,
I called him David.
That is America, this is Nigeria.
And I am Lucien.
And I am Nigerian.
The moment I call someone
of your age difference
by name...
it means I have...
I have stopped respecting you.
Why are you always so defensive?
You know, when you taught me
how to drive stick...
you were very relaxed.
I was the tutor then. In control.
Mm-hmm, then relax.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Yes.
-The medical student?
-How do you know?
I know.
And with your boyfriend,
are you also in control?
That's not something...
I'm comfortable discussing with you.
[laughs]
So you can talk to me about
the economic effect of Brexit
within the European Union,
but your sex life is a no-go area?
Come on!
So it is forbidden?
Now you've really got me curious.
I have a funny feeling that in bed
you like riding horse.
If that's all, I want to leave.
That will be all.
Moremi?
My favorite color is red.
In spite of my informing
Miss Oluwa that...
I do not appreciate
any sexual advance from her...
she pulled down her pants...
and showed me a glimpse of her underwear.
I was utterly shocked and embarrassed.
Professor N'Dyare, after that incident,
did you bring this matter to the attention
of the dean of postgraduate school?
Unfortunately not.
Why?
I wished not to adversely affect
Miss Oluwa's coursework.
And I thought she would get over
her infatuation with me
in due course.
And did she get over the infatuation?
There was no infatuation.
Miss Oluwa,
you will conduct yourself appropriately.
-Yes, Professor N'Dyare?
-[sighs] For a while.
And then my tutorial class
embarked upon a trip to Dakar.
[Koyejo] Dakar?
As in Senegal?
[Moremi, in Yoruba] It's a field trip.
It's part of my course requirements.
Professor N'Dyare really had to pull
some strings to get the trip approved.
[Koyejo] N'Dyare?
Same lecturer who tried to
figure out your sexual preference?
Come on,
it wasn't quite like that, Koyejo.
Okay, you're the one who came
running to me with complaints.
You told me Professor
was talking inappropriately,
like he's been inappropriate with you.
Maybe I overreacted.
[Koyejo] Maybe you don't want to
read the writing on the wall.
That was over a month ago,
but everything's been cool since then.
Remi, that man is on your case.
It's okay, it's okay.
Don't worry, it's okay.
You see this field trip, eh?
Truthfully,
from my mind of mind,
I don't like it.
I don't want you to go.
-Excuse me?
-Yes!
Join another tutorial group,
do you understand?
You guys are not the only group
going on a field trip.
There are different groups in the class,
you can join another one.
I'm not here to ask your permission.
I came to inform you.
So it's like that?
Hmm?
It's like that now?
Dude!
The last time I looked,
it wasn't your signature
on the check that pays my tuition fees.
Koyejo!
Lucien!
Professor Sembene.
[French] Good to see you.
I'm pleased to see you too,
our traveling professor.
-In fact, in fact.
-It's been quite a while.
Indeed, good to see you.
And this must be the Nigerian tribe
that has adopted you.
In fact, in fact.
Everybody, please come down, come down.
Let me introduce you to Professor.
This time around, I brought ten students.
I must say, they are all exceptional.
The goal is to share some
Senegalese culture with them
-and to tour them around Dakar.
-That's very good.
Everybody is here? Yes, I believe so, yes.
So it is my honor to introduce you
to Professor Sembene.
-Mm-hmm.
-He's the head of, uh...
of department of International Relations
here at Université Cheikh Anta Diop.
But more importantly,
he's my old lecturer.
-Not too old though.
-[laughs]
You're correct.
-A very warm welcome to you all.
-Thank you.
I'll be hosting a reception for you
at the Dean's lodge this evening
where you can meet some
of your Senegalese colleagues.
He's saying that we are going to
have a dinner tonight at the Dean's lodge.
-Thank you, sir.
-Thank you.
Is anyone fluent in French?
French?
She's my brightest star.
-Yes?
-She speaks French fluently.
Moremi.
-It's nice to meet you, Moremi.
-Good day, Professor.
-How are you?
-I am fine, thank you.
I am delighted.
You will be the official interpreter.
Yes, okay, with all pleasure, sir.
-That's good.
-Thanks a lot.
All right, I will be waiting
when you all are done for today.
You're welcome
and I will be the translator.
-See you tonight.
-See you all tonight.
-Thank you, Doctor.
-I'm going for an appointment now.
-Very well, see you later.
-Yes, see you later.
See you tonight. Okay.
Come on, guys, go up.
It was so fun. It's beautiful.
Oh, my gosh.
-Thank you, Prof.
-[students cheering]
-My translator.
-Good evening, sir.
-How are you?
-I'm fine, thank you.
-Hope you are having a good time?
-Mm-hmm. Thank you.
So near, yet so far.
I'm fine.
I know that look. Lovers' tiff.
don't let anyone spoil this
wonderful experience for you.
Don't believe a word this man says.
I taught him everything he knows.
Professor.
[indistinct chatter]
-As you can see.
-What's that?
I kept your old Peugeot for you.
Really? You should have sold the jalopy.
No! You used to love driving it.
[laughs]
Thanks for hosting us tonight, okay?
So, we'll see you very soon.
Okay, thanks, Uncle.
-My translator.
-Thanks, Professor.
-Thanks a lot, sir.
-Very well.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, everyone.
[Prof. Sembene] In conclusion...
it is imperative to weigh
the social ramification of
imposing economic sanctions
vis-à-vis the political issues
in that country.
It's crucial to weigh
the social consequences
of these economic sanctions.
...otherwise an embargo
will do more harm than good.
That's it. Professor, finally,
thanks once again.
-Thank you, too.
-Thanks for the privilege.
-Dear students, thank you.
-Thank you to my Nigerian students.
[students cheering]
Thank you, sir.
-I think it's cool, you know.
-It is really cool, to be honest.
And next, after the market,
we have more things and then,
-you know--
-Hey! Hey! Check this out.
[inaudible]
So right here is something
that was donated by Guadeloupe.
That happened in 1999.
It's called
the Statue of the Liberation of Slaves.
What we have here is
very important to the island.
It came from France back in 1902, 1904...
[indistinct chatter]
-Good afternoon.
-Good day.
-What is your name?
-Samba.
Where are we going?
[Moremi] Beautiful.
It's unbelievable.
Even more beautiful at night.
This is probably
the best view of the country.
I want you to...
bask in the serenity of the view,
before the others arrive with
their noise and camera phones. That's it.
I'll give you a few minutes...
then bring your colleagues, enjoy.
Don't go. Not yet, Professor.
This is my village. I grew up here.
-But you never mentioned it.
-Right.
As a child,
I grew up without a shirt on my back.
My father was the local market inspector,
a drunk who spent his earnings
on drink and women,
while my mother and I
lived destitute from hand-to-mouth.
When I was in despair
I would stand here at this very spot,
then imagine that...
if I could just spread my wings...
I could conquer the whole world.
I will take my leave now.
Thank you.
Finally.
Thank you, Jesus.
We're sorry to keep you waiting.
-We shall go now.
-All right.
Where did you get to?
I wandered.
Got lost, he found me.
[Lucien] It became very apparent
that Miss Oluwa would do anything
to be with me.
Alone.
But quite often a student
can grow attached to a tutor,
even of the same gender,
based purely on academic admiration,
without implying any sexual liaison,
not so?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, correct, madam.
That's precisely what I assumed.
In your report about that incident,
you mentioned something
about an awkward incident
that happened at a bonfire
somewhere in, um...
-Cape Verde.
-Yes, Cape Verde.
But that was not
part of your trip itinerary.
No.
Well, in Dakar...
my class has been...
swamped throughout the week
with symposiums,
seminars, joint classes
with Senegalese counterparts.
So on the last day
I decided to fly everybody to Cape Verde,
which is just an hour away from Dakar,
at my expense.
Just so they could relax
and unwind from a most taxing week.
[all singing]
[Moremi] I know you're tired of her.
Listen, I know Gloria can be
a pain in the butt sometimes.
But I know you miss her.
Look, a pain I can deal with,
but indifferent
leaves me feeling like
a mirage in the Sahara desert.
Now you're just waxing philosophical.
Gloria does not feel indifferent to you.
Well, of late, she has been.
I feel she's...
seeing someone back on campus in Nigeria.
No way!
Gloria doesn't date small boys.
Maybe he's not a student then.
[sighs] Look, I've spotted her
coming back from staff quarters
on my early morning jogs.
[phone ringing]
-Mr. Kwesi, can you please hold this?
-All right.
You better come back quick
or else I'll finish this.
What will you expect me to do?
So I'm just supposed to leave Senegal,
go back to Lagos and do what?
Do what? I told you that. Do you trust me?
The professor is not even doing anything.
I don't understand the problem.
Okay, so I come back and then what?
You're going to think that something
happened with Professor Lucien?
Cool. You know what?
Can we end it?
[French] Hello.
Good day, Professor.
You're alone.
-I just needed some space.
-Ah.
Well, plenty of space here.
Historical sources claim that...
out from these very shores,
400 years ago...
over a million
African slaves were shipped.
It makes me wonder...
how many secrets
are buried out in that sea.
The doctor?
-He broke up with me.
-Oh.
Sorry to hear.
If he was dumb enough to let you go,
then he was never smart enough
to have you in the first place.
I'm sorry. Moremi!
[Lucien] She was upset.
With issues from her personal life,
with her boyfriend, I think.
I comforted her.
And then she tried to kiss me.
She tried to kiss you?
Yes, she did,
but I stopped her, of course.
Professor N'Dyare...
when you returned to Nigeria,
did you report the incident to the Dean?
-No, I did not.
-Really?
Okay, fine. Did you report to anybody?
Professor N'Dyare,
you will answer for the record.
I did not report the incident.
I excused Miss Oluwa's behavior
as an emotional outburst...
to problems she was having
in her personal life.
Did you and Miss Oluwa
ever refer back to that incident?
It came in conversation.
[Gloria] Gosh, I really missed.
Like, I missed.
It was really no biggie.
Yeah, right.
We went to that boring ECOWAS office
in Abuja, my team and I,
and you guys got to go to Cape Verde
and Senegal.
And you tell me I didn't miss much?
Yeah, right.
To be honest, I wish I hadn't even gone.
Girlfriend, I heard all the juicy details.
I mean, heard everything about you
and the professor.
Please!
I heard you guys were bonded together,
you know, like Nigeria and Cameroon.
No wonder you were warding me off the guy.
You already had eyes for him.
[Pidgin] You are dating a genius,
to be sincere.
-Gloria, something happened--
- [Lucien] Moremi.
Oh, shit! I was hoping to avoid him.
-Okay, so I better be going.
-No, no, stay with me, stay with me.
I haven't seen you in class.
I've been busy working on my
dissertation, chapters four and five.
[French] About what
happened in Cape Verde.
I'd rather not talk about that, sir.
I acted inappropriately.
I don't know what came over me.
It was a moment of weakness
that I now find utterly embarrassing.
My profound apology.
So you will return to class?
Yes.
Have a good day.
What... Wait...
What just happened?
Nothing, come on.
-Nothing?
-Nothing.
[Gloria] Remi!
I guess after she apologized
for her transgression,
there was no need for me
to take the case any further.
Miss Oluwa apologized to you
over that incident?
Yes, she did, in front
of her colleague Gloria Dokai.
You can check, please.
Well, ladies and gentlemen,
it's been a full day,
so I think we should shut down for the day
and, uh, tomorrow morning at 9:00 a.m.
we would start again,
where we will take
our witness testimonies.
And at 12:00 we will reconvene
to continue the session.
Please do not forget my admonition.
No personal contact or communication
with any of the witnesses.
It will not be tolerated in any form.
Thank you very much,
gentlemen and ladies, for your work.
Have a good evening.
[indistinct chatter]
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Correct guy. Hold this sister well.
Koyejo!
Come on.
[Yoruba] we're not
supposed to be speaking.
Even you?
Ah-ah! It's shocking.
-That's how highly you think of me?
-No, that's not the point.
That's not it.
I warned you not to get overfamiliar
with that man. You ignored me.
I told you not to go to Dakar.
You stubbornly went.
Yeah, so...
All I know is that you were my babe.
But now... not anymore.
All I know is...
I wanted you to believe in me...
but you don't.
Oh, shit!
Didn't I just see you
communicating with a witness,
due to give testimony at the hearing?
I ran into him by mistake.
Oh, really?
You're PG? So tell me,
what are you doing in med school?
I had a migraine.
I thought I could pick up a prescription.
Can I see it?
-The prescription, Miss Oluwa.
-Babes...
Give me a break.
I'm just fighting for my life.
Get some rest.
I think that's a better prescription
for migraine. Have a nice day.
[Kwesi] Well, they were close,
but I didn't notice
anything out of the ordinary.
I mean, despite
their different capacities...
intellectually they were on par.
Well, Moremi always had this saying.
I mean, she's fond of saying
that age to her was just
a function of mind over matter.
I mean, if she didn't mind,
it didn't matter.
And she was clearly obsessed
with this man that is
older than her by 20 years.
I definitely saw Remi
take an interest in the professor
that was very, very unusual.
It was obvious she admires him.
Everyone in class knew.
But, as for me,
I believe Jesus will intervene.
Prof. N'Dyare actually
gave preferential attention to Moremi.
It was an open secret in the class
that she was his pet student.
Well, I wouldn't say that she was his pet.
Look, she's the youngest in the class,
but academically
she's by far the smartest.
I mean, that is bound to
catch any lecturer's attention.
At Goree Island they kept us waiting
for ages while they went AWOL.
When they did show up, it was odd.
But I believe Jesus will intervene.
Well, I was there, I was there
when she approached the professor,
trying to apologize for her trying
to kiss him during their field trip.
The professor has always
been such a consummate professional,
but she... she has always
been on the man, like...
tirelessly.
No, no, no. It was actually the prof
that was chasing after Moremi,
especially during the field trip.
Wherever Moremi went to,
you'll see the professor running
after her like, um...
a lovesick puppy.
It was blatant.
Moremi never complained to me
that he was harassing her.
But after the Easter party,
I sensed she was
deeply troubled about something.
She appeared quiet,
withdrawn.
Moremi did confess to me that, um...
you know, she was going to...
bed the professor
before the end of the semester.
That was her only way of guaranteeing
that she had an interview for the UN.
She was infatuated by this man, clearly.
[Prof. Osagie] Miss Oluwa,
regarding the first five chapters
of your dissertation...
what gave you the impression
that Professor N'Dyare
had approved it in the first place?
He told me so.
When?
Where?
In tutorial class?
In his house.
And...
what on earth were you doing in your
course supervisor's house, Miss Oluwa?
He invited the whole class over
on Easter Sunday,
a public holiday, for a social gathering.
Here comes the pizza.
Please go ahead.
It's for you. Don't be shy.
But I wish she was here today,
that would have been nice.
Gloria, I mean, she is a pain in the ass.
A little bit, sometimes.
[Moremi] It was a fun, relaxed gathering,
but something I ate
didn't sit right with me,
and I was in the bathroom
for over 30 minutes, purging.
-See you soon, okay?
-All right, Prof.
-See you in class, thank you so much.
-My pleasure, thanks for coming.
-Thank you very much, yeah.
-Thank you so much, Prof. God bless you.
-No, it was a pleasure.
See you in class. Yes.
-Thank you, sir.
-Okay.
-Prof.
-Thanks for hosting us.
Take care. Yes, indeed.
Okay. It was a pleasure.
Prof.
-Thank you. See you soon.
-Thanks for coming. Okay.
-All right.
-Bye-bye. See you in class.
Okay, sir.
[yawns]
Moremi?
[French] Where is everyone?
They left. I thought you had gone, too.
Something I ate.
Maybe it was my Senegalese jollof rice.
-Are you all right now?
-Better.
Thanks for a lovely evening. I should go.
No problem.
Please, can you at least help me clear up
before you run off?
-Okay.
-Yeah? Thank you.
I wasn't going to reveal it here and now,
but I have approved the first five
chapters of your thesis.
You came up with some fascinating theories
on conflict resolution in the Middle East.
-Exceptional.
-I don't know what to say.
I'm pretty certain
you're going to say thank you,
when I tell you that I've also referred
you to a high-ranking colleague at the UN.
There will be an interview
awaiting you in New York
once you complete
your postgraduate studies.
Thank you so much!
It's okay. Keep up the good work.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay. No problem.
You look ravishing this evening.
Thank you.
Do you mind?
Let me have your hand.
Come on, come closer.
What do you think you're doing?
You know that I...
-Stop pretending.
-No!
Why are you pretending?
Please let me go!
But you have been
staring at me all evening.
-No!
-Teasing me with your eyes.
-See how you are dressed.
You wore this to seduce me.
You intentionally stayed back.
No, I didn't.
Stop the pretense! Be still!
Stop it!
You wore this dress to seduce me.
Please don't hurt me!
Can't you see that I care about you
too much to harm you?
-I promise to be gentle.
-No!
Then why were you staring at me?
Stop it! Stop it! Stop this!
Be still!
You wore this dress to seduce me.
No!
Why are you pretending?
Keep quiet!
Okay.
-Okay.
-Be calm.
-Are we good? Yeah?
All right, I will be gentle and slow.
Miss Oluwa, are you implying
that your course supervisor,
a senior lecturer of this university,
a professor of international repute,
attempted to assault you?
No, sir.
I'm saying he attempted to rape me.
Oh! Rape?
Did you make an official complaint?
-Not at the time, no.
-And, um... why not?
Because I treated his fuck-up!
Miss Oluwa, I know tempers are rising,
but you cannot speak
with that kind of language.
He's still your professor.
My dear.
[Lucien screams]
It's not over yet!
Professor N'Dyare?
Well, part of her story is accurate.
But the rest...
is a complete figment
of Miss Oluwa's fertile imagination.
Yes, she did stay back
after her colleagues had left.
But it was she...
who offered sex to me.
It was I...
who rejected it.
There was never any offer
of interview at the UN.
Or any mention whatsoever
of her dissertation.
Obviously there is...
never...
ever...
any attempted rape.
Did you inform anyone she offered you sex?
Of course I did.
The following morning.
To the dean of the postgraduate school
present here, Professor Osagie.
I can confirm that...
Professor N'Dyare mentioned
the incident to me.
Now imagine this belonged
to your sister...
or daughter!
Now, that wasn't a very
smart stunt you pulled in there.
The panel were never going
to accept that exhibit into evidence.
I had to do something.
He sat there all week
and told lie after lie
to suit his bullshit narrative.
All right, no problem.
-You were very brave in there.
-Brave?
-Very good.
-More like a brave fool.
He's clever. Manipulative, credible.
They believe him, not me.
My own faculty dean, Professor Osagie,
is giving me dirty looks.
Look, calm down.
The Ajike Advocacy is in this with you
all the way.
With all due respect, ma'am
Ajike is just an organization using
my situation to make a name for itself.
Remi, that is uncalled for.
I won't be a case study.
This is my education, my reputation.
My future is on the line right now!
We're doing our very best here.
But it's not making any difference.
No wonder some students
take matters into their own hands.
Justice isn't blind here.
It has 20/20 vision,
all in favor of the faculty.
I need to get into his head.
Into his past.
-That was a good tutorial.
-Yeah, it was.
-You know?
-I know.
Hey, that was some good lecture.
Yeah, I feel like we're picking up
a lot of stuff.
True, exactly.
Oh, man! I can do
some swimming this afternoon.
I think I'll join you. It's too hot.
-It's way too hot.
-It is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[French]
Don't walk too near the edge of the cliff,
in case the wind
blows the wrong way and...
stumbles you over.
What was that?
What are you doing?
[French] Please excuse me.
I'm looking for a lecturer who works here.
His name is Cardosa.
Cardosa?
Sorry, no lecturer bearing that name here.
Oh! I'm sure that was his name.
He had it written on his lab coat.
He must be a laboratory assistant.
He can't be a lecturer,
because they don't wear name labels.
-Okay.
-But they don't work weekends.
[sighs] Thank you.
[bell ringing]
As you can see,
I kept your old Peugeot for you.
Really? You should have sold the jalopy.
No, you used to love driving it.
[laughs]
Thanks for keeping my car.
I don't want you to make fun of me.
I don't know how to drive stick.
Excuse me?
What are you doing here, Moremi?
I am looking for someone.
Moremi, you know...
I have followed reports
of your hearing online.
for the record,
I believe Lucien is innocent...
of the allegation you made against him.
So you think I'm deliberately
trying to ruin his career?
I think you may...
be a student who
cannot accept the fact that...
your best just wasn't good enough.
I am trying to locate Mr. Cardosa.
Cardosa?
I've never heard of him.
He's a laboratory assistant
in the science faculty.
That's not my area of expertise.
But you have access to
university records and contact details.
Miss, what's this Cardosa got to do
with your problem in Nigeria?
That's what I need to find out.
I am not going to conspire with you
to bring down the career of a good tutor.
You know...
Lucien is a former student of mine.
I've worked alongside him. I know the man.
Lucien would never request sex
in exchange for marks from a student.
Never!
Thanks for your time.
I'll be staying overnight
at the university guest house.
Did Professor N'Dyare ever tell you
how my close friendship with him started?
I taught him how to drive a car...
with a manual gear shift.
Samba?
[crowd chanting]
[French] I am looking for Mr. Cardosa.
[crowd cheering]
[French] Mr. Cardosa?
[French] Finally you are here. Please sit.
[Moremi] He was right.
It's more beautiful here.
Not as beautiful as my country.
You're not Senegalese?
Lack of work made me
relocate to Senegal many years ago.
However, it was always my dream
for my daughter
to attend university
in the country of my birth.
Cape Verde.
We struggled to get by.
Had plenty mouths to feed
on my lowly clerk salary.
But Diatta was a shining beacon of light.
Excuse me?
No, no, no. Her.
Lucien was her supervising lecturer.
He saw the potential in her.
Mentored her, guided her,
secured her a scholarship.
My family felt indebted to him.
We considered him
a blessing to our family.
We prayed for him,
thanked God for him.
But, alas,
he was a wolf in sheep's clothing.
She was a poor girl
from an impoverished family,
but her education meant the world to her.
She gave in to him time after time.
But it was when she
found herself with child
that he displayed
his brutally true colors.
Diatta returned to Senegal
a broken woman.
No matter how much I assured her,
she felt she had let us down,
and shamed us.
Three days after
giving birth to her baby,
having fed him, rocked him to sleep,
put him to bed...
she came to this very spot...
and returned to her Maker.
Lucien is a psychopath.
Maybe growing up with an uncaring father
made him turn that way.
-Who knows?
-No.
He's just evil, manipulative, cunning.
[laughter and indistinct chatter]
Okay, see you, Remi.
-See you too.
-Take care.
[Lucien] This is just impossible,
I can't drive this car.
Very manipulative indeed.
Lucien visits his son sometimes...
but for the most part
he just sends money for his upkeep.
He secured me a job at the university.
Samba is his son, right?
We were bribed...
to keep our silence,
to save his job and his family.
I took the blood money
to feed the rest of my family.
I've regretted it ever since.
[in English] When you came, I knew.
There have been so many,
but nobody wanted to speak up.
I spoke up.
I came here for your help,
but you've suffered enough loss.
Thank you.
[in French] Thanks for your time. Goodbye.
I think we've waited enough.
We should go ahead.
Ma'am, your client isn't here.
I think we are going to have to go ahead.
We've tried to wait.
We've been considerate here.
My apologies for my tardiness.
Okay, this had better be good.
Madam chair, our witness
expresses himself better
in French and Portuguese.
-Portuguese?
-I understand the language.
-Oh, you do?
-We are good to go
Okay, fantastic. Please, have a seat.
I'm sorry, but... why is he here?
He is completely irrelevant
to this hearing.
We will be the judge of that,
Professor N'Dyare.
So please, sit down.
Excuse me, young lady.
I possess two Masters degrees...
a highly published PhD thesis,
and membership in 18
well-renowned academic fellowships.
So now, I understand
you are one of the panel here,
but I strongly suggest
that you adjust your tone
when addressing me.
And I am a Rhodes Scholar.
I possess two PhD's,
one Doctor of Letter,
I belong to 23 academic
fellowships across the world,
and on top of that
I was previously nominated
for the Nobel Prize in Economics.
And as the chair of this panel,
Professor N'Dyare, sit down!
Sit!
Thank you.
Mr. Cardosa? Let's proceed.
[Portuguese] I am Mr. Vicente Cardosa.
I work as a laboratory assistant
at the University in Dakar, Senegal,
Cheikh Anta Diop.
I am here to give
testimony at this hearing,
because I have been an acquaintance
of Professor Lucien N'Dyare
for many years.
That was a breakthrough.
It just might have helped.
[French] I only wish I acted faster,
like this young warrior here.
Thank you so much.
Continue fighting the good fight.
You can make a difference.
Safe trip.
Thank you.
How long do you think
the panel will deliberate for?
They will get in touch.
We did good in there.
Keep the faith.
Somebody is looking for you.
Thank you so much for your support, ma'am.
-My pleasure.
-Yeah.
Miss Oluwa's...
display of interest
in Professor N'Dyare...
did it go far beyond
a student-lecturer relationship?
In any way?
No.
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
Are you okay?
[Prof. Lucien] And that goes to
the crux of the economic diversification,
of the role of the military
in the Egyptian political system.
That's a very good job, Kwesi.
Now you can progress
to chapters six and seven.
Thanks very much, Prof.
Now, Moremi Oluwa...
I've gone through
your first five chapters,
and I must say that
I'm rather disappointed.
You made a complete departure
from the approved premise.
There is a distinct lack of citation,
research, or any real analytical substance
to your hypothesis.
There's no structure at all.
Your dissertation
is an unmitigated disaster,
far below what I expect
from postgraduate work.
But, sir...
You need to get back to your premise,
and remind yourself
what you set out to explore.
So now I'm taking out...
your first five chapters,
and I want you to start again.
You're going to
have to start all over again.
From scratch.
-That's it.
-But, sir!
Have a good day.
Sir!
Professor N'Dyare!
[French] Why did you do that, sir?
As I said in class,
your work is below par.
The other night, in your house,
you called my work "exemplary."
I've raised the standard since.
If you raise the standard,
it will be impossible for me
to recover that kind of ground
in time to graduate.
I'll have to extend my course
for an extra semester.
And how is that my problem?
This is all because I turned you down
the other night.
Don't flatter yourself.
You tried to force yourself on me.
It's your word against mine.
And now...
you intend to fail me.
No. You failed yourself.
But worry not, I believe in you.
So I'll retain you next semester too.
I will break you.
Lucien!
It's not over yet!
It's okay. Let's go.
You won't believe this.
I got contacted by six women
who studied in the universities
of America, in the UK,
in France, in Cape Verde.
All universities where
Professor N'Dyare taught.
All six women claimed that they
had been either sexually harassed
or molested by Professor N'Dyare
whilst he was their lecturer.
-Oh, my God.
-Now you see?
You see why I had to make so much noise?
Your story has given these women
the courage to stand up and be counted.
Is this good? Can it help?
I'm so sorry.
Not in this instance.
But these testimonies establish
a clear pattern of victimization.
I know, but we are already at verdict.
All we can hope for from these testimonies
is that they will help us
in the court of public opinion
-if we should lose.
-Lose?
Jeez!
I know.
Okay, come on, let's go.
Babe, are you good?
Ma, I will wait right here for you.
-Okay.
-Yes, Ma.
Babe, please stay solid for me, okay?
-Okay.
-It's just going to be fine.
Come here.
I love you.
I'd like to welcome everyone
to the final day of this panel hearing.
But before we go on,
I'd like very much to thank everyone
for your part in the whole process.
Especially the members of the panel.
Uzoamaka,
thank you very much for your hard work.
And, uh, Professor Osagie,
very grateful for your diligence
and your dedication.
Professor Yahaya, thank you very much
for being such a great support.
And Dr. Mrs. Nwosu, very appreciative
of all the hard work that you put in.
Our decision.
In the complaint of Miss Moremi Oluwa
versus Professor Lucien N'Dyare...
the panel members of
this university senate hearing
have meticulously studied the facts,
evidence, and witness accounts
which has been presented by all parties.
We also took the liberty
of sending the first five chapters
of Miss Oluwa's dissertation to
an independent expert for consideration.
Based on all the aforementioned,
and our deliberations,
we have reached our conclusions.
We therefore conclude unanimously...
that Professor N'Dyare...
is guilty...
of sexual harassment,
abuse of power and privileges...
unethical and immoral behavior
unbecoming of a member of faculty
of this great institution
of higher learning.
Professor N'Dyare's
employment with the university
is hereby terminated
with immediate effect.
As some of these offences fall
within the framework of criminal activity,
this complaint will be passed on
to the office of the state prosecutor
for further action.
Miss Oluwa, you are hereby exonerated
of any wrongdoing in this matter.
-We did it.
-Yes!
-We did it!
Can we please complete our assignment.
Thank you.
I'd like to thank the members of the panel
for your work once again.
And I'd like to say
that our work is done here.
Thank you very much.
We won! We won!
Auntie...
thank you.
All right, let's go.
Mummy, thank you so much.
Yes!
Baby, I love you!
I swear with all of my heart!
Yeah!
[all cheering]
No sex for grades!
Moremi, how do you feel
about your vindication?
Moremi, does your victory
now leave the door open
for you to take on the professor
in a criminal court?
What do you have to say
to other women worldwide in your position?
Go ahead.
First of all...
I want to thank God
-and the female advocacy NGO...
-Ajike.
...for helping me
through this troubling journey.
I'm just a girl trying to go to school
in order to attain a dream.
It was never my intention
to become the poster face
for sexual harassment on campuses.
But it is a hat I am proud
and willing to wear.
I hope my victory serves
as a clarion call for change,
and I hope my victory gives a voice
to the silent girls or women
in all walks of life
facing sexual harassment
just due to their gender.
-Thank you.
-All right.
-Greatest Nigerian students!
-[all cheering]
[Prof. Osagie] Hence...
international waters...
are considered...
as part and parcel of...
a borderline of a sovereign state.
Any incursion into these waters...
is considered...
a breach...
of the sovereign state.
Albeit...
a vessel may be as far away
as 12 nautical miles...
from the shoreline.
And then if...
Sorry I'm late, sir.
[students cheering]