Why are you hounding her?
Are you the one paying her school fees?
But that is the difference,
you are a dullard.
You know what I mean,
like a compound dullard.
I guess that makes me Nigerian.
Two punches.
Three punches.
My elder brother.
My name is Moremi.
So you can speak Yoruba?
You are saying it
like you are speaking the Egun dialect.
My ball.
Where were you during freshers week?
What were you looking
for during freshers week?
No, no. Excuse me.
Yeah, how can I help you?
First of all...
I have been searching for you.
I have looked everywhere for you.
I went to every department, every faculty,
even every cafeteria.
And then it dawned on me...
God, as if the ground should open up
and swallow me.
No need. I'd push you in myself.
-"I'm Koyejo. Final year med school."
-She got me.
Do you still want me to push you
in the ground?
Please, please don't be angry.
Don't push me into it.
This is impossible,
I can't drive this car.
What a mess.
I can see that you're having issues
with your car.
You speak French?
Yes. I have a French
baccalaureate qualification.
Did you take any electives
in mechanical engineering?
I must tell you...
I don't want you to make fun of me.
I learned how to drive in America
on an automatic gear shift.
But this university
loaned me a car with a stick shift.
Your car key, sir?
What do you intend on doing?
Shall we?
Where are you heading?
-Road 8.
-Okay.
Sir, you've got to understand...
I think it's just
too much information and jargon.
An automatic is much easier.
But with manual,
-Thank you so much.
-You're very welcome, sir.
I have to ask the university for a driver
or get an automatic car instead.
Just practice. It makes perfect.
If you continue to teach me,
then no problem.
Please come in. Least I can do is offer
you a drink, some refreshments maybe?
That's okay. I was heading
to the supermarket when I ran into you.
But it's a long way from here.
Goodbye.
-Okay, all right.
-Yeah.
I don't know why, it keeps stalling.
Calm down.
There has to be a balance
between the accelerator and the clutch.
There is no logic to this.
We have two legs, why make three pedals?
It's ridiculous.
Listen.
Don't forget...
Perfect! Brilliant!
Well done. Okay.
-Like this?
-Perfect.
Very good.
You're really getting the hang of it.
-Okay, great.
-That works.
I can see that you're now an expert.
Thanks to you.
You were very patient with me.
-Thank you.
-My pleasure, sir.
I love to resolve conflicts.
Conflicts? Which conflicts
are we talking about?
-There's no conflict.
-Sir,
What was it like working at the UN?
Working at the UN?
It's nice but quite stressful.
When you're working for a common goal,
people will want
to frustrate your efforts.
For as long as I can remember,
You?
Somehow I saw an academic in you.
Well, first of all,
Then secondly...
A photojournalist who could do nothing
but stand aside
to record the image for posterity.
It haunted the photographer too.
He committed suicide a year later.
Like your namesake Moremi Ajasoro?
You've read about her?
Of course, I did my research.
Infiltrated the ranks
of the Ugbo forest tribe,
discovered their weakness and...
saved her people of Ile-Ife from invasion.
She was quite the heroine.
I can only aspire.
We all aspire, my dear.
But sometimes a prophet is without honor
only in his hometown.
Would you like to take a walk?
Yes.
You and I, we are new age rebels.
We ruffle feathers.
Please, please, please.
Please. I don't do lecturers.
You're too extra, please.
-My pal.
-My brother.
-Thank you.
-How are you?
You shall grow old and live long.
Charlie, hope you're enjoying Nigeria?
Yetty, please bring the cake.
Have it.
-Treat her well.
-I will.
-Enjoy.
-I hail!
It's amazing.
That was superb.
Seun is my friend anyways.
Money
We use our feet to fight
Money, money
Money
They've arrived, they've arrived
Put them together, give me the answer
You see, in karate,
there are different stages.
Are you listening?
Is it not all about fighting Chinese?
-Do you understand?
-Okay.
I hope you're not using style
to tap current.
Wait, calm down, okay.
-Go on, try it.
-Okay.
-Relax.
-Relax what?
-Don't damage my family planning.
I saw you on Thursday.
Seeing you with him like that.
Are you listening?
I don't like it.
You know how some men see
over-familiarity as a green light.
I assumed that if I had a presupposition,
I have to defend it
with research and citations.
Yeah, with original content.
I like your premise,
and your first chapter is excellent.
But for chapters two and three,
I am not so sure.
It talks more of the situation
from a third party's point of view
than it does from yours.
It's like, whose dissertation is this?
Is it yours or your source?
Aside from that,
let me hear your hypothesis.
Take note of my comments in red.
Okay.
Thank you, professor.
Professor?
When it's just you and I together,
you can call me Lucien.
I'm not entirely sure
that would be appropriate.
But I insist.
I'd rather maintain the status quo.
My old supervising professor at Harvard,
I called him David.
And I am Lucien.
And I am Nigerian.
The moment
I call someone
of your age difference by name,
it means I have...
I have stopped respecting you.
Why are you always so defensive?
You know...
I was the tutor then, in control.
Then, relax.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Yes.
The medical student?
How do you know?
I know.
And with your boyfriend,
are you also in control?
That's not something
I am comfortable discussing with you.
So, you can talk to me about the economic
effect of Brexit within the European Union
but your sex life is a no-go area?
Come on.
So, it is forbidden?
Now you've really got me curious.
If that's all, I want to leave.
That will be all.
My favorite color is red.
It's a field trip.
It's part of my course requirements.
The same lecturer who tried to figure out
your sexual preference?
Come on.
It wasn't quite like that, Koyejo.
Okay.
You're the one who came running to me
with complaints.
You told me the professor
was talking inappropriately.
Maybe I overreacted.
Maybe you don't want
to read the writing on the wall.
That was over a month ago.
But now everything's been cool since then.
Join another tutorial group.
Do you understand?
You guys are not the only group
going on a field trip.
I'm not here to ask your permission.
I came to inform you.
So, it's like that?
Good to see you.
I'm pleased to see you too,
our traveling professor.
-In fact, in fact.
-It's been an age.
Indeed, good to see you.
And this must be the Nigerian tribe
that has adopted you.
In fact, in fact.
This time around, I brought ten students.
I must say they are all exceptional.
The goal is to share some
of this Senegalese culture with them,
-and to tour them around Dakar.
-That's very good.
Not too old.
You're correct.
-A very warm welcome to you all.
-Thank you.
I'll be hosting a reception for you
at the dean's lodge this evening,
where you can meet some
of your Senegalese colleagues.
Thank you.
-Is anyone fluent in French?
-French?
-She's my brightest star.
-Yes.
She speaks French fluently, Moremi.
-It's nice to meet you, Moremi.
-Good day.
-How are you?
-I am fine, thank you.
I am delighted.
You will be the official interpreter.
Yes, okay, with all pleasure, sir.
-That's good.
-Thanks a lot.
All right! I will be waiting
when you all are done for today.
See you tonight.
-Thank you, doctor.
-I'm going for an appointment now.
-Very well. See you later.
-Yes.
-My translator.
-Good evening, sir.
-How are you?
-I'm fine. Thank you.
-I hope you are having a good time.
-Thank you.
So near yet so far.
I'm fine.
I know that look, lovers tiff.
Don't let anyone spoil
this wonderful experience for you.
Don't believe a word this man says.
I taught him everything he knows.
Professor.
I hope you enjoyed yourself?
Yes, everything was great. Thank you.
-As you can see...
-What's that?
I kept your old Peugeot for you.
-Really? You should have sold the jalopy.
-No. You used to love driving it.
Thanks for hosting us tonight.
-So, we would see you very soon.
Okay. Thanks, uncle.
-My translator.
-Thanks a lot, sir.
-Very good.
-Goodbye.
Goodbye, everyone.
In conclusion...
it is imperative to weigh
the social ramification
of the imposing of economic sanctions
vis-a-vis the political issues
in that country.
Otherwise, an embargo will do
more harm than good.
That's it. So, professor,
finally, thanks once again.
-Thank you, too.
-Thanks for the privilege.
Dear students, thank you.
Thank you to my Nigerian students.
-Thank you, sir.
-Thank you.
It's called the statue
of the Liberation of Slaves.
Good afternoon.
Good day.
What is your name?
Where are we going?
Beautiful.
It's unbelievable.
Even more beautiful at night.
This probably is the best view
of the country.
I want you to...
bask in the serenity of the view
before the others arrive with their noise
and camera phones.
That's it.
I'll give you a few minutes,
then bring your colleagues, enjoy.
Don't go, not yet professor.
This is my village. I grew up here.
-But you never mentioned it.
-Right.
As a child,
I grew up without a shirt on my back.
My father was the local market inspector,
a drunk who spent his earnings
on drink and women,
while my mother and I lived destitute,
from hand to mouth.
When I was in despair,
I would stand here at this very spot
then imagine that...
if I could just spread my wings...
I could conquer the whole world.
I will take my leave now.
Thank you.
Hello.
Good day, professor.
You're alone.
I just needed some space.
Well, plenty of space here.
Historical sources claim that...
over a million African slaves
were shipped.
It makes me wonder
how many secrets
are buried out in that sea.
The doctor?
If he was dumb enough to let you go,
then he was never smart enough
to have you in the first place.
I'm sorry.
You certainly picked a good catch
in the market. I won’t lie.
About what happened in Cape Verde...
I'd rather not talk about that, sir.
I acted inappropriately.
I don't know what came over me.
It was a moment of weakness
that now I find utterly embarrassing.
My profound apology.
So you will return to class?
Yes.
We're not supposed to be speaking.
Even you?
It's shocking.
I warned you not to get over-familiar
with that man. You ignored me.
I told you not to go to Dakar.
You stubbornly went.
Where is everyone?
They left. I thought you had gone too.
Something I ate.
Maybe it was my Senegalese jollof rice.
Are you all right now?
Better.
Thanks for a lovely evening. I should go.
No problem.
Please, can you at least help me clear up
before you go?
Okay.
Thank you.
I wasn't going to reveal it here and now,
but I have approved
the first five chapters of your thesis.
You came up with some fascinating theories
on conflict resolution in the Middle East.
Exceptional.
I don't know what to say.
I'm pretty certain you're going to say
thank you when I tell you that
I've also referred you
to a high-ranking colleague at the UN.
There will be an interview waiting for you
in New York once you complete
your postgraduate studies.
Thank you so much.
It's okay. Keep up the good work.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
No problem...
You look ravishing this evening.
Thank you.
Do you mind? Let me have your hand.
Come on, come closer.
What do you think you're doing?
You know that I...
Stop pretending.
Why are you pretending?
Please let me go!
But you have been staring
at me all evening.
-Teasing me with your eyes.
-No!
See how you are dressed.
You wore this to seduce me.
You intentionally stayed back.
No, I didn't.
Stop the pretense! Be still!
You wore this dress to seduce me.
Please don't hurt me.
Can't you see that I care about you
too much to harm you?
I promise to be gentle.
Then why are you staring at me?
Stop it! Stop this!
Be still!
You wore this dress to seduce me.
Why are you pretending?
Keep quiet!
Be calm.
All right. I will be gentle and slow.
I'm going to be very gentle.
My dear.
It's not over yet!
Don't walk too near the edge of the cliff
in case the wind blows the wrong way
and tumbles you over.
Please excuse me.
I'm looking for a lecturer who works here.
His name is Cardosa.
Cardosa?
Sorry, there's no lecturer
bearing that name here.
Oh, I'm sure that was his name.
He had it written on his lab coat.
He must be a laboratory assistant.
He can't be a lecturer
because they don't wear name labels.
-Okay.
-But they don't work weekends.
Thank you.
As you can see,
I kept your old Peugeot for you.
Really? You should have sold the jalopy.
No, you used to love driving it.
Thanks for keeping my car.
I don't want you to make fun of me.
What are you doing here, Moremi?
I am looking for someone.
Moremi, you know...
I have followed reports
of your hearing online.
For the record,
I believe Lucien is innocent
of the allegations you made against him.
So, you think I'm deliberately trying
to ruin his career?
I think you may be...
a student who cannot accept the fact
that your best just wasn't good enough.
I am trying to locate Mr. Cardosa.
I've never heard of him.
He is a laboratory assistant
in the science faculty.
That's not my area of expertise.
But you have access to university records
and contact details.
Miss, what's this Cardosa got to do
with your problem in Nigeria?
That's what I need to find out.
I am not going to conspire with you
to bring down the career of a good tutor.
You know...
Lucien is a former student of mine.
I've worked alongside him. I know the man.
Lucien would never request sex
in exchange for marks from a student.
Never!
Thanks for your time.
I'll be staying overnight
at the university guest house.
Did Professor N'Dyare ever tell you...
how my close friendship with him started?
I taught him how to drive a car
with a manual gear shift.
I am looking for Mr. Cardosa.
Mr. Cardosa.
Finally, you are here.
Please sit.
He was right.
It's more beautiful here.
No. Not as beautiful as my country.
You're not Senegalese?
Lack of work made me relocate to Senegal
many years ago.
However...
it was always my dream for my daughter
to attend university
in the country of my birth.
Cape Verde.
We struggled to get by.
Had plenty of mouths to feed
on my lowly clerk salary.
But Diatta was a shining beacon of light.
Excuse me.
No, no, no. Her.
Lucien was her supervising lecturer.
He saw the potential in her...
mentored her, guided her,
secured her a scholarship.
My family felt indebted to him.
We considered him a blessing
to our family.
We prayed for him, thanked God for him.
But alas, he was a wolf
in sheep's clothing.
She was a poor girl
from an impoverished family...
but her education meant the world to her.
She gave in to him time after time.
It was when she found herself with child
that he displayed
his brutally true colors.
Diatta returned to Senegal a broken woman.
No matter how much I assured her,
she felt she had let us down...
and shamed us.
Three days after...
she gave birth to her baby.
She fed her baby, rocked him to sleep,
put him to bed...
then came to this very spot...
and returned to her Maker.
Lucien is a psychopath.
Maybe growing up with an uncaring father
made him turn that way.
Who knows?
He's just evil, manipulative, cunning.
This is just impossible.
I can't drive this car.
Very manipulative indeed.
Lucien visits his son sometimes...
but for the most part,
he just sends money for his upkeep...
and secured me a job at the university.
Samba is his son, right?
We were bribed...
to keep our silence
to save his job and his family.
I took the blood money
to feed the rest of my family.
I've regretted it ever since.
Thanks for your time.
Goodbye.
Mr. Cardosa...
I am Mr. Vicente Cardosa.
I work as a laboratory assistant
at the university in Dakar, Senegal,
Cheikh Anta Diop.
I am here
to give testimony at this hearing
because I have been an acquaintance
of Professor Lucien N'Dyare
for many years.
I only wish I acted faster
like this young warrior here.
Thank you so much.
Continue fighting the good fight.
You can make a difference.
Safe trip.
Why did you do that, sir?
As I said in class,
your work is below par.
The other night, in your house,
you called my work "exemplary."
I've raised the standard since.
If you've raised the standard,
it will be impossible for me
to recover that kind of ground
in time to graduate.
I'll have to extend my course
for an extra semester.
And how is that my problem?
This is all because
I turned you down the other night.
Don't flatter yourself.
You tried to force yourself on me.
It is your word against mine.
And now you intend to fail me.
No. You failed yourself.
But worry not. I believe in you.
So, I'll retain you next semester, too.
I will break you.
It's not over yet!