-== Caption Maker£ºShiLei ==-
"Rung Shi Hall,
by the order of His Majesty"
Inside the Ning Kuo Mansion
of Jinling City
...is the much-envied powerful Jia family
Ancestors so patriotic;
while its descendants are rich
There're 12 young maids in two ranks
And many other maidens in the Da Guan Yuan
that happened in the lives of
the female denizens
Let me go, let me go
Listen
Hadn't I, Jiu Da,
carried your great grandfather...
from the heap of corpses long time ago
...you would not even exist
Yes...
Even old great granny has to
give me some face
Who do you think you are?
Lai Er? The Head housekeeper?
What the hell do you think you are doing?
You sent me for a no-good job
at the Ning residence
why'd the affairs of the Rung mansion
concern me?
And you send me out of the city
to get Miss Lin
I tell you, even if her mother
Jia Man were alive
...she'd have to be nice to me
Right...
That Miss Lin, she could have stayed at...
Soo Chow, yet she wants to get
mixed up with this lot
This mansion is full of bad elements
each one of them
up to their own bad ways
Out of my way, I'm coming over
I have to go to old Master
at the ancestral temple
Old Master
Don't let Miss Lin come here
No glory remains
for the Ning & Rung mansion
except these pristine lions'
two pairs at the gates...
Grandmother
Dai Yu
Madam Lian, Miss Lin has arrived
She's here already?
She is in Old granny's room
I'll change my clothes and come
Bring ten broomsticks, ten dusters
Alright...
You still on medicine now?
Yes, second aunty
I have been taking medicine since I born
Then you need to take care of your health
I'm late...
Old granny, I'm late
Dai Yu, meet cousin Lian
Cousin Lian
You're too kind, arise
No wonder you've been thought
of night and day
You're like a great beauty in a painting
Dai Yu, stay here from now on
Make yourself at home
This is in fact your home
Anything you want to eat or need
...just tell me
I'll make sure you get it
Look at how you speak
She is the famous shrew in the house
Quite well-known in Nanking as Hot Chilly
Thank you, cousin Lian
Madam Chow
get Miss Lin's entourage settled in
Yes
Come with me
Dai Yu's chaperone is too young
Take my...
Ji Juan, you will serve Miss Lin
from now on
Yes
Greet Miss Lin
Never mind
Master Bao is back
Greetings
Good boy
Greetings, madams
Bao Yu
We have a guest
Come and meet cousin Lin
Bao Yu
Sister Lin?
- Sister Lin
- Bao Yu
Sister Lin
I thought you looked familiar
Nonsense! Where have you seen her before?
She's just come today,
how could you have seen her?
I might not have met her
but she looks familiar
It seems my heart has known her
Good, then you'll get along fine
Cousin Lin, have you studied before?
Your name?
Dai Yu
Any alias?
None
No alias?
Do you have any jade?
Your piece ofjade is a very precious one
Not everybody could have one
Bao Yu
They say it's rare and has a spirit in it
Well, I don't really care!
Bao Yu...
Brother Bao
This kid
Bao Yu, wear it
Come, brother Bao
Wicked child
You can do whatever you like to
let off steam
But not on that piece ofjade!
None of the sisters got thatjade
except me
Now the fairy-like cousin is here
& not even she's got
So you can tell it's not a good thing
Brother Bao, come, wear it quickly
No
Wear it quickly
Bao Yu
Brother Bao, Bao Yu, wear it quickly
Brother Bao
Brother Bao, come, wear it quickly
Bao Yu
Brother Bao, be careful your dad
might know
Brother Bao, wear it quickly
Hasn't old granny been saying all along?
This family's asset depends on this child
What is this?
It's the 26th of April today
This afternoon begins the festival
of summer
After the festival summer will come
Flowers will fade
We have to bid the flower god farewell
What is this then?
The water is pure,
I throw these petals in it
and don't make these dirty
They'll be dirty eventually
I have a flower grave over there
Put the petals in the gauze
then bury them
Flower grave? That's great
Brother Bao
Brother Bao, cousin Lin
Aunty Xue and Sister Bao Chai
...have all moved in here
Madam wants you to meet them
Sister Bao is here too
Yes, now you have
...another play mate
Go, quickly
Ping Er, tidy up Lai Heung Room
and bring Aunty Xue and Miss Bao
to stay there
Yes, madam
Come and meet aunty Xue and sister Bao
Aunty Xue, Sister Bao
Never mind
Lose Not and Forget Not; Live a Long Life
Leave Not and Abandon Not;
Keep a youthful mind
Look like a real pair made in heaven
Lose Not and Forget Not; Live a Long Life
Leave Not and Abandon Not;
Keep a youthful mind
Indeed, a real pair made in heaven
What fragrance, sister Bao, what is it?
It must be the aromatic pellet
...I took this morning
Does it really smell so good?
Sister Bao, let me try one
Stop messing
How could you take medicine
for the fun of it?
Didn't you ask me to play chess with you?
Come, let me take a pupil
You should be my pupil
Look
I picked up two pebbles
There are writings on them
Writings?
What writings?
Lose Not and Forget Not; Live a Long Life
I knew she has nothing good to say
Really? This one has writings too
Leave Not and Abandon Not;
Keep a youthful mind
We're really a pair
You...
See if you dare again?
Please...
Smells good
It must be the aromatic pellet
I took this morning
You...
See where you can run?
Master Pao
Old master wants to see you
What?
Proper relations & virtues are
one's basic obligations
To be loyal to the emperor
To be filial to your father
That is why loyal servants
come from filial families
Bao Yu
Yes
Don't mess around with girls anymore
You have to study hard and...
you'll understand what proper
relations & virtues are
Yes
Sister
I am so prone to illness and melancholy
Your beauty is such that kingdoms
will fall for it
Nonsense, you tease me
Good sister, don't, stop hitting me
You are full of nonsense
You've written this lustful rhyme
and say such nonsense to mock me
I'll tell uncle and aunty
Good sister
Give me a chance
If I mean to mock you
Let me fall into the river
be eaten by the turtle and
become a bastard
When you become an official's lady
one day
and die in old age
Let me carry your tombstone
for my whole life
Mr. Zhang has the guts to climb over
the wall
...and ask Hong Liang to send her
a letter
Miss Cui dares to see him at night
Wai Ming dares to wander around
the army camp
I thought you were as bold
but in fact you're only for show
You said it, you said those words
Fine, I'll tell on you
Bao Yu
Get out of my way
Get out of my way. I have to go
Go on...
Sister...
My humble greetings
Good sister, give this to me, okay?
What good is it?
In any event someone's bound to
give it to you
Someone's better than me at writing
and has treasures like gold and jade
Look... there you go again
You're are a wise person
you should know the philosophy of
bonding with family first
rather than outsiders
Why would I distance you because of her?
Have I told you to alienate her?
What kind of person would I be?
I am only following my heart
So am I
Then you only know your heart
and not mine?
Master Bao
What is it?
Master Fung has brought a box of fans
to sell to you
You look familiar
but I have forgotten your name
I am Cheung Yu Han,
and I sang at your residence
No wonder
then you should know the famous Chi Guan
That is my pseudonym
What a pleasure!
It's my honour!
I love your "Bai Mei Jiao" most
I must learn it today
Come, over here
I haven't sang that for a long time
I might get out of tune
You're too modest, I long to hear it
Alright then, your wish is my command
You are delightedly a born beauty
like a fairy having come from the
blue heavens
At such a tender age
happy couples are timely made
looking at the milky way high up
in the sky
listening to drums beating
holding lamps as they draw
the curtains stealthily
Excellent
Master Bao is getting out of line
How could he befriend an actor?
So what? Is not an actor a human being?
This is what I carry with me
Please accept it as a token
Are you going just like that?
The prince would not let you
go this easily
An actor is basically a lowly person
who laughs on stage and cries in silence
slightly better than a whore
and a musician
and even less than a dog
Yu Han
Have a safe trip and take care
I heard your son gave this to Chi Guan
Chi Guan is the actor of
our Jung Shuen palace
and best-loved by the prince
He has not returned to palace
for days and...
is understood to have been closely
related to your son
It's also your son's idea
he should leave the palace
Please therefore convey to your son
that Chi Guan should return to us
Firstly the prince will
appreciate this, and
secondly, you'll avoid
unnecessary troubles
Come, men
Yes
Ask Bao Yu to come here
Master Bao
Old master is calling you
and is very angry
Wicked child
Kneel down
Kneel properly
You beast
Come, tie him up
Yes
You... you fail to glorify your ancestors
and meddle with actors
and have caused a scandal
I'll beat you to death today
so you won't ruin our family
Prepare our family's cardinal punishment
Yes
Really?
Tell Madam quickly
Beat him hard
Yes
Master Bao, yell loudly, quick
Yell, yell out now
Shout louder
Louder still
Heavens, to think our Jia family
with its deep-rooted tradition,
eruditeness
reputation and wealth
...has produced such a no-good bastard
Master Bao, Shout louder
Louder still
Get out of my way
Master
Master...
Bao Yu is guilty, yet you should
take care as well
If you beat Bao Yu to death
that is not as serious as
causing great distress to old madam
Bao Yu
I am not filial to have raised such a kid
I must kill him to prevent
further troubles
Master...
Please look upon our marriage
I am advanced in years
and only have this one child
Bao Yu, let us die together
It's all your fault
...to spoil him like this
I must strangle him today
Get me a rope...
Get me a rope
Alright, if you must strangle him
strangle me first
Beat me to death first...
Beat me to death first... then kill him
Bao Yu, quick...
Open it, open it
You treated him like a thief. Bao Yu
Bao Yu...
Master Bao
Bao Yu
Bao Yu...
What does old madam want
Just ask me to go in
Why bother old madam to come herself
So you're talking to me
I have some instructions to give
Unfortunately I have not raised
a good child
...in my whole life
Who should I talk to? Who indeed?
Instructions?
To whom do I dare give instructions?
I train him up to glorify our ancestors
Old madam, if you say so...
how can I take it up?
I have only said one sentence
and already you can't take it
How do you think then that Bao Yu
could take the beating from
the wooden plank?
Granny
Bao Yu...
You naughty, no-good grand child
Dilute it with wine and dress his wounds
When the bruising disappears
he'll be alright
Yes, Miss Bao
Thank you, sister Bao
You have to mend your ways
How can you be-friend an actor?
Miss Bao is right
Bao Yu, rest well
I'm going
Wouldn't you stay for a while?
No, remember the medicine
I know
When did you come?
What's the big deal with
this physical pain?
You've suffered much
Even if I die for these people
I am convinced it's worth it
Yin Yang
It's just a casual visit
When master Bao awakes
second madam will come over with old madam
I'm going back
Farewell
Stay longer
I can't let people see my eyes
Ching Man...
Master Bao, can I help you?
Send this to Miss Lin
I...
Go on
Tears weld in my eyes
For whom do they fall
Hair scarf as a gift
Grieve for the loved one
His love is like filigree on
a handkerchief
while my heavy heart cries out
between each line
If we were not meant for each other
why then do our hearts and souls unite
If we were meant for each other
why then do walls and mountains
separate us
I don't care Miss Whoever she is
They come here for no reason whatsoever...
and disturb my sleep at night
Who is it?
It's me
They're all asleep
By master Bao's instructions
No one is allowed to come in
Miss Bao, are you leaving?
Won't you stay a while longer?
Have a safe trip and take care
Go back
Yes
Think
You've been sold as a maid
Who do you think you are? A Miss?
Frankly, in this mansion
if you don't know
...how to play politics
you will be finished
I tell you, sooner or later
you lazy bones will
...be driven out
Ou Shang terrace full of
floral extravagance
Laughter and jokes prevail in Da Guan Yuan
Mellifluous words abound in abundance
The flow of sweet wine is endless
But there is someone else here
...suffering in deep melancholy
Flowers fade and fall everywhere
Who will sing their elegy?
Sorrow permeates and lingers
I will hoe the earth for the flowers
Flowers bloom in extravagance
but fade in silence
Melancholy weighs down the one
burying the flowers
Lonely and in silence she cries
Blood stains in the branches
Follow the flowers to the ends
of the heavens
There is no resting place
at the end of the heavens
for the beautiful that has died
The earth will cover romance that has gone
People laugh at me burying the flowers
Who will be the one buried years from now?
Time and tide waits for no beauty
Flowers fade and people pass away
Sister Lin...
Please listen to me
I know you're ignoring me
I just want to say one thing
From now on we walk on our own way
Go on, speak
What if I speak more?
It's the past actions which determine
our present
So what's the issue with
the present and the past?
When you first came to my place
we slept in the same bed
What I told you is truly from my heart
And I let you take my beloved stuff
I feared the maids did not serve you well
and I prepared everything for you
As soon as I see you frown
I cheered you up
You've now out-grown all this
and treat me like an enemy
Beat me and scold me if I'm at fault
but why treat me with such aloofness?
If you are sad, speak out
and be done with it
Why suffer in silence?
I really don't understand you
Why? Why do you ignore me?
Why hide from me?
I have to know if it's the last thing I do
What is the reason?
Why? I was just going to ask you
When I came the other day
why didn't you ask the maid to
open the door?
What?
What do you mean?
I swear I didn't, if I did let me
die right now
I didn't do it, how could I admit it?
One shouldn't swear in the morning
I really didn't see you
Even sister Bao only sat for a while
and went away
Maybe the maids were too lazy to move
and said you were asleep
Wait till I find out who they were
and I'll teach them a lesson
They deserve it
To have infuriated me is a small matter
but to have made other Miss mad
then it is a big problem
You... are you infuriating me
or cursing me?
Look, is this worth being so angry over?
Sister Lin, don't worry
What's there to worry?
You really don't realise this?
It's because of your worry that
you're still sick
If you understood me more
wouldn't you be better?
Sister, let me say one more thing, okay?
What's there to say?
I understand what you have say
Sister
Was sister's cough better last night?
Much better
Amitabha
Master Bao, even you are
reciting prayers now?
This is a sign of desperation
Ji Juan, you wear such thin clothes
Be careful you don't catch a cold,
sister Lin is sick
and if you're sick, what should we do?
Go, put on more clothing
Master Bao, when you speak
keep your hands to yourself
You're now a grown-up
if people saw it they'll gossip
Miss Lin said the other day
You can't be like a child anymore
You ought to behave properly
with the ladies
You must learn to respect propriety
Look
Miss Lin is staying away from you
Ji Juan, Master Bao is sulking outside
Go and see what's wrong
Take it, I'll take a look
Master Bao...
What are you dong here all by yourself?
Grown up
Grown up?
What's the big deal about having grown up?
They get married and leave
They don't bother with me any more
Isn't that so true?
Even Miss Lin is returning to Soo Chow
Nonsense
There's no one in her home now
Why would she want to go back?
Do you think I'm fooling you?
Miss Lin will be going home next year
You are lying
I know
You only have the Xue family in your heart
You forget Lin is also a big family
Miss Lin is not a member of the Jia family
How can Miss Lin be married
from the Jia family
A swallow must return to its old nest
Besides, Miss Lin's marriage
has been pre-arranged
Miss says
...she is prepared to return
what you gave her
and you should return what she gave you
Master Bao...
Master Bao, what's wrong with you?
Bao Yu
Bao Yu...
Brother Bao...
Master Bao
Master Bao...
Ji Juan
Ji Juan, you can't leave
If you must, we'll leave together
What's the matter?
Ji Juan
What's going on?
Tell me what's going on
I... I only joked with master Bao
I said...
Miss Lin will be returning to Soo Chow
then he...
So, it's like this
Old madam
Lin said Prince Bei Jing will give
master Bao a boat
Ask them to carry it in
Yes
Oh no...
The Lin family has come to
pick up Miss Lin
Get them out...
Okay... get them out...
Quick...
Yes
Get them out...
Go on
Bao Yu, now you can relax
Okay, Bao Yu will be fine
From now on except sister Lin
no one is allowed to go by the name of Lin
No one by the name of Lin is allowed
in here
and no one can say that name in here
Do you hear?
No one by the name of Lin is allowed
in here
and no one can say that name in here
Brother Bao
Oh no, look...
That boat has come to
fetch sister Lin, look
The Lin family's boat has come to
pick up Miss Lin
Depart
Get the boat out of here quickly
Do it, quick
Depart
Sister Lin will never leave again
Bao Yu has a strange illness
Dai Yu 's condition is not stable either
They were okay when they were
together as kids
Now...
Old madam you should let Bao Yu marry
The auspicious event might bring
good fortune
Bao Yu and Dai Yu are a good match, but...
Right
But sister Lin is too thin and frail
Unlike Miss Bao who is healthy and proper
Miss Bao is not bad
If Bao Yu marries her
maybe he'll recover and be mature
Old madam you're right
Good
Since you think the Miss Bao is not bad
It's decided then
What, Yin Yang?
Old madam
Go ahead
If Miss Lin know this
she might not be able to take it
Besides master Bao is impotent
When Ji Juan said Miss Lin has to go home
He already became like mad
A family like ours
if people knew
...our children are like that
we'll have no face
Dai Yu is alright, but Bao Yu...
This is a problem
Not really, I have an idea
Go ahead
Leave us, all of you
Yes
Stop
I tell you all
whoever leaks this out
I'll rip out your lips
Yes
Go on, speak
We will use a plan
...to switch the bride
...by covering her face at the wedding
asking Ji Juan to help her at the side
Deceive Bao Yu that the bride
is sister Lin
Hiding the truth for the time being
When the situation is irreversible
then nobody can do anything about it
I forgot my handkerchief
I'm going back to get it
What's the matter with you?
Even if I said something wrong
my sister shouldn't have smacked me
What did you say?
They forbade me to tell you
but I'm bent on doing so
It's nothing bad, what's to fear?
It's a good match
A good match?
Yes, master Bao is going to marry Miss Bao
What?
Master Bao is going to marry Miss Bao
The news has shocked her so much
that she became weak
All became silent
Miss...
Miss, where are you going?
I... l'm going to ask Bao Yu
Miss
Miss Lin...
Miss, please go back to take your medicine
Bao Yu, you're sick
I'm sick
Why are you sick?
I...
I am sick because of Miss Lin
Your heart?
My heart...
my heart is with Miss Lin
Everything is a sham
One dolefully lamenting
The other full of cares
One like the reflection of the moon
in the water
The other like a flower's reflection
in the mirror
Miss...
How much can you cry?
How can one stop nature take its course?
Are you all clear?
Yes
Remember
Really? I can marry sister Lin?
Yes, but madam Lien said
if you keep displaying your antics
then you'll not be allowed to do so
Who says I'm sick or mad?
My heart is with sister Lin
Now that I can marry her
my heart is returned and I'm well again
You don't believe it?
Okay, I'll recite the books for you
Proper relations & virtues are
one's basic obligations
To be loyal to your emperor
To be filial to your father
Am I recovered?
Am I?
I tell you I'm not sick
My sickness is because of their pressure
I tell you I'm not sick,
they caused my sickness
Ji Juan
Master Bao is really going to marry...
Master Bao is really going to
marry Miss Bao
lt'll take place tonight
The couple's room is separately arranged
Everyone is aware
I only heard of this indirectly
The orders were that we are not
supposed to know
These people are so cruel
Bao Yu, I think if she's dead tomorrow
You are shameless to come to see me
Miss Ji Juan
What is it? Madam Chow
How is Miss Lin?
Second madam and old madam
discussed this just now
You are needed over there
Sure, no problem
Madam Chow you go first.
After Miss Lin was dead
We'll wait on you
It's just that Miss Lin is still alive
Miss
You can say this to me
but how am I going to report this?
Report it as it is
What? There'll be big trouble
What trouble?
Suet Ngan, come with me
No
What, no one will go?
They will not spare us, come
Sister Ji Juan...
I spend nights and days with you
How could I bear seeing you like this
I prepare your medicine, and you reject it
I prepare your food, yet you refuse it
Look at you, you're faded like a flower
Your tears on the pillow are heavy
as the Autumn rain
Miss, melancholy has caused your illness
You dote too much
The icy wind chills the leaves
and night embraces the milky way
Cease shedding tears
Keep yourself well
Nurture your frail spirit
Groom your beautiful self
Smooth your frowning brows
Close your book of distress
What's the use of food and medicine?
Even a panacea will not cure me
I was born more evanescent than dew
My frail body is like a candle in the wind
Flowers falling with one sweep of the wind
Beauty and colour are gone with one
fell swoop
Sister, do not miss me
We meet and depart like the rising
and ebbing tide
Miss, why say such sad things
A good person like you should have
a good ending
There must be good medicine for sickness
Besides, the whole family loves you
and great granny loves you like treasure
All sisters treat you as one of their own
Ji Juan, Stop it
Stop talking about this family
they are all insensitive to
others' feelings
Congratulations...
Miss
Chafer
Looking back at our old dreams
I regretted to send letter to Bao Yu
We setup the Begonia Club
for us to write poems
Playing games over at Yi Hung Mansion
Scoring old songs at the
Shiau Shiang Mansion
Tears persist though love has ended
The silk worm regrets to leave
its silk when it died
You can't tell the tear
and ink marks on the paper
Who say lovers are more sentimental
Let my heart and blood become ashes
Even the heaven and the mortals
unaware of it
Miss
I mourn Spring's farewell
and flowers' fading
I mourn the coming of Fall's deluge
two lonely hearts
tears drown the heart of Ji Juan
Great granny, the bride and groom are here
Miss...
Sister Lin...
Are you better?
Why are you covered in this?
Why do we use such trite politeness?
Brother Bao
Come here
Aren't you concerned others might
laugh at you?
You should know what is propriety
Be gentle
You're not shy but the bride does
Right, Bao Yu
You're a man now
I wish you both long life and happiness
Be gentle
My heart is with her already
Would I not be gentle with her?
Bao Yu, come
You must remember this
It's for your own good
I know
Be careful
My mother died when I was a mere child!
My father was sacrificed in Kwong Lin
I'm seeking shelter at grandmother's home
Someone from a different family
is treated differently
Thank you for taking care of me
If it weren't for you
who would keep me company day and night
Doing sewing and embroidery early
in the morning
Having a close relation during
our childhood
But the west wind brings me
to the spirit world
Don't burn for me paper money
at the Ghost festival
Neither would I need respects
at Ching Ming occasion
Each year this time when it becomes quiet
Call my name a few times
at the bamboo forest
Miss
Ji Juan, I have to ask you for a favour
I have no family here
Till now I am honest and chaste
No matter what, you ask them
to send me back
I'd rather die in a virtuous place
I don't want to be buried in an
immoral surrounding
I don't want to be buried in a dirty place
Bao Yu... you...
Miss...
Miss!
It's difficult to search for a potion
for love
The heavens should weep for
star-crossed lovers
Dai Yu died at the Shiau Shiang Mansion
Life's grievances are lengthy as the river
Where am I? Where am I?
Am I dreaming?
What are you talking about?
Granny is sitting right here
Old master and guests are
in the Rung Shi Hall
What are you doing?
You tell me
Who is that?
Your new bride
I'm confused. Who is my bride?
Miss Bao
So what about Miss Lin?
Old master arranged your marriage
to Miss Bao
Yes...
It had been Miss Bao all along
You're married to Miss Bao
It's Miss Bao
Yes
Miss Bao?
Granny, what is going on here?
What is going on here?
Bao Yu, you're married Miss Bao
Why are you mad like this?
It's Miss Bao
I am sure I married sister Lin
Suet Ngan helped her
How could she have become someone else?
Why?
Oh why?
Bao Yu
Great granny
Old madam
Old madam...
Never mind
Things will work themselves out
Sister Lin
Bao Yu...
Bao Yu
Brother Bao
I thought this wedding night
was auspicious
but it is a tragedy of errors
Who made the swap
Why has the turtledove occupied
the magpie's nest
Granny loves me like treasure
why has she deceived me too?
Sister Bao knew I was in love
with sister Lin
Why has she forced me into such suffering?
Sister Lin, my love for you hasn't changed
Brother Bao
Master Bao
Bao Yu
Brother Bao
Master Bao
Bao Yu
Born in the same bed and die
in the same coffin
Granny, I want to die...
Bao Yu
Granny, there's something I must say
Alright, go on...
Great granny
Sister Lin and I are sick
and for the same reason
One is full of melancholy,
the other full of hate
Please put us together in one room
so we could be with each other
and spend our days together
And we want to bury together after we died
Oh, Great granny
There is nothing else I want
Just to live and die with sister Lin
Bao Yu... this is your auspicious day
Yet you're sick like this
I feel such pain for you!
Bao Yu, where are you going?
Miss
Bao Yu
I'm going to find sister Lin
Bao Yu, sister Lin is...
She is already dead
Bao Yu...
- Master Bao...
- Bao Yu...
"Spiritual Tablet of Dai Yu"
Who? Who set this cruel trap
...to separate us both
Separating the two of us
Sister Lin
Until eternity I can call yet
there won't be response
I grieve you're asleep alone in death
I regret I could not even say farewell
I feel remorse I could not be
your pall bearer
Sister Lin
Our love was like brother and sister
it was sweet and innocent
Bao Yu's love is true and sincere
Sister you were full of woes
and yet you kept silent
I pined for our wedding night and...
thought our love would be
auspiciously consummated
Little did I expect you would
become sister Bao
and Shiau Shiang Mansion has become
Heng Wu Yuan
My heart tripped and fell
and realised you were forced to your death
I was deceived by Suet Ngan
who lured me to the nuptial room
The scheme has caused your death
I tear down the curtain fiercely
Your tears are like blood
becoming the azalea flower
Shiau Shiang Mansion remains the same
but you the fairy of
Shiau Shiang Mansion are gone
Miss was deeply saddened by the poems
What elegant poetry!
It has a lofty character
It's written in blood and tears
Why burn it?
It's saturated with self-pity
Nobody appreciates it, so why keep it?
The jade zither is sister's bosom friend
it can interpret the melancholic rain
and play a tune with the clouds and moon
Now its strings are broken
so is my heart, and I have no more words
There is no audience for my sad song
The broomstick & the hoe
are used to bury flowers
Flowers fade and flowers bloom
Sister, you're like a white jade
buried in dirt
From now on I can only see
the flowers but not you
Master Bao, please go back
Your wife is waiting for you
This is a day for newly weds
Bao Yu... how are you?
Bao Yu...
Even the parrot knows of the love
The people simply cannot be compared
Master Bao, please go back,
it's almost dawn
It's almost dawn
The royal decree, kneel and receive it
Long live the king
Official Jia has been delinquent in duty
He failed the Emperor's trust
& shamed the ancestors
He is now dismissed from his post
The assets of the Jia family
...will now be confiscated by officials
Fate does not govern lovers' destinies
Clearly it's the red chamber dream's
mourning & sorrow
All debts are paid
Those who transcend joy and pain
take the monastic vow
Those yearning for love lose their lives
Like a forest where the birds are gone
...all that's left is a land forlorn!